<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for TIBCO Software Inc. -- TIBCO PartnerExpress</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tibco%20software%20inc./tibco%20partnerexpress.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for TIBCO Software Inc. -- TIBCO PartnerExpress</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 20:23:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43048|2024-08-04T03:47:13.219Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20partnerexpress
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43048</link>
      <description>The Interior Server and Gateway Server components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO PartnerExpress contain a vulnerability that theoretically allows an unauthenticated attacker with network access to execute a clickjacking attack on the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability does not require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO PartnerExpress: versions 6.2.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43048|2024-08-04T03:47:13.219Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43047|2024-08-04T03:47:13.246Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20partnerexpress
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43047</link>
      <description>The Interior Server and Gateway Server components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO PartnerExpress contain easily exploitable Stored and Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities that allow a low privileged attacker to social engineer a legitimate user with network access to execute scripts targeting the affected system or the victim's local system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO PartnerExpress: versions 6.2.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43047|2024-08-04T03:47:13.246Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43046|2024-08-04T03:47:13.158Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20partnerexpress
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43046</link>
      <description>The Interior Server and Gateway Server components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO PartnerExpress contain an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated attacker with network access to obtain session tokens for the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO PartnerExpress: versions 6.2.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43046|2024-08-04T03:47:13.158Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27147|2024-08-04T16:11:35.673Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20partnerexpress
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27147</link>
      <description>The REST API component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO PartnerExpress contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows an unauthenticated attacker with network access to obtain an authenticated login URL for the affected system via a REST API. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO PartnerExpress: version 6.2.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27147|2024-08-04T16:11:35.673Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
