<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for TIBCO Software Inc. -- TIBCO JasperReports Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tibco%20software%20inc./tibco%20jasperreports%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for TIBCO Software Inc. -- TIBCO JasperReports Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 10:23:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5430|2024-08-05T05:33:44.336Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5430</link>
      <description>The Spring web flows of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS contain a vulnerability which may allow any authenticated user read-only access to the contents of the web application, including key configuration files. Affected releases include TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions up to and including 6.2.4; 6.3.0; 6.3.2; 6.3.3;6.4.0; 6.4.2, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS: versions up to and including 6.4.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5430|2024-08-05T05:33:44.336Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5431|2024-08-05T05:33:44.377Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5431</link>
      <description>The domain designer component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS contains a vulnerability which may allow, in the context of a non-default permissions configuration, persisted cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks. Affected releases include TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions up to and including 6.2.4; 6.3.0; 6.3.2; 6.3.3; 6.4.0; 6.4.2, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS: versions up to and including 6.4.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5431|2024-08-05T05:33:44.377Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5429|2024-08-05T05:33:44.416Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5429</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the report scripting component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO JasperReports Library, TIBCO JasperReports Library Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Library for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy, TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS, TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio, TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio Community Edition, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio for ActiveMatrix BPM may allow analytic reports that contain scripting to perform arbitrary code execution. Affected releases include TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions up to and including 6.2.4; 6.3.0; 6.3.2;6.3.3; 6.4.0; 6.4.2, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO JasperReports Library: versions up to and including 6.2.4; 6.3.0; 6.3.2; 6.3.3; 6.4.0; 6.4.1; 6.4.2, TIBCO JasperReports Library Community Edition: versions up to and including 6.4.3, TIBCO JasperReports Library for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio: versions up to and including 6.2.4; 6.3.0; 6.3.2; 6.3.3; 6.4.0; 6.4.2, TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio Community Edition: versions up to and including 6.4.3, TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5429|2024-08-05T05:33:44.416Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
