<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for TIBCO Software Inc. -- TIBCO FTL - Community Edition</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tibco%20software%20inc./tibco%20ftl%20-%20community%20edition.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for TIBCO Software Inc. -- TIBCO FTL - Community Edition</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 09:23:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12412|2024-09-17T02:06:27.359Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ftl%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12412</link>
      <description>The realm server (tibrealmserver) component of TIBCO Software Inc. TIBCO FTL - Community Edition, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition contains a vulnerability which may allow an attacker to perform cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc. TIBCO FTL - Community Edition: versions up to and including 5.4.0, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition: versions up to and including 5.4.0, TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: versions up to and including 5.4.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12412|2024-09-17T02:06:27.359Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28820|2024-09-17T03:18:44.039Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ftl%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28820</link>
      <description>The FTL Server (tibftlserver), FTL C API, FTL Golang API, FTL Java API, and FTL .Net API components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition contain a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with local access on the Windows operating system to insert malicious software. The affected component can be abused to execute the malicious software inserted by the attacker with the elevated privileges of the component. This vulnerability results from the affected component searching for run-time artifacts outside of the installation hierarchy. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition: versions 6.5.0 and below, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.5.0 and below, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.5.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28820|2024-09-17T03:18:44.039Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 20:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43052|2024-09-17T00:10:54.268Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ftl%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43052</link>
      <description>The Realm Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows authentication bypass due to a hard coded secret used in the default realm server of the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition: versions 6.7.2 and below, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.7.2 and below, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.7.2 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43052|2024-09-17T00:10:54.268Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 18:25:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
