<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for TIBCO Software Inc. -- TIBCO BusinessConnect Trading Community Management</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tibco%20software%20inc./tibco%20businessconnect%20trading%20community%20management.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for TIBCO Software Inc. -- TIBCO BusinessConnect Trading Community Management</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 11:20:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22777|2024-08-03T03:21:49.131Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20businessconnect%20trading%20community%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22777</link>
      <description>The Web Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BusinessConnect Trading Community Management contains easily exploitable Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities that allow an unauthenticated attacker with network access to execute scripts targeting the affected system or the victim's local system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BusinessConnect Trading Community Management: versions 6.1.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22777|2024-08-03T03:21:49.131Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22778|2024-08-03T03:21:49.163Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20businessconnect%20trading%20community%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22778</link>
      <description>The Web Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BusinessConnect Trading Community Management contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated attacker with network access to execute Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) on the affected system. A successful attack using this vulnerability requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BusinessConnect Trading Community Management: versions 6.1.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22778|2024-08-03T03:21:49.163Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22776|2024-08-03T03:21:49.157Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20businessconnect%20trading%20community%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22776</link>
      <description>The Web Server component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BusinessConnect Trading Community Management contains easily exploitable vulnerabilities that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) on the affected system. A successful attack using these vulnerabilities requires human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO BusinessConnect Trading Community Management: versions 6.1.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22776|2024-08-03T03:21:49.157Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
