<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for TIBCO Software Inc. -- TIBCO FTL - Community Edition</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tibco%20software%20inc./tibco%20ftl%20-%20community%20edition.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for TIBCO Software Inc. -- TIBCO FTL - Community Edition</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:22:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30574|2024-08-03T06:56:12.980Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ftl%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30574</link>
      <description>The ftlserver component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition, TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition, TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition, TIBCO eFTL - Community Edition, TIBCO eFTL - Developer Edition, TIBCO eFTL - Enterprise Edition, and TIBCO eFTL - Enterprise Edition contains a difficult to exploit vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with local access to obtain user credentials to the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition: versions 6.0.0 through 6.8.0, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.0.1 through 6.8.0, TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.0.0 through 6.7.3, TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: version 6.8.0, TIBCO eFTL - Community Edition: versions 6.0.0 through 6.8.0, TIBCO eFTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.0.1 through 6.8.0, TIBCO eFTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.0.0 through 6.7.3, and TIBCO eFTL - Enterprise Edition: version 6.8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30574|2024-08-03T06:56:12.980Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30573|2024-08-03T06:56:12.870Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ftl%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30573</link>
      <description>The ftlserver component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition, TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute a privilege escalation on the affected ftlserver. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition: versions 6.0.0 through 6.8.0, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.0.1 through 6.8.0, TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.0.0 through 6.7.3, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: version 6.8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30573|2024-08-03T06:56:12.870Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28819|2024-08-03T21:55:11.563Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ftl%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28819</link>
      <description>The Windows Installation component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with local access on some versions of the Windows operating system to insert malicious software. The affected component can be abused to execute the malicious software inserted by the attacker with the elevated privileges of the component. This vulnerability results from a lack of access restrictions on certain files and/or folders in the installation. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition: versions 6.5.0 and below, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.5.0 and below, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.5.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28819|2024-08-03T21:55:11.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28820|2024-08-03T21:55:11.578Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20ftl%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28820</link>
      <description>The FTL Server (tibftlserver), FTL C API, FTL Golang API, FTL Java API, and FTL .Net API components of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition contain a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with local access on the Windows operating system to insert malicious software. The affected component can be abused to execute the malicious software inserted by the attacker with the elevated privileges of the component. This vulnerability results from the affected component searching for run-time artifacts outside of the installation hierarchy. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO FTL - Community Edition: versions 6.5.0 and below, TIBCO FTL - Developer Edition: versions 6.5.0 and below, and TIBCO FTL - Enterprise Edition: versions 6.5.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28820|2024-08-03T21:55:11.578Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
