<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for TIBCO Software Inc. -- TIBCO JasperReports Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tibco%20software%20inc./tibco%20jasperreports%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for TIBCO Software Inc. -- TIBCO JasperReports Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 19:20:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-5533|2024-08-05T15:04:15.360Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-5533</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the server content cache of TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS contains a vulnerability which fails to prevent remote access to all the contents of the web application, including key configuration files. Affected releases are TIBCO JasperReports Server 6.4.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition 6.4.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM 6.4.0, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy 6.4.0, TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS 6.4.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-5533|2024-08-05T15:04:15.360Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-5528|2024-08-05T15:04:14.869Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-5528</link>
      <description>Multiple JasperReports Server components contain vulnerabilities which may allow authorized users to perform cross-site scripting (XSS) and cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks.  The impact of this vulnerability includes the theoretical disclosure of sensitive information.  Affects TIBCO JasperReports Server (versions 6.1.1 and below, 6.2.0, 6.2.1, and 6.3.0), TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition (versions 6.3.0 and below), TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM (versions 6.2.0 and below), TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy (versions 6.2.0 and below), and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS (versions 6.2.0 and below).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-5528|2024-08-05T15:04:14.869Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18808|2024-08-05T11:23:08.199Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18808</link>
      <description>The domain management component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS contains a race-condition vulnerability that may allow any users with domain save privileges to gain superuser privileges. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions up to and including 6.3.4; 6.4.0; 6.4.1; 6.4.2; 6.4.3; 7.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition: versions up to and including 7.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.3, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy: versions up to and including 7.1.0, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS: versions up to and including 7.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18808|2024-08-05T11:23:08.199Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-5532|2024-08-05T15:04:15.302Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-5532</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the report renderer component of TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO JasperReports Library, TIBCO JasperReports Library for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy, TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS, TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio for ActiveMatrix BPM may allow a subset of authorized users to perform persistent cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks. Affected releases are TIBCO JasperReports Server 6.2.3 and below; 6.3.0; 6.3.1; 6.3.2; 6.4.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition 6.4.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM 6.4.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Library 6.2.3 and below; 6.3.0; 6.3.1; 6.3.2; 6.4.0; 6.4.1, TIBCO JasperReports Library for ActiveMatrix BPM 6.4.1 and below, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy 6.4.0 and below, TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS 6.4.0 and below, TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio 6.2.3 and below; 6.3.0; 6.3.1; 6.3.2; 6.4.0, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio for ActiveMatrix BPM 6.4.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-5532|2024-08-05T15:04:15.302Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18816|2024-08-05T11:23:08.207Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18816</link>
      <description>The repository component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy, TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS contains a persistent cross site scripting vulnerability. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions up to and including 6.3.4; 6.4.0; 6.4.1; 6.4.2; 6.4.3; 7.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition: versions up to and including 7.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.3, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi- Tenancy versions up to and including 7.1.0, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS: versions up to and including 7.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18816|2024-08-05T11:23:08.207Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18815|2024-08-05T11:23:07.855Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18815</link>
      <description>The REST API component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows unauthenticated users to bypass authorization checks for portions of the HTTP interface to the JasperReports Server. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: 6.4.0; 6.4.1; 6.4.2; 6.4.3; 7.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition: versions up to and including 7.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.3, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy: versions up to and including 7.1.0, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS: versions up to and including 7.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18815|2024-08-05T11:23:07.855Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5430|2024-08-05T05:33:44.336Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5430</link>
      <description>The Spring web flows of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS contain a vulnerability which may allow any authenticated user read-only access to the contents of the web application, including key configuration files. Affected releases include TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions up to and including 6.2.4; 6.3.0; 6.3.2; 6.3.3;6.4.0; 6.4.2, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS: versions up to and including 6.4.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5430|2024-08-05T05:33:44.336Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5431|2024-08-05T05:33:44.377Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5431</link>
      <description>The domain designer component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS contains a vulnerability which may allow, in the context of a non-default permissions configuration, persisted cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks. Affected releases include TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions up to and including 6.2.4; 6.3.0; 6.3.2; 6.3.3; 6.4.0; 6.4.2, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS: versions up to and including 6.4.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5431|2024-08-05T05:33:44.377Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5429|2024-08-05T05:33:44.416Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5429</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the report scripting component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO JasperReports Library, TIBCO JasperReports Library Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Library for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy, TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS, TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio, TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio Community Edition, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio for ActiveMatrix BPM may allow analytic reports that contain scripting to perform arbitrary code execution. Affected releases include TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions up to and including 6.2.4; 6.3.0; 6.3.2;6.3.3; 6.4.0; 6.4.2, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO JasperReports Library: versions up to and including 6.2.4; 6.3.0; 6.3.2; 6.3.3; 6.4.0; 6.4.1; 6.4.2, TIBCO JasperReports Library Community Edition: versions up to and including 6.4.3, TIBCO JasperReports Library for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio: versions up to and including 6.2.4; 6.3.0; 6.3.2; 6.3.3; 6.4.0; 6.4.2, TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio Community Edition: versions up to and including 6.4.3, TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5429|2024-08-05T05:33:44.416Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
