<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for TIBCO Software Inc. -- TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Community Edition</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tibco%20software%20inc./tibco%20activespaces%20-%20community%20edition.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for TIBCO Software Inc. -- TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Community Edition</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 22:22:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12411|2024-09-16T18:03:18.833Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20activespaces%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12411</link>
      <description>The administrative daemon (tibdgadmind) of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Community Edition, TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Developer Edition, and TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Enterprise Edition contains a vulnerability which may allow an attacker to perform cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Community Edition: 3.3.0; 3.4.0; 3.5.0, TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Developer Edition: 3.0.0; 3.1.0; 3.3.0; 3.4.0; 3.5.0, and TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Enterprise Edition: 3.0.0; 3.1.0; 3.2.0; 3.3.0; 3.4.0; 3.5.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12411|2024-09-16T18:03:18.833Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28824|2024-09-16T17:08:34.597Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20activespaces%20-%20community%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28824</link>
      <description>The Windows Installation component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Community Edition, TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Developer Edition, and TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Enterprise Edition contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows a low privileged attacker with local access on some versions of the Windows operating system to insert malicious software. The affected component can be abused to execute the malicious software inserted by the attacker with the elevated privileges of the component. This vulnerability results from a lack of access restrictions on certain files and/or folders in the installation. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Community Edition: versions 4.5.0 and below, TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Developer Edition: versions 4.5.0 and below, and TIBCO ActiveSpaces - Enterprise Edition: versions 4.5.0 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28824|2024-09-16T17:08:34.597Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 20:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
