<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for TIBCO Software Inc. -- TIBCO JasperReports Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tibco%20software%20inc./tibco%20jasperreports%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for TIBCO Software Inc. -- TIBCO JasperReports Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 13:24:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35496|2024-09-17T03:43:38.702Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35496</link>
      <description>The XMLA Connections component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure contains a difficult to exploit vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to interfere with XML processing in the affected component. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 7.2.1 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 7.5.0 and 7.5.1, TIBCO JasperReports Server: version 7.8.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server: version 7.9.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition: versions 7.8.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition: versions 7.9.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace: versions 7.9.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions 7.9.0 and below, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure: version 7.8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35496|2024-09-17T03:43:38.702Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 17:35:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-8986|2024-09-17T03:37:40.244Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-8986</link>
      <description>The SOAP API component vulnerability of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM contains a vulnerability that may allow a malicious authenticated user to copy text files from the host operating system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions up to and including 6.3.4; 6.4.0; 6.4.1; 6.4.2; 6.4.3, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-8986|2024-09-17T03:37:40.244Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5429|2024-09-17T00:32:19.534Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5429</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the report scripting component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO JasperReports Library, TIBCO JasperReports Library Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Library for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy, TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS, TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio, TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio Community Edition, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio for ActiveMatrix BPM may allow analytic reports that contain scripting to perform arbitrary code execution. Affected releases include TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions up to and including 6.2.4; 6.3.0; 6.3.2;6.3.3; 6.4.0; 6.4.2, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO JasperReports Library: versions up to and including 6.2.4; 6.3.0; 6.3.2; 6.3.3; 6.4.0; 6.4.1; 6.4.2, TIBCO JasperReports Library Community Edition: versions up to and including 6.4.3, TIBCO JasperReports Library for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio: versions up to and including 6.2.4; 6.3.0; 6.3.2; 6.3.3; 6.4.0; 6.4.2, TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio Community Edition: versions up to and including 6.4.3, TIBCO Jaspersoft Studio for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5429|2024-09-17T00:32:19.534Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5431|2024-09-17T01:56:35.755Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5431</link>
      <description>The domain designer component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy, and TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS contains a vulnerability which may allow, in the context of a non-default permissions configuration, persisted cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks. Affected releases include TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions up to and including 6.2.4; 6.3.0; 6.3.2; 6.3.3; 6.4.0; 6.4.2, TIBCO JasperReports Server Community Edition: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO Jaspersoft for AWS with Multi-Tenancy: versions up to and including 6.4.2, TIBCO Jaspersoft Reporting and Analytics for AWS: versions up to and including 6.4.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5431|2024-09-17T01:56:35.755Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41561|2024-09-17T02:05:41.937Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41561</link>
      <description>The JNDI Data Sources component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a privileged/administrative attacker with network access to execute Remote Code Execution to obtain a reverse shell on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 8.0.2 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server: version 8.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition: versions 8.1.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition: versions 8.1.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace: versions 8.0.2 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace: version 8.1.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure: versions 8.0.2 and below, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure: version 8.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41561|2024-09-17T02:05:41.937Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 03:44:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35494|2024-09-17T00:51:58.556Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35494</link>
      <description>The Rest API component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure contain a race condition that allows a low privileged authenticated attacker via the REST API to obtain read access to temporary objects created by other users on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 7.2.1 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 7.5.0 and 7.5.1, TIBCO JasperReports Server: version 7.8.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server: version 7.9.0, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Community Edition: versions 7.8.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server - Developer Edition: versions 7.9.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace: versions 7.9.0 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions 7.9.0 and below, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for Microsoft Azure: version 7.8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35494|2024-09-17T00:51:58.556Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 17:35:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9409|2024-09-17T01:16:13.966Z -- tibco%20software%20inc. -- tibco%20jasperreports%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9409</link>
      <description>The administrative UI component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM contains a vulnerability that theoretically allows an unauthenticated attacker to obtain the permissions of a JasperReports Server "superuser" for the affected systems. The attacker can theoretically exploit the vulnerability consistently, remotely, and without authenticating. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO JasperReports Server: versions 7.1.1 and below, TIBCO JasperReports Server for AWS Marketplace: versions 7.1.1 and below, and TIBCO JasperReports Server for ActiveMatrix BPM: versions 7.1.1 and below.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9409|2024-09-17T01:16:13.966Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 12:25:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
