<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for ahmyi -- RivetTracker</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ahmyi/rivettracker.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for ahmyi -- RivetTracker</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 22:22:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2012-10003|2024-08-06T21:36:02.353Z -- ahmyi -- rivettracker
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10003</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in ahmyi RivetTracker. This issue affects some unknown processing. The manipulation of the argument $_SERVER['PHP_SELF'] leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The patch is named f053c5cc2bc44269b0496b5f275e349928a92ef9. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-217271.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in ahmyi RivetTracker entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments $_SERVER['PHP_SELF'] mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Patch wird als f053c5cc2bc44269b0496b5f275e349928a92ef9 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2012-10003|2024-08-06T21:36:02.353Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 11:03:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2012-10002|2024-08-06T21:36:02.359Z -- ahmyi -- rivettracker
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10002</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in ahmyi RivetTracker. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function changeColor of the file css.php. The manipulation of the argument set_css leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The patch is named 45a0f33876d58cb7e4a0f17da149e58fc893b858. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-217267.
In ahmyi RivetTracker wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Betroffen ist die Funktion changeColor der Datei css.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments set_css mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Patch wird als 45a0f33876d58cb7e4a0f17da149e58fc893b858 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2012-10002|2024-08-06T21:36:02.359Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 08:22:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
