<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for LabVantage -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/labvantage/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for LabVantage -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 11:19:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6182|2024-06-20T11:00:07.345Z -- labvantage -- lims
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6182</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in LabVantage LIMS 2017. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /labvantage/rc?command=page&amp;page=LV_ViewSampleSpec&amp;oosonly=Y&amp;_sdialog=Y. The manipulation of the argument sdcid/keyid1 leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-269153 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in LabVantage LIMS 2017 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei /labvantage/rc?command=page&amp;page=LV_ViewSampleSpec&amp;oosonly=Y&amp;_sdialog=Y. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments sdcid/keyid1 mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6182|2024-06-20T11:00:07.345Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 11:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6181|2024-06-20T11:00:05.666Z -- labvantage -- lims
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6181</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in LabVantage LIMS 2017. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /labvantage/rc?command=file&amp;file=WEB-CORE/elements/files/filesembedded.jsp&amp;size=32. The manipulation of the argument height/width leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-269152. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In LabVantage LIMS 2017 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei /labvantage/rc?command=file&amp;file=WEB-CORE/elements/files/filesembedded.jsp&amp;size=32. Durch Manipulation des Arguments height/width mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6181|2024-06-20T11:00:05.666Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6058|2024-06-17T18:00:04.540Z -- labvantage -- lims</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6058</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in LabVantage LIMS 2017. This affects an unknown part of the file /labvantage/rc?command=page&amp;amp;page=SampleHistoricalList&amp;_iframename=list&amp;__crc=crc_1701669816260. The manipulation of the argument height/width leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-268785 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in LabVantage LIMS 2017 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei /labvantage/rc?command=page&amp;amp;page=SampleHistoricalList&amp;_iframename=list&amp;__crc=crc_1701669816260. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments height/width mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6058|2024-06-17T18:00:04.540Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 18:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5771|2024-06-08T22:00:05.022Z -- labvantage -- lims</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5771</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in LabVantage LIMS 2017. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /labvantage/rc?command=page&amp;amp;page=SampleList&amp;_iframename=list of the component POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument param1 leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-267454 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In LabVantage LIMS 2017 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei /labvantage/rc?command=page&amp;amp;page=SampleList&amp;_iframename=list der Komponente POST Request Handler. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments param1 mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5771|2024-06-08T22:00:05.022Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 22:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6058|2024-06-18T15:49:19.125Z -- labvantage -- lims</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6058</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in LabVantage LIMS 2017. This affects an unknown part of the file /labvantage/rc?command=page&amp;amp;page=SampleHistoricalList&amp;_iframename=list&amp;__crc=crc_1701669816260. The manipulation of the argument height/width leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-268785 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in LabVantage LIMS 2017 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei /labvantage/rc?command=page&amp;amp;page=SampleHistoricalList&amp;_iframename=list&amp;__crc=crc_1701669816260. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments height/width mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6058|2024-06-18T15:49:19.125Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 18:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
