<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cambium Networks -- ePMP</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cambium%20networks/epmp.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cambium Networks -- ePMP</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 18:24:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-5256|2024-08-05T14:55:35.813Z -- cambium%20networks -- epmp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-5256</link>
      <description>In version 3.5 and prior of Cambium Networks ePMP firmware, all authenticated users have the ability to update the Device Name and System Description fields in the web administration console, and those fields are vulnerable to persistent cross-site scripting (XSS) injection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-5256|2024-08-05T14:55:35.813Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-5254|2024-08-05T14:55:35.703Z -- cambium%20networks -- epmp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-5254</link>
      <description>In version 3.5 and prior of Cambium Networks ePMP firmware, the non-administrative users 'installer' and 'home' have the capability of changing passwords for other accounts, including admin, after disabling a client-side protection mechanism.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-5254|2024-08-05T14:55:35.703Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-5258|2024-08-05T14:55:35.779Z -- cambium%20networks -- epmp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-5258</link>
      <description>In version 3.5 and prior of Cambium Networks ePMP firmware, an attacker who knows or can guess the RW community string can provide a URL for a configuration file over SNMP with XSS strings in certain SNMP OIDs, serve it via HTTP, and the affected device will perform a configuration restore using the attacker's supplied config file, including the inserted XSS strings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-5258|2024-08-05T14:55:35.779Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-5255|2024-08-05T14:55:35.811Z -- cambium%20networks -- epmp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-5255</link>
      <description>In version 3.5 and prior of Cambium Networks ePMP firmware, a lack of input sanitation for certain parameters on the web management console allows any authenticated user (including the otherwise low-privilege readonly user) to inject shell meta-characters as part of a specially-crafted POST request to the get_chart function and run OS-level commands, effectively as root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-5255|2024-08-05T14:55:35.811Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-5257|2024-08-05T14:55:35.818Z -- cambium%20networks -- epmp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-5257</link>
      <description>In version 3.5 and prior of Cambium Networks ePMP firmware, an attacker who knows (or guesses) the SNMP read/write (RW) community string can insert XSS strings in certain SNMP OIDs which will execute in the context of the currently-logged on user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-5257|2024-08-05T14:55:35.818Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
