<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for moment -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/moment/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for moment -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 17:21:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31129|2024-08-03T07:11:39.222Z -- moment -- moment
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31129</link>
      <description>moment is a JavaScript date library for parsing, validating, manipulating, and formatting dates. Affected versions of moment were found to use an inefficient parsing algorithm. Specifically using string-to-date parsing in moment (more specifically rfc2822 parsing, which is tried by default) has quadratic (N^2) complexity on specific inputs. Users may notice a noticeable slowdown is observed with inputs above 10k characters. Users who pass user-provided strings without sanity length checks to moment constructor are vulnerable to (Re)DoS attacks. The problem is patched in 2.29.4, the patch can be applied to all affected versions with minimal tweaking. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should consider limiting date lengths accepted from user input.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31129|2024-08-03T07:11:39.222Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24785|2024-08-03T04:20:50.533Z -- moment -- moment
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24785</link>
      <description>Moment.js is a JavaScript date library for parsing, validating, manipulating, and formatting dates. A path traversal vulnerability impacts npm (server) users of Moment.js between versions 1.0.1 and 2.29.1, especially if a user-provided locale string is directly used to switch moment locale. This problem is patched in 2.29.2, and the patch can be applied to all affected versions. As a workaround, sanitize the user-provided locale name before passing it to Moment.js.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24785|2024-08-03T04:20:50.533Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
