<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for LG -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/lg/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for LG -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:23:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40499|2024-06-06T15:47:32.541Z -- lg -- simple%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40499</link>
      <description>LG Simple Editor mkdir Directory Traversal Arbitrary File Deletion Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to delete arbitrary files on affected installations of LG Simple Editor. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the mkdir command implemented in the makeDetailContent method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to delete files in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-19926.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40499|2024-06-06T15:47:32.541Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40493|2024-06-05T19:46:41.214Z -- lg -- simple%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40493</link>
      <description>LG Simple Editor copySessionFolder Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of LG Simple Editor. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the copySessionFolder command. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-19920.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40493|2024-06-05T19:46:41.214Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6317|2024-04-18T07:34:37.533Z -- lg -- webos</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6317</link>
      <description>A prompt bypass exists in the secondscreen.gateway service running on webOS version 4 through 7. An attacker can create a privileged account without asking the user for the security PIN. 

Full versions and TV models affected:

webOS 4.9.7 - 5.30.40 running on LG43UM7000PLA 
webOS 5.5.0 - 04.50.51 running on OLED55CXPUA 
webOS 6.3.3-442 (kisscurl-kinglake) - 03.36.50 running on OLED48C1PUB  
webOS 7.3.1-43 (mullet-mebin) - 03.33.85 running on OLED55A23LA</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6317|2024-04-18T07:34:37.533Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 13:41:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
