<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for LG -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/lg/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for LG -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 16:24:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6319|2024-07-12T15:20:35.161Z -- lg -- webos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6319</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability exists in the getAudioMetadata method from the com.webos.service.attachedstoragemanager service on webOS version 4 through 7. A series of specially crafted requests can lead to command execution as the root user. An attacker can make authenticated requests to trigger this vulnerability.

  *  webOS 4.9.7 - 5.30.40 running on LG43UM7000PLA 

  *  webOS 5.5.0 - 04.50.51 running on OLED55CXPUA 

  *  webOS 6.3.3-442 (kisscurl-kinglake) - 03.36.50 running on OLED48C1PUB 

  *  webOS 7.3.1-43 (mullet-mebin) - 03.33.85 running on OLED55A23LA

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6319|2024-07-12T15:20:35.161Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 13:42:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6320|2024-06-20T15:40:09.500Z -- lg -- webos</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6320</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability exists in the com.webos.service.connectionmanager/tv/setVlanStaticAddress endpoint on webOS versions 5 and 6. A series of specially crafted requests can lead to command execution as the dbus user. An attacker can make authenticated requests to trigger this vulnerability.

Full versions and TV models affected:
  *  webOS 5.5.0 - 04.50.51 running on OLED55CXPUA 

  *  webOS 6.3.3-442 (kisscurl-kinglake) - 03.36.50 running on OLED48C1PUB</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6320|2024-06-20T15:40:09.500Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 13:43:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6317|2024-04-18T07:34:37.533Z -- lg -- webos</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6317</link>
      <description>A prompt bypass exists in the secondscreen.gateway service running on webOS version 4 through 7. An attacker can create a privileged account without asking the user for the security PIN. 

Full versions and TV models affected:

webOS 4.9.7 - 5.30.40 running on LG43UM7000PLA 
webOS 5.5.0 - 04.50.51 running on OLED55CXPUA 
webOS 6.3.3-442 (kisscurl-kinglake) - 03.36.50 running on OLED48C1PUB  
webOS 7.3.1-43 (mullet-mebin) - 03.33.85 running on OLED55A23LA</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6317|2024-04-18T07:34:37.533Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 13:41:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6320|2024-04-18T07:35:31.817Z -- lg -- webos</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6320</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability exists in the com.webos.service.connectionmanager/tv/setVlanStaticAddress endpoint on webOS versions 5 and 6. A series of specially crafted requests can lead to command execution as the dbus user. An attacker can make authenticated requests to trigger this vulnerability.

Full versions and TV models affected:
  *  webOS 5.5.0 - 04.50.51 running on OLED55CXPUA 

  *  webOS 6.3.3-442 (kisscurl-kinglake) - 03.36.50 running on OLED48C1PUB</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6320|2024-04-18T07:35:31.817Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 13:43:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6319|2024-04-18T07:35:16.311Z -- lg -- webos</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6319</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability exists in the getAudioMetadata method from the com.webos.service.attachedstoragemanager service on webOS version 4 through 7. A series of specially crafted requests can lead to command execution as the root user. An attacker can make authenticated requests to trigger this vulnerability.

  *  webOS 4.9.7 - 5.30.40 running on LG43UM7000PLA 

  *  webOS 5.5.0 - 04.50.51 running on OLED55CXPUA 

  *  webOS 6.3.3-442 (kisscurl-kinglake) - 03.36.50 running on OLED48C1PUB 

  *  webOS 7.3.1-43 (mullet-mebin) - 03.33.85 running on OLED55A23LA</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6319|2024-04-18T07:35:16.311Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 13:42:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6318|2024-04-18T07:34:59.024Z -- lg -- webos</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6318</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability exists in the processAnalyticsReport method from the com.webos.service.cloudupload service on webOS version 5 through 7. A series of specially crafted requests can lead to command execution as the root user. An attacker can make authenticated requests to trigger this vulnerability.

Full versions and TV models affected:

  *  webOS 5.5.0 - 04.50.51 running on OLED55CXPUA 

  *  webOS 6.3.3-442 (kisscurl-kinglake) - 03.36.50 running on OLED48C1PUB 

  *  webOS 7.3.1-43 (mullet-mebin) - 03.33.85 running on OLED55A23LA</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6318|2024-04-18T07:34:59.024Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 13:41:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40495|2024-06-04T17:18:47.925Z -- lg -- simple%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40495</link>
      <description>LG Simple Editor copyTemplateAll Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of LG Simple Editor. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the copyTemplateAll method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-19922.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40495|2024-06-04T17:18:47.925Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40505|2024-06-04T17:18:49.233Z -- lg -- simple%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40505</link>
      <description>LG Simple Editor createThumbnailByMovie Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of LG Simple Editor. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the createThumbnailByMovie method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-19978.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40505|2024-06-04T17:18:49.233Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40513|2024-06-04T17:18:50.118Z -- lg -- simple%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40513</link>
      <description>LG Simple Editor UserManageController getImageByFilename Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of LG Simple Editor. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the getImageByFilename method in the UserManageController class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-20015.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40513|2024-06-04T17:18:50.118Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40499|2024-06-06T15:47:32.541Z -- lg -- simple%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40499</link>
      <description>LG Simple Editor mkdir Directory Traversal Arbitrary File Deletion Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to delete arbitrary files on affected installations of LG Simple Editor. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the mkdir command implemented in the makeDetailContent method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to delete files in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-19926.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40499|2024-06-06T15:47:32.541Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40509|2024-06-04T17:18:51.008Z -- lg -- simple%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40509</link>
      <description>LG Simple Editor deleteCanvas Directory Traversal Arbitrary File Deletion Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to delete arbitrary files on affected installations of LG Simple Editor. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the deleteCanvas method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to delete files in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-20011.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40509|2024-06-04T17:18:51.008Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40508|2024-06-04T17:18:51.423Z -- lg -- simple%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40508</link>
      <description>LG Simple Editor putCanvasDB Directory Traversal Arbitrary File Deletion Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to delete arbitrary files on affected installations of LG Simple Editor. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the putCanvasDB method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to delete files in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-20010.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40508|2024-06-04T17:18:51.423Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40498|2024-06-11T14:31:48.380Z -- lg -- simple%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40498</link>
      <description>LG Simple Editor cp Command Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of LG Simple Editor. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the cp command implemented in the makeDetailContent method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-19925.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40498|2024-06-11T14:31:48.380Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40512|2024-06-04T17:18:52.303Z -- lg -- simple%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40512</link>
      <description>LG Simple Editor PlayerController getImageByFilename Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of LG Simple Editor. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the getImageByFilename method in the PlayerController class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-20014.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40512|2024-06-04T17:18:52.303Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40504|2024-06-04T17:18:52.747Z -- lg -- simple%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40504</link>
      <description>LG Simple Editor readVideoInfo Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of LG Simple Editor. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the readVideoInfo method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-19953.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40504|2024-06-04T17:18:52.747Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40494|2024-06-04T17:18:54.067Z -- lg -- simple%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40494</link>
      <description>LG Simple Editor deleteFolder Directory Traversal Arbitrary File Deletion Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to delete arbitrary files on affected installations of LG Simple Editor. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the deleteFolder method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to delete files in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-19921.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40494|2024-06-04T17:18:54.067Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40493|2024-06-05T19:46:41.214Z -- lg -- simple%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40493</link>
      <description>LG Simple Editor copySessionFolder Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of LG Simple Editor. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the copySessionFolder command. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-19920.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40493|2024-06-05T19:46:41.214Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40503|2024-06-04T17:18:56.651Z -- lg -- simple%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40503</link>
      <description>LG Simple Editor saveXmlFile XML External Entity Processing Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of LG Simple Editor. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the saveXmlFile method. Due to the improper restriction of XML External Entity (XXE) references, a crafted document specifying a URI causes the XML parser to access the URI and embed the contents back into the XML document for further processing. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-19952.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40503|2024-06-04T17:18:56.651Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40515|2024-06-04T17:18:57.106Z -- lg -- simple%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40515</link>
      <description>LG Simple Editor joinAddUser Improper Input Validation Denial-of-Service Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to create a denial-of-service condition on affected installations of LG Simple Editor. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the joinAddUser method. The issue results from improper input validation. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to create a denial-of-service condition on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-20048.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40515|2024-06-04T17:18:57.106Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40514|2024-06-04T17:18:58.842Z -- lg -- simple%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40514</link>
      <description>LG Simple Editor FileManagerController getImageByFilename Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of LG Simple Editor. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the getImageByFilename method in the FileManagerController class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-20016.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40514|2024-06-04T17:18:58.842Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40502|2024-06-04T17:18:59.264Z -- lg -- simple%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40502</link>
      <description>LG Simple Editor cropImage Directory Traversal Arbitrary File Deletion Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to delete arbitrary files on affected installations of LG Simple Editor. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the cropImage command. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to delete files in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-19951.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40502|2024-06-04T17:18:59.264Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40492|2024-06-04T17:19:01.010Z -- lg -- simple%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40492</link>
      <description>LG Simple Editor deleteCheckSession Directory Traversal Arbitrary File Deletion Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to delete arbitrary files on affected installations of LG Simple Editor. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the deleteCheckSession method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to delete files in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-19919.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40492|2024-06-04T17:19:01.010Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40517|2024-06-04T17:19:03.647Z -- lg -- supersign%20media%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40517</link>
      <description>LG SuperSign Media Editor ContentRestController getObject Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of LG SuperSign Media Editor. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the getObject method implemented in the ContentRestController class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-20328.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40517|2024-06-04T17:19:03.647Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40501|2024-05-03T02:11:30.132Z -- lg -- simple%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40501</link>
      <description>LG Simple Editor copyContent Exposed Dangerous Function Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of LG Simple Editor. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the copyContent command. The issue results from an exposed dangerous function. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-19945.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40501|2024-05-03T02:11:30.132Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40500|2024-05-03T02:11:29.373Z -- lg -- simple%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40500</link>
      <description>LG Simple Editor copyContent Exposed Dangerous Function Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of LG Simple Editor. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the copyContent command. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-19944.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40500|2024-05-03T02:11:29.373Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40516|2024-06-04T17:19:07.804Z -- lg -- simple%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40516</link>
      <description>LG Simple Editor Incorrect Permission Assignment Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of LG Simple Editor. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the product installer. The product sets incorrect permissions on folders. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-20327.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40516|2024-06-04T17:19:07.804Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40511|2024-06-04T17:19:09.138Z -- lg -- simple%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40511</link>
      <description>LG Simple Editor checkServer Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of LG Simple Editor. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the checkServer method. The issue results from the exposure of plaintext credentials. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-20013.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40511|2024-06-04T17:19:09.138Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40507|2024-06-04T17:19:09.585Z -- lg -- simple%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40507</link>
      <description>LG Simple Editor copyContent XML External Entity Processing Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of LG Simple Editor. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the copyContent command. Due to the improper restriction of XML External Entity (XXE) references, a crafted document specifying a URI causes the XML parser to access the URI and embed the contents back into the XML document for further processing. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-20006.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40507|2024-06-04T17:19:09.585Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40497|2024-06-04T17:19:10.017Z -- lg -- simple%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40497</link>
      <description>LG Simple Editor saveXml Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of LG Simple Editor. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the saveXml command implemented in the makeDetailContent method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-19924.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40497|2024-06-04T17:19:10.017Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40496|2024-06-04T17:19:11.805Z -- lg -- simple%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40496</link>
      <description>LG Simple Editor copyStickerContent Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of LG Simple Editor. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the copyStickerContent command. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-19923.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40496|2024-06-04T17:19:11.805Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40506|2024-06-04T17:19:13.185Z -- lg -- simple%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40506</link>
      <description>LG Simple Editor copyContent XML External Entity Processing Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of LG Simple Editor. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the copyContent command. Due to the improper restriction of XML External Entity (XXE) references, a crafted document specifying a URI causes the XML parser to access the URI and embed the contents back into the XML document for further processing. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-20005.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40506|2024-06-04T17:19:13.185Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40510|2024-06-04T17:19:13.596Z -- lg -- simple%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40510</link>
      <description>LG Simple Editor getServerSetting Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of LG Simple Editor. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the getServerSetting method. The issue results from the exposure of plaintext credentials. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-20012.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40510|2024-06-04T17:19:13.596Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41181|2024-06-04T17:21:31.088Z -- lg -- supersign%20media%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41181</link>
      <description>LG SuperSign Media Editor getSubFolderList Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of LG SuperSign Media Editor. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the getSubFolderList method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-20330.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41181|2024-06-04T17:21:31.088Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6317|2024-07-05T17:22:37.217Z -- lg -- webos</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6317</link>
      <description>A prompt bypass exists in the secondscreen.gateway service running on webOS version 4 through 7. An attacker can create a privileged account without asking the user for the security PIN. 

Full versions and TV models affected:

webOS 4.9.7 - 5.30.40 running on LG43UM7000PLA 
webOS 5.5.0 - 04.50.51 running on OLED55CXPUA 
webOS 6.3.3-442 (kisscurl-kinglake) - 03.36.50 running on OLED48C1PUB  
webOS 7.3.1-43 (mullet-mebin) - 03.33.85 running on OLED55A23LA</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6317|2024-07-05T17:22:37.217Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 13:41:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
