<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for LG -- SuperSign Media Editor</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/lg/supersign%20media%20editor.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for LG -- SuperSign Media Editor</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41181|2024-06-04T17:21:31.088Z -- lg -- supersign%20media%20editor
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41181</link>
      <description>LG SuperSign Media Editor getSubFolderList Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of LG SuperSign Media Editor. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the getSubFolderList method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-20330.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41181|2024-06-04T17:21:31.088Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40517|2024-06-04T17:19:03.647Z -- lg -- supersign%20media%20editor
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40517</link>
      <description>LG SuperSign Media Editor ContentRestController getObject Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of LG SuperSign Media Editor. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the getObject method implemented in the ContentRestController class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-20328.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40517|2024-06-04T17:19:03.647Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
