<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for wptipsntricks -- WordPress Simple Shopping Cart</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/wptipsntricks/wordpress%20simple%20shopping%20cart.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for wptipsntricks -- WordPress Simple Shopping Cart</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 09:23:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6497|2024-08-02T08:35:13.232Z -- wptipsntricks -- wordpress%20simple%20shopping%20cart
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6497</link>
      <description>The WordPress Simple Shopping Cart plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the automatic redirect URL setting in all versions up to and including 4.7.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6497|2024-08-02T08:35:13.232Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 03:32:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1431|2024-08-02T05:49:11.675Z -- wptipsntricks -- wordpress%20simple%20shopping%20cart
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1431</link>
      <description>The WP Simple Shopping Cart plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in versions up to, and including, 4.6.3 due to the plugin saving shopping cart data exports in a publicly accessible location (/wp-content/plugins/wordpress-simple-paypal-shopping-cart/includes/admin/). This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view information that should be limited to administrators only and can include data like first name, last name, email, address, IP Address, and more.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1431|2024-08-02T05:49:11.675Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 12:36:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
