<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Splunk, Inc -- Splunk Enterprise</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/splunk%2C%20inc/splunk%20enterprise.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Splunk, Inc -- Splunk Enterprise</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 17:22:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-32158|2024-08-03T07:32:56.019Z -- splunk%2C%20inc -- splunk%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32158</link>
      <description>Splunk Enterprise deployment servers in versions before 8.1.10.1, 8.2.6.1, and 9.0 let clients deploy forwarder bundles to other deployment clients through the deployment server. An attacker that compromised a Universal Forwarder endpoint could use the vulnerability to execute arbitrary code on all other Universal Forwarder endpoints subscribed to the deployment server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-32158|2024-08-03T07:32:56.019Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-32154|2024-08-03T07:32:55.969Z -- splunk%2C%20inc -- splunk%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32154</link>
      <description>Dashboards in Splunk Enterprise versions before 9.0 might let an attacker inject risky search commands into a form token when the token is used in a query in a cross-origin request. The result bypasses SPL safeguards for risky commands. See New capabilities can limit access to some custom and potentially risky commands (https://docs.splunk.com/Documentation/Splunk/9.0.0/Security/SPLsafeguards#New_capabilities_can_limit_access_to_some_custom_and_potentially_risky_commands) for more information. Note that the attack is browser-based and an attacker cannot exploit it at will.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-32154|2024-08-03T07:32:55.969Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-32153|2024-08-03T07:32:56.026Z -- splunk%2C%20inc -- splunk%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32153</link>
      <description>Splunk Enterprise peers in Splunk Enterprise versions before 9.0 and Splunk Cloud Platform versions before 8.2.2203 did not validate the TLS certificates during Splunk-to-Splunk communications by default. Splunk peer communications configured properly with valid certificates were not vulnerable. However, an attacker with administrator credentials could add a peer without a valid certificate and connections from misconfigured nodes without valid certificates did not fail by default. For Splunk Enterprise, update to Splunk Enterprise version 9.0 and Configure TLS host name validation for Splunk-to-Splunk communications (https://docs.splunk.com/Documentation/Splunk/9.0.0/Security/EnableTLSCertHostnameValidation) to enable the remediation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-32153|2024-08-03T07:32:56.026Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-32151|2024-08-03T07:32:56.016Z -- splunk%2C%20inc -- splunk%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32151</link>
      <description>The httplib and urllib Python libraries that Splunk shipped with Splunk Enterprise did not validate certificates using the certificate authority (CA) certificate stores by default in Splunk Enterprise versions before 9.0 and Splunk Cloud Platform versions before 8.2.2203. Python 3 client libraries now verify server certificates by default and use the appropriate CA certificate stores for each library. Apps and add-ons that include their own HTTP libraries are not affected. For Splunk Enterprise, update to Splunk Enterprise version 9.0 and Configure TLS host name validation for Splunk-to-Splunk communications (https://docs.splunk.com/Documentation/Splunk/9.0.0/Security/EnableTLSCertHostnameValidation) to enable the remediation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-32151|2024-08-03T07:32:56.016Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-32157|2024-08-03T07:32:56.013Z -- splunk%2C%20inc -- splunk%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32157</link>
      <description>Splunk Enterprise deployment servers in versions before 9.0 allow unauthenticated downloading of forwarder bundles. Remediation requires you to update the deployment server to version 9.0 and Configure authentication for deployment servers and clients (https://docs.splunk.com/Documentation/Splunk/9.0.0/Security/ConfigDSDCAuthEnhancements#Configure_authentication_for_deployment_servers_and_clients). Once enabled, deployment servers can manage only Universal Forwarder versions 9.0 and higher. Though the vulnerability does not directly affect Universal Forwarders, remediation requires updating all Universal Forwarders that the deployment server manages to version 9.0 or higher prior to enabling the remediation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-32157|2024-08-03T07:32:56.013Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
