<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Proofpoint -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/proofpoint/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Proofpoint -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5770|2024-01-09T22:02:03.839Z -- proofpoint -- proofpoint%20enterprise%20protection
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5770</link>
      <description>Proofpoint Enterprise Protection contains a vulnerability in the email delivery agent that allows an unauthenticated attacker to inject improperly encoded HTML into the email body of a message through the email subject.  The vulnerability is caused by inappropriate encoding when rewriting the email before delivery.This issue affects Proofpoint Enterprise Protection: from 8.20.2 before patch 4809, from 8.20.0 before patch 4805, from 8.18.6 before patch 4804 and all other prior versions.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5770|2024-01-09T22:02:03.839Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 22:02:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5771|2023-11-06T20:06:30.766Z -- proofpoint -- proofpoint%20enterprise%20protection
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5771</link>
      <description>Proofpoint Enterprise Protection contains a stored XSS vulnerability in the AdminUI. An unauthenticated attacker can send a specially crafted email with HTML in the subject which triggers XSS when viewing quarantined messages.  This issue affects Proofpoint Enterprise Protection: from 8.20.0 before patch 4796, from 8.18.6 before patch 4795 and all other prior versions.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5771|2023-11-06T20:06:30.766Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 20:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0090|2023-07-12T19:00:06.801Z -- proofpoint -- enterprise_protection
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0090</link>
      <description>The webservices in Proofpoint Enterprise Protection (PPS/POD) contain a vulnerability that allows for an anonymous user to execute remote code through 'eval injection'.  Exploitation requires network access to the webservices API, but such access is a non-standard configuration.  This affects all versions 8.20.0 and below.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0090|2023-07-12T19:00:06.801Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:27:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0089|2023-03-08T00:27:25.544Z -- proofpoint -- enterprise_protection
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0089</link>
      <description>
The webutils in Proofpoint Enterprise Protection (PPS/POD) contain a vulnerability that allows an authenticated user to execute remote code through 'eval injection'.

This affects all versions 8.20.0 and below. 





</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0089|2023-03-08T00:27:25.544Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:27:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4801|2023-09-13T15:14:36.165Z -- proofpoint -- insider%20threat%20management
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4801</link>
      <description>An improper certification validation vulnerability in the Insider Threat Management (ITM) Agent for MacOS could be used by an anonymous actor on an adjacent network to establish a man-in-the-middle position between the agent and the ITM server after the agent has registered. All versions prior to 7.14.3.69 are affected. Agents for Windows, Linux, and Cloud are unaffected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4801|2023-09-13T15:14:36.165Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 15:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4828|2023-10-13T21:50:46.186Z -- proofpoint -- itm%20server
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4828</link>
      <description>An improper check for an exceptional condition in the Insider Threat Management (ITM) Server could be used by an attacker to change the server's configuration of any already-registered agent so that the agent sends all future communications to an attacker-chosen URL. This could result in disclosure of sensitive data events from the agent about the personally identifiable information (PII) and intellectual property it monitors, and all such data could be altered or deleted before reaching the ITM Server. An attacker must first successfully obtain valid agent credentials and agent hostname. All versions prior to 7.14.3.69 are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4828|2023-10-13T21:50:46.186Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 15:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4803|2023-10-13T21:46:56.911Z -- proofpoint -- itm%20server
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4803</link>
      <description>A reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability in the WriteWindowTitle endpoint of the Insider Threat Management (ITM) Server's web console could be used by an authenticated administrator to run arbitrary javascript within another web console administrator's browser. All versions prior to 7.14.3.69 are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4803|2023-10-13T21:46:56.911Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 15:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4802|2023-10-13T21:46:33.623Z -- proofpoint -- itm%20server
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4802</link>
      <description>A reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability in the UpdateInstalledSoftware endpoint of the Insider Threat Management (ITM) Server's web console could be used by an authenticated administrator to run arbitrary javascript within another web console administrator's browser. All versions prior to 7.14.3.69 are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4802|2023-10-13T21:46:33.623Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 15:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-36000|2023-06-27T14:32:01.270Z -- proofpoint -- insider%20threat%20management
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-36000</link>
      <description>A missing authorization check in the MacOS agent configuration endpoint of the Insider Threat Management Server enables an anonymous attacker on an adjacent network to obtain sensitive information. Successful exploitation requires an attacker to first obtain a valid agent authentication token. All versions before 7.14.3 are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-36000|2023-06-27T14:32:01.270Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 14:32:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-36002|2023-06-27T14:32:26.673Z -- proofpoint -- insider%20threat%20management
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-36002</link>
      <description>A missing authorization check in multiple URL validation endpoints of the Insider Threat Management Server enables an anonymous attacker on an adjacent network to smuggle content via DNS lookups. All versions before 7.14.3 are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-36002|2023-06-27T14:32:26.673Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 14:32:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35998|2023-06-27T14:30:53.460Z -- proofpoint -- insider%20threat%20management
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35998</link>
      <description>A missing authorization check in multiple SOAP endpoints of the Insider Threat Management Server enables an attacker on an adjacent network to read and write unauthorized objects. Successful exploitation requires an attacker to first obtain a valid agent authentication token. All versions before 7.14.3 are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35998|2023-06-27T14:30:53.460Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 14:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2818|2023-06-27T14:31:22.344Z -- proofpoint -- insider%20threat%20management
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-2818</link>
      <description>An insecure filesystem permission in the Insider Threat Management Agent for Windows enables local unprivileged users to disrupt agent monitoring. All versions prior to 7.14.3 are affected. Agents for MacOS and Linux and Cloud are unaffected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2818|2023-06-27T14:31:22.344Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 14:29:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2819|2023-06-14T21:14:38.212Z -- proofpoint -- threat%20response%20auto%20pull
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-2819</link>
      <description>A stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Sources UI in Proofpoint Threat Response/ Threat Response Auto Pull (PTR/TRAP) could allow an authenticated administrator on an adjacent network to replace the image file with an arbitrary MIME type.  This could result in arbitrary javascript code execution in an admin context. All versions prior to 5.10.0 are affected.  </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2819|2023-06-14T21:14:38.212Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 21:14:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2820|2023-06-16T20:24:43.802Z -- proofpoint -- threat%20response%20auto%20pull
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-2820</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability in the faye endpoint in Proofpoint Threat Response / Threat Response Auto-Pull (PTR/TRAP) could be used by an attacker on an adjacent network to obtain credentials to integrated services via a man-in-the-middle position or cryptanalysis of the session traffic. An attacker could use these credentials to impersonate PTR/TRAP to these services. All versions prior to 5.10.0 are affected. 
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2820|2023-06-16T20:24:43.802Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 21:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0862|2024-05-14T19:07:04.897Z -- proofpoint -- enterprise%20protection
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0862</link>
      <description>The Proofpoint Encryption endpoint of Proofpoint Enterprise Protection contains a Server-Side Request Forgery vulnerability that allows an authenticated user to relay HTTP requests from the Protection server to otherwise private network addresses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0862|2024-05-14T19:07:04.897Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:07:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3676|2024-06-04T17:31:16.298Z -- proofpoint -- enterprise%20protection
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3676</link>
      <description>The Proofpoint Encryption endpoint of Proofpoint Enterprise Protection contains an Improper Input Validation vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated remote attacker with a specially crafted HTTP request to create additional Encryption user accounts under the attacker's control.  These accounts are able to send spoofed email to any users within the domains configured by the Administrator.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3676|2024-06-04T17:31:16.298Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:07:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
