<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Proofpoint -- Insider Threat Management</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/proofpoint/insider%20threat%20management.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Proofpoint -- Insider Threat Management</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 21:22:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-36000|2024-08-02T16:37:41.242Z -- proofpoint -- insider%20threat%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36000</link>
      <description>A missing authorization check in the MacOS agent configuration endpoint of the Insider Threat Management Server enables an anonymous attacker on an adjacent network to obtain sensitive information. Successful exploitation requires an attacker to first obtain a valid agent authentication token. All versions before 7.14.3 are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-36000|2024-08-02T16:37:41.242Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 14:32:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35998|2024-08-02T16:37:41.192Z -- proofpoint -- insider%20threat%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35998</link>
      <description>A missing authorization check in multiple SOAP endpoints of the Insider Threat Management Server enables an attacker on an adjacent network to read and write unauthorized objects. Successful exploitation requires an attacker to first obtain a valid agent authentication token. All versions before 7.14.3 are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35998|2024-08-02T16:37:41.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 14:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2818|2024-08-02T06:33:05.639Z -- proofpoint -- insider%20threat%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2818</link>
      <description>An insecure filesystem permission in the Insider Threat Management Agent for Windows enables local unprivileged users to disrupt agent monitoring. All versions prior to 7.14.3 are affected. Agents for MacOS and Linux and Cloud are unaffected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2818|2024-08-02T06:33:05.639Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 14:29:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4801|2024-08-02T07:38:00.701Z -- proofpoint -- insider%20threat%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4801</link>
      <description>An improper certification validation vulnerability in the Insider Threat Management (ITM) Agent for MacOS could be used by an anonymous actor on an adjacent network to establish a man-in-the-middle position between the agent and the ITM server after the agent has registered. All versions prior to 7.14.3.69 are affected. Agents for Windows, Linux, and Cloud are unaffected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4801|2024-08-02T07:38:00.701Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 15:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-36002|2024-08-02T16:37:40.673Z -- proofpoint -- insider%20threat%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36002</link>
      <description>A missing authorization check in multiple URL validation endpoints of the Insider Threat Management Server enables an anonymous attacker on an adjacent network to smuggle content via DNS lookups. All versions before 7.14.3 are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-36002|2024-08-02T16:37:40.673Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 14:32:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
