<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Proofpoint -- ITM Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/proofpoint/itm%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Proofpoint -- ITM Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 12:26:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4828|2024-08-02T07:38:00.805Z -- proofpoint -- itm%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4828</link>
      <description>An improper check for an exceptional condition in the Insider Threat Management (ITM) Server could be used by an attacker to change the server's configuration of any already-registered agent so that the agent sends all future communications to an attacker-chosen URL. This could result in disclosure of sensitive data events from the agent about the personally identifiable information (PII) and intellectual property it monitors, and all such data could be altered or deleted before reaching the ITM Server. An attacker must first successfully obtain valid agent credentials and agent hostname. All versions prior to 7.14.3.69 are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4828|2024-08-02T07:38:00.805Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 15:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4803|2024-08-02T07:38:00.773Z -- proofpoint -- itm%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4803</link>
      <description>A reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability in the WriteWindowTitle endpoint of the Insider Threat Management (ITM) Server's web console could be used by an authenticated administrator to run arbitrary javascript within another web console administrator's browser. All versions prior to 7.14.3.69 are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4803|2024-08-02T07:38:00.773Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 15:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4802|2024-08-02T07:38:00.847Z -- proofpoint -- itm%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4802</link>
      <description>A reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability in the UpdateInstalledSoftware endpoint of the Insider Threat Management (ITM) Server's web console could be used by an authenticated administrator to run arbitrary javascript within another web console administrator's browser. All versions prior to 7.14.3.69 are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4802|2024-08-02T07:38:00.847Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 15:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
