<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for ColumbiaSoft -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/columbiasoft/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for ColumbiaSoft -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 14:22:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5830|2024-08-02T08:14:24.335Z -- columbiasoft -- document%20locator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5830</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in ColumbiaSoft Document Locator. This affects an unknown part of the file /api/authentication/login of the component WebTools. The manipulation of the argument Server leads to improper authentication. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 7.2 SP4 and 2021.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-243729 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in ColumbiaSoft Document Locator entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei /api/authentication/login der Komponente WebTools. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments Server mit unbekannten Daten kann eine improper authentication-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 7.2 SP4 and 2021.1 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5830|2024-08-02T08:14:24.335Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
