<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for bytecodealliance -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/bytecodealliance/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for bytecodealliance -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 12:25:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39218|2024-08-04T01:58:18.261Z -- bytecodealliance -- wasmtime
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39218</link>
      <description>Wasmtime is an open source runtime for WebAssembly &amp; WASI. In Wasmtime from version 0.26.0 and before version 0.30.0 is affected by a memory unsoundness vulnerability. There was an invalid free and out-of-bounds read and write bug when running Wasm that uses `externref`s in Wasmtime. To trigger this bug, Wasmtime needs to be running Wasm that uses `externref`s, the host creates non-null `externrefs`, Wasmtime performs a garbage collection (GC), and there has to be a Wasm frame on the stack that is at a GC safepoint where there are no live references at this safepoint, and there is a safepoint with live references earlier in this frame's function. Under this scenario, Wasmtime would incorrectly use the GC stack map for the safepoint from earlier in the function instead of the empty safepoint. This would result in Wasmtime treating arbitrary stack slots as `externref`s that needed to be rooted for GC. At the *next* GC, it would be determined that nothing was referencing these bogus `externref`s (because nothing could ever reference them, because they are not really `externref`s) and then Wasmtime would deallocate them and run `&lt;ExternRef as Drop&gt;::drop` on them. This results in a free of memory that is not necessarily on the heap (and shouldn't be freed at this moment even if it was), as well as potential out-of-bounds reads and writes. Even though support for `externref`s (via the reference types proposal) is enabled by default, unless you are creating non-null `externref`s in your host code or explicitly triggering GCs, you cannot be affected by this bug. We have reason to believe that the effective impact of this bug is relatively small because usage of `externref` is currently quite rare. This bug has been patched and users should upgrade to Wasmtime version 0.30.0. If you cannot upgrade Wasmtime at this time, you can avoid this bug by disabling the reference types proposal by passing `false` to `wasmtime::Config::wasm_reference_types`.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39218|2024-08-04T01:58:18.261Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 20:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43790|2024-08-04T04:03:08.681Z -- bytecodealliance -- lucet
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43790</link>
      <description>Lucet is a native WebAssembly compiler and runtime. There is a bug in the main branch of `lucet-runtime` affecting all versions published to crates.io that allows a use-after-free in an Instance object that could result in memory corruption, data race, or other related issues. This bug was introduced early in the development of Lucet and is present in all releases. As a result of this bug, and dependent on the memory backing for the Instance objects, it is possible to trigger a use-after-free when the Instance is dropped. Users should upgrade to the main branch of the Lucet repository. Lucet no longer provides versioned releases on crates.io. There is no way to remediate this vulnerability without upgrading.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43790|2024-08-04T04:03:08.681Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 23:55:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39219|2024-08-04T01:58:18.272Z -- bytecodealliance -- wasmtime
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39219</link>
      <description>Wasmtime is an open source runtime for WebAssembly &amp; WASI. Wasmtime before version 0.30.0 is affected by a type confusion vulnerability. As a Rust library the `wasmtime` crate clearly marks which functions are safe and which are `unsafe`, guaranteeing that if consumers never use `unsafe` then it should not be possible to have memory unsafety issues in their embeddings of Wasmtime. An issue was discovered in the safe API of `Linker::func_*` APIs. These APIs were previously not sound when one `Engine` was used to create the `Linker` and then a different `Engine` was used to create a `Store` and then the `Linker` was used to instantiate a module into that `Store`. Cross-`Engine` usage of functions is not supported in Wasmtime and this can result in type confusion of function pointers, resulting in being able to safely call a function with the wrong type. Triggering this bug requires using at least two `Engine` values in an embedding and then additionally using two different values with a `Linker` (one at the creation time of the `Linker` and another when instantiating a module with the `Linker`). It's expected that usage of more-than-one `Engine` in an embedding is relatively rare since an `Engine` is intended to be a globally shared resource, so the expectation is that the impact of this issue is relatively small. The fix implemented is to change this behavior to `panic!()` in Rust instead of silently allowing it. Using different `Engine` instances with a `Linker` is a programmer bug that `wasmtime` catches at runtime. This bug has been patched and users should upgrade to Wasmtime version 0.30.0. If you cannot upgrade Wasmtime and are using more than one `Engine` in your embedding it's recommended to instead use only one `Engine` for the entire program if possible. An `Engine` is designed to be a globally shared resource that is suitable to have only one for the lifetime of an entire process. If using multiple `Engine`s is required then code should be audited to ensure that `Linker` is only used with one `Engine`.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39219|2024-08-04T01:58:18.272Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 20:10:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39216|2024-08-04T01:58:18.335Z -- bytecodealliance -- wasmtime
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39216</link>
      <description>Wasmtime is an open source runtime for WebAssembly &amp; WASI. In Wasmtime from version 0.19.0 and before version 0.30.0 there was a use-after-free bug when passing `externref`s from the host to guest Wasm content. To trigger the bug, you have to explicitly pass multiple `externref`s from the host to a Wasm instance at the same time, either by passing multiple `externref`s as arguments from host code to a Wasm function, or returning multiple `externref`s to Wasm from a multi-value return function defined in the host. If you do not have host code that matches one of these shapes, then you are not impacted. If Wasmtime's `VMExternRefActivationsTable` became filled to capacity after passing the first `externref` in, then passing in the second `externref` could trigger a garbage collection. However the first `externref` is not rooted until we pass control to Wasm, and therefore could be reclaimed by the collector if nothing else was holding a reference to it or otherwise keeping it alive. Then, when control was passed to Wasm after the garbage collection, Wasm could use the first `externref`, which at this point has already been freed. We have reason to believe that the effective impact of this bug is relatively small because usage of `externref` is currently quite rare. The bug has been fixed, and users should upgrade to Wasmtime 0.30.0. If you cannot upgrade Wasmtime yet, you can avoid the bug by disabling reference types support in Wasmtime by passing `false` to `wasmtime::Config::wasm_reference_types`.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39216|2024-08-04T01:58:18.335Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 20:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30266|2024-06-04T17:38:20.190Z -- bytecodealliance -- wasmtime</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30266</link>
      <description>wasmtime is a runtime for WebAssembly. The 19.0.0 release of Wasmtime contains a regression introduced during its development which can lead to a guest WebAssembly module causing a panic in the host runtime. A valid WebAssembly module, when executed at runtime, may cause this panic. This vulnerability has been patched in version 19.0.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30266|2024-06-04T17:38:20.190Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 15:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30266|2024-08-02T01:32:07.072Z -- bytecodealliance -- wasmtime</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30266</link>
      <description>wasmtime is a runtime for WebAssembly. The 19.0.0 release of Wasmtime contains a regression introduced during its development which can lead to a guest WebAssembly module causing a panic in the host runtime. A valid WebAssembly module, when executed at runtime, may cause this panic. This vulnerability has been patched in version 19.0.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30266|2024-08-02T01:32:07.072Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 15:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
