<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for TYPO3 -- TYPO3.CMS</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/typo3/typo3.cms.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for TYPO3 -- TYPO3.CMS</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 21:22:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26227|2024-08-04T15:56:03.033Z -- typo3 -- typo3.cms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26227</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an open source PHP based web content management system. In TYPO3 before versions 9.5.23 and 10.4.10 the system extension Fluid (typo3/cms-fluid) of the TYPO3 core is vulnerable to cross-site scripting passing user-controlled data as argument to Fluid view helpers. Update to TYPO3 versions 9.5.23 or 10.4.10 that fix the problem described.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26227|2024-08-04T15:56:03.033Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 21:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26228|2024-08-04T15:56:03.135Z -- typo3 -- typo3.cms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26228</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an open source PHP based web content management system. In TYPO3 before versions 9.5.23 and 10.4.10 user session identifiers were stored in cleartext - without processing with additional cryptographic hashing algorithms. This vulnerability cannot be exploited directly and occurs in combination with a chained attack - like for instance SQL injection in any other component of the system. Update to TYPO3 versions 9.5.23 or 10.4.10 that fix the problem described.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26228|2024-08-04T15:56:03.135Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 21:10:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26229|2024-08-04T15:56:03.052Z -- typo3 -- typo3.cms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26229</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an open source PHP based web content management system. In TYPO3 from version 10.4.0, and before version 10.4.10, RSS widgets are susceptible to XML external entity processing. This vulnerability is reasonable, but is theoretical - it was not possible to actually reproduce the vulnerability with current PHP versions of supported and maintained system distributions. At least with libxml2 version 2.9, the processing of XML external entities is disabled per default - and cannot be exploited. Besides that, a valid backend user account is needed. Update to TYPO3 version 10.4.10 to fix the problem described.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26229|2024-08-04T15:56:03.052Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 21:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
