<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for TYPO3 -- typo3</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/typo3/typo3.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for TYPO3 -- typo3</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 21:21:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31046|2024-08-03T07:03:40.293Z -- typo3 -- typo3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31046</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an open source web content management system. Prior to versions 7.6.57 ELTS, 8.7.47 ELTS, 9.5.34 ELTS, 10.4.29, and 11.5.11, the export functionality fails to limit the result set to allowed columns of a particular database table. This way, authenticated users can export internal details of database tables they already have access to. TYPO3 versions 7.6.57 ELTS, 8.7.47 ELTS, 9.5.34 ELTS, 10.4.29, 11.5.11 fix the problem described above. In order to address this issue, access to mentioned export functionality is completely denied for regular backend users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31046|2024-08-03T07:03:40.293Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 20:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36108|2024-08-03T09:52:00.564Z -- typo3 -- typo3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36108</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an open source PHP based web content management system released under the GNU GPL. It has been discovered that the `f:asset.css` view helper is vulnerable to cross-site scripting when user input is passed as variables to the CSS. Update to TYPO3 version 10.4.32 or 11.5.16 that fix the problem. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36108|2024-08-03T09:52:00.564Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 17:20:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31048|2024-08-03T07:03:40.296Z -- typo3 -- typo3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31048</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an open source web content management system. Prior to versions 8.7.47 ELTS, 9.5.34 ELTS, 10.4.29, and 11.5.11, the Form Designer backend module of the Form Framework is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. A valid backend user account with access to the form module is needed to exploit this vulnerability. TYPO3 versions 8.7.47 ELTS, 9.5.34 ELTS, 10.4.29, and 11.5.11 contain a fix for the problem.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31048|2024-08-03T07:03:40.296Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 20:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31047|2024-08-03T07:03:40.244Z -- typo3 -- typo3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31047</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an open source web content management system. Prior to versions 7.6.57 ELTS, 8.7.47 ELTS, 9.5.34 ELTS, 10.4.29, and 11.5.11, system internal credentials or keys (e.g. database credentials) can be logged as plaintext in exception handlers, when logging the complete exception stack trace. TYPO3 versions 7.6.57 ELTS, 8.7.47 ELTS, 9.5.34 ELTS, 10.4.29, 11.5.11 contain a fix for the problem.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31047|2024-08-03T07:03:40.244Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 20:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23501|2024-08-03T03:43:46.437Z -- typo3 -- typo3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23501</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an open source PHP based web content management system. In versions prior to 8.7.49, 9.5.38, 10.4.33, 11.5.20, and 12.1.1 TYPO3 is vulnerable to Improper Authentication. Restricting frontend login to specific users, organized in different storage folders (partitions), can be bypassed. A potential attacker might use this ambiguity in usernames to get access to a different account - however, credentials must be known to the adversary.  This issue is patched in versions 8.7.49 ELTS, 9.5.38 ELTS, 10.4.33, 11.5.20, 12.1.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23501|2024-08-03T03:43:46.437Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 07:23:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36104|2024-08-03T09:52:00.655Z -- typo3 -- typo3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36104</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an open source PHP based web content management system released under the GNU GPL. In affected versions requesting invalid or non-existing resources via HTTP triggers the page error handler which again could retrieve content to be shown as an error message from another page. This leads to a scenario in which the application is calling itself recursively - amplifying the impact of the initial attack until the limits of the web server are exceeded. Users are advised to update to TYPO3 version 11.5.16 to resolve this issue. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36104|2024-08-03T09:52:00.655Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 17:20:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36107|2024-08-03T09:52:00.556Z -- typo3 -- typo3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36107</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an open source PHP based web content management system released under the GNU GPL. It has been discovered that the `FileDumpController` (backend and frontend context) is vulnerable to cross-site scripting when malicious files are displayed using this component. A valid backend user account is needed to exploit this vulnerability. Update to TYPO3 version 7.6.58 ELTS, 8.7.48 ELTS, 9.5.37 ELTS, 10.4.32 or 11.5.16 that fix the problem. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36107|2024-08-03T09:52:00.556Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 17:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31050|2024-08-03T07:03:40.247Z -- typo3 -- typo3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31050</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an open source web content management system. Prior to versions 9.5.34 ELTS, 10.4.29, and 11.5.11, Admin Tool sessions initiated via the TYPO3 backend user interface had not been revoked even if the corresponding user account was degraded to lower permissions or disabled completely. This way, sessions in the admin tool theoretically could have been prolonged without any limit. TYPO3 versions 9.5.34 ELTS, 10.4.29, and 11.5.11 contain a fix for the problem.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31050|2024-08-03T07:03:40.247Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 20:55:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23502|2024-08-03T03:43:46.456Z -- typo3 -- typo3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23502</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an open source PHP based web content management system. In versions prior to 10.4.33, 11.5.20, and 12.1.1, When users reset their password using the corresponding password recovery functionality, existing sessions for that particular user account were not revoked. This applied to both frontend user sessions and backend user sessions. This issue is patched in versions 10.4.33, 11.5.20, 12.1.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23502|2024-08-03T03:43:46.456Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 07:34:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36105|2024-08-03T09:52:00.502Z -- typo3 -- typo3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36105</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an open source PHP based web content management system released under the GNU GPL. It has been discovered that observing response time during user authentication (backend and frontend) can be used to distinguish between existing and non-existing user accounts. Extension authors of 3rd party TYPO3 extensions providing a custom authentication service should check if the extension is affected by the described problem. Affected extensions must implement new `MimicServiceInterface::mimicAuthUser`, which simulates corresponding times regular processing would usually take. Update to TYPO3 version 7.6.58 ELTS, 8.7.48 ELTS, 9.5.37 ELTS, 10.4.32 or 11.5.16 that fix this problem. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36105|2024-08-03T09:52:00.502Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 17:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23503|2024-08-03T03:43:46.542Z -- typo3 -- typo3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23503</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an open source PHP based web content management system. Versions prior to 8.7.49, 9.5.38, 10.4.33, 11.5.20, and 12.1.1 are vulnerable to Code Injection. Due to the lack of separating user-submitted data from the internal configuration in the Form Designer backend module, it is possible to inject code instructions to be processed and executed via TypoScript as PHP code. The existence of individual TypoScript instructions for a particular form item and a valid backend user account with access to the form module are needed to exploit this vulnerability. This issue is patched in versions 8.7.49 ELTS, 9.5.38 ELTS, 10.4.33, 11.5.20, 12.1.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23503|2024-08-03T03:43:46.542Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 07:51:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36106|2024-08-03T09:52:00.554Z -- typo3 -- typo3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36106</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an open source PHP based web content management system released under the GNU GPL. It has been discovered that the expiration time of a password reset link for TYPO3 backend users has never been evaluated. As a result, a password reset link could be used to perform a password reset even if the default expiry time of two hours has been exceeded. Update to TYPO3 version 10.4.32 or 11.5.16 that fix the problem. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36106|2024-08-03T09:52:00.554Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 17:35:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31049|2024-08-03T07:03:40.221Z -- typo3 -- typo3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31049</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an open source web content management system. Prior to versions 9.5.34 ELTS, 10.4.29, and 11.5.11, user submitted content was used without being properly encoded in HTML emails sent to users. The actually affected components were mail clients used to view those messages. TYPO3 versions 9.5.34 ELTS, 10.4.29, and 11.5.11 contain a fix for the problem.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31049|2024-08-03T07:03:40.221Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 20:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23504|2024-08-03T03:43:46.501Z -- typo3 -- typo3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23504</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an open source PHP based web content management system. Versions prior to 9.5.38, 10.4.33, 11.5.20, and 12.1.1 are subject to Sensitive Information Disclosure. Due to the lack of handling user-submitted YAML placeholder expressions in the site configuration backend module, attackers could expose sensitive internal information, such as system configuration or HTTP request messages of other website visitors. A valid backend user account having administrator privileges is needed to exploit this vulnerability. This issue has been patched in versions 9.5.38 ELTS, 10.4.33, 11.5.20, 12.1.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23504|2024-08-03T03:43:46.501Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 07:58:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23500|2024-08-03T03:43:46.001Z -- typo3 -- typo3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23500</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an open source PHP based web content management system. In versions prior to 9.5.38, 10.4.33, 11.5.20, and 12.1.1, requesting invalid or non-existing resources via HTTP triggers the page error handler, which again could retrieve content to be shown as an error message from another page. This leads to a scenario in which the application is calling itself recursively - amplifying the impact of the initial attack until the limits of the web server are exceeded. This vulnerability is very similar, but not identical, to the one described in CVE-2021-21359. This issue is patched in versions 9.5.38 ELTS, 10.4.33, 11.5.20 or 12.1.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23500|2024-08-03T03:43:46.001Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 07:07:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34357|2024-08-02T02:51:11.194Z -- typo3 -- typo3</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34357</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an enterprise content management system. Starting in version 9.0.0 and prior to versions 9.5.48 ELTS, 10.4.45 ELTS, 11.5.37 LTS, 12.4.15 LTS, and 13.1.1, failing to properly encode user-controlled values in file entities, the `ShowImageController` (`_eID tx_cms_showpic_`) is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. Exploiting this vulnerability requires a valid backend user account with access to file entities. TYPO3 versions 9.5.48 ELTS, 10.4.45 ELTS, 11.5.37 LTS, 12.4.15 LTS, 13.1.1 fix the problem described.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34357|2024-08-02T02:51:11.194Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:13:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34356|2024-08-02T02:51:11.450Z -- typo3 -- typo3</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34356</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an enterprise content management system. Starting in version 9.0.0 and prior to versions 9.5.48 ELTS, 10.4.45 ELTS, 11.5.37 LTS, 12.4.15 LTS, and 13.1.1, the form manager backend module is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. Exploiting this vulnerability requires a valid backend user account with access to the form module. TYPO3 versions 9.5.48 ELTS, 10.4.45 ELTS, 11.5.37 LTS, 12.4.15 LTS, and 13.1.1 fix the problem described.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34356|2024-08-02T02:51:11.450Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34355|2024-08-02T02:51:11.144Z -- typo3 -- typo3</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34355</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an enterprise content management system. Starting in version 13.0.0 and prior to version 13.1.1, the history backend module is vulnerable to HTML injection. Although Content-Security-Policy headers effectively prevent JavaScript execution, adversaries can still inject malicious HTML markup. Exploiting this vulnerability requires a valid backend user account. TYPO3 version 13.1.1 fixes the problem described.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34355|2024-08-02T02:51:11.144Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:01:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34358|2024-08-02T02:51:11.435Z -- typo3 -- typo3</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34358</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an enterprise content management system. Starting in version 9.0.0 and prior to versions 9.5.48 ELTS, 10.4.45 ELTS, 11.5.37 LTS, 12.4.15 LTS, and 13.1.1, the `ShowImageController` (`_eID tx_cms_showpic_`) lacks a cryptographic HMAC-signature on the `frame` HTTP query parameter (e.g. `/index.php?eID=tx_cms_showpic?file=3&amp;...&amp;amp;frame=12345`). This allows adversaries to instruct the system to produce an arbitrary number of thumbnail images on the server side. TYPO3 versions 9.5.48 ELTS, 10.4.45 ELTS, 11.5.37 LTS, 12.4.15 LTS, 13.1.1 fix the problem described.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34358|2024-08-02T02:51:11.435Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34355|2024-06-04T17:42:41.383Z -- typo3 -- typo3</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-34355</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an enterprise content management system. Starting in version 13.0.0 and prior to version 13.1.1, the history backend module is vulnerable to HTML injection. Although Content-Security-Policy headers effectively prevent JavaScript execution, adversaries can still inject malicious HTML markup. Exploiting this vulnerability requires a valid backend user account. TYPO3 version 13.1.1 fixes the problem described.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34355|2024-06-04T17:42:41.383Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:01:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34358|2024-05-14T14:26:36.422Z -- typo3 -- typo3</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-34358</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an enterprise content management system. Starting in version 9.0.0 and prior to versions 9.5.48 ELTS, 10.4.45 ELTS, 11.5.37 LTS, 12.4.15 LTS, and 13.1.1, the `ShowImageController` (`_eID tx_cms_showpic_`) lacks a cryptographic HMAC-signature on the `frame` HTTP query parameter (e.g. `/index.php?eID=tx_cms_showpic?file=3&amp;...&amp;amp;frame=12345`). This allows adversaries to instruct the system to produce an arbitrary number of thumbnail images on the server side. TYPO3 versions 9.5.48 ELTS, 10.4.45 ELTS, 11.5.37 LTS, 12.4.15 LTS, 13.1.1 fix the problem described.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34358|2024-05-14T14:26:36.422Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34357|2024-05-14T14:25:53.339Z -- typo3 -- typo3</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-34357</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an enterprise content management system. Starting in version 9.0.0 and prior to versions 9.5.48 ELTS, 10.4.45 ELTS, 11.5.37 LTS, 12.4.15 LTS, and 13.1.1, failing to properly encode user-controlled values in file entities, the `ShowImageController` (`_eID tx_cms_showpic_`) is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. Exploiting this vulnerability requires a valid backend user account with access to file entities. TYPO3 versions 9.5.48 ELTS, 10.4.45 ELTS, 11.5.37 LTS, 12.4.15 LTS, 13.1.1 fix the problem described.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34357|2024-05-14T14:25:53.339Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:13:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34356|2024-06-04T17:41:04.744Z -- typo3 -- typo3</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-34356</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an enterprise content management system. Starting in version 9.0.0 and prior to versions 9.5.48 ELTS, 10.4.45 ELTS, 11.5.37 LTS, 12.4.15 LTS, and 13.1.1, the form manager backend module is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. Exploiting this vulnerability requires a valid backend user account with access to the form module. TYPO3 versions 9.5.48 ELTS, 10.4.45 ELTS, 11.5.37 LTS, 12.4.15 LTS, and 13.1.1 fix the problem described.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34356|2024-06-04T17:41:04.744Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25118|2024-06-04T17:35:53.986Z -- typo3 -- typo3</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25118</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an open source PHP based web content management system released under the GNU GPL. Password hashes were being reflected in the editing forms of the TYPO3 backend user interface. This allowed attackers to crack the plaintext password using brute force techniques. Exploiting this vulnerability requires a valid backend user account. Users are advised to update to TYPO3 versions 8.7.57 ELTS, 9.5.46 ELTS, 10.4.43 ELTS, 11.5.35 LTS, 12.4.11 LTS, 13.0.1 that fix the problem described. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25118|2024-06-04T17:35:53.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 22:19:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25119|2024-06-04T17:35:39.545Z -- typo3 -- typo3</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25119</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an open source PHP based web content management system released under the GNU GPL. The plaintext value of `$GLOBALS['SYS']['encryptionKey']` was displayed in the editing forms of the TYPO3 Install Tool user interface. This allowed attackers to utilize the value to generate cryptographic hashes used for verifying the authenticity of HTTP request parameters. Exploiting this vulnerability requires an administrator-level backend user account with system maintainer permissions. Users are advised to update to TYPO3 versions 8.7.57 ELTS, 9.5.46 ELTS, 10.4.43 ELTS, 11.5.35 LTS, 12.4.11 LTS, 13.0.1 that fix the problem described. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25119|2024-06-04T17:35:39.545Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 22:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25120|2024-06-04T17:35:11.339Z -- typo3 -- typo3</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25120</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an open source PHP based web content management system released under the GNU GPL. The TYPO3-specific `t3://` URI scheme could be used to access resources outside of the users' permission scope. This encompassed files, folders, pages, and records (although only if a valid link-handling configuration was provided). Exploiting this vulnerability requires a valid backend user account. Users are advised to update to TYPO3 versions 8.7.57 ELTS, 9.5.46 ELTS, 10.4.43 ELTS, 11.5.35 LTS, 12.4.11 LTS, 13.0.1 that fix the problem described. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25120|2024-06-04T17:35:11.339Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 22:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25121|2024-02-13T22:14:40.926Z -- typo3 -- typo3</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25121</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an open source PHP based web content management system released under the GNU GPL. In affected versions of TYPO3 entities of the File Abstraction Layer (FAL) could be persisted directly via `DataHandler`. This allowed attackers to reference files in the fallback storage directly and retrieve their file names and contents. The fallback storage ("zero-storage") is used as a backward compatibility layer for files located outside properly configured file storages and within the public web root directory. Exploiting this vulnerability requires a valid backend user account. Users are advised to update to TYPO3 version 8.7.57 ELTS, 9.5.46 ELTS, 10.4.43 ELTS, 11.5.35 LTS, 12.4.11 LTS, or 13.0.1 which fix the problem described. When persisting entities of the File Abstraction Layer directly via DataHandler, `sys_file` entities are now denied by default, and `sys_file_reference` &amp; `sys_file_metadata` entities are not permitted to reference files in the fallback storage anymore. When importing data from secure origins, this must be explicitly enabled in the corresponding DataHandler instance by using `$dataHandler-&gt;isImporting = true;`.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25121|2024-02-13T22:14:40.926Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 22:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34358|2024-06-12T15:46:38.522Z -- typo3 -- typo3</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-34358</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an enterprise content management system. Starting in version 9.0.0 and prior to versions 9.5.48 ELTS, 10.4.45 ELTS, 11.5.37 LTS, 12.4.15 LTS, and 13.1.1, the `ShowImageController` (`_eID tx_cms_showpic_`) lacks a cryptographic HMAC-signature on the `frame` HTTP query parameter (e.g. `/index.php?eID=tx_cms_showpic?file=3&amp;...&amp;amp;frame=12345`). This allows adversaries to instruct the system to produce an arbitrary number of thumbnail images on the server side. TYPO3 versions 9.5.48 ELTS, 10.4.45 ELTS, 11.5.37 LTS, 12.4.15 LTS, 13.1.1 fix the problem described.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34358|2024-06-12T15:46:38.522Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34357|2024-06-12T15:47:27.316Z -- typo3 -- typo3</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-34357</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an enterprise content management system. Starting in version 9.0.0 and prior to versions 9.5.48 ELTS, 10.4.45 ELTS, 11.5.37 LTS, 12.4.15 LTS, and 13.1.1, failing to properly encode user-controlled values in file entities, the `ShowImageController` (`_eID tx_cms_showpic_`) is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. Exploiting this vulnerability requires a valid backend user account with access to file entities. TYPO3 versions 9.5.48 ELTS, 10.4.45 ELTS, 11.5.37 LTS, 12.4.15 LTS, 13.1.1 fix the problem described.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34357|2024-06-12T15:47:27.316Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:13:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
