<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for TYPO3 -- TYPO3.CMS</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/typo3/typo3.cms.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for TYPO3 -- TYPO3.CMS</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 19:19:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21357|2024-08-03T18:09:15.663Z -- typo3 -- typo3.cms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21357</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an open source PHP based web content management system. In TYPO3 before versions 8.7.40, 9.5.25, 10.4.14, 11.1.1 due to improper input validation, attackers can by-pass restrictions of predefined options and submit arbitrary data in the Form Designer backend module of the Form Framework. In the default configuration of the Form Framework this allows attackers to explicitly allow arbitrary mime-types for file uploads - however, default _fileDenyPattern_ successfully blocked files like _.htaccess_ or _malicious.php_. Besides that, attackers can persist those files in any writable directory of the corresponding TYPO3 installation. A valid backend user account with access to the form module is needed to exploit this vulnerability. This is fixed in versions 8.7.40, 9.5.25, 10.4.14, 11.1.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21357|2024-08-03T18:09:15.663Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 01:50:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21370|2024-08-03T18:09:15.935Z -- typo3 -- typo3.cms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21370</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an open source PHP based web content management system. In TYPO3 before versions 7.6.51, 8.7.40, 9.5.25, 10.4.14, 11.1.1 it has been discovered that content elements of type _menu_ are vulnerable to cross-site scripting when their referenced items get previewed in the page module. A valid backend user account is needed to exploit this vulnerability. This is fixed in versions 7.6.51, 8.7.40, 9.5.25, 10.4.14, 11.1.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21370|2024-08-03T18:09:15.935Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 01:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21339|2024-08-03T18:09:15.911Z -- typo3 -- typo3.cms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21339</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an open source PHP based web content management system. In TYPO3 before versions 6.2.57, 7.6.51, 8.7.40, 9.5.25, 10.4.14, 11.1.1 user session identifiers were stored in cleartext - without processing of additional cryptographic hashing algorithms. This vulnerability cannot be exploited directly and occurs in combination with a chained attack - like for instance SQL injection in any other component of the system. This is fixed in versions 6.2.57, 7.6.51, 8.7.40, 9.5.25, 10.4.14, 11.1.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21339|2024-08-03T18:09:15.911Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 01:50:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21338|2024-08-03T18:09:15.687Z -- typo3 -- typo3.cms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21338</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an open source PHP based web content management system. In TYPO3 before versions 6.2.57, 7.6.51, 8.7.40, 9.5.25, 10.4.14, 11.1.1 it has been discovered that Login Handling is susceptible to open redirection which allows attackers redirecting to arbitrary content, and conducting phishing attacks. No authentication is required in order to exploit this vulnerability. This is fixed in versions 6.2.57, 7.6.51, 8.7.40, 9.5.25, 10.4.14, 11.1.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21338|2024-08-03T18:09:15.687Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 01:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21359|2024-08-03T18:09:15.893Z -- typo3 -- typo3.cms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21359</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an open source PHP based web content management system. In TYPO3 before versions 9.5.25, 10.4.14, 11.1.1 requesting invalid or non-existing resources via HTTP triggers the page error handler which again could retrieve content to be shown as error message from another page. This leads to a scenario in which the application is calling itself recursively - amplifying the impact of the initial attack until the limits of the web server are exceeded. This is fixed in versions 9.5.25, 10.4.14, 11.1.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21359|2024-08-03T18:09:15.893Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 01:55:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21355|2024-08-03T18:09:15.669Z -- typo3 -- typo3.cms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21355</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an open source PHP based web content management system. In TYPO3 before versions 8.7.40, 9.5.25, 10.4.14, 11.1.1, due to the lack of ensuring file extensions belong to configured allowed mime-types, attackers can upload arbitrary data with arbitrary file extensions - however, default _fileDenyPattern_ successfully blocked files like _.htaccess_ or _malicious.php_. Besides that, _UploadedFileReferenceConverter_ transforming uploaded files into proper FileReference domain model objects handles possible file uploads for other extensions as well - given those extensions use the Extbase MVC framework, make use of FileReference items in their direct or inherited domain model definitions and did not implement their own type converter. In case this scenario applies, _UploadedFileReferenceConverter_ accepts any file mime-type and persists files in the default location. In any way, uploaded files are placed in the default location _/fileadmin/user_upload/_, in most scenarios keeping the submitted filename - which allows attackers to directly reference files, or even correctly guess filenames used by other individuals, disclosing this information. No authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability. This is fixed in versions 8.7.40, 9.5.25, 10.4.14, 11.1.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21355|2024-08-03T18:09:15.669Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 01:50:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21358|2024-08-03T18:09:15.902Z -- typo3 -- typo3.cms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21358</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an open source PHP based web content management system. In TYPO3 before versions 10.4.14, 11.1.1 it has been discovered that the Form Designer backend module of the Form Framework is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. A valid backend user account with access to the form module is needed to exploit this vulnerability. This is fixed in versions 10.4.14, 11.1.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21358|2024-08-03T18:09:15.902Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 01:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21340|2024-08-03T18:09:15.910Z -- typo3 -- typo3.cms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21340</link>
      <description>TYPO3 is an open source PHP based web content management system. In TYPO3 before versions 10.4.14, 11.1.1 it has been discovered that database fields used as _descriptionColumn_ are vulnerable to cross-site scripting when their content gets previewed. A valid backend user account is needed to exploit this vulnerability. This is fixed in versions 10.4.14, 11.1.1 .</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21340|2024-08-03T18:09:15.910Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 01:50:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
