<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for OpenCycleCompass -- server-php</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/opencyclecompass/server-php.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for OpenCycleCompass -- server-php</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 13:23:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2015-10086|2024-08-06T08:58:26.108Z -- opencyclecompass -- server-php
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-10086</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in OpenCycleCompass server-php. Affected is an unknown function of the file api1/login.php. The manipulation of the argument user leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The name of the patch is fa0d9bcf81c711a88172ad0d37a842f029ac3782. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-221808.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in OpenCycleCompass server-php gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei api1/login.php. Durch Manipulation des Arguments user mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Dieses Produkt verzichtet auf eine Versionierung und verwendet stattdessen Rolling Releases. Deshalb sind keine Details zu betroffenen oder zu aktualisierende Versionen vorhanden. Der Patch wird als fa0d9bcf81c711a88172ad0d37a842f029ac3782 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2015-10086|2024-08-06T08:58:26.108Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 00:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
