<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for stylemix -- Directory Listings WordPress plugin – uListing</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/stylemix/directory%20listings%20wordpress%20plugin%20%E2%80%93%20ulisting.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for stylemix -- Directory Listings WordPress plugin – uListing</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 21:21:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-4341|2024-08-03T17:23:10.628Z -- stylemix -- directory%20listings%20wordpress%20plugin%20%E2%80%93%20ulisting
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4341</link>
      <description>The uListing plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass via Ajax due to missing capability checks, missing input validation, and a missing security nonce in the stm_update_email_data AJAX action in versions up to, and including, 1.6.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change any WordPress option in the database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-4341|2024-08-03T17:23:10.628Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 01:51:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-4340|2024-08-03T17:23:10.676Z -- stylemix -- directory%20listings%20wordpress%20plugin%20%E2%80%93%20ulisting
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4340</link>
      <description>The uListing plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to generic SQL Injection via the ‘listing_id’ parameter in versions up to, and including, 1.6.6 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-4340|2024-08-03T17:23:10.676Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 01:51:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-4345|2024-08-03T17:23:10.564Z -- stylemix -- directory%20listings%20wordpress%20plugin%20%E2%80%93%20ulisting
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4345</link>
      <description>The uListing plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass due to missing capability and nonce checks on the UlistingUserRole::save_role_api method in versions up to, and including, 1.6.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to remove or add roles, and add capabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-4345|2024-08-03T17:23:10.564Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 01:51:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-4343|2024-08-03T17:23:10.530Z -- stylemix -- directory%20listings%20wordpress%20plugin%20%E2%80%93%20ulisting
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4343</link>
      <description>The Unauthenticated Account Creation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Unauthenticated Account Creation in versions up to, and including, 1.6.6. This is due to the stm_listing_register AJAX action function being accessible and taking roles unprotected. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create accounts, even those with administrator privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-4343|2024-08-03T17:23:10.530Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 01:51:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-4370|2024-08-03T17:23:10.721Z -- stylemix -- directory%20listings%20wordpress%20plugin%20%E2%80%93%20ulisting
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4370</link>
      <description>The uListing plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass as most actions and endpoints are accessible to unauthenticated users, lack security nonces, and data is seldom validated. This issue exists in versions up to, and including, 1.6.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to conduct numerous administrative actions, including those less critical than the explicitly outlined ones in our detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-4370|2024-08-03T17:23:10.721Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 01:51:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-4346|2024-08-03T17:23:10.595Z -- stylemix -- directory%20listings%20wordpress%20plugin%20%E2%80%93%20ulisting
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4346</link>
      <description>The uListing plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Account Changes in versions up to, and including, 1.6.6. This is due to missing login checks on the stm_listing_profile_edit AJAX action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to edit any account on the blog, such as changing the admin account's email address.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-4346|2024-08-03T17:23:10.595Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 01:51:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-4339|2024-08-03T17:23:10.571Z -- stylemix -- directory%20listings%20wordpress%20plugin%20%E2%80%93%20ulisting
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4339</link>
      <description>The uListing plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass due to a missing capability check in the "ulisting/includes/route.php" file on the /1/api/ulisting-user/search REST-API route in versions up to, and including, 1.6.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the list of all users and their email address in the database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-4339|2024-08-03T17:23:10.571Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 01:51:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-4381|2024-08-03T17:23:10.724Z -- stylemix -- directory%20listings%20wordpress%20plugin%20%E2%80%93%20ulisting
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4381</link>
      <description>The uListing plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass via wp_route due to missing capability checks, and a missing security nonce, in the StmListingSingleLayout::import_new_layout method in versions up to, and including, 1.6.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change any WordPress option in the database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-4381|2024-08-03T17:23:10.724Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 01:51:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-4357|2024-08-03T17:23:10.721Z -- stylemix -- directory%20listings%20wordpress%20plugin%20%E2%80%93%20ulisting
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4357</link>
      <description>The uListing plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass due to missing capability checks, and a missing security nonce, on the UlistingUserRole::save_role_api function in versions up to, and including, 1.6.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to arbitrarily delete site posts and pages.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-4357|2024-08-03T17:23:10.721Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 01:51:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
