<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Spring by Pivotal -- Spring Framework</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/spring%20by%20pivotal/spring%20framework.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Spring by Pivotal -- Spring Framework</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 07:21:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1271|2024-08-05T03:51:49.212Z -- spring%20by%20pivotal -- spring%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1271</link>
      <description>Spring Framework, versions 5.0 prior to 5.0.5 and versions 4.3 prior to 4.3.15 and older unsupported versions, allow applications to configure Spring MVC to serve static resources (e.g. CSS, JS, images). When static resources are served from a file system on Windows (as opposed to the classpath, or the ServletContext), a malicious user can send a request using a specially crafted URL that can lead a directory traversal attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1271|2024-08-05T03:51:49.212Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1272|2024-08-05T03:51:49.063Z -- spring%20by%20pivotal -- spring%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1272</link>
      <description>Spring Framework, versions 5.0 prior to 5.0.5 and versions 4.3 prior to 4.3.15 and older unsupported versions, provide client-side support for multipart requests. When Spring MVC or Spring WebFlux server application (server A) receives input from a remote client, and then uses that input to make a multipart request to another server (server B), it can be exposed to an attack, where an extra multipart is inserted in the content of the request from server A, causing server B to use the wrong value for a part it expects. This could to lead privilege escalation, for example, if the part content represents a username or user roles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1272|2024-08-05T03:51:49.063Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1273|2024-08-05T03:51:48.994Z -- spring%20by%20pivotal -- spring%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1273</link>
      <description>Spring Data Commons, versions prior to 1.13 to 1.13.10, 2.0 to 2.0.5, and older unsupported versions, contain a property binder vulnerability caused by improper neutralization of special elements. An unauthenticated remote malicious user (or attacker) can supply specially crafted request parameters against Spring Data REST backed HTTP resources or using Spring Data's projection-based request payload binding hat can lead to a remote code execution attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1273|2024-08-05T03:51:48.994Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1275|2024-08-05T03:51:48.962Z -- spring%20by%20pivotal -- spring%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1275</link>
      <description>Spring Framework, versions 5.0 prior to 5.0.5 and versions 4.3 prior to 4.3.16 and older unsupported versions, allow applications to expose STOMP over WebSocket endpoints with a simple, in-memory STOMP broker through the spring-messaging module. A malicious user (or attacker) can craft a message to the broker that can lead to a remote code execution attack. This CVE addresses the partial fix for CVE-2018-1270 in the 4.3.x branch of the Spring Framework.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1275|2024-08-05T03:51:48.962Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1274|2024-08-05T03:51:49.173Z -- spring%20by%20pivotal -- spring%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1274</link>
      <description>Spring Data Commons, versions 1.13 to 1.13.10, 2.0 to 2.0.5, and older unsupported versions, contain a property path parser vulnerability caused by unlimited resource allocation. An unauthenticated remote malicious user (or attacker) can issue requests against Spring Data REST endpoints or endpoints using property path parsing which can cause a denial of service (CPU and memory consumption).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1274|2024-08-05T03:51:49.173Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1270|2024-08-05T03:51:48.998Z -- spring%20by%20pivotal -- spring%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1270</link>
      <description>Spring Framework, versions 5.0 prior to 5.0.5 and versions 4.3 prior to 4.3.15 and older unsupported versions, allow applications to expose STOMP over WebSocket endpoints with a simple, in-memory STOMP broker through the spring-messaging module. A malicious user (or attacker) can craft a message to the broker that can lead to a remote code execution attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1270|2024-08-05T03:51:48.998Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
