<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SUSE -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/suse/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SUSE -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 19:20:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31256|2024-09-16T16:32:57.789Z -- suse -- opensuse%20factory
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31256</link>
      <description>A Improper Link Resolution Before File Access ('Link Following') vulnerability in a script called by the sendmail systemd service of openSUSE Factory allows local attackers to escalate from user mail to root. This issue affects: SUSE openSUSE Factory sendmail versions prior to 8.17.1-1.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31256|2024-09-16T16:32:57.789Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 08:55:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3695|2024-09-16T18:03:10.964Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20high%20performance%20computing%2015-espos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3695</link>
      <description>A Improper Control of Generation of Code vulnerability in the packaging of pcp of SUSE Linux Enterprise High Performance Computing 15-ESPOS, SUSE Linux Enterprise High Performance Computing 15-LTSS, SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Development Tools 15, SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Development Tools 15-SP1, SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Open Buildservice Development Tools 15, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15-LTSS, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 15, SUSE Linux Enterprise Software Development Kit 12-SP4, SUSE Linux Enterprise Software Development Kit 12-SP5; openSUSE Leap 15.1 allows the user pcp to run code as root by placing it into /var/log/pcp/configs.sh This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise High Performance Computing 15-ESPOS pcp versions prior to 3.11.9-5.8.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise High Performance Computing 15-LTSS pcp versions prior to 3.11.9-5.8.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Development Tools 15 pcp versions prior to 3.11.9-5.8.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Development Tools 15-SP1 pcp versions prior to 4.3.1-3.5.3. SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Open Buildservice Development Tools 15 pcp versions prior to 3.11.9-5.8.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15-LTSS pcp versions prior to 3.11.9-5.8.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 15 pcp versions prior to 3.11.9-5.8.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Software Development Kit 12-SP4 pcp versions prior to 3.11.9-6.14.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Software Development Kit 12-SP5 pcp versions prior to 3.11.9-6.14.1. openSUSE Leap 15.1 pcp versions prior to 4.3.1-lp151.2.3.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3695|2024-09-16T18:03:10.964Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 11:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8027|2024-09-16T17:54:21.630Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20server%2015-ltss
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8027</link>
      <description>A Insecure Temporary File vulnerability in openldap2 of SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15-LTSS, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 15; openSUSE Leap 15.1, openSUSE Leap 15.2 allows local attackers to overwrite arbitrary files and gain access to the openldap2 configuration This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15-LTSS openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.46-9.37.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 15 openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.46-9.37.1. openSUSE Leap 15.1 openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.46-lp151.10.18.1. openSUSE Leap 15.2 openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.46-lp152.14.9.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8027|2024-09-16T17:54:21.630Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 16:10:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-36784|2024-09-16T18:08:54.118Z -- suse -- rancher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-36784</link>
      <description>A Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in SUSE Rancher allows users with the restricted-admin role to escalate to full admin. This issue affects: SUSE Rancher Rancher versions prior to 2.5.13; Rancher versions prior to 2.6.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-36784|2024-09-16T18:08:54.118Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 07:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31252|2024-09-16T18:40:06.727Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20server%2012-sp5
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31252</link>
      <description>A Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in chkstat of SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP5; openSUSE Leap 15.3, openSUSE Leap 15.4, openSUSE Leap Micro 5.2 did not consider group writable path components, allowing local attackers with access to a group what can write to a location included in the path to a privileged binary to influence path resolution. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP5 permissions versions prior to 20170707. openSUSE Leap 15.3 permissions versions prior to 20200127. openSUSE Leap 15.4 permissions versions prior to 20201225. openSUSE Leap Micro 5.2 permissions versions prior to 20181225.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31252|2024-09-16T18:40:06.727Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 17:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-36775|2024-09-16T18:34:57.999Z -- suse -- rancher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-36775</link>
      <description>a Improper Access Control vulnerability in SUSE Rancher allows users to keep privileges that should have been revoked. This issue affects: SUSE Rancher Rancher versions prior to 2.4.18; Rancher versions prior to 2.5.12; Rancher versions prior to 2.6.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-36775|2024-09-16T18:34:57.999Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 07:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-36783|2024-09-16T18:13:16.201Z -- suse -- rancher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-36783</link>
      <description>A Insufficiently Protected Credentials vulnerability in SUSE Rancher allows authenticated Cluster Owners, Cluster Members, Project Owners and Project Members to read credentials, passwords and API tokens that have been stored in cleartext and exposed via API endpoints. This issue affects: SUSE Rancher Rancher versions prior to 2.6.4; Rancher versions prior to 2.5.13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-36783|2024-09-16T18:13:16.201Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 08:20:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-20106|2024-09-16T17:23:19.129Z -- suse -- yast2-printer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-20106</link>
      <description>In yast2-printer up to and including version 4.0.2 the SMB printer settings don't escape characters in passwords properly. If a password with backticks or simliar characters is supplied this allows for executing code as root. This requires tricking root to enter such a password in yast.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-20106|2024-09-16T17:23:19.129Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31248|2024-09-16T16:22:26.146Z -- suse -- suse%20manager%20server%204.1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31248</link>
      <description>A Observable Response Discrepancy vulnerability in spacewalk-java of SUSE Manager Server 4.1, SUSE Manager Server 4.2 allows remote attackers to discover valid usernames. This issue affects: SUSE Manager Server 4.1 spacewalk-java versions prior to 4.1.46-1. SUSE Manager Server 4.2 spacewalk-java versions prior to 4.2.37-1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31248|2024-09-16T16:22:26.146Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 10:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21952|2024-09-16T18:54:14.410Z -- suse -- suse%20manager%20server%204.1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21952</link>
      <description>A Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability in spacewalk-java of SUSE Manager Server 4.1, SUSE Manager Server 4.2 allows remote attackers to easily exhaust available disk resources leading to DoS. This issue affects: SUSE Manager Server 4.1 spacewalk-java versions prior to 4.1.46. SUSE Manager Server 4.2 spacewalk-java versions prior to 4.2.37.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21952|2024-09-16T18:54:14.410Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 10:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14806|2024-09-16T16:48:59.649Z -- suse -- studio%20onsite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14806</link>
      <description>A Improper Certificate Validation vulnerability in susestudio-common of SUSE Studio onsite allows remote attackers to MITM connections to the repositories, which allows the modification of packages received over these connections. This issue affects: SUSE Studio onsite susestudio-common version 1.3.17-56.6.3 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14806|2024-09-16T16:48:59.649Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 09:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8029|2024-09-16T18:33:16.586Z -- suse -- suse%20caas%20platform%204.5
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8029</link>
      <description>A Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource vulnerability in skuba of SUSE CaaS Platform 4.5 allows local attackers to gain access to the kublet key. This issue affects: SUSE CaaS Platform 4.5 skuba versions prior to https://github.com/SUSE/skuba/pull/1416.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8029|2024-09-16T18:33:16.586Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 16:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25321|2024-09-16T18:43:24.802Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20server%2011-sp4-ltss
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25321</link>
      <description>A UNIX Symbolic Link (Symlink) Following vulnerability in arpwatch of SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11-SP4-LTSS, SUSE Manager Server 4.0, SUSE OpenStack Cloud Crowbar 9; openSUSE Factory, Leap 15.2 allows local attackers with control of the runtime user to run arpwatch as to escalate to root upon the next restart of arpwatch. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11-SP4-LTSS arpwatch versions prior to 2.1a15. SUSE Manager Server 4.0 arpwatch versions prior to 2.1a15. SUSE OpenStack Cloud Crowbar 9 arpwatch versions prior to 2.1a15. openSUSE Factory arpwatch version 2.1a15-169.5 and prior versions. openSUSE Leap 15.2 arpwatch version 2.1a15-lp152.5.5 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25321|2024-09-16T18:43:24.802Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 08:25:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8013|2024-09-16T17:23:50.476Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20server%2012
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8013</link>
      <description>A UNIX Symbolic Link (Symlink) Following vulnerability in chkstat of SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11 set permissions intended for specific binaries on other binaries because it erroneously followed symlinks. The symlinks can't be controlled by attackers on default systems, so exploitation is difficult. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12 permissions versions prior to 2015.09.28.1626-17.27.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 permissions versions prior to 20181116-9.23.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11 permissions versions prior to 2013.1.7-0.6.12.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8013|2024-09-16T17:23:50.476Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 16:35:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3698|2024-09-16T16:33:41.138Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20server%2012
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3698</link>
      <description>UNIX Symbolic Link (Symlink) Following vulnerability in the cronjob shipped with nagios of SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11; openSUSE Factory allows local attackers to cause cause DoS or potentially escalate privileges by winning a race. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12 nagios version 3.5.1-5.27 and prior versions. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11 nagios version 3.0.6-1.25.36.3.1 and prior versions. openSUSE Factory nagios version 4.4.5-2.1 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3698|2024-09-16T16:33:41.138Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 13:20:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-4200|2024-09-16T17:54:05.276Z -- suse -- rancher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4200</link>
      <description>A Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in SUSE Rancher allows write access to the Catalog for any user when restricted-admin role is enabled. This issue affects: SUSE Rancher Rancher versions prior to 2.5.13; Rancher versions prior to 2.6.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-4200|2024-09-16T17:54:05.276Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 07:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-32000|2024-09-16T17:48:09.451Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20server%2012%20sp3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-32000</link>
      <description>A UNIX Symbolic Link (Symlink) Following vulnerability in the clone-master-clean-up.sh script of clone-master-clean-up in SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12 SP3, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 SP1; openSUSE Factory allows local attackers to delete arbitrary files. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12 SP3 clone-master-clean-up version 1.6-4.6.1 and prior versions. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 SP1 clone-master-clean-up version 1.6-3.9.1 and prior versions. openSUSE Factory clone-master-clean-up version 1.6-1.4 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-32000|2024-09-16T17:48:09.451Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 09:35:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17953|2024-09-16T17:28:34.555Z -- suse -- pam
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17953</link>
      <description>A incorrect variable in a SUSE specific patch for pam_access rule matching in PAM 1.3.0 in openSUSE Leap 15.0 and SUSE Linux Enterprise 15 could lead to pam_access rules not being applied (fail open).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17953|2024-09-16T17:28:34.555Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18898|2024-09-16T18:24:53.684Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20server%2015%20sp1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18898</link>
      <description>UNIX Symbolic Link (Symlink) Following vulnerability in the trousers package of SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 SP1; openSUSE Factory allowed local attackers escalate privileges from user tss to root. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 SP1 trousers versions prior to 0.3.14-6.3.1. openSUSE Factory trousers versions prior to 0.3.14-7.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18898|2024-09-16T18:24:53.684Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 14:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8023|2024-09-16T18:33:45.008Z -- suse -- suse%20enterprise%20storage%205
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8023</link>
      <description>A acceptance of Extraneous Untrusted Data With Trusted Data vulnerability in the start script of openldap2 of SUSE Enterprise Storage 5, SUSE Linux Enterprise Debuginfo 11-SP3, SUSE Linux Enterprise Debuginfo 11-SP4, SUSE Linux Enterprise Point of Sale 11-SP3, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11-SECURITY, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11-SP4-LTSS, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP2-BCL, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP2-LTSS, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP3-BCL, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP3-LTSS, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP4, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP5, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15-LTSS, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 12-SP2, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 12-SP3, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 15, SUSE OpenStack Cloud 7, SUSE OpenStack Cloud 8, SUSE OpenStack Cloud Crowbar 8; openSUSE Leap 15.1, openSUSE Leap 15.2 allows local attackers to escalate privileges from user ldap to root. This issue affects: SUSE Enterprise Storage 5 openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.41-18.71.2. SUSE Linux Enterprise Debuginfo 11-SP3 openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.26-0.74.13.1,. SUSE Linux Enterprise Debuginfo 11-SP4 openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.26-0.74.13.1,. SUSE Linux Enterprise Point of Sale 11-SP3 openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.26-0.74.13.1,. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11-SECURITY openldap2-client-openssl1 versions prior to 2.4.26-0.74.13.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11-SP4-LTSS openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.26-0.74.13.1,. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP2-BCL openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.41-18.71.2. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP2-LTSS openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.41-18.71.2. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP3-BCL openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.41-18.71.2. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP3-LTSS openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.41-18.71.2. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP4 openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.41-18.71.2. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP5 openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.41-18.71.2. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15-LTSS openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.46-9.31.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 12-SP2 openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.41-18.71.2. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 12-SP3 openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.41-18.71.2. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 15 openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.46-9.31.1. SUSE OpenStack Cloud 7 openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.41-18.71.2. SUSE OpenStack Cloud 8 openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.41-18.71.2. SUSE OpenStack Cloud Crowbar 8 openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.41-18.71.2. openSUSE Leap 15.1 openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.46-lp151.10.12.1. openSUSE Leap 15.2 openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.46-lp152.14.3.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8023|2024-09-16T18:33:45.008Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 11:25:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8030|2024-09-16T16:39:10.268Z -- suse -- suse%20caas%20platform%204.5
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8030</link>
      <description>A Insecure Temporary File vulnerability in skuba of SUSE CaaS Platform 4.5 allows local attackers to leak the bootstrapToken or modify the configuration file before it is processed, leading to arbitrary modifications of the machine/cluster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8030|2024-09-16T16:39:10.268Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 16:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-43753|2024-09-16T17:14:12.848Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20module%20for%20suse%20manager%20server%204.2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43753</link>
      <description>A Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in spacewalk/Uyuni of SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for SUSE Manager Server 4.2, SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for SUSE Manager Server 4.3, SUSE Manager Server 4.2 allows remote attackers to read files available to the user running the process, typically tomcat. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for SUSE Manager Server 4.2 hub-xmlrpc-api-0.7-150300.3.9.2, inter-server-sync-0.2.4-150300.8.25.2, locale-formula-0.3-150300.3.3.2, py27-compat-salt-3000.3-150300.7.7.26.2, python-urlgrabber-3.10.2.1py2_3-150300.3.3.2, spacecmd-4.2.20-150300.4.30.2, spacewalk-backend-4.2.25-150300.4.32.4, spacewalk-client-tools-4.2.21-150300.4.27.3, spacewalk-java-4.2.43-150300.3.48.2, spacewalk-utils-4.2.18-150300.3.21.2, spacewalk-web-4.2.30-150300.3.30.3, susemanager-4.2.38-150300.3.44.3, susemanager-doc-indexes-4.2-150300.12.36.3, susemanager-docs_en-4.2-150300.12.36.2, susemanager-schema-4.2.25-150300.3.30.3, susemanager-sls versions prior to 4.2.28. SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for SUSE Manager Server 4.3 spacewalk-java versions prior to 4.3.39. SUSE Manager Server 4.2 release-notes-susemanager versions prior to 4.2.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-43753|2024-09-16T17:14:12.848Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 07:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-9286|2024-09-16T16:28:16.718Z -- suse -- nextcloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-9286</link>
      <description>The packaging of NextCloud in openSUSE used /srv/www/htdocs in an unsafe manner, which could have allowed scripts running as wwwrun user to escalate privileges to root during nextcloud package upgrade.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-9286|2024-09-16T16:28:16.718Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3690|2024-09-16T16:38:49.600Z -- suse -- permissions
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3690</link>
      <description>The chkstat tool in the permissions package followed symlinks before commit a9e1d26cd49ef9ee0c2060c859321128a6dd4230 (please also check the additional hardenings after this fix). This allowed local attackers with control over a path that is traversed by chkstat to escalate privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3690|2024-09-16T16:38:49.600Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 15:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-9274|2024-09-16T18:59:31.976Z -- suse -- obs-service-source_validator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-9274</link>
      <description>A shell command injection in the obs-service-source_validator before 0.7 could be used to execute code as the packager when checking RPM SPEC files with specific macro constructs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-9274|2024-09-16T18:59:31.976Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-43754|2024-09-16T16:27:41.750Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20module%20for%20suse%20manager%20server%204.2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43754</link>
      <description>An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in spacewalk/Uyuni of SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for SUSE Manager Server 4.2, SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for SUSE Manager Server 4.3, SUSE Manager Server 4.2 allows remote attackers to embed Javascript code via /rhn/audit/scap/Search.do This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for SUSE Manager Server 4.2 hub-xmlrpc-api-0.7-150300.3.9.2, inter-server-sync-0.2.4-150300.8.25.2, locale-formula-0.3-150300.3.3.2, py27-compat-salt-3000.3-150300.7.7.26.2, python-urlgrabber-3.10.2.1py2_3-150300.3.3.2, spacecmd-4.2.20-150300.4.30.2, spacewalk-backend-4.2.25-150300.4.32.4, spacewalk-client-tools-4.2.21-150300.4.27.3, spacewalk-java-4.2.43-150300.3.48.2, spacewalk-utils-4.2.18-150300.3.21.2, spacewalk-web-4.2.30-150300.3.30.3, susemanager-4.2.38-150300.3.44.3, susemanager-doc-indexes-4.2-150300.12.36.3, susemanager-docs_en-4.2-150300.12.36.2, susemanager-schema-4.2.25-150300.3.30.3, susemanager-sls versions prior to 4.2.28. SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for SUSE Manager Server 4.3 spacewalk-java versions prior to 4.3.39. SUSE Manager Server 4.2 release-notes-susemanager versions prior to 4.2.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-43754|2024-09-16T16:27:41.750Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 07:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18904|2024-09-16T16:58:59.728Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20high%20performance%20computing%2015-espos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18904</link>
      <description>A Uncontrolled Resource Consumption vulnerability in rmt of SUSE Linux Enterprise High Performance Computing 15-ESPOS, SUSE Linux Enterprise High Performance Computing 15-LTSS, SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Public Cloud 15-SP1, SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Server Applications 15, SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Server Applications 15-SP1, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15-LTSS, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 15; openSUSE Leap 15.1 allows remote attackers to cause DoS against rmt by requesting migrations. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise High Performance Computing 15-ESPOS rmt-server versions prior to 2.5.2-3.26.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise High Performance Computing 15-LTSS rmt-server versions prior to 2.5.2-3.26.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Public Cloud 15-SP1 rmt-server versions prior to 2.5.2-3.9.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Server Applications 15 rmt-server versions prior to 2.5.2-3.26.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Server Applications 15-SP1 rmt-server versions prior to 2.5.2-3.9.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15-LTSS rmt-server versions prior to 2.5.2-3.26.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 15 rmt-server versions prior to 2.5.2-3.26.1. openSUSE Leap 15.1 rmt-server versions prior to 2.5.2-lp151.2.9.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18904|2024-09-16T16:58:59.728Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 07:10:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
