<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SUSE -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/suse/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SUSE -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 07:21:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18902|2024-08-05T02:02:39.848Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20server%2012
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18902</link>
      <description>A Use After Free vulnerability in wicked of SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15; openSUSE Leap 15.1, Factory allows remote attackers to cause DoS or potentially code execution. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12 wicked versions prior to 0.6.60-3.5.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 wicked versions prior to 0.6.60-3.21.1. openSUSE Leap 15.1 wicked versions prior to 0.6.60-lp151.2.6.1. openSUSE Factory wicked versions prior to 0.6.62.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18902|2024-08-05T02:02:39.848Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18903|2024-08-05T02:02:39.712Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20server%2012
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18903</link>
      <description>A Use After Free vulnerability in wicked of SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15; openSUSE Leap 15.1, Factory allows remote attackers to cause DoS or potentially code execution. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12 wicked versions prior to 0.6.60-2.18.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 wicked versions prior to 0.6.60-28.26.1. openSUSE Leap 15.1 wicked versions prior to 0.6.60-lp151.2.9.1. openSUSE Factory wicked versions prior to 0.6.62.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18903|2024-08-05T02:02:39.712Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7685|2024-08-05T06:31:05.075Z -- suse -- libzypp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7685</link>
      <description>The decoupled download and installation steps in libzypp before 17.5.0 could lead to a corrupted RPM being left in the cache, where a later call would not display the corrupted RPM warning and allow installation, a problem caused by malicious warnings only displayed during download.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7685|2024-08-05T06:31:05.075Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18897|2024-08-05T02:02:39.827Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20server%2012
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18897</link>
      <description>A UNIX Symbolic Link (Symlink) Following vulnerability in the packaging of salt of SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15; openSUSE Factory allows local attackers to escalate privileges from user salt to root. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12 salt-master version 2019.2.0-46.83.1 and prior versions. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 salt-master version 2019.2.0-6.21.1 and prior versions. openSUSE Factory salt-master version 2019.2.2-3.1 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18897|2024-08-05T02:02:39.827Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18898|2024-08-05T02:02:39.883Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20server%2015%20sp1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18898</link>
      <description>UNIX Symbolic Link (Symlink) Following vulnerability in the trousers package of SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 SP1; openSUSE Factory allowed local attackers escalate privileges from user tss to root. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 SP1 trousers versions prior to 0.3.14-6.3.1. openSUSE Factory trousers versions prior to 0.3.14-7.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18898|2024-08-05T02:02:39.883Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18901|2024-08-05T02:02:39.892Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20server%2012
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18901</link>
      <description>A UNIX Symbolic Link (Symlink) Following vulnerability in the mysql-systemd-helper of the mariadb packaging of SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 allows local attackers to change the permissions of arbitrary files to 0640. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12 mariadb versions prior to 10.2.31-3.25.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 mariadb versions prior to 10.2.31-3.26.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18901|2024-08-05T02:02:39.892Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18906|2024-08-05T02:02:39.856Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20server%20for%20sap%2012-sp5
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18906</link>
      <description>A Improper Authentication vulnerability in cryptctl of SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 12-SP5, SUSE Manager Server 4.0 allows attackers with access to the hashed password to use it without having to crack it. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 12-SP5 cryptctl versions prior to 2.4. SUSE Manager Server 4.0 cryptctl versions prior to 2.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18906|2024-08-05T02:02:39.856Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18905|2024-08-05T02:02:39.805Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20server%2012
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18905</link>
      <description>A Insufficient Verification of Data Authenticity vulnerability in autoyast2 of SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 allows remote attackers to MITM connections when deprecated and unused functionality of autoyast is used to create images. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12 autoyast2 version 4.1.9-3.9.1 and prior versions. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 autoyast2 version 4.0.70-3.20.1 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18905|2024-08-05T02:02:39.805Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18900|2024-08-05T02:02:39.846Z -- suse -- caas%20platform%203.0
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18900</link>
      <description>: Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability in libzypp of SUSE CaaS Platform 3.0, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 allowed local attackers to read a cookie store used by libzypp, exposing private cookies. This issue affects: SUSE CaaS Platform 3.0 libzypp versions prior to 16.21.2-27.68.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12 libzypp versions prior to 16.21.2-2.45.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 17.19.0-3.34.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18900|2024-08-05T02:02:39.846Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18904|2024-08-05T02:02:39.899Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20high%20performance%20computing%2015-espos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18904</link>
      <description>A Uncontrolled Resource Consumption vulnerability in rmt of SUSE Linux Enterprise High Performance Computing 15-ESPOS, SUSE Linux Enterprise High Performance Computing 15-LTSS, SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Public Cloud 15-SP1, SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Server Applications 15, SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Server Applications 15-SP1, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15-LTSS, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 15; openSUSE Leap 15.1 allows remote attackers to cause DoS against rmt by requesting migrations. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise High Performance Computing 15-ESPOS rmt-server versions prior to 2.5.2-3.26.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise High Performance Computing 15-LTSS rmt-server versions prior to 2.5.2-3.26.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Public Cloud 15-SP1 rmt-server versions prior to 2.5.2-3.9.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Server Applications 15 rmt-server versions prior to 2.5.2-3.26.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Server Applications 15-SP1 rmt-server versions prior to 2.5.2-3.9.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15-LTSS rmt-server versions prior to 2.5.2-3.26.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 15 rmt-server versions prior to 2.5.2-3.26.1. openSUSE Leap 15.1 rmt-server versions prior to 2.5.2-lp151.2.9.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18904|2024-08-05T02:02:39.899Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
