<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SUSE -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/suse/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SUSE -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:23:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8030|2024-08-04T09:48:24.680Z -- suse -- suse%20caas%20platform%204.5
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8030</link>
      <description>A Insecure Temporary File vulnerability in skuba of SUSE CaaS Platform 4.5 allows local attackers to leak the bootstrapToken or modify the configuration file before it is processed, leading to arbitrary modifications of the machine/cluster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8030|2024-08-04T09:48:24.680Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8019|2024-08-04T09:48:25.595Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20debuginfo%2011-sp3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8019</link>
      <description>A UNIX Symbolic Link (Symlink) Following vulnerability in the packaging of syslog-ng of SUSE Linux Enterprise Debuginfo 11-SP3, SUSE Linux Enterprise Debuginfo 11-SP4, SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Legacy Software 12, SUSE Linux Enterprise Point of Sale 11-SP3, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11-SP4-LTSS, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 12-SP1; openSUSE Backports SLE-15-SP1, openSUSE Leap 15.1 allowed local attackers controlling the user news to escalate their privileges to root. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Debuginfo 11-SP3 syslog-ng versions prior to 2.0.9-27.34.40.5.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Debuginfo 11-SP4 syslog-ng versions prior to 2.0.9-27.34.40.5.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Legacy Software 12 syslog-ng versions prior to 3.6.4-12.8.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Point of Sale 11-SP3 syslog-ng versions prior to 2.0.9-27.34.40.5.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11-SP4-LTSS syslog-ng versions prior to 2.0.9-27.34.40.5.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 12-SP1 syslog-ng versions prior to 3.6.4-12.8.1. openSUSE Backports SLE-15-SP1 syslog-ng versions prior to 3.19.1-bp151.4.6.1. openSUSE Leap 15.1 syslog-ng versions prior to 3.19.1-lp151.3.6.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8019|2024-08-04T09:48:25.595Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8016|2024-08-04T09:48:24.747Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20module%20for%20desktop%20applications%2015-sp1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8016</link>
      <description>A Race Condition Enabling Link Following vulnerability in the packaging of texlive-filesystem of SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Desktop Applications 15-SP1, SUSE Linux Enterprise Software Development Kit 12-SP4, SUSE Linux Enterprise Software Development Kit 12-SP5; openSUSE Leap 15.1 allows local users to corrupt files or potentially escalate privileges. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Desktop Applications 15-SP1 texlive-filesystem versions prior to 2017.135-9.5.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Software Development Kit 12-SP4 texlive-filesystem versions prior to 2013.74-16.5.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Software Development Kit 12-SP5 texlive-filesystem versions prior to 2013.74-16.5.1. openSUSE Leap 15.1 texlive-filesystem versions prior to 2017.135-lp151.8.3.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8016|2024-08-04T09:48:24.747Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8013|2024-08-04T09:48:24.923Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20server%2012
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8013</link>
      <description>A UNIX Symbolic Link (Symlink) Following vulnerability in chkstat of SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11 set permissions intended for specific binaries on other binaries because it erroneously followed symlinks. The symlinks can't be controlled by attackers on default systems, so exploitation is difficult. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12 permissions versions prior to 2015.09.28.1626-17.27.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 permissions versions prior to 20181116-9.23.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11 permissions versions prior to 2013.1.7-0.6.12.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8013|2024-08-04T09:48:24.923Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8023|2024-08-04T09:48:25.193Z -- suse -- suse%20enterprise%20storage%205
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8023</link>
      <description>A acceptance of Extraneous Untrusted Data With Trusted Data vulnerability in the start script of openldap2 of SUSE Enterprise Storage 5, SUSE Linux Enterprise Debuginfo 11-SP3, SUSE Linux Enterprise Debuginfo 11-SP4, SUSE Linux Enterprise Point of Sale 11-SP3, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11-SECURITY, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11-SP4-LTSS, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP2-BCL, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP2-LTSS, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP3-BCL, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP3-LTSS, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP4, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP5, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15-LTSS, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 12-SP2, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 12-SP3, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 15, SUSE OpenStack Cloud 7, SUSE OpenStack Cloud 8, SUSE OpenStack Cloud Crowbar 8; openSUSE Leap 15.1, openSUSE Leap 15.2 allows local attackers to escalate privileges from user ldap to root. This issue affects: SUSE Enterprise Storage 5 openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.41-18.71.2. SUSE Linux Enterprise Debuginfo 11-SP3 openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.26-0.74.13.1,. SUSE Linux Enterprise Debuginfo 11-SP4 openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.26-0.74.13.1,. SUSE Linux Enterprise Point of Sale 11-SP3 openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.26-0.74.13.1,. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11-SECURITY openldap2-client-openssl1 versions prior to 2.4.26-0.74.13.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11-SP4-LTSS openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.26-0.74.13.1,. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP2-BCL openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.41-18.71.2. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP2-LTSS openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.41-18.71.2. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP3-BCL openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.41-18.71.2. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP3-LTSS openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.41-18.71.2. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP4 openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.41-18.71.2. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP5 openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.41-18.71.2. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15-LTSS openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.46-9.31.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 12-SP2 openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.41-18.71.2. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 12-SP3 openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.41-18.71.2. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 15 openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.46-9.31.1. SUSE OpenStack Cloud 7 openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.41-18.71.2. SUSE OpenStack Cloud 8 openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.41-18.71.2. SUSE OpenStack Cloud Crowbar 8 openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.41-18.71.2. openSUSE Leap 15.1 openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.46-lp151.10.12.1. openSUSE Leap 15.2 openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.46-lp152.14.3.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8023|2024-08-04T09:48:25.193Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3688|2024-08-04T19:19:16.840Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20server%2015
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3688</link>
      <description>The /usr/sbin/pinger binary packaged with squid in SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 before and including version 4.8-5.8.1 and in SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12 before and including 3.5.21-26.17.1 had squid:root, 0750 permissions. This allowed an attacker that compromissed the squid user to gain persistence by changing the binary</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3688|2024-08-04T19:19:16.840Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3698|2024-08-04T19:19:17.452Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20server%2012
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3698</link>
      <description>UNIX Symbolic Link (Symlink) Following vulnerability in the cronjob shipped with nagios of SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11; openSUSE Factory allows local attackers to cause cause DoS or potentially escalate privileges by winning a race. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12 nagios version 3.5.1-5.27 and prior versions. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11 nagios version 3.0.6-1.25.36.3.1 and prior versions. openSUSE Factory nagios version 4.4.5-2.1 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3698|2024-08-04T19:19:17.452Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-36779|2024-08-04T01:01:59.764Z -- suse -- longhorn
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-36779</link>
      <description>A Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability in SUSE Longhorn allows any workload in the cluster to execute any binary present in the image on the host without authentication. This issue affects: SUSE Longhorn longhorn versions prior to 1.1.3; longhorn versions prior to 1.2.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-36779|2024-08-04T01:01:59.764Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3681|2024-08-04T19:12:09.655Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20module%20for%20development%20tools%2015
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3681</link>
      <description>A External Control of File Name or Path vulnerability in osc of SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Development Tools 15, SUSE Linux Enterprise Software Development Kit 12-SP5, SUSE Linux Enterprise Software Development Kit 12-SP4; openSUSE Leap 15.1, openSUSE Factory allowed remote attackers that can change downloaded packages to overwrite arbitrary files. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Development Tools 15 osc versions prior to 0.169.1-3.20.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Software Development Kit 12-SP5 osc versions prior to 0.162.1-15.9.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Software Development Kit 12-SP4 osc versions prior to 0.162.1-15.9.1. openSUSE Leap 15.1 osc versions prior to 0.169.1-lp151.2.15.1. openSUSE Factory osc versions prior to 0.169.0 .</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3681|2024-08-04T19:12:09.655Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3684|2024-08-04T19:19:16.826Z -- suse -- suse%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3684</link>
      <description>SUSE Manager until version 4.0.7 and Uyuni until commit 1b426ad5ed0a7191a6fb46bb83e98ae4b99a5ade created world-readable swap files on systems that don't have a swap already configured and don't have btrfs as filesystem</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3684|2024-08-04T19:19:16.826Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3689|2024-08-04T19:19:17.496Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20server%2012
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3689</link>
      <description>The nfs-utils package in SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12 before and including version 1.3.0-34.18.1 and in SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 before and including version 2.1.1-6.10.2 the directory /var/lib/nfs is owned by statd:nogroup. This directory contains files owned and managed by root. If statd is compromised, it can therefore trick processes running with root privileges into creating/overwriting files anywhere on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3689|2024-08-04T19:19:17.496Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-46705|2024-08-04T05:17:42.665Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20server%2015%20sp4
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-46705</link>
      <description>A Insecure Temporary File vulnerability in grub-once of grub2 in SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 SP4, openSUSE Factory allows local attackers to truncate arbitrary files. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 SP4 grub2 versions prior to 2.06-150400.7.1. SUSE openSUSE Factory grub2 versions prior to 2.06-18.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-46705|2024-08-04T05:17:42.665Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3693|2024-08-04T19:19:17.443Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20server%2011
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3693</link>
      <description>A symlink following vulnerability in the packaging of mailman in SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12; openSUSE Leap 15.1 allowed local attackers to escalate their privileges from user wwwrun to root. Additionally arbitrary files could be changed to group mailman. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11 mailman versions prior to 2.1.15-9.6.15.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12 mailman versions prior to 2.1.17-3.11.1. openSUSE Leap 15.1 mailman version 2.1.29-lp151.2.14 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3693|2024-08-04T19:19:17.443Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-36782|2024-08-04T01:01:59.069Z -- suse -- rancher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-36782</link>
      <description>A Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information vulnerability in SUSE Rancher allows authenticated Cluster Owners, Cluster Members, Project Owners, Project Members and User Base to use the Kubernetes API to retrieve plaintext version of sensitive data. This issue affects: SUSE Rancher Rancher versions prior to 2.5.16; Rancher versions prior to 2.6.7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-36782|2024-08-04T01:01:59.069Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3692|2024-08-04T19:19:17.781Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20server%2011
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3692</link>
      <description>The packaging of inn on SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11; openSUSE Factory, Leap 15.1 allows local attackers to escalate from user inn to root via symlink attacks. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11 inn version 2.4.2-170.21.3.1 and prior versions. openSUSE Factory inn version 2.6.2-2.2 and prior versions. openSUSE Leap 15.1 inn version 2.5.4-lp151.2.47 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3692|2024-08-04T19:19:17.781Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3691|2024-08-04T19:19:16.810Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20server%2015
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3691</link>
      <description>A Symbolic Link (Symlink) Following vulnerability in the packaging of munge in SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15; openSUSE Factory allowed local attackers to escalate privileges from user munge to root. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 munge versions prior to 0.5.13-4.3.1. openSUSE Factory munge versions prior to 0.5.13-6.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3691|2024-08-04T19:19:16.810Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8028|2024-08-04T09:48:25.486Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20module%20for%20suse%20manager%20server%204.1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8028</link>
      <description>A Improper Access Control vulnerability in the configuration of salt of SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for SUSE Manager Server 4.1, SUSE Manager Proxy 4.0, SUSE Manager Retail Branch Server 4.0, SUSE Manager Server 3.2, SUSE Manager Server 4.0 allows local users to escalate to root on every system managed by SUSE manager. On the managing node itself code can be executed as user salt, potentially allowing for escalation to root there. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for SUSE Manager Server 4.1 google-gson versions prior to 2.8.5-3.4.3, httpcomponents-client-4.5.6-3.4.2, httpcomponents-. SUSE Manager Proxy 4.0 release-notes-susemanager-proxy versions prior to 4.0.9-0.16.38.1. SUSE Manager Retail Branch Server 4.0 release-notes-susemanager-proxy versions prior to 4.0.9-0.16.38.1. SUSE Manager Server 3.2 salt-netapi-client versions prior to 0.16.0-4.14.1, spacewalk-. SUSE Manager Server 4.0 release-notes-susemanager versions prior to 4.0.9-3.54.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8028|2024-08-04T09:48:25.486Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-36783|2024-08-04T01:01:59.781Z -- suse -- rancher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-36783</link>
      <description>A Insufficiently Protected Credentials vulnerability in SUSE Rancher allows authenticated Cluster Owners, Cluster Members, Project Owners and Project Members to read credentials, passwords and API tokens that have been stored in cleartext and exposed via API endpoints. This issue affects: SUSE Rancher Rancher versions prior to 2.6.4; Rancher versions prior to 2.5.13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-36783|2024-08-04T01:01:59.781Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-36775|2024-08-04T01:01:59.325Z -- suse -- rancher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-36775</link>
      <description>a Improper Access Control vulnerability in SUSE Rancher allows users to keep privileges that should have been revoked. This issue affects: SUSE Rancher Rancher versions prior to 2.4.18; Rancher versions prior to 2.5.12; Rancher versions prior to 2.6.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-36775|2024-08-04T01:01:59.325Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8029|2024-08-04T09:48:25.210Z -- suse -- suse%20caas%20platform%204.5
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8029</link>
      <description>A Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource vulnerability in skuba of SUSE CaaS Platform 4.5 allows local attackers to gain access to the kublet key. This issue affects: SUSE CaaS Platform 4.5 skuba versions prior to https://github.com/SUSE/skuba/pull/1416.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8029|2024-08-04T09:48:25.210Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-36784|2024-08-04T01:01:59.670Z -- suse -- rancher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-36784</link>
      <description>A Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in SUSE Rancher allows users with the restricted-admin role to escalate to full admin. This issue affects: SUSE Rancher Rancher versions prior to 2.5.13; Rancher versions prior to 2.6.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-36784|2024-08-04T01:01:59.670Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-36776|2024-08-04T01:01:59.794Z -- suse -- rancher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-36776</link>
      <description>A Improper Access Control vulnerability in SUSE Rancher allows remote attackers impersonate arbitrary users. This issue affects: SUSE Rancher Rancher versions prior to 2.5.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-36776|2024-08-04T01:01:59.794Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3695|2024-08-04T19:19:17.572Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20high%20performance%20computing%2015-espos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3695</link>
      <description>A Improper Control of Generation of Code vulnerability in the packaging of pcp of SUSE Linux Enterprise High Performance Computing 15-ESPOS, SUSE Linux Enterprise High Performance Computing 15-LTSS, SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Development Tools 15, SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Development Tools 15-SP1, SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Open Buildservice Development Tools 15, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15-LTSS, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 15, SUSE Linux Enterprise Software Development Kit 12-SP4, SUSE Linux Enterprise Software Development Kit 12-SP5; openSUSE Leap 15.1 allows the user pcp to run code as root by placing it into /var/log/pcp/configs.sh This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise High Performance Computing 15-ESPOS pcp versions prior to 3.11.9-5.8.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise High Performance Computing 15-LTSS pcp versions prior to 3.11.9-5.8.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Development Tools 15 pcp versions prior to 3.11.9-5.8.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Development Tools 15-SP1 pcp versions prior to 4.3.1-3.5.3. SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Open Buildservice Development Tools 15 pcp versions prior to 3.11.9-5.8.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15-LTSS pcp versions prior to 3.11.9-5.8.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 15 pcp versions prior to 3.11.9-5.8.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Software Development Kit 12-SP4 pcp versions prior to 3.11.9-6.14.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Software Development Kit 12-SP5 pcp versions prior to 3.11.9-6.14.1. openSUSE Leap 15.1 pcp versions prior to 4.3.1-lp151.2.3.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3695|2024-08-04T19:19:17.572Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8018|2024-08-04T09:48:25.267Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20server%2015%20sp1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8018</link>
      <description>A Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability in the SLES15-SP1-CHOST-BYOS and SLES15-SP1-CAP-Deployment-BYOS images of SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 SP1 allows local attackers with the UID 1000 to escalate to root due to a /etc directory owned by the user This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 SP1 SLES15-SP1-CAP-Deployment-BYOS version 1.0.1 and prior versions; SLES15-SP1-CHOST-BYOS versions prior to 1.0.3 and prior versions;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8018|2024-08-04T09:48:25.267Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3686|2024-08-04T19:19:16.806Z -- suse -- openqa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3686</link>
      <description>openQA before commit c172e8883d8f32fced5e02f9b6faaacc913df27b was vulnerable to XSS in the distri and version parameter. This was reported through the bug bounty program of Offensive Security</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3686|2024-08-04T19:19:16.806Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-10220|2024-08-04T22:17:19.719Z -- suse -- kernel%3A
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-10220</link>
      <description>Linux kernel CIFS implementation, version 4.9.0 is vulnerable to a relative paths injection in directory entry lists.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-10220|2024-08-04T22:17:19.719Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 15:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8025|2024-08-04T09:48:25.473Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20server%2012-sp4
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8025</link>
      <description>A Incorrect Execution-Assigned Permissions vulnerability in the permissions package of SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP4, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15-LTSS, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 15; openSUSE Leap 15.1, openSUSE Tumbleweed sets the permissions for some of the directories of the pcp package to unintended settings. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP4 permissions versions prior to 20170707-3.24.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15-LTSS permissions versions prior to 20180125-3.27.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 15 permissions versions prior to 20180125-3.27.1. openSUSE Leap 15.1 permissions versions prior to 20181116-lp151.4.24.1. openSUSE Tumbleweed permissions versions prior to 20200624.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8025|2024-08-04T09:48:25.473Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-36778|2024-08-04T01:01:59.196Z -- suse -- rancher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-36778</link>
      <description>A Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in SUSE Rancher allows administrators of third-party repositories to gather credentials that are sent to their servers. This issue affects: SUSE Rancher Rancher versions prior to 2.5.12; Rancher versions prior to 2.6.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-36778|2024-08-04T01:01:59.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8027|2024-08-04T09:48:24.820Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20server%2015-ltss
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8027</link>
      <description>A Insecure Temporary File vulnerability in openldap2 of SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15-LTSS, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 15; openSUSE Leap 15.1, openSUSE Leap 15.2 allows local attackers to overwrite arbitrary files and gain access to the openldap2 configuration This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15-LTSS openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.46-9.37.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 15 openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.46-9.37.1. openSUSE Leap 15.1 openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.46-lp151.10.18.1. openSUSE Leap 15.2 openldap2 versions prior to 2.4.46-lp152.14.9.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8027|2024-08-04T09:48:24.820Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8022|2024-08-04T09:48:25.548Z -- suse -- suse%20enterprise%20storage%205
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8022</link>
      <description>A Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability in the packaging of tomcat on SUSE Enterprise Storage 5, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP2-BCL, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP2-LTSS, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP3-BCL, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP3-LTSS, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP4, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP5, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15-LTSS, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 12-SP2, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 12-SP3, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 15, SUSE OpenStack Cloud 7, SUSE OpenStack Cloud 8, SUSE OpenStack Cloud Crowbar 8 allows local attackers to escalate from group tomcat to root. This issue affects: SUSE Enterprise Storage 5 tomcat versions prior to 8.0.53-29.32.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP2-BCL tomcat versions prior to 8.0.53-29.32.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP2-LTSS tomcat versions prior to 8.0.53-29.32.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP3-BCL tomcat versions prior to 8.0.53-29.32.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP3-LTSS tomcat versions prior to 8.0.53-29.32.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP4 tomcat versions prior to 9.0.35-3.39.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP5 tomcat versions prior to 9.0.35-3.39.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15-LTSS tomcat versions prior to 9.0.35-3.57.3. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 12-SP2 tomcat versions prior to 8.0.53-29.32.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 12-SP3 tomcat versions prior to 8.0.53-29.32.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 15 tomcat versions prior to 9.0.35-3.57.3. SUSE OpenStack Cloud 7 tomcat versions prior to 8.0.53-29.32.1. SUSE OpenStack Cloud 8 tomcat versions prior to 8.0.53-29.32.1. SUSE OpenStack Cloud Crowbar 8 tomcat versions prior to 8.0.53-29.32.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8022|2024-08-04T09:48:25.548Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-36780|2024-08-04T01:01:59.672Z -- suse -- longhorn
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-36780</link>
      <description>A Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability in longhorn of SUSE Longhorn allows attackers to connect to a longhorn-engine replica instance granting it the ability to read and write data to and from a replica that they should not have access to. This issue affects: SUSE Longhorn longhorn versions prior to 1.1.3; longhorn versions prior to 1.2.3v.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-36780|2024-08-04T01:01:59.672Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3696|2024-08-04T19:19:17.737Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20high%20performance%20computing%2015-espos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3696</link>
      <description>A Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory vulnerability in the packaging of pcp of SUSE Linux Enterprise High Performance Computing 15-ESPOS, SUSE Linux Enterprise High Performance Computing 15-LTSS, SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Development Tools 15, SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Development Tools 15-SP1, SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Open Buildservice Development Tools 15, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15-LTSS, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 15, SUSE Linux Enterprise Software Development Kit 12-SP4, SUSE Linux Enterprise Software Development Kit 12-SP5; openSUSE Leap 15.1 allows local user pcp to overwrite arbitrary files with arbitrary content. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise High Performance Computing 15-ESPOS pcp versions prior to 3.11.9-5.8.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise High Performance Computing 15-LTSS pcp versions prior to 3.11.9-5.8.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Development Tools 15 pcp versions prior to 3.11.9-5.8.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Development Tools 15-SP1 pcp versions prior to 4.3.1-3.5.3. SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Open Buildservice Development Tools 15 pcp versions prior to 3.11.9-5.8.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15-LTSS pcp versions prior to 3.11.9-5.8.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 15 pcp versions prior to 3.11.9-5.8.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Software Development Kit 12-SP4 pcp versions prior to 3.11.9-6.14.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Software Development Kit 12-SP5 pcp versions prior to 3.11.9-6.14.1. openSUSE Leap 15.1 pcp versions prior to 4.3.1-lp151.2.3.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3696|2024-08-04T19:19:17.737Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3682|2024-08-04T19:19:16.823Z -- suse -- suse%20caas%20platform%203.0
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3682</link>
      <description>The docker-kubic package in SUSE CaaS Platform 3.0 before 17.09.1_ce-7.6.1 provided access to an insecure API locally on the Kubernetes master node.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3682|2024-08-04T19:19:16.823Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3687|2024-08-04T19:19:16.823Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3687</link>
      <description>The permission package in SUSE Linux Enterprise Server allowed all local users to run dumpcap in the "easy" permission profile and sniff network traffic. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server permissions versions starting from 85c83fef7e017f8ab7f8602d3163786d57344439 to 081d081dcfaf61710bda34bc21c80c66276119aa.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3687|2024-08-04T19:19:16.823Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8017|2024-08-04T09:48:24.833Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20module%20for%20desktop%20applications%2015-sp1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8017</link>
      <description>A Race Condition Enabling Link Following vulnerability in the cron job shipped with texlive-filesystem of SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Desktop Applications 15-SP1, SUSE Linux Enterprise Software Development Kit 12-SP4, SUSE Linux Enterprise Software Development Kit 12-SP5; openSUSE Leap 15.1 allows local users in group mktex to delete arbitrary files on the system This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for Desktop Applications 15-SP1 texlive-filesystem versions prior to 2017.135-9.5.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Software Development Kit 12-SP4 texlive-filesystem versions prior to 2013.74-16.5.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Software Development Kit 12-SP5 texlive-filesystem versions prior to 2013.74-16.5.1. openSUSE Leap 15.1 texlive-filesystem versions prior to 2017.135-lp151.8.3.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8017|2024-08-04T09:48:24.833Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3690|2024-08-04T19:19:16.801Z -- suse -- permissions
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3690</link>
      <description>The chkstat tool in the permissions package followed symlinks before commit a9e1d26cd49ef9ee0c2060c859321128a6dd4230 (please also check the additional hardenings after this fix). This allowed local attackers with control over a path that is traversed by chkstat to escalate privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3690|2024-08-04T19:19:16.801Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3683|2024-08-04T19:19:17.419Z -- suse -- suse%20openstack%20cloud%208
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3683</link>
      <description>The keystone-json-assignment package in SUSE Openstack Cloud 8 before commit d7888c75505465490250c00cc0ef4bb1af662f9f every user listed in the /etc/keystone/user-project-map.json was assigned full "member" role access to every project. This allowed these users to access, modify, create and delete arbitrary resources, contrary to expectations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3683|2024-08-04T19:19:17.419Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
