<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SUSE -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/suse/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SUSE -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 17:21:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31256|2024-08-03T07:11:39.944Z -- suse -- opensuse%20factory
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31256</link>
      <description>A Improper Link Resolution Before File Access ('Link Following') vulnerability in a script called by the sendmail systemd service of openSUSE Factory allows local attackers to escalate from user mail to root. This issue affects: SUSE openSUSE Factory sendmail versions prior to 8.17.1-1.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31256|2024-08-03T07:11:39.944Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31255|2024-08-03T07:11:39.978Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20module%20for%20suse%20manager%20server%204.2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31255</link>
      <description>An Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in spacewalk/Uyuni of SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for SUSE Manager Server 4.2, SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for SUSE Manager Server 4.3, SUSE Manager Server 4.2 allows remote attackers to read files available to the user running the process, typically tomcat. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for SUSE Manager Server 4.2 hub-xmlrpc-api-0.7-150300.3.9.2, inter-server-sync-0.2.4-150300.8.25.2, locale-formula-0.3-150300.3.3.2, py27-compat-salt-3000.3-150300.7.7.26.2, python-urlgrabber-3.10.2.1py2_3-150300.3.3.2, spacecmd-4.2.20-150300.4.30.2, spacewalk-backend-4.2.25-150300.4.32.4, spacewalk-client-tools-4.2.21-150300.4.27.3, spacewalk-java-4.2.43-150300.3.48.2, spacewalk-utils-4.2.18-150300.3.21.2, spacewalk-web-4.2.30-150300.3.30.3, susemanager-4.2.38-150300.3.44.3, susemanager-doc-indexes-4.2-150300.12.36.3, susemanager-docs_en-4.2-150300.12.36.2, susemanager-schema-4.2.25-150300.3.30.3, susemanager-sls versions prior to 4.2.28. SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for SUSE Manager Server 4.3 spacewalk-java versions prior to 4.3.39. SUSE Manager Server 4.2 release-notes-susemanager versions prior to 4.2.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31255|2024-08-03T07:11:39.978Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-45155|2024-08-03T14:09:56.396Z -- suse -- opensuse%20factory
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45155</link>
      <description>An Improper Handling of Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in obs-service-go_modules of openSUSE Factory allows attackers that can influence the call to the service to delete files and directories on the system of the victim. This issue affects: SUSE openSUSE Factory obs-service-go_modules versions prior to 0.6.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-45155|2024-08-03T14:09:56.396Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-43755|2024-08-03T13:40:06.266Z -- suse -- rancher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43755</link>
      <description>A Insufficient Entropy vulnerability in SUSE Rancher allows attackers that gained knowledge of the cattle-token to continue abusing this even after the token was renewed. This issue affects: SUSE Rancher Rancher versions prior to 2.6.10; Rancher versions prior to 2.7.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-43755|2024-08-03T13:40:06.266Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-43758|2024-08-03T13:40:06.453Z -- suse -- rancher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43758</link>
      <description>A Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in SUSE Rancher allows code execution for user with the ability to add an untrusted Helm catalog or modifying the URL configuration used to download KDM (only admin users by default) This issue affects: SUSE Rancher Rancher versions prior to 2.5.17; Rancher versions prior to 2.6.10; Rancher versions prior to 2.7.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-43758|2024-08-03T13:40:06.453Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31252|2024-08-03T07:11:39.924Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20server%2012-sp5
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31252</link>
      <description>A Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in chkstat of SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP5; openSUSE Leap 15.3, openSUSE Leap 15.4, openSUSE Leap Micro 5.2 did not consider group writable path components, allowing local attackers with access to a group what can write to a location included in the path to a privileged binary to influence path resolution. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12-SP5 permissions versions prior to 20170707. openSUSE Leap 15.3 permissions versions prior to 20200127. openSUSE Leap 15.4 permissions versions prior to 20201225. openSUSE Leap Micro 5.2 permissions versions prior to 20181225.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31252|2024-08-03T07:11:39.924Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31254|2024-08-03T07:11:39.905Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20server%20for%20sap%2015
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31254</link>
      <description>A Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability in rmt-server-regsharing service of SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 15, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 15-SP1, SUSE Manager Server 4.1; openSUSE Leap 15.3, openSUSE Leap 15.4 allows local attackers with access to the _rmt user to escalate to root. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 15 rmt-server versions prior to 2.10. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 15-SP1 rmt-server versions prior to 2.10. SUSE Manager Server 4.1 rmt-server versions prior to 2.10. openSUSE Leap 15.3 rmt-server versions prior to 2.10. openSUSE Leap 15.4 rmt-server versions prior to 2.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31254|2024-08-03T07:11:39.905Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-43753|2024-08-03T13:40:06.426Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20module%20for%20suse%20manager%20server%204.2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43753</link>
      <description>A Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in spacewalk/Uyuni of SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for SUSE Manager Server 4.2, SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for SUSE Manager Server 4.3, SUSE Manager Server 4.2 allows remote attackers to read files available to the user running the process, typically tomcat. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for SUSE Manager Server 4.2 hub-xmlrpc-api-0.7-150300.3.9.2, inter-server-sync-0.2.4-150300.8.25.2, locale-formula-0.3-150300.3.3.2, py27-compat-salt-3000.3-150300.7.7.26.2, python-urlgrabber-3.10.2.1py2_3-150300.3.3.2, spacecmd-4.2.20-150300.4.30.2, spacewalk-backend-4.2.25-150300.4.32.4, spacewalk-client-tools-4.2.21-150300.4.27.3, spacewalk-java-4.2.43-150300.3.48.2, spacewalk-utils-4.2.18-150300.3.21.2, spacewalk-web-4.2.30-150300.3.30.3, susemanager-4.2.38-150300.3.44.3, susemanager-doc-indexes-4.2-150300.12.36.3, susemanager-docs_en-4.2-150300.12.36.2, susemanager-schema-4.2.25-150300.3.30.3, susemanager-sls versions prior to 4.2.28. SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for SUSE Manager Server 4.3 spacewalk-java versions prior to 4.3.39. SUSE Manager Server 4.2 release-notes-susemanager versions prior to 4.2.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-43753|2024-08-03T13:40:06.426Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21952|2024-08-03T03:00:54.521Z -- suse -- suse%20manager%20server%204.1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21952</link>
      <description>A Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability in spacewalk-java of SUSE Manager Server 4.1, SUSE Manager Server 4.2 allows remote attackers to easily exhaust available disk resources leading to DoS. This issue affects: SUSE Manager Server 4.1 spacewalk-java versions prior to 4.1.46. SUSE Manager Server 4.2 spacewalk-java versions prior to 4.2.37.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21952|2024-08-03T03:00:54.521Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-43757|2024-08-03T13:40:06.199Z -- suse -- rancher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43757</link>
      <description>A Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information vulnerability in SUSE Rancher allows users on managed clusters to gain access to credentials. The impact depends on the credentials exposed This issue affects: SUSE Rancher Rancher versions prior to 2.5.17; Rancher versions prior to 2.6.10; Rancher versions prior to 2.7.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-43757|2024-08-03T13:40:06.199Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31251|2024-08-03T07:11:39.925Z -- suse -- opensuse%20factory
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31251</link>
      <description>A Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability in the packaging of the slurm testsuite of openSUSE Factory allows local attackers with control over the slurm user to escalate to root. This issue affects: openSUSE Factory slurm versions prior to 22.05.2-3.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31251|2024-08-03T07:11:39.925Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-43760|2024-08-03T13:40:06.301Z -- suse -- rancher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43760</link>
      <description>An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SUSE Rancher allows users in some higher-privileged groups to to inject code that is 
executed within another user's browser, allowing the attacker to steal 
sensitive information, manipulate web content, or perform other 
malicious activities on behalf of the victims. This could result in a 
user with write access to the affected areas being able to act on behalf
 of an administrator, once an administrator opens the affected web page.


This issue affects Rancher: from &gt;= 2.6.0 before &lt; 2.6.13, from &gt;= 2.7.0 before &lt; 2.7.4.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-43760|2024-08-03T13:40:06.301Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 12:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31249|2024-08-03T07:11:39.931Z -- suse -- rancher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31249</link>
      <description>A Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in wrangler of SUSE Rancher allows remote attackers to inject commands in the underlying host via crafted commands passed to Wrangler. This issue affects: SUSE Rancher wrangler version 0.7.3 and prior versions; wrangler version 0.8.4 and prior versions; wrangler version 1.0.0 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31249|2024-08-03T07:11:39.931Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21949|2024-08-03T03:00:53.787Z -- suse -- open%20build%20service
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21949</link>
      <description>A Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference vulnerability in SUSE Open Build Service allows remote attackers to reference external entities in certain operations. This can be used to gain information from the server that can be abused to escalate to Admin privileges on OBS. This issue affects: SUSE Open Build Service Open Build Service versions prior to 2.10.13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21949|2024-08-03T03:00:53.787Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-43756|2024-08-03T13:40:06.577Z -- suse -- rancher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43756</link>
      <description>A Improper Neutralization of Special Elements in Output Used by a Downstream Component ('Injection') vulnerability in SUSE Rancher allows remote attackers to cause denial of service by supplying specially crafted git credentials. This issue affects: SUSE Rancher wrangler version 0.7.3 and prior versions; wrangler version 0.8.4 and prior versions; wrangler version 1.0.0 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-43756|2024-08-03T13:40:06.577Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-43754|2024-08-03T13:40:06.449Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20module%20for%20suse%20manager%20server%204.2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43754</link>
      <description>An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in spacewalk/Uyuni of SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for SUSE Manager Server 4.2, SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for SUSE Manager Server 4.3, SUSE Manager Server 4.2 allows remote attackers to embed Javascript code via /rhn/audit/scap/Search.do This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for SUSE Manager Server 4.2 hub-xmlrpc-api-0.7-150300.3.9.2, inter-server-sync-0.2.4-150300.8.25.2, locale-formula-0.3-150300.3.3.2, py27-compat-salt-3000.3-150300.7.7.26.2, python-urlgrabber-3.10.2.1py2_3-150300.3.3.2, spacecmd-4.2.20-150300.4.30.2, spacewalk-backend-4.2.25-150300.4.32.4, spacewalk-client-tools-4.2.21-150300.4.27.3, spacewalk-java-4.2.43-150300.3.48.2, spacewalk-utils-4.2.18-150300.3.21.2, spacewalk-web-4.2.30-150300.3.30.3, susemanager-4.2.38-150300.3.44.3, susemanager-doc-indexes-4.2-150300.12.36.3, susemanager-docs_en-4.2-150300.12.36.2, susemanager-schema-4.2.25-150300.3.30.3, susemanager-sls versions prior to 4.2.28. SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for SUSE Manager Server 4.3 spacewalk-java versions prior to 4.3.39. SUSE Manager Server 4.2 release-notes-susemanager versions prior to 4.2.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-43754|2024-08-03T13:40:06.449Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21947|2024-08-03T03:00:54.558Z -- suse -- rancher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21947</link>
      <description>A Exposure of Resource to Wrong Sphere vulnerability in Rancher Desktop of SUSE allows attackers in the local network to connect to the Dashboard API (steve) to carry out arbitrary actions. This issue affects: SUSE Rancher Desktop versions prior to V.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21947|2024-08-03T03:00:54.558Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21951|2024-08-03T03:00:54.452Z -- suse -- rancher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21951</link>
      <description>A Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information vulnerability in SUSE Rancher, Rancher allows attackers on the network to read and change network data due to missing encryption of data transmitted via the network when a cluster is created from an RKE template with the CNI value overridden This issue affects: SUSE Rancher Rancher versions prior to 2.5.14; Rancher versions prior to 2.6.5.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21951|2024-08-03T03:00:54.452Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21953|2024-08-03T03:00:54.295Z -- suse -- rancher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21953</link>
      <description>A Missing Authorization vulnerability in of SUSE Rancher allows authenticated user to create an unauthorized shell pod and kubectl access in the local cluster This issue affects: SUSE Rancher Rancher versions prior to 2.5.17; Rancher versions prior to 2.6.10; Rancher versions prior to 2.7.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21953|2024-08-03T03:00:54.295Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-45153|2024-08-03T14:09:55.968Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20module%20for%20sap%20applications%2015-sp1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45153</link>
      <description>An Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability in saphanabootstrap-formula of SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for SAP Applications 15-SP1, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 12-SP5; openSUSE Leap 15.4 allows local attackers to escalate to root by manipulating the sudo configuration that is created. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for SAP Applications 15-SP1 saphanabootstrap-formula versions prior to 0.13.1+git.1667812208.4db963e. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP 12-SP5 saphanabootstrap-formula versions prior to 0.13.1+git.1667812208.4db963e. openSUSE Leap 15.4 saphanabootstrap-formula versions prior to 0.13.1+git.1667812208.4db963e.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-45153|2024-08-03T14:09:55.968Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-43759|2024-08-03T13:40:06.453Z -- suse -- rancher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43759</link>
      <description>A Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in SUSE Rancher, allows users with access to the escalate verb on PRTBs to escalate permissions for any -promoted resource in any cluster. This issue affects: SUSE Rancher Rancher versions prior to 2.5.17; Rancher versions prior to 2.6.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-43759|2024-08-03T13:40:06.453Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31248|2024-08-03T07:11:39.904Z -- suse -- suse%20manager%20server%204.1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31248</link>
      <description>A Observable Response Discrepancy vulnerability in spacewalk-java of SUSE Manager Server 4.1, SUSE Manager Server 4.2 allows remote attackers to discover valid usernames. This issue affects: SUSE Manager Server 4.1 spacewalk-java versions prior to 4.1.46-1. SUSE Manager Server 4.2 spacewalk-java versions prior to 4.2.37-1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31248|2024-08-03T07:11:39.904Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31247|2024-08-03T07:11:39.936Z -- suse -- rancher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31247</link>
      <description>An Improper Authorization vulnerability in SUSE Rancher, allows any user who has permissions to create/edit cluster role template bindings or project role template bindings (such as cluster-owner, manage cluster members, project-owner and manage project members) to gain owner permission in another project in the same cluster or in another project on a different downstream cluster. This issue affects: SUSE Rancher Rancher versions prior to 2.6.7; Rancher versions prior to 2.5.16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31247|2024-08-03T07:11:39.936Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-45154|2024-08-03T14:09:56.382Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20server%2012
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45154</link>
      <description>A Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information vulnerability in suppportutils of SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 SP3 allows attackers that get access to the support logs to gain knowledge of the stored credentials This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12 supportutils version 3.0.10-95.51.1CWE-312: Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information and prior versions. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 supportutils version 3.1.21-150000.5.44.1 and prior versions. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 SP3 supportutils version 3.1.21-150300.7.35.15.1 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-45154|2024-08-03T14:09:56.382Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
