<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SUSE -- Rancher</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/suse/rancher.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SUSE -- Rancher</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 15:22:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-43755|2024-08-03T13:40:06.266Z -- suse -- rancher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43755</link>
      <description>A Insufficient Entropy vulnerability in SUSE Rancher allows attackers that gained knowledge of the cattle-token to continue abusing this even after the token was renewed. This issue affects: SUSE Rancher Rancher versions prior to 2.6.10; Rancher versions prior to 2.7.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-43755|2024-08-03T13:40:06.266Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-43758|2024-08-03T13:40:06.453Z -- suse -- rancher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43758</link>
      <description>A Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in SUSE Rancher allows code execution for user with the ability to add an untrusted Helm catalog or modifying the URL configuration used to download KDM (only admin users by default) This issue affects: SUSE Rancher Rancher versions prior to 2.5.17; Rancher versions prior to 2.6.10; Rancher versions prior to 2.7.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-43758|2024-08-03T13:40:06.453Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-43757|2024-08-03T13:40:06.199Z -- suse -- rancher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43757</link>
      <description>A Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information vulnerability in SUSE Rancher allows users on managed clusters to gain access to credentials. The impact depends on the credentials exposed This issue affects: SUSE Rancher Rancher versions prior to 2.5.17; Rancher versions prior to 2.6.10; Rancher versions prior to 2.7.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-43757|2024-08-03T13:40:06.199Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-43760|2024-08-03T13:40:06.301Z -- suse -- rancher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43760</link>
      <description>An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SUSE Rancher allows users in some higher-privileged groups to to inject code that is 
executed within another user's browser, allowing the attacker to steal 
sensitive information, manipulate web content, or perform other 
malicious activities on behalf of the victims. This could result in a 
user with write access to the affected areas being able to act on behalf
 of an administrator, once an administrator opens the affected web page.


This issue affects Rancher: from &gt;= 2.6.0 before &lt; 2.6.13, from &gt;= 2.7.0 before &lt; 2.7.4.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-43760|2024-08-03T13:40:06.301Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 12:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31249|2024-08-03T07:11:39.931Z -- suse -- rancher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31249</link>
      <description>A Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in wrangler of SUSE Rancher allows remote attackers to inject commands in the underlying host via crafted commands passed to Wrangler. This issue affects: SUSE Rancher wrangler version 0.7.3 and prior versions; wrangler version 0.8.4 and prior versions; wrangler version 1.0.0 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31249|2024-08-03T07:11:39.931Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-43756|2024-08-03T13:40:06.577Z -- suse -- rancher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43756</link>
      <description>A Improper Neutralization of Special Elements in Output Used by a Downstream Component ('Injection') vulnerability in SUSE Rancher allows remote attackers to cause denial of service by supplying specially crafted git credentials. This issue affects: SUSE Rancher wrangler version 0.7.3 and prior versions; wrangler version 0.8.4 and prior versions; wrangler version 1.0.0 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-43756|2024-08-03T13:40:06.577Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21947|2024-08-03T03:00:54.558Z -- suse -- rancher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21947</link>
      <description>A Exposure of Resource to Wrong Sphere vulnerability in Rancher Desktop of SUSE allows attackers in the local network to connect to the Dashboard API (steve) to carry out arbitrary actions. This issue affects: SUSE Rancher Desktop versions prior to V.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21947|2024-08-03T03:00:54.558Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21951|2024-08-03T03:00:54.452Z -- suse -- rancher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21951</link>
      <description>A Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information vulnerability in SUSE Rancher, Rancher allows attackers on the network to read and change network data due to missing encryption of data transmitted via the network when a cluster is created from an RKE template with the CNI value overridden This issue affects: SUSE Rancher Rancher versions prior to 2.5.14; Rancher versions prior to 2.6.5.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21951|2024-08-03T03:00:54.452Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21953|2024-08-03T03:00:54.295Z -- suse -- rancher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21953</link>
      <description>A Missing Authorization vulnerability in of SUSE Rancher allows authenticated user to create an unauthorized shell pod and kubectl access in the local cluster This issue affects: SUSE Rancher Rancher versions prior to 2.5.17; Rancher versions prior to 2.6.10; Rancher versions prior to 2.7.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21953|2024-08-03T03:00:54.295Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-43759|2024-08-03T13:40:06.453Z -- suse -- rancher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43759</link>
      <description>A Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in SUSE Rancher, allows users with access to the escalate verb on PRTBs to escalate permissions for any -promoted resource in any cluster. This issue affects: SUSE Rancher Rancher versions prior to 2.5.17; Rancher versions prior to 2.6.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-43759|2024-08-03T13:40:06.453Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31247|2024-08-03T07:11:39.936Z -- suse -- rancher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31247</link>
      <description>An Improper Authorization vulnerability in SUSE Rancher, allows any user who has permissions to create/edit cluster role template bindings or project role template bindings (such as cluster-owner, manage cluster members, project-owner and manage project members) to gain owner permission in another project in the same cluster or in another project on a different downstream cluster. This issue affects: SUSE Rancher Rancher versions prior to 2.6.7; Rancher versions prior to 2.5.16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31247|2024-08-03T07:11:39.936Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
