<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SUSE -- SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/suse/suse%20linux%20enterprise%20server%2012.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SUSE -- SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:21:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8013|2024-09-16T17:23:50.476Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20server%2012
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8013</link>
      <description>A UNIX Symbolic Link (Symlink) Following vulnerability in chkstat of SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11 set permissions intended for specific binaries on other binaries because it erroneously followed symlinks. The symlinks can't be controlled by attackers on default systems, so exploitation is difficult. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12 permissions versions prior to 2015.09.28.1626-17.27.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 15 permissions versions prior to 20181116-9.23.1. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11 permissions versions prior to 2013.1.7-0.6.12.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8013|2024-09-16T17:23:50.476Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 16:35:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3698|2024-09-16T16:33:41.138Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20server%2012
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3698</link>
      <description>UNIX Symbolic Link (Symlink) Following vulnerability in the cronjob shipped with nagios of SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12, SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11; openSUSE Factory allows local attackers to cause cause DoS or potentially escalate privileges by winning a race. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 12 nagios version 3.5.1-5.27 and prior versions. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 11 nagios version 3.0.6-1.25.36.3.1 and prior versions. openSUSE Factory nagios version 4.4.5-2.1 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3698|2024-09-16T16:33:41.138Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 13:20:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
