<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SUSE -- SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for SUSE Manager Server 4.1</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/suse/suse%20linux%20enterprise%20module%20for%20suse%20manager%20server%204.1.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SUSE -- SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for SUSE Manager Server 4.1</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 18:24:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8028|2024-08-04T09:48:25.486Z -- suse -- suse%20linux%20enterprise%20module%20for%20suse%20manager%20server%204.1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8028</link>
      <description>A Improper Access Control vulnerability in the configuration of salt of SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for SUSE Manager Server 4.1, SUSE Manager Proxy 4.0, SUSE Manager Retail Branch Server 4.0, SUSE Manager Server 3.2, SUSE Manager Server 4.0 allows local users to escalate to root on every system managed by SUSE manager. On the managing node itself code can be executed as user salt, potentially allowing for escalation to root there. This issue affects: SUSE Linux Enterprise Module for SUSE Manager Server 4.1 google-gson versions prior to 2.8.5-3.4.3, httpcomponents-client-4.5.6-3.4.2, httpcomponents-. SUSE Manager Proxy 4.0 release-notes-susemanager-proxy versions prior to 4.0.9-0.16.38.1. SUSE Manager Retail Branch Server 4.0 release-notes-susemanager-proxy versions prior to 4.0.9-0.16.38.1. SUSE Manager Server 3.2 salt-netapi-client versions prior to 0.16.0-4.14.1, spacewalk-. SUSE Manager Server 4.0 release-notes-susemanager versions prior to 4.0.9-3.54.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8028|2024-08-04T09:48:25.486Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
