<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Samba -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/samba/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Samba -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:23:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-44142|2024-08-04T04:17:24.423Z -- samba -- samba
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-44142</link>
      <description>The Samba vfs_fruit module uses extended file attributes (EA, xattr) to provide "...enhanced compatibility with Apple SMB clients and interoperability with a Netatalk 3 AFP fileserver." Samba versions prior to 4.13.17, 4.14.12 and 4.15.5 with vfs_fruit configured allow out-of-bounds heap read and write via specially crafted extended file attributes. A remote attacker with write access to extended file attributes can execute arbitrary code with the privileges of smbd, typically root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-44142|2024-08-04T04:17:24.423Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-10218|2024-08-04T22:17:19.002Z -- samba -- samba
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-10218</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the samba client, all samba versions before samba 4.11.2, 4.10.10 and 4.9.15, where a malicious server can supply a pathname to the client with separators. This could allow the client to access files and folders outside of the SMB network pathnames. An attacker could use this vulnerability to create files outside of the current working directory using the privileges of the client user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-10218|2024-08-04T22:17:19.002Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-10197|2024-08-04T22:17:18.912Z -- samba -- samba
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-10197</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in samba versions 4.9.x up to 4.9.13, samba 4.10.x up to 4.10.8 and samba 4.11.x up to 4.11.0rc3, when certain parameters were set in the samba configuration file. An unauthenticated attacker could use this flaw to escape the shared directory and access the contents of directories outside the share.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-10197|2024-08-04T22:17:18.912Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 14:50:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14342|2024-08-04T12:39:36.529Z -- samba -- cifs-utils
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14342</link>
      <description>It was found that cifs-utils' mount.cifs was invoking a shell when requesting the Samba password, which could be used to inject arbitrary commands. An attacker able to invoke mount.cifs with special permission, such as via sudo rules, could use this flaw to escalate their privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14342|2024-08-04T12:39:36.529Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 11:13:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
