<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for XiaoBingBy -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/xiaobingby/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for XiaoBingBy -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 14:23:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1398|2024-08-02T05:49:10.353Z -- xiaobingby -- teacms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1398</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in XiaoBingBy TeaCMS 2.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/upload. The manipulation leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-222985 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In XiaoBingBy TeaCMS 2.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei /admin/upload. Durch Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine path traversal: '../filedir'-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1398|2024-08-02T05:49:10.353Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 14:43:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1483|2024-08-02T05:49:11.639Z -- xiaobingby -- teacms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1483</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in XiaoBingBy TeaCMS up to 2.0.2 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/getallarticleinfo. The manipulation of the argument searchInfo leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. VDB-223366 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In XiaoBingBy TeaCMS bis 2.0.2 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle gefunden. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei /admin/getallarticleinfo. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments searchInfo mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1483|2024-08-02T05:49:11.639Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 09:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1616|2024-08-02T05:57:24.321Z -- xiaobingby -- teacms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1616</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in XiaoBingBy TeaCMS up to 2.0.2. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the component Article Title Handler. The manipulation with the input &lt;script&gt;alert(document.cookie)&lt;/script&gt; leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-223800.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in XiaoBingBy TeaCMS bis 2.0.2 ausgemacht. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Komponente Article Title Handler. Mittels dem Manipulieren mit der Eingabe &lt;script&gt;alert(document.cookie)&lt;/script&gt; mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1616|2024-08-02T05:57:24.321Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 07:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
