<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Ubuntu -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ubuntu/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Ubuntu -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:23:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-1586|2024-08-05T23:02:11.670Z -- ubuntu -- oxide
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-1586</link>
      <description>A malicious webview could install long-lived unload handlers that re-use an incognito BrowserContext that is queued for destruction in versions of Oxide before 1.18.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-1586|2024-08-05T23:02:11.670Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15794|2024-08-05T00:56:22.473Z -- ubuntu -- linux%20kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15794</link>
      <description>Overlayfs in the Linux kernel and shiftfs, a non-upstream patch to the Linux kernel included in the Ubuntu 5.0 and 5.3 kernel series, both replace vma-&gt;vm_file in their mmap handlers. On error the original value is not restored, and the reference is put for the file to which vm_file points. On upstream kernels this is not an issue, as no callers dereference vm_file following after call_mmap() returns an error. However, the aufs patchs change mmap_region() to replace the fput() using a local variable with vma_fput(), which will fput() vm_file, leading to a refcount underflow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15794|2024-08-05T00:56:22.473Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-1584|2024-08-05T23:02:11.707Z -- ubuntu -- unity8
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-1584</link>
      <description>In all versions of Unity8 a running but not active application on a large-screen device could talk with Maliit and consume keyboard input.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-1584|2024-08-05T23:02:11.707Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6557|2024-08-05T06:10:10.072Z -- ubuntu -- base-files
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6557</link>
      <description>The MOTD update script in the base-files package in Ubuntu 18.04 LTS before 10.1ubuntu2.2, and Ubuntu 18.10 before 10.1ubuntu6 incorrectly handled temporary files. A local attacker could use this issue to cause a denial of service, or possibly escalate privileges if kernel symlink restrictions were disabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6557|2024-08-05T06:10:10.072Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15792|2024-08-05T00:56:22.476Z -- ubuntu -- shiftfs%20in%20the%20linux%20kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15792</link>
      <description>In shiftfs, a non-upstream patch to the Linux kernel included in the Ubuntu 5.0 and 5.3 kernel series, shiftfs_btrfs_ioctl_fd_replace() calls fdget(oldfd), then without further checks passes the resulting file* into shiftfs_real_fdget(), which casts file-&gt;private_data, a void* that points to a filesystem-dependent type, to a "struct shiftfs_file_info *". As the private_data is not required to be a pointer, an attacker can use this to cause a denial of service or possibly execute arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15792|2024-08-05T00:56:22.476Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-1573|2024-08-05T23:02:11.780Z -- ubuntu -- unity8
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-1573</link>
      <description>Versions of Unity8 before 8.11+16.04.20160122-0ubuntu1 file plugins/Dash/CardCreator.js will execute any code found in place of a fallback image supplied by a scope.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-1573|2024-08-05T23:02:11.780Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15791|2024-08-05T00:56:22.393Z -- ubuntu -- shiftfs%20in%20the%20linux%20kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15791</link>
      <description>In shiftfs, a non-upstream patch to the Linux kernel included in the Ubuntu 5.0 and 5.3 kernel series, shiftfs_btrfs_ioctl_fd_replace() installs an fd referencing a file from the lower filesystem without taking an additional reference to that file. After the btrfs ioctl completes this fd is closed, which then puts a reference to that file, leading to a refcount underflow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15791|2024-08-05T00:56:22.393Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-1579|2024-08-05T23:02:11.685Z -- ubuntu -- ubuntu%20download%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-1579</link>
      <description>UDM provides support for running commands after a download is completed, this is currently made use of for click package installation. This functionality was not restricted to unconfined applications. Before UDM version 1.2+16.04.20160408-0ubuntu1 any confined application could make use of the UDM C++ API to run arbitrary commands in an unconfined environment as the phablet user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-1579|2024-08-05T23:02:11.685Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15793|2024-08-05T00:56:22.425Z -- ubuntu -- shiftfs%20in%20the%20linux%20kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15793</link>
      <description>In shiftfs, a non-upstream patch to the Linux kernel included in the Ubuntu 5.0 and 5.3 kernel series, several locations which shift ids translate user/group ids before performing operations in the lower filesystem were translating them into init_user_ns, whereas they should have been translated into the s_user_ns for the lower filesystem. This resulted in using ids other than the intended ones in the lower fs, which likely did not map into the shifts s_user_ns. A local attacker could use this to possibly bypass discretionary access control permissions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15793|2024-08-05T00:56:22.425Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-1587|2024-08-05T23:02:12.189Z -- ubuntu -- snapweb
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-1587</link>
      <description>The Snapweb interface before version 0.21.2 was exposing controls to install or remove snap packages without controlling the identity of the user, nor the origin of the connection. An attacker could have used the controls to remotely add a valid, but malicious, snap package, from the Store, potentially using system resources without permission from the legitimate administrator of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-1587|2024-08-05T23:02:12.189Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
