<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for ExpressTech -- Responsive Menu – Create Mobile-Friendly Menu</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/expresstech/responsive%20menu%20%E2%80%93%20create%20mobile-friendly%20menu.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for ExpressTech -- Responsive Menu – Create Mobile-Friendly Menu</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 20:22:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-24162|2024-08-03T19:21:18.635Z -- expresstech -- responsive%20menu%20%E2%80%93%20create%20mobile-friendly%20menu
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-24162</link>
      <description>In the Reponsive Menu (free and Pro) WordPress plugins before 4.0.4, attackers could craft a request and trick an administrator into importing all new settings. These settings could be modified to include malicious JavaScript, therefore allowing an attacker to inject payloads that could aid in further infection of the site.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-24162|2024-08-03T19:21:18.635Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 18:27:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-24160|2024-08-03T19:21:18.582Z -- expresstech -- responsive%20menu%20%E2%80%93%20create%20mobile-friendly%20menu
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-24160</link>
      <description>In the Reponsive Menu (free and Pro) WordPress plugins before 4.0.4, subscribers could upload zip archives containing malicious PHP files that would get extracted to the /rmp-menu/ directory. These files could then be accessed via the front end of the site to trigger remote code execution and ultimately allow an attacker to execute commands to further infect a WordPress site.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-24160|2024-08-03T19:21:18.582Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 18:27:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-24161|2024-08-03T19:21:18.537Z -- expresstech -- responsive%20menu%20%E2%80%93%20create%20mobile-friendly%20menu
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-24161</link>
      <description>In the Reponsive Menu (free and Pro) WordPress plugins before 4.0.4, attackers could craft a request and trick an administrator into uploading a zip archive containing malicious PHP files. The attacker could then access those files to achieve remote code execution and further infect the targeted site.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-24161|2024-08-03T19:21:18.537Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 18:27:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
