<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Zhong Bang -- CRMEB</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/zhong%20bang/crmeb.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Zhong Bang -- CRMEB</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 19:19:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3233|2024-08-02T06:48:08.208Z -- zhong%20bang -- crmeb
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3233</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Zhong Bang CRMEB up to 4.6.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function get_image_base64 of the file api/controller/v1/PublicController.php. The manipulation leads to server-side request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-231504. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Zhong Bang CRMEB bis 4.6.0 ausgemacht. Betroffen hiervon ist die Funktion get_image_base64 der Datei api/controller/v1/PublicController.php. Durch das Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine server-side request forgery-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3233|2024-08-02T06:48:08.208Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 06:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3232|2024-08-02T06:48:08.180Z -- zhong%20bang -- crmeb
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3232</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Zhong Bang CRMEB up to 4.6.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /api/wechat/app_auth of the component Image Upload. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-231503. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Zhong Bang CRMEB bis 4.6.0 gefunden. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei /api/wechat/app_auth der Komponente Image Upload. Durch Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine deserialization-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3232|2024-08-02T06:48:08.180Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 06:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3234|2024-08-02T06:48:08.207Z -- zhong%20bang -- crmeb
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3234</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Zhong Bang CRMEB up to 4.6.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function put_image of the file api/controller/v1/PublicController.php. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-231505 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Zhong Bang CRMEB bis 4.6.0 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Es geht um die Funktion put_image der Datei api/controller/v1/PublicController.php. Durch Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine deserialization-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3234|2024-08-02T06:48:08.207Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 06:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2419|2024-08-02T06:19:14.983Z -- zhong%20bang -- crmeb
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2419</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Zhong Bang CRMEB 4.6.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function videoUpload of the file \crmeb\app\services\system\attachment\SystemAttachmentServices.php. The manipulation of the argument filename leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-227716.
In Zhong Bang CRMEB 4.6.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Das betrifft die Funktion videoUpload der Datei \crmeb\app\services\system\attachment\SystemAttachmentServices.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments filename mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2419|2024-08-02T06:19:14.983Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 01:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
