<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Logsign -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/logsign/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Logsign -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 18:24:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7602|2024-08-21T16:06:09.754Z -- logsign -- unified%20secops%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7602</link>
      <description>Logsign Unified SecOps Platform Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Logsign Unified SecOps Platform. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP API service, which listens on TCP port 443 by default. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-25027.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7602|2024-08-21T16:06:09.754Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 16:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7603|2024-08-21T16:06:13.270Z -- logsign -- unified%20secops%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7603</link>
      <description>Logsign Unified SecOps Platform Directory Traversal Arbitrary Directory Deletion Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to delete arbitrary directories on affected installations of Logsign Unified SecOps Platform. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP API service, which listens on TCP port 443 by default. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to delete directories in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-25028.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7603|2024-08-21T16:06:13.270Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 16:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7604|2024-08-21T16:06:17.339Z -- logsign -- unified%20secops%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7604</link>
      <description>Logsign Unified SecOps Platform Incorrect Authorization Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of Logsign Unified SecOps Platform. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP API service, which listens on TCP port 443 by default. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the user's license expiration date. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-25029.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7604|2024-08-21T16:06:17.339Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 16:06:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7601|2024-08-21T16:06:06.261Z -- logsign -- unified%20secops%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7601</link>
      <description>Logsign Unified SecOps Platform Directory data_export_delete_all Traversal Arbitrary File Deletion Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to delete arbitrary files on affected installations of Logsign Unified SecOps Platform. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP API service, which listens on TCP port 443 by default. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to delete files in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-25026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7601|2024-08-21T16:06:06.261Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 16:06:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7600|2024-08-21T16:06:01.959Z -- logsign -- unified%20secops%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7600</link>
      <description>Logsign Unified SecOps Platform Directory Traversal Arbitrary File Deletion Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to delete arbitrary files on affected installations of Logsign Unified SecOps Platform. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP API service, which listens on TCP port 443 by default. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to delete files in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-25025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7600|2024-08-21T16:06:01.959Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 16:06:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7564|2024-08-06T15:47:49.467Z -- logsign -- unified%20secops%20platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7564</link>
      <description>Logsign Unified SecOps Platform Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Logsign Unified SecOps Platform. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the get_response_json_result endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-24680.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7564|2024-08-06T15:47:49.467Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:47:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7564|2024-08-07T13:34:22.057Z -- logsign -- unified%20secops%20platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7564</link>
      <description>Logsign Unified SecOps Platform Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Logsign Unified SecOps Platform. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the get_response_json_result endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-24680.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7564|2024-08-07T13:34:22.057Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:47:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
