<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for mbis -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/mbis/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for mbis -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 22:02:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-2738|2024-04-09T18:58:55.481Z -- mbis -- Permalink Manager Lite
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2738</link><description>The Permalink Manager Lite and Pro plugins for WordPress are vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘s’ parameter in multiple instances in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.3.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2738|2024-04-09T18:58:55.481Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:58:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2538|2024-03-20T05:32:54.399Z -- mbis -- Permalink Manager Pro
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2538</link><description>The Permalink Manager Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'ajax_save_permalink' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.3.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author access and above, to modify the permalinks of arbitrary posts.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2538|2024-03-20T05:32:54.399Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 05:32:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2543|2024-04-09T18:58:58.216Z -- mbis -- Permalink Manager Lite
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2543</link><description>The Permalink Manager Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'get_uri_editor' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.3.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view the permalinks of all posts.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2543|2024-04-09T18:58:58.216Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:58:58 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>