<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for backstage -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/backstage/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for backstage -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:22:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43783|2024-08-04T04:03:08.643Z -- backstage -- backstage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43783</link>
      <description>@backstage/plugin-scaffolder-backend is the backend for the default Backstage software templates. In affected versions a malicious actor with write access to a registered scaffolder template is able to manipulate the template in a way that writes files to arbitrary paths on the scaffolder-backend host instance. This vulnerability can in some situation also be exploited through user input when executing a template, meaning you do not need write access to the templates. This method will not allow the attacker to control the contents of the injected file however, unless the template is also crafted in a specific way that gives control of the file contents. This vulnerability is fixed in version `0.15.14` of the `@backstage/plugin-scaffolder-backend`. This attack is mitigated by restricting access and requiring reviews when registering or modifying scaffolder templates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43783|2024-08-04T04:03:08.643Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 19:20:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41151|2024-08-04T02:59:31.637Z -- backstage -- backstage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41151</link>
      <description>Backstage is an open platform for building developer portals. In affected versions A malicious actor could read sensitive files from the environment where Scaffolder Tasks are run. The attack is executed by crafting a custom Scaffolder template with a `github:publish:pull-request` action and a particular source path. When the template is executed the sensitive files would be included in the published pull request. This vulnerability is mitigated by the fact that an attacker would need access to create and register templates in the Backstage catalog, and that the attack is very visible given that the exfiltration happens via a pull request. The vulnerability is patched in the `0.15.9` release of `@backstage/plugin-scaffolder-backend`.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41151|2024-08-04T02:59:31.637Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 20:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43776|2024-08-04T04:03:08.688Z -- backstage -- backstage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43776</link>
      <description>Backstage is an open platform for building developer portals. In affected versions the auth-backend plugin allows a malicious actor to trick another user into visiting a vulnerable URL that executes an XSS attack. This attack can potentially allow the attacker to exfiltrate access tokens or other secrets from the user's browser. The default CSP does prevent this attack, but it is expected that some deployments have these policies disabled due to incompatibilities. This is vulnerability is patched in version `0.4.9` of `@backstage/plugin-auth-backend`.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43776|2024-08-04T04:03:08.688Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 18:15:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-26150|2024-06-04T17:48:21.482Z -- backstage -- backstage</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-26150</link>
      <description>`@backstage/backend-common` is a common functionality library for backends for Backstage, an open platform for building developer portals. In `@backstage/backend-common` prior to versions 0.21.1, 0.20.2, and 0.19.10, paths checks with the `resolveSafeChildPath` utility were not exhaustive enough, leading to risk of path traversal vulnerabilities if symlinks can be injected by attackers. This issue is patched in `@backstage/backend-common` versions 0.21.1, 0.20.2, and 0.19.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-26150|2024-06-04T17:48:21.482Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 15:46:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
