<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Essential Addons -- Essential Addons for Elementor Pro</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/essential%20addons/essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20pro.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Essential Addons -- Essential Addons for Elementor Pro</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 10:22:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3645|2024-04-22T13:51:46.929Z -- essential%20addons -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20pro</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3645</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Counter widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.8.11 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes such as 'title_html_tag'. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3645|2024-04-22T13:51:46.929Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 13:51:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5612|2024-06-07T04:33:24.031Z -- essential%20addons -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20pro</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5612</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘eael_lightbox_open_btn_icon’ parameter within the Lightbox &amp; Modal widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.8.15 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5612|2024-06-07T04:33:24.031Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 04:33:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
