<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Eaton -- Intelligent Power manager (IPM)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/eaton/intelligent%20power%20manager%20%28ipm%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Eaton -- Intelligent Power manager (IPM)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 21:21:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23278|2024-08-03T19:05:55.635Z -- eaton -- intelligent%20power%20manager%20%28ipm%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23278</link>
      <description>Eaton Intelligent Power Manager (IPM) prior to 1.69 is vulnerable to authenticated arbitrary file delete vulnerability induced due to improper input validation at server/maps_srv.js with action removeBackground and server/node_upgrade_srv.js with action removeFirmware. An attacker can send specially crafted packets to delete the files on the system where IPM software is installed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23278|2024-08-03T19:05:55.635Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23280|2024-08-03T19:05:55.663Z -- eaton -- intelligent%20power%20manager%20%28ipm%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23280</link>
      <description>Eaton Intelligent Power Manager (IPM) prior to 1.69 is vulnerable to authenticated arbitrary file upload vulnerability. IPM’s maps_srv.js allows an attacker to upload a malicious NodeJS file using uploadBackgroud action. An attacker can upload a malicious code or execute any command using a specially crafted packet to exploit the vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23280|2024-08-03T19:05:55.663Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23277|2024-08-03T19:05:55.736Z -- eaton -- intelligent%20power%20manager%20%28ipm%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23277</link>
      <description>Eaton Intelligent Power Manager (IPM) prior to 1.69 is vulnerable to unauthenticated eval injection vulnerability. The software does not neutralize code syntax from users before using in the dynamic evaluation call in loadUserFile function under scripts/libs/utils.js. Successful exploitation can allow attackers to control the input to the function and execute attacker controlled commands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23277|2024-08-03T19:05:55.736Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23281|2024-08-03T19:05:55.648Z -- eaton -- intelligent%20power%20manager%20%28ipm%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23281</link>
      <description>Eaton Intelligent Power Manager (IPM) prior to 1.69 is vulnerable to unauthenticated remote code execution vulnerability. IPM software does not sanitize the date provided via coverterCheckList action in meta_driver_srv.js class. Attackers can send a specially crafted packet to make IPM connect to rouge SNMP server and execute attacker-controlled code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23281|2024-08-03T19:05:55.648Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23276|2024-08-03T19:05:54.415Z -- eaton -- intelligent%20power%20manager%20%28ipm%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23276</link>
      <description>Eaton Intelligent Power Manager (IPM) prior to 1.69 is vulnerable to authenticated SQL injection. A malicious user can send a specially crafted packet to exploit the vulnerability. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability can allow attackers to add users in the data base.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23276|2024-08-03T19:05:54.415Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23279|2024-08-03T19:05:55.624Z -- eaton -- intelligent%20power%20manager%20%28ipm%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23279</link>
      <description>Eaton Intelligent Power Manager (IPM) prior to 1.69 is vulnerable to unauthenticated arbitrary file delete vulnerability induced due to improper input validation in meta_driver_srv.js class with saveDriverData action using invalidated driverID. An attacker can send specially crafted packets to delete the files on the system where IPM software is installed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23279|2024-08-03T19:05:55.624Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
