<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for ruddernation -- TinyChat Room Spy Plugin</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ruddernation/tinychat%20room%20spy%20plugin.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for ruddernation -- TinyChat Room Spy Plugin</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 22:22:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2015-10110|2024-08-06T08:58:26.473Z -- ruddernation -- tinychat%20room%20spy%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-10110</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in ruddernation TinyChat Room Spy Plugin up to 1.2.8 on WordPress. This vulnerability affects the function wp_show_room_spy of the file room-spy.php. The manipulation of the argument room leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 1.2.9 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is ab72627a963d61fb3bc31018e3855b08dc94a979. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-230392.
In ruddernation TinyChat Room Spy Plugin bis 1.2.8 für WordPress wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist die Funktion wp_show_room_spy der Datei room-spy.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments room mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 1.2.9 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als ab72627a963d61fb3bc31018e3855b08dc94a979 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2015-10110|2024-08-06T08:58:26.473Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 22:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
