<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for OX Software GmbH -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ox%20software%20gmbh/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for OX Software GmbH -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29043|2024-01-12T07:07:53.229Z -- ox%20software%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-29043</link>
      <description>Presentations may contain references to images, which are user-controlled, and could include malicious script code that is being processed when editing a document. Script code embedded in malicious documents could be executed in the context of the user editing the document when performing certain actions, like copying content. The relevant attribute does now get encoded to avoid the possibility of executing script code. No publicly available exploits are known.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29043|2024-01-12T07:07:53.229Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29045|2024-01-12T07:08:13.807Z -- ox%20software%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-29045</link>
      <description>Documents operations, in this case "drawing", could be manipulated to contain invalid data types, possibly script code. Script code could be injected to an operation that would be executed for users that are actively collaborating on the same document. Operation data exchanged between collaborating parties does now gets checked for validity to avoid code execution. No publicly available exploits are known.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29045|2024-01-12T07:08:13.807Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:01:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29044|2024-01-12T07:08:04.419Z -- ox%20software%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-29044</link>
      <description>Documents operations could be manipulated to contain invalid data types, possibly script code. Script code could be injected to an operation that would be executed for users that are actively collaborating on the same document. Operation data exchanged between collaborating parties does now get escaped to avoid code execution. No publicly available exploits are known.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29044|2024-01-12T07:08:04.419Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:01:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29047|2024-01-12T07:08:31.530Z -- ox%20software%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-29047</link>
      <description>Imageconverter API endpoints provided methods that were not sufficiently validating and sanitizing client input, allowing to inject arbitrary SQL statements. An attacker with access to the adjacent network and potentially API credentials, could read and modify database content which is accessible to the imageconverter SQL user account. None No publicly available exploits are known.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29047|2024-01-12T07:08:31.530Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29046|2024-01-12T07:08:22.530Z -- ox%20software%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-29046</link>
      <description>Connections to external data sources, like e-mail autoconfiguration, were not terminated in case they hit a timeout, instead those connections were logged. Some connections use user-controlled endpoints, which could be malicious and attempt to keep the connection open for an extended period of time. As a result users were able to trigger large amount of egress network connections, possibly exhausting network pool resources and lock up legitimate requests. A new mechanism has been introduced to cancel external connections that might access user-controlled endpoints. No publicly available exploits are known.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29046|2024-01-12T07:08:22.530Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26441|2024-01-12T07:12:52.505Z -- ox%20software%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-26441</link>
      <description>Cacheservice did not correctly check if relative cache object were pointing to the defined absolute location when accessing resources. An attacker with access to the database and a local or restricted network would be able to read arbitrary local file system resources that are accessible by the services system user account. We have improved path validation and make sure that any access is contained to the defined root directory. No publicly available exploits are known.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26441|2024-01-12T07:12:52.505Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 12:23:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26436|2024-01-12T07:13:36.698Z -- ox%20software%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-26436</link>
      <description>Attackers with access to the "documentconverterws" API were able to inject serialized Java objects, that were not properly checked during deserialization. Access to this API endpoint is restricted to local networks by default. Arbitrary code could be injected that is being executed when processing the request. A check has been introduced to restrict processing of legal and expected classes for this API. We now log a warning in case there are attempts to inject illegal classes. No publicly available exploits are known.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26436|2024-01-12T07:13:36.698Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 07:52:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26440|2024-01-12T07:13:03.470Z -- ox%20software%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-26440</link>
      <description>The cacheservice API could be abused to indirectly inject parameters with SQL syntax which was insufficiently sanitized and would later be executed when creating new cache groups. Attackers with access to a local or restricted network could perform arbitrary SQL queries. We have improved the input check for API calls and filter for potentially malicious content. No publicly available exploits are known.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26440|2024-01-12T07:13:03.470Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 12:23:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26456|2024-01-12T07:09:35.360Z -- ox%20software%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-26456</link>
      <description>Users were able to set an arbitrary "product name" for OX Guard. The chosen value was not sufficiently sanitized before processing it at the user interface, allowing for indirect cross-site scripting attacks. Accounts that were temporarily taken over could be configured to trigger persistent code execution, allowing an attacker to build a foothold. Sanitization is in place for product names now. No publicly available exploits are known.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26456|2024-01-12T07:09:35.360Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26430|2024-01-12T07:14:31.982Z -- ox%20software%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-26430</link>
      <description>Attackers with access to user accounts can inject arbitrary control characters to SIEVE mail-filter rules. This could be abused to access SIEVE extension that are not allowed by App Suite or to inject rules which would break per-user filter processing, requiring manual cleanup of such rules. We have added sanitization to all mail-filter APIs to avoid forwardning control characters to subsystems. No publicly available exploits are known.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26430|2024-01-12T07:14:31.982Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 12:22:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26451|2024-01-12T07:08:44.957Z -- ox%20software%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-26451</link>
      <description>Functions with insufficient randomness were used to generate authorization tokens of the integrated oAuth Authorization Service. Authorization codes were predictable for third parties and could be used to intercept and take over the client authorization process. As a result, other users accounts could be compromised. The oAuth Authorization Service is not enabled by default. We have updated the implementation to use sources with sufficient randomness to generate authorization tokens. No publicly available exploits are known.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26451|2024-01-12T07:08:44.957Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 12:23:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26447|2024-01-12T07:11:58.378Z -- ox%20software%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-26447</link>
      <description>The "upsell" widget for the portal allows to specify a product description. This description taken from a user-controllable jslob did not get escaped before being added to DOM. Malicious script code can be executed within the victims context. This can lead to session hijacking or triggering unwanted actions via the web interface and API. To exploit this an attacker would require temporary access to the users account or lure a user to a compromised account. We now sanitize jslob content. No publicly available exploits are known.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26447|2024-01-12T07:11:58.378Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 12:23:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26446|2024-01-12T07:12:05.775Z -- ox%20software%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-26446</link>
      <description>The users clientID at "application passwords" was not sanitized or escaped before being added to DOM. Malicious script code can be executed within the victims context. This can lead to session hijacking or triggering unwanted actions via the web interface and API. To exploit this an attacker would require temporary access to the users account or lure a user to a compromised account. We now sanitize the user-controllable clientID parameter. No publicly available exploits are known.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26446|2024-01-12T07:12:05.775Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 12:23:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26450|2024-01-12T07:11:32.841Z -- ox%20software%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-26450</link>
      <description>The "OX Count" web service did not specify a media-type when processing responses by external resources. Malicious script code can be executed within the victims context. This can lead to session hijacking or triggering unwanted actions via the web interface and API. To exploit this an attacker would require temporary access to the users account or lure a user to a compromised account. We are now defining the accepted media-type to avoid code execution. No publicly available exploits are known.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26450|2024-01-12T07:11:32.841Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 12:23:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26427|2024-01-12T07:15:33.896Z -- ox%20software%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-26427</link>
      <description>Default permissions for a properties file were too permissive. Local system users could read potentially sensitive information. We updated the default permissions for noreply.properties set during package installation. No publicly available exploits are known.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26427|2024-01-12T07:15:33.896Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 07:51:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26431|2024-01-12T07:14:23.981Z -- ox%20software%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-26431</link>
      <description>IPv4-mapped IPv6 addresses did not get recognized as "local" by the code and a connection attempt is made. Attackers with access to user accounts could use this to bypass existing deny-list functionality and trigger requests to restricted network infrastructure to gain insight about topology and running services. We now respect possible IPV4-mapped IPv6 addresses when checking if contained in a deny-list. No publicly available exploits are known.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26431|2024-01-12T07:14:23.981Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 07:51:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26432|2024-01-12T07:14:13.966Z -- ox%20software%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-26432</link>
      <description>When adding an external mail account, processing of SMTP "capabilities" responses are not limited to plausible sizes. Attacker with access to a rogue SMTP service could trigger requests that lead to excessive resource usage and eventually service unavailability. We now limit accepted SMTP server response to reasonable length/size. No publicly available exploits are known.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26432|2024-01-12T07:14:13.966Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 07:51:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26449|2024-01-12T07:11:41.641Z -- ox%20software%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-26449</link>
      <description>The "OX Chat" web service did not specify a media-type when processing responses by external resources. Malicious script code can be executed within the victims context. This can lead to session hijacking or triggering unwanted actions via the web interface and API. To exploit this an attacker would require temporary access to the users account or lure a user to a compromised account. We are now defining the accepted media-type to avoid code execution. No publicly available exploits are known.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26449|2024-01-12T07:11:41.641Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 12:23:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26428|2024-01-12T07:14:53.031Z -- ox%20software%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-26428</link>
      <description>Attackers can successfully request arbitrary snippet IDs, including E-Mail signatures of other users within the same context. Signatures of other users could be read even though they are not explicitly shared. We improved permission handling when requesting snippets that are not explicitly shared with other users. No publicly available exploits are known.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26428|2024-01-12T07:14:53.031Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 07:51:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26445|2024-01-12T07:12:13.627Z -- ox%20software%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-26445</link>
      <description>Frontend themes are defined by user-controllable jslob settings and could point to a malicious resource which gets processed during login. Malicious script code can be executed within the victims context. This can lead to session hijacking or triggering unwanted actions via the web interface and API. To exploit this an attacker would require temporary access to the users account or lure a user to a compromised account. We now sanitize the theme value and use a default fallback if no theme matches. No publicly available exploits are known.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26445|2024-01-12T07:12:13.627Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 12:23:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26453|2024-01-12T07:09:05.302Z -- ox%20software%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-26453</link>
      <description>Requests to cache an image could be abused to include SQL queries that would be executed unchecked. Exploiting this vulnerability requires at least access to adjacent networks of the imageconverter service, which is not exposed to public networks by default. Arbitrary SQL statements could be executed in the context of the services database user account. API requests are now properly checked for valid content and attempts to circumvent this check are being logged as error. No publicly available exploits are known.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26453|2024-01-12T07:09:05.302Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26452|2024-01-12T07:08:54.928Z -- ox%20software%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-26452</link>
      <description>Requests to cache an image and return its metadata could be abused to include SQL queries that would be executed unchecked. Exploiting this vulnerability requires at least access to adjacent networks of the imageconverter service, which is not exposed to public networks by default. Arbitrary SQL statements could be executed in the context of the services database user account. API requests are now properly checked for valid content and attempts to circumvent this check are being logged as error. No publicly available exploits are known.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26452|2024-01-12T07:08:54.928Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26429|2024-01-12T07:14:43.792Z -- ox%20software%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-26429</link>
      <description>Control characters were not removed when exporting user feedback content. This allowed attackers to include unexpected content via user feedback and potentially break the exported data structure. We now drop all control characters that are not whitespace character during the export. No publicly available exploits are known.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26429|2024-01-12T07:14:43.792Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 07:51:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26448|2024-01-12T07:11:49.742Z -- ox%20software%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-26448</link>
      <description>Custom log-in and log-out locations are used-defined as jslob but were not checked to contain malicious protocol handlers. Malicious script code can be executed within the victims context. This can lead to session hijacking or triggering unwanted actions via the web interface and API. To exploit this an attacker would require temporary access to the users account or lure a user to a compromised account. We now sanitize jslob content for those locations to avoid redirects to malicious content. No publicly available exploits are known.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26448|2024-01-12T07:11:49.742Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 12:23:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26433|2024-01-12T07:14:03.915Z -- ox%20software%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-26433</link>
      <description>When adding an external mail account, processing of IMAP "capabilities" responses are not limited to plausible sizes. Attacker with access to a rogue IMAP service could trigger requests that lead to excessive resource usage and eventually service unavailability. We now limit accepted IMAP server response to reasonable length/size. No publicly available exploits are known.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26433|2024-01-12T07:14:03.915Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 07:51:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26438|2024-01-12T07:13:21.611Z -- ox%20software%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-26438</link>
      <description>External service lookups for a number of protocols were vulnerable to a time-of-check/time-of-use (TOCTOU) weakness, involving the JDK DNS cache. Attackers that were timing DNS cache expiry correctly were able to inject configuration that would bypass existing network deny-lists. Attackers could exploit this weakness to discover the existence of restricted network infrastructure and service availability. Improvements were made to include deny-lists not only during the check of the provided connection data, but also during use. No publicly available exploits are known.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26438|2024-01-12T07:13:21.611Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 12:22:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26443|2024-01-12T07:09:45.991Z -- ox%20software%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-26443</link>
      <description>Full-text autocomplete search allows user-provided SQL syntax to be injected to SQL statements. With existing sanitization in place, this can be abused to trigger benign SQL Exceptions but could potentially be escalated to a malicious SQL injection vulnerability. We now properly encode single quotes for SQL FULLTEXT queries. No publicly available exploits are known.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26443|2024-01-12T07:09:45.991Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 12:23:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26455|2024-01-12T07:09:24.702Z -- ox%20software%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-26455</link>
      <description>RMI was not requiring authentication when calling ChronosRMIService:setEventOrganizer. Attackers with local or adjacent network access could abuse the RMI service to modify calendar items using RMI. RMI access is restricted to localhost by default. The interface has been updated to require authenticated requests. No publicly available exploits are known.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26455|2024-01-12T07:09:24.702Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:01:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26434|2024-01-12T07:13:55.429Z -- ox%20software%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-26434</link>
      <description>When adding an external mail account, processing of POP3 "capabilities" responses are not limited to plausible sizes. Attacker with access to a rogue POP3 service could trigger requests that lead to excessive resource usage and eventually service unavailability. We now limit accepted POP3 server response to reasonable length/size. No publicly available exploits are known.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26434|2024-01-12T07:13:55.429Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 07:51:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26435|2024-01-12T07:13:46.277Z -- ox%20software%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-26435</link>
      <description>It was possible to call filesystem and network references using the local LibreOffice instance using manipulated ODT documents. Attackers could discover restricted network topology and services as well as including local files with read permissions of the open-xchange system user. This was limited to specific file-types, like images. We have improved existing content filters and validators to avoid including any local resources. No publicly available exploits are known.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26435|2024-01-12T07:13:46.277Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 07:51:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26454|2024-01-12T07:09:14.919Z -- ox%20software%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-26454</link>
      <description>Requests to fetch image metadata could be abused to include SQL queries that would be executed unchecked. Exploiting this vulnerability requires at least access to adjacent networks of the imageconverter service, which is not exposed to public networks by default. Arbitrary SQL statements could be executed in the context of the services database user account. API requests are now properly checked for valid content and attempts to circumvent this check are being logged as error. No publicly available exploits are known.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26454|2024-01-12T07:09:14.919Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 13:01:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26442|2024-01-12T07:12:42.331Z -- ox%20software%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-26442</link>
      <description>In case Cacheservice was configured to use a sproxyd object-storage backend, it would follow HTTP redirects issued by that backend. An attacker with access to a local or restricted network with the capability to intercept and replay HTTP requests to sproxyd (or who is in control of the sproxyd service) could perform a server-side request-forgery attack and make Cacheservice connect to unexpected resources. We have disabled the ability to follow HTTP redirects when connecting to sproxyd resources. No publicly available exploits are known.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26442|2024-01-12T07:12:42.331Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 12:23:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26439|2024-01-12T07:13:12.378Z -- ox%20software%20gmbh -- ox%20app%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-26439</link>
      <description>The cacheservice API could be abused to inject parameters with SQL syntax which was insufficiently sanitized before getting executed as SQL statement. Attackers with access to a local or restricted network were able to perform arbitrary SQL queries, discovering other users cached data. We have improved the input check for API calls and filter for potentially malicious content. No publicly available exploits are known.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26439|2024-01-12T07:13:12.378Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 12:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
