<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for simpleledger -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/simpleledger/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for simpleledger -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 13:23:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11071|2024-08-04T11:21:14.616Z -- simpleledger -- slpjs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11071</link>
      <description>SLPJS (npm package slpjs) before version 0.27.2, has a vulnerability where users could experience false-negative validation outcomes for MINT transaction operations. A poorly implemented SLP wallet could allow spending of the affected tokens which would result in the destruction of a user's minting baton. This is fixed in version 0.27.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11071|2024-08-04T11:21:14.616Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 00:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11014|2024-08-04T11:21:14.319Z -- simpleledger -- electron-cash-slp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11014</link>
      <description>Electron-Cash-SLP before version 3.6.2 has a vulnerability. All token creators that use the "Mint Tool" feature of the Electron Cash SLP Edition are at risk of sending the minting authority baton to the wrong SLP address. Sending the mint baton to the wrong address will give another party the ability to issue new tokens or permanently destroy future minting capability. This is fixed version 3.6.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11014|2024-08-04T11:21:14.319Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 20:10:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11072|2024-08-04T11:21:14.682Z -- simpleledger -- slp-validate
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11072</link>
      <description>In SLP Validate (npm package slp-validate) before version 1.2.1, users could experience false-negative validation outcomes for MINT transaction operations. A poorly implemented SLP wallet could allow spending of the affected tokens which would result in the destruction of a user's minting baton. This has been fixed in slp-validate in version 1.2.1. Additonally, slpjs version 0.27.2 has a related fix under related CVE-2020-11071.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11072|2024-08-04T11:21:14.682Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 00:45:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
