<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for dbartholomae -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/dbartholomae/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for dbartholomae -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 18:24:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-4437|2024-08-03T17:30:07.795Z -- dbartholomae -- lambda-middleware%20frameguard
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4437</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in dbartholomae lambda-middleware frameguard up to 1.0.4. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file packages/json-deserializer/src/JsonDeserializer.ts of the component JSON Mime-Type Handler. The manipulation leads to inefficient regular expression complexity. Upgrading to version 1.1.0 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as f689404d830cbc1edd6a1018d3334ff5f44dc6a6. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-253406 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in dbartholomae lambda-middleware frameguard bis 1.0.4 entdeckt. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei packages/json-deserializer/src/JsonDeserializer.ts der Komponente JSON Mime-Type Handler. Durch Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine inefficient regular expression complexity-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 1.1.0 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als f689404d830cbc1edd6a1018d3334ff5f44dc6a6 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-4437|2024-08-03T17:30:07.795Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 19:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
