<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for CyberArk -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cyberark/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for CyberArk -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 15:22:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4062|2024-08-04T07:52:20.924Z -- cyberark -- conjur%20oss%20helm%20chart
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4062</link>
      <description>In Conjur OSS Helm Chart before 2.0.0, a recently identified critical vulnerability resulted in the installation of the Conjur Postgres database with an open port. This allows an attacker to gain full read &amp; write access to the Conjur Postgres database, including escalating the attacker's privileges to assume full control. A malicious actor who knows the IP address and port number of the Postgres database and has access into the Kubernetes cluster where Conjur runs can gain full read &amp; write access to the Postgres database. This enables the attacker to write a policy that allows full access to retrieve any secret. This Helm chart is a method to install Conjur OSS into a Kubernetes environment. Hence, the systems impacted are only Conjur OSS systems that were deployed using this chart. Other deployments including Docker and the CyberArk Dynamic Access Provider (DAP) are not affected. To remediate this vulnerability, clone the latest Helm Chart and follow the upgrade instructions. If you are not able to fully remediate this vulnerability immediately, you can mitigate some of the risk by making sure Conjur OSS is deployed on an isolated Kubernetes cluster or namespace. The term "isolated" refers to: - No other workloads besides Conjur OSS and its backend database are running in that Kubernetes cluster/namespace. - Kubernetes and helm access to the cluster/namespace is limited to security administrators via Role-Based Access Control (RBAC).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4062|2024-08-04T07:52:20.924Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 15:20:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-37151|2024-08-04T01:16:02.865Z -- cyberark -- identity
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-37151</link>
      <description>CyberArk Identity 21.5.131, when handling an invalid authentication attempt, sometimes reveals whether the username is valid. In certain authentication policy configurations with MFA, the API response length can be used to differentiate between a valid user and an invalid one (aka Username Enumeration). Response differentiation enables attackers to enumerate usernames of valid application users. Attackers can use this information to leverage brute-force and dictionary attacks in order to discover valid account information such as passwords.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-37151|2024-08-04T01:16:02.865Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 12:35:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
