<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Pivotal -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/pivotal/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Pivotal -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 09:23:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11088|2024-09-17T03:14:36.305Z -- pivotal -- application%20service
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11088</link>
      <description>Pivotal Applications Manager in Pivotal Application Service, versions 2.0 prior to 2.0.21 and 2.1 prior to 2.1.13 and 2.2 prior to 2.2.5, contains a bug which may allow escalation of privileges. A space developer with access to the system org may be able to access an artifact which contains the CF admin credential, allowing them to escalate to an admin role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11088|2024-09-17T03:14:36.305Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11087|2024-09-17T03:58:41.663Z -- pivotal -- spring%20amqp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11087</link>
      <description>Pivotal Spring AMQP, 1.x versions prior to 1.7.10 and 2.x versions prior to 2.0.6, expose a man-in-the-middle vulnerability due to lack of hostname validation. A malicious user that has the ability to intercept traffic would be able to view data in transit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11087|2024-09-17T03:58:41.663Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11288|2024-09-17T04:09:48.305Z -- pivotal -- pivotal%20tc%20server%204.x
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11288</link>
      <description>In Pivotal tc Server, 3.x versions prior to 3.2.19 and 4.x versions prior to 4.0.10, and Pivotal tc Runtimes, 7.x versions prior to 7.0.99.B, 8.x versions prior to 8.5.47.A, and 9.x versions prior to 9.0.27.A, when a tc Runtime instance is configured with the JMX Socket Listener, a local attacker without access to the tc Runtime process or configuration files is able to manipulate the RMI registry to perform a man-in-the-middle attack to capture user names and passwords used to access the JMX interface. The attacker can then use these credentials to access the JMX interface and gain complete control over the tc Runtime instance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11288|2024-09-17T04:09:48.305Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 18:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5406|2024-09-17T03:17:26.159Z -- pivotal -- vmware%20tanzu%20application%20service%20for%20vms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5406</link>
      <description>VMware Tanzu Application Service for VMs, 2.6.x versions prior to 2.6.18, 2.7.x versions prior to 2.7.11, and 2.8.x versions prior to 2.8.5, includes a version of PCF Autoscaling that writes database connection properties to its log, including database username and password. A malicious user with access to those logs may gain unauthorized access to the database being used by Autoscaling.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5406|2024-09-17T03:17:26.159Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 18:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15758|2024-09-17T01:16:40.202Z -- pivotal -- spring%20security%20oauth
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15758</link>
      <description>Spring Security OAuth, versions 2.3 prior to 2.3.4, and 2.2 prior to 2.2.3, and 2.1 prior to 2.1.3, and 2.0 prior to 2.0.16, and older unsupported versions could be susceptible to a privilege escalation under certain conditions. A malicious user or attacker can craft a request to the approval endpoint that can modify the previously saved authorization request and lead to a privilege escalation on the subsequent approval. This scenario can happen if the application is configured to use a custom approval endpoint that declares AuthorizationRequest as a controller method argument. This vulnerability exposes applications that meet all of the following requirements: Act in the role of an Authorization Server (e.g. @EnableAuthorizationServer) and use a custom Approval Endpoint that declares AuthorizationRequest as a controller method argument. This vulnerability does not expose applications that: Act in the role of an Authorization Server and use the default Approval Endpoint, act in the role of a Resource Server only (e.g. @EnableResourceServer), act in the role of a Client only (e.g. @EnableOAuthClient).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15758|2024-09-17T01:16:40.202Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11040|2024-09-17T02:06:00.434Z -- pivotal -- spring%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11040</link>
      <description>Spring Framework, versions 5.0.x prior to 5.0.7 and 4.3.x prior to 4.3.18 and older unsupported versions, allows web applications to enable cross-domain requests via JSONP (JSON with Padding) through AbstractJsonpResponseBodyAdvice for REST controllers and MappingJackson2JsonView for browser requests. Both are not enabled by default in Spring Framework nor Spring Boot, however, when MappingJackson2JsonView is configured in an application, JSONP support is automatically ready to use through the "jsonp" and "callback" JSONP parameters, enabling cross-domain requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11040|2024-09-17T02:06:00.434Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5409|2024-09-17T02:47:32.788Z -- pivotal -- concourse
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5409</link>
      <description>Pivotal Concourse, most versions prior to 6.0.0, allows redirects to untrusted websites in its login flow. A remote unauthenticated attacker could convince a user to click on a link using the OAuth redirect link with an untrusted website and gain access to that user's access token in Concourse. (This issue is similar to, but distinct from, CVE-2018-15798.)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5409|2024-09-17T02:47:32.788Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 23:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15798|2024-09-17T03:18:08.124Z -- pivotal -- concourse
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15798</link>
      <description>Pivotal Concourse Release, versions 4.x prior to 4.2.2, login flow allows redirects to untrusted websites. A remote unauthenticated attacker could convince a user to click on a link using the oAuth redirect link with an untrusted website and gain access to that user's access token in Concourse.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15798|2024-09-17T03:18:08.124Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11049|2024-09-17T04:20:09.305Z -- pivotal -- pivotal%20operations%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11049</link>
      <description>RSA Identity Governance and Lifecycle, RSA Via Lifecycle and Governance, and RSA IMG releases have an uncontrolled search vulnerability. The installation scripts set an environment variable in an unintended manner. A local authenticated malicious user could trick the root user to run malicious code on the targeted system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11049|2024-09-17T04:20:09.305Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11081|2024-09-17T01:26:01.975Z -- pivotal -- pivotal-ops-manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11081</link>
      <description>Pivotal Operations Manager, versions 2.2.x prior to 2.2.1, 2.1.x prior to 2.1.11, 2.0.x prior to 2.0.16, and 1.11.x prior to 2, fails to write the Operations Manager UAA config onto the temp RAM disk, thus exposing the configs directly onto disk. A remote user that has gained access to the Operations Manager VM, can now file search and find the UAA credentials for Operations Manager on the system disk..</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11081|2024-09-17T01:26:01.975Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1258|2024-09-17T02:56:37.459Z -- pivotal -- spring%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1258</link>
      <description>Spring Framework version 5.0.5 when used in combination with any versions of Spring Security contains an authorization bypass when using method security. An unauthorized malicious user can gain unauthorized access to methods that should be restricted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1258|2024-09-17T02:56:37.459Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3793|2024-09-17T02:42:24.279Z -- pivotal -- apps%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3793</link>
      <description>Pivotal Apps Manager Release, versions 665.0.x prior to 665.0.28, versions 666.0.x prior to 666.0.21, versions 667.0.x prior to 667.0.7, contain an invitation service that accepts HTTP. A remote unauthenticated user could listen to network traffic and gain access to the authorization credentials used to make the invitation requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3793|2024-09-17T02:42:24.279Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 15:21:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3792|2024-09-17T01:46:43.383Z -- pivotal -- concourse
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3792</link>
      <description>Pivotal Concourse version 5.0.0, contains an API that is vulnerable to SQL injection. An Concourse resource can craft a version identifier that can carry a SQL injection payload to the Concourse server, allowing the attacker to read privileged data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3792|2024-09-17T01:46:43.383Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 20:54:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1256|2024-09-17T01:06:26.892Z -- pivotal -- spring%20cloud%20sso%20connector
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1256</link>
      <description>Spring Cloud SSO Connector, version 2.1.2, contains a regression which disables issuer validation in resource servers that are not bound to the SSO service. In PCF deployments with multiple SSO service plans, a remote attacker can authenticate to unbound resource servers which use this version of the SSO Connector with tokens generated from another service plan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1256|2024-09-17T01:06:26.892Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3801|2024-09-17T02:56:41.904Z -- pivotal -- uaa%20release%20%28lts%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3801</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry cf-deployment, versions prior to 7.9.0, contain java components that are using an insecure protocol to fetch dependencies when building. A remote unauthenticated malicious attacker could hijack the DNS entry for the dependency, and inject malicious code into the component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3801|2024-09-17T02:56:41.904Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 20:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3776|2024-09-17T00:11:48.970Z -- pivotal -- pivotal%20ops%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3776</link>
      <description>Pivotal Operations Manager, 2.1.x versions prior to 2.1.20, 2.2.x versions prior to 2.2.16, 2.3.x versions prior to 2.3.10, 2.4.x versions prior to 2.4.3, contains a reflected cross site scripting vulnerability. A remote user that is able to convince an Operations Manager user to interact with malicious content could execute arbitrary JavaScript in the user's browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3776|2024-09-17T00:11:48.970Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11291|2024-09-17T00:31:38.392Z -- pivotal -- rabbitmq
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11291</link>
      <description>Pivotal RabbitMQ, 3.7 versions prior to v3.7.20 and 3.8 version prior to v3.8.1, and RabbitMQ for PCF, 1.16.x versions prior to 1.16.7 and 1.17.x versions prior to 1.17.4, contain two endpoints, federation and shovel, which do not properly sanitize user input. A remote authenticated malicious user with administrative access could craft a cross site scripting attack via the vhost or node name fields that could grant access to virtual hosts and policy management information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11291|2024-09-17T00:31:38.392Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 22:56:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1261|2024-09-17T01:46:47.886Z -- pivotal -- spring%20integration%20zip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1261</link>
      <description>Spring-integration-zip versions prior to 1.0.1 exposes an arbitrary file write vulnerability, which can be achieved using a specially crafted zip archive (affects other archives as well, bzip2, tar, xz, war, cpio, 7z) that holds path traversal filenames. So when the filename gets concatenated to the target extraction directory, the final path ends up outside of the target folder.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1261|2024-09-17T01:46:47.886Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15759|2024-09-17T01:50:35.021Z -- pivotal -- on%20demand%20services%20sdk
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15759</link>
      <description>Pivotal Cloud Foundry On Demand Services SDK, versions prior to 0.24 contain an insecure method of verifying credentials. A remote unauthenticated malicious user may make many requests to the service broker with different credentials, allowing them to infer valid credentials and gain access to perform broker operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15759|2024-09-17T01:50:35.021Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1279|2024-09-17T00:37:15.917Z -- pivotal -- rabbitmq%20for%20pcf
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1279</link>
      <description>Pivotal RabbitMQ for PCF, all versions, uses a deterministically generated cookie that is shared between all machines when configured in a multi-tenant cluster. A remote attacker who can gain information about the network topology can guess this cookie and, if they have access to the right ports on any server in the MQ cluster can use this cookie to gain full control over the entire cluster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1279|2024-09-17T00:37:15.917Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1260|2024-09-17T03:44:21.413Z -- pivotal -- spring%20security%20oauth
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1260</link>
      <description>Spring Security OAuth, versions 2.3 prior to 2.3.3, 2.2 prior to 2.2.2, 2.1 prior to 2.1.2, 2.0 prior to 2.0.15 and older unsupported versions contains a remote code execution vulnerability. A malicious user or attacker can craft an authorization request to the authorization endpoint that can lead to remote code execution when the resource owner is forwarded to the approval endpoint.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1260|2024-09-17T03:44:21.413Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11275|2024-09-17T02:57:24.557Z -- pivotal -- apps%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11275</link>
      <description>Pivotal Application Manager, versions 666.0.x prior to 666.0.36, versions 667.0.x prior to 667.0.22, versions 668.0.x prior to 668.0.21, versions 669.0.x prior to 669.0.13, and versions 670.0.x prior to 670.0.7, contain a vulnerability where a remote authenticated user can create an app with a name such that a csv program can interpret into a formula and gets executed. The malicious user can possibly gain access to a usage report that requires a higher privilege.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11275|2024-09-17T02:57:24.557Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 14:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5404|2024-09-17T01:02:01.211Z -- pivotal -- reactor%20netty
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5404</link>
      <description>The HttpClient from Reactor Netty, versions 0.9.x prior to 0.9.5, and versions 0.8.x prior to 0.8.16, may be used incorrectly, leading to a credentials leak during a redirect to a different domain. In order for this to happen, the HttpClient must have been explicitly configured to follow redirects.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5404|2024-09-17T01:02:01.211Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 17:55:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
