<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Pivotal -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/pivotal/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Pivotal -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 20:23:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15756|2024-09-16T16:59:11.041Z -- pivotal -- spring%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15756</link>
      <description>Spring Framework, version 5.1, versions 5.0.x prior to 5.0.10, versions 4.3.x prior to 4.3.20, and older unsupported versions on the 4.2.x branch provide support for range requests when serving static resources through the ResourceHttpRequestHandler, or starting in 5.0 when an annotated controller returns an org.springframework.core.io.Resource. A malicious user (or attacker) can add a range header with a high number of ranges, or with wide ranges that overlap, or both, for a denial of service attack. This vulnerability affects applications that depend on either spring-webmvc or spring-webflux. Such applications must also have a registration for serving static resources (e.g. JS, CSS, images, and others), or have an annotated controller that returns an org.springframework.core.io.Resource. Spring Boot applications that depend on spring-boot-starter-web or spring-boot-starter-webflux are ready to serve static resources out of the box and are therefore vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15756|2024-09-16T16:59:11.041Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11280|2024-09-16T19:20:44.714Z -- pivotal -- pivotal%20application%20service%20%28pas%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11280</link>
      <description>Pivotal Apps Manager, included in Pivotal Application Service versions 2.3.x prior to 2.3.18, 2.4.x prior to 2.4.14, 2.5.x prior to 2.5.10, and 2.6.x prior to 2.6.5, contains an invitations microservice which allows users to invite others to their organizations. A remote authenticated user can gain additional privileges by inviting themselves to spaces that they should not have access to.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11280|2024-09-16T19:20:44.714Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 18:35:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11281|2024-09-16T19:05:38.917Z -- pivotal -- rabbitmq
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11281</link>
      <description>Pivotal RabbitMQ, versions prior to v3.7.18, and RabbitMQ for PCF, versions 1.15.x prior to 1.15.13, versions 1.16.x prior to 1.16.6, and versions 1.17.x prior to 1.17.3, contain two components, the virtual host limits page, and the federation management UI, which do not properly sanitize user input. A remote authenticated malicious user with administrative access could craft a cross site scripting attack that would gain access to virtual hosts and policy management information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11281|2024-09-16T19:05:38.917Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 15:23:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11273|2024-09-16T18:04:10.968Z -- pivotal -- pivotal%20container%20service%20%28pks%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11273</link>
      <description>Pivotal Container Services (PKS) versions 1.3.x prior to 1.3.7, and versions 1.4.x prior to 1.4.1, contains a vulnerable component which logs the username and password to the billing database. A remote authenticated user with access to those logs may be able to retrieve non-sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11273|2024-09-16T18:04:10.968Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 22:34:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11276|2024-09-16T16:13:54.745Z -- pivotal -- pivotal%20application%20service%20%28pas%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11276</link>
      <description>Pivotal Apps Manager, included in Pivotal Application Service versions 2.3.x prior to 2.3.16, 2.4.x prior to 2.4.12, 2.5.x prior to 2.5.8, and 2.6.x prior to 2.6.3, makes a request to the /cloudapplication endpoint via Spring actuator, and subsequent requests via unsecured http. An adjacent unauthenticated user could eavesdrop on the network traffic and gain access to the unencrypted token allowing the attacker to read the type of access a user has over an app. They may also modify the logging level, potentially leading to lost information that would otherwise have been logged.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11276|2024-09-16T16:13:54.745Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 14:49:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1263|2024-09-16T16:38:32.767Z -- pivotal -- spring%20integration%20zip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1263</link>
      <description>Addresses partial fix in CVE-2018-1261. Pivotal spring-integration-zip, versions prior to 1.0.2, exposes an arbitrary file write vulnerability, that can be achieved using a specially crafted zip archive (affects other archives as well, bzip2, tar, xz, war, cpio, 7z), that holds path traversal filenames. So when the filename gets concatenated to the target extraction directory, the final path ends up outside of the target folder.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1263|2024-09-16T16:38:32.767Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11292|2024-09-16T18:54:10.028Z -- pivotal -- pivotal%20ops%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11292</link>
      <description>Pivotal Ops Manager, versions 2.4.x prior to 2.4.27, 2.5.x prior to 2.5.24, 2.6.x prior to 2.6.16, and 2.7.x prior to 2.7.5, logs all query parameters to tomcat’s access file. If the query parameters are used to provide authentication, ie. credentials, then they will be logged as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11292|2024-09-16T18:54:10.028Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 23:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1259|2024-09-16T16:33:36.641Z -- pivotal -- spring%20data%20commons
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1259</link>
      <description>Spring Data Commons, versions 1.13 prior to 1.13.12 and 2.0 prior to 2.0.7, used in combination with XMLBeam 1.4.14 or earlier versions, contains a property binder vulnerability caused by improper restriction of XML external entity references as underlying library XMLBeam does not restrict external reference expansion. An unauthenticated remote malicious user can supply specially crafted request parameters against Spring Data's projection-based request payload binding to access arbitrary files on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1259|2024-09-16T16:33:36.641Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15763|2024-09-16T18:48:32.330Z -- pivotal -- pivotal%20container%20service
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15763</link>
      <description>Pivotal Container Service, versions prior to 1.2.0, contains an information disclosure vulnerability which exposes IaaS credentials to application logs. A malicious user with access to application logs may be able to obtain IaaS credentials and perform actions using these credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15763|2024-09-16T18:48:32.330Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1280|2024-09-16T19:51:38.651Z -- pivotal -- greenplum%20command%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1280</link>
      <description>Pivotal Greenplum Command Center versions 2.x prior to 2.5.1 contains a blind SQL injection vulnerability. An unauthenticated user can perform a SQL injection in the command center which results in disclosure of database contents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1280|2024-09-16T19:51:38.651Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-0715|2024-09-16T16:48:30.435Z -- pivotal -- pivotal%20cloud%20foundry%20elastic%20runtime
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-0715</link>
      <description>Pivotal Cloud Foundry Elastic Runtime version 1.4.0 through 1.4.5, 1.5.0 through 1.5.11 and 1.6.0 through 1.6.11 is vulnerable to a remote information disclosure. It was found that original mitigation configuration instructions provided as part of CVE-2016-0708 were incomplete and could leave PHP Buildpack, Staticfile Buildpack and potentially other custom Buildpack applications vulnerable to remote information disclosure. Affected applications use automated buildpack detection, serve files directly from the root of the application and have a buildpack that matched after the Java Buildpack in the system buildpack priority when Java Buildpack versions 2.0 through 3.4 were present.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-0715|2024-09-16T16:48:30.435Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
