<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Pivotal -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/pivotal/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Pivotal -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 21:23:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15758|2024-08-05T10:01:54.565Z -- pivotal -- spring%20security%20oauth
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15758</link>
      <description>Spring Security OAuth, versions 2.3 prior to 2.3.4, and 2.2 prior to 2.2.3, and 2.1 prior to 2.1.3, and 2.0 prior to 2.0.16, and older unsupported versions could be susceptible to a privilege escalation under certain conditions. A malicious user or attacker can craft a request to the approval endpoint that can modify the previously saved authorization request and lead to a privilege escalation on the subsequent approval. This scenario can happen if the application is configured to use a custom approval endpoint that declares AuthorizationRequest as a controller method argument. This vulnerability exposes applications that meet all of the following requirements: Act in the role of an Authorization Server (e.g. @EnableAuthorizationServer) and use a custom Approval Endpoint that declares AuthorizationRequest as a controller method argument. This vulnerability does not expose applications that: Act in the role of an Authorization Server and use the default Approval Endpoint, act in the role of a Resource Server only (e.g. @EnableResourceServer), act in the role of a Client only (e.g. @EnableOAuthClient).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15758|2024-08-05T10:01:54.565Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1263|2024-08-05T03:51:49.195Z -- pivotal -- spring%20integration%20zip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1263</link>
      <description>Addresses partial fix in CVE-2018-1261. Pivotal spring-integration-zip, versions prior to 1.0.2, exposes an arbitrary file write vulnerability, that can be achieved using a specially crafted zip archive (affects other archives as well, bzip2, tar, xz, war, cpio, 7z), that holds path traversal filenames. So when the filename gets concatenated to the target extraction directory, the final path ends up outside of the target folder.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1263|2024-08-05T03:51:49.195Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8046|2024-08-05T16:19:29.628Z -- pivotal -- pivotal%20spring%20data%20rest%20and%20spring%20boot
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8046</link>
      <description>Malicious PATCH requests submitted to servers using Spring Data REST versions prior to 2.6.9 (Ingalls SR9), versions prior to 3.0.1 (Kay SR1) and Spring Boot versions prior to 1.5.9, 2.0 M6 can use specially crafted JSON data to run arbitrary Java code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8046|2024-08-05T16:19:29.628Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2018 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11045|2024-08-05T07:54:36.497Z -- pivotal -- pivotal%20operations%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11045</link>
      <description>Pivotal Operations Manager, versions 2.1 prior to 2.1.6 and 2.0 prior to 2.0.15 and 1.12 prior to 1.12.22, contains a static Linux Random Number Generator (LRNG) seed file embedded in the appliance image. An attacker with knowledge of the exact version and IaaS of a running OpsManager could get the contents of the corresponding seed from the published image and therefore infer the initial state of the LRNG.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11045|2024-08-05T07:54:36.497Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11081|2024-08-05T07:54:36.568Z -- pivotal -- pivotal-ops-manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11081</link>
      <description>Pivotal Operations Manager, versions 2.2.x prior to 2.2.1, 2.1.x prior to 2.1.11, 2.0.x prior to 2.0.16, and 1.11.x prior to 2, fails to write the Operations Manager UAA config onto the temp RAM disk, thus exposing the configs directly onto disk. A remote user that has gained access to the Operations Manager VM, can now file search and find the UAA credentials for Operations Manager on the system disk..</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11081|2024-08-05T07:54:36.568Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11039|2024-08-05T07:54:36.406Z -- pivotal -- spring%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11039</link>
      <description>Spring Framework (versions 5.0.x prior to 5.0.7, versions 4.3.x prior to 4.3.18, and older unsupported versions) allow web applications to change the HTTP request method to any HTTP method (including TRACE) using the HiddenHttpMethodFilter in Spring MVC. If an application has a pre-existing XSS vulnerability, a malicious user (or attacker) can use this filter to escalate to an XST (Cross Site Tracing) attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11039|2024-08-05T07:54:36.406Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1261|2024-08-05T03:51:48.973Z -- pivotal -- spring%20integration%20zip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1261</link>
      <description>Spring-integration-zip versions prior to 1.0.1 exposes an arbitrary file write vulnerability, which can be achieved using a specially crafted zip archive (affects other archives as well, bzip2, tar, xz, war, cpio, 7z) that holds path traversal filenames. So when the filename gets concatenated to the target extraction directory, the final path ends up outside of the target folder.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1261|2024-08-05T03:51:48.973Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1260|2024-08-05T03:51:48.982Z -- pivotal -- spring%20security%20oauth
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1260</link>
      <description>Spring Security OAuth, versions 2.3 prior to 2.3.3, 2.2 prior to 2.2.2, 2.1 prior to 2.1.2, 2.0 prior to 2.0.15 and older unsupported versions contains a remote code execution vulnerability. A malicious user or attacker can craft an authorization request to the authorization endpoint that can lead to remote code execution when the resource owner is forwarded to the approval endpoint.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1260|2024-08-05T03:51:48.982Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11040|2024-08-05T07:54:36.553Z -- pivotal -- spring%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11040</link>
      <description>Spring Framework, versions 5.0.x prior to 5.0.7 and 4.3.x prior to 4.3.18 and older unsupported versions, allows web applications to enable cross-domain requests via JSONP (JSON with Padding) through AbstractJsonpResponseBodyAdvice for REST controllers and MappingJackson2JsonView for browser requests. Both are not enabled by default in Spring Framework nor Spring Boot, however, when MappingJackson2JsonView is configured in an application, JSONP support is automatically ready to use through the "jsonp" and "callback" JSONP parameters, enabling cross-domain requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11040|2024-08-05T07:54:36.553Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11088|2024-08-05T07:54:36.479Z -- pivotal -- application%20service
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11088</link>
      <description>Pivotal Applications Manager in Pivotal Application Service, versions 2.0 prior to 2.0.21 and 2.1 prior to 2.1.13 and 2.2 prior to 2.2.5, contains a bug which may allow escalation of privileges. A space developer with access to the system org may be able to access an artifact which contains the CF admin credential, allowing them to escalate to an admin role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11088|2024-08-05T07:54:36.479Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1278|2024-08-05T03:59:37.602Z -- pivotal -- pivotal%20application%20service
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1278</link>
      <description>Apps Manager included in Pivotal Application Service, versions 1.12.x prior to 1.12.22, 2.0.x prior to 2.0.13, and 2.1.x prior to 2.1.4 contains an authorization enforcement vulnerability. A member of any org is able to create invitations to any org for which the org GUID can be discovered. Accepting this invitation gives unauthorized access to view the member list, domains, quotas and other information about the org.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1278|2024-08-05T03:59:37.602Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15759|2024-08-05T10:01:54.572Z -- pivotal -- on%20demand%20services%20sdk
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15759</link>
      <description>Pivotal Cloud Foundry On Demand Services SDK, versions prior to 0.24 contain an insecure method of verifying credentials. A remote unauthenticated malicious user may make many requests to the service broker with different credentials, allowing them to infer valid credentials and gain access to perform broker operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15759|2024-08-05T10:01:54.572Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1258|2024-08-05T03:51:49.125Z -- pivotal -- spring%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1258</link>
      <description>Spring Framework version 5.0.5 when used in combination with any versions of Spring Security contains an authorization bypass when using method security. An unauthorized malicious user can gain unauthorized access to methods that should be restricted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1258|2024-08-05T03:51:49.125Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11049|2024-08-05T07:54:36.550Z -- pivotal -- pivotal%20operations%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11049</link>
      <description>RSA Identity Governance and Lifecycle, RSA Via Lifecycle and Governance, and RSA IMG releases have an uncontrolled search vulnerability. The installation scripts set an environment variable in an unintended manner. A local authenticated malicious user could trick the root user to run malicious code on the targeted system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11049|2024-08-05T07:54:36.550Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11086|2024-08-05T07:54:36.637Z -- pivotal -- application%20service
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11086</link>
      <description>Pivotal Usage Service in Pivotal Application Service, versions 2.0 prior to 2.0.21 and 2.1 prior to 2.1.13 and 2.2 prior to 2.2.5, contains a bug which may allow escalation of privileges. A space developer with access to the system org may be able to access an artifact which contains the CF admin credential, allowing them to escalate to an admin role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11086|2024-08-05T07:54:36.637Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11087|2024-08-05T07:54:36.646Z -- pivotal -- spring%20amqp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11087</link>
      <description>Pivotal Spring AMQP, 1.x versions prior to 1.7.10 and 2.x versions prior to 2.0.6, expose a man-in-the-middle vulnerability due to lack of hostname validation. A malicious user that has the ability to intercept traffic would be able to view data in transit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11087|2024-08-05T07:54:36.646Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1279|2024-08-05T03:59:37.260Z -- pivotal -- rabbitmq%20for%20pcf
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1279</link>
      <description>Pivotal RabbitMQ for PCF, all versions, uses a deterministically generated cookie that is shared between all machines when configured in a multi-tenant cluster. A remote attacker who can gain information about the network topology can guess this cookie and, if they have access to the right ports on any server in the MQ cluster can use this cookie to gain full control over the entire cluster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1279|2024-08-05T03:59:37.260Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15798|2024-08-05T10:01:54.676Z -- pivotal -- concourse
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15798</link>
      <description>Pivotal Concourse Release, versions 4.x prior to 4.2.2, login flow allows redirects to untrusted websites. A remote unauthenticated attacker could convince a user to click on a link using the oAuth redirect link with an untrusted website and gain access to that user's access token in Concourse.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15798|2024-08-05T10:01:54.676Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11046|2024-08-05T07:54:36.558Z -- pivotal -- operations%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11046</link>
      <description>Pivotal Operations Manager, versions 2.1.x prior to 2.1.6 and version 2.0.14, includes NGINX packages that lacks security vulnerability patches. An attacker with access to the NGINX processes and knowledge of how to exploit the unpatched vulnerabilities may be able to impact Operations Manager</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11046|2024-08-05T07:54:36.558Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15763|2024-08-05T10:01:54.533Z -- pivotal -- pivotal%20container%20service
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15763</link>
      <description>Pivotal Container Service, versions prior to 1.2.0, contains an information disclosure vulnerability which exposes IaaS credentials to application logs. A malicious user with access to application logs may be able to obtain IaaS credentials and perform actions using these credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15763|2024-08-05T10:01:54.533Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1257|2024-08-05T03:51:49.126Z -- pivotal -- spring%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1257</link>
      <description>Spring Framework, versions 5.0.x prior to 5.0.6, versions 4.3.x prior to 4.3.17, and older unsupported versions allows applications to expose STOMP over WebSocket endpoints with a simple, in-memory STOMP broker through the spring-messaging module. A malicious user (or attacker) can craft a message to the broker that can lead to a regular expression, denial of service attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1257|2024-08-05T03:51:49.126Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15756|2024-08-05T10:01:54.549Z -- pivotal -- spring%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15756</link>
      <description>Spring Framework, version 5.1, versions 5.0.x prior to 5.0.10, versions 4.3.x prior to 4.3.20, and older unsupported versions on the 4.2.x branch provide support for range requests when serving static resources through the ResourceHttpRequestHandler, or starting in 5.0 when an annotated controller returns an org.springframework.core.io.Resource. A malicious user (or attacker) can add a range header with a high number of ranges, or with wide ranges that overlap, or both, for a denial of service attack. This vulnerability affects applications that depend on either spring-webmvc or spring-webflux. Such applications must also have a registration for serving static resources (e.g. JS, CSS, images, and others), or have an annotated controller that returns an org.springframework.core.io.Resource. Spring Boot applications that depend on spring-boot-starter-web or spring-boot-starter-webflux are ready to serve static resources out of the box and are therefore vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15756|2024-08-05T10:01:54.549Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11044|2024-08-05T07:54:36.532Z -- pivotal -- pivotal%20application%20service
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11044</link>
      <description>Pivotal Apps Manager included in Pivotal Application Service, versions 2.2.x prior to 2.2.1 and 2.1.x prior to 2.1.8 and 2.0.x prior to 2.0.17 and 1.12.x prior to 1.12.26, does not escape all user-provided content when sending invitation emails. A malicious authenticated user can inject content into an invite to another user, exploiting the trust implied by the source of the email.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11044|2024-08-05T07:54:36.532Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1280|2024-08-05T03:59:37.283Z -- pivotal -- greenplum%20command%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1280</link>
      <description>Pivotal Greenplum Command Center versions 2.x prior to 2.5.1 contains a blind SQL injection vulnerability. An unauthenticated user can perform a SQL injection in the command center which results in disclosure of database contents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1280|2024-08-05T03:59:37.283Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1256|2024-08-05T03:51:49.033Z -- pivotal -- spring%20cloud%20sso%20connector
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1256</link>
      <description>Spring Cloud SSO Connector, version 2.1.2, contains a regression which disables issuer validation in resource servers that are not bound to the SSO service. In PCF deployments with multiple SSO service plans, a remote attacker can authenticate to unbound resource servers which use this version of the SSO Connector with tokens generated from another service plan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1256|2024-08-05T03:51:49.033Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1198|2024-08-05T03:51:49.023Z -- pivotal -- cloud%20cache
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1198</link>
      <description>Pivotal Cloud Cache, versions prior to 1.3.1, prints a superuser password in plain text during BOSH deployment logs. A malicious user with access to the logs could escalate their privileges using this password.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1198|2024-08-05T03:51:49.023Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1259|2024-08-05T03:51:48.968Z -- pivotal -- spring%20data%20commons
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1259</link>
      <description>Spring Data Commons, versions 1.13 prior to 1.13.12 and 2.0 prior to 2.0.7, used in combination with XMLBeam 1.4.14 or earlier versions, contains a property binder vulnerability caused by improper restriction of XML external entity references as underlying library XMLBeam does not restrict external reference expansion. An unauthenticated remote malicious user can supply specially crafted request parameters against Spring Data's projection-based request payload binding to access arbitrary files on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1259|2024-08-05T03:51:48.968Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
