<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Pivotal -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/pivotal/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Pivotal -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 06:24:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1263|2024-08-05T03:51:49.195Z -- pivotal -- spring%20integration%20zip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1263</link>
      <description>Addresses partial fix in CVE-2018-1261. Pivotal spring-integration-zip, versions prior to 1.0.2, exposes an arbitrary file write vulnerability, that can be achieved using a specially crafted zip archive (affects other archives as well, bzip2, tar, xz, war, cpio, 7z), that holds path traversal filenames. So when the filename gets concatenated to the target extraction directory, the final path ends up outside of the target folder.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1263|2024-08-05T03:51:49.195Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1261|2024-08-05T03:51:48.973Z -- pivotal -- spring%20integration%20zip
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1261</link>
      <description>Spring-integration-zip versions prior to 1.0.1 exposes an arbitrary file write vulnerability, which can be achieved using a specially crafted zip archive (affects other archives as well, bzip2, tar, xz, war, cpio, 7z) that holds path traversal filenames. So when the filename gets concatenated to the target extraction directory, the final path ends up outside of the target folder.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1261|2024-08-05T03:51:48.973Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1260|2024-08-05T03:51:48.982Z -- pivotal -- spring%20security%20oauth
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1260</link>
      <description>Spring Security OAuth, versions 2.3 prior to 2.3.3, 2.2 prior to 2.2.2, 2.1 prior to 2.1.2, 2.0 prior to 2.0.15 and older unsupported versions contains a remote code execution vulnerability. A malicious user or attacker can craft an authorization request to the authorization endpoint that can lead to remote code execution when the resource owner is forwarded to the approval endpoint.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1260|2024-08-05T03:51:48.982Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1278|2024-08-05T03:59:37.602Z -- pivotal -- pivotal%20application%20service
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1278</link>
      <description>Apps Manager included in Pivotal Application Service, versions 1.12.x prior to 1.12.22, 2.0.x prior to 2.0.13, and 2.1.x prior to 2.1.4 contains an authorization enforcement vulnerability. A member of any org is able to create invitations to any org for which the org GUID can be discovered. Accepting this invitation gives unauthorized access to view the member list, domains, quotas and other information about the org.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1278|2024-08-05T03:59:37.602Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1258|2024-08-05T03:51:49.125Z -- pivotal -- spring%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1258</link>
      <description>Spring Framework version 5.0.5 when used in combination with any versions of Spring Security contains an authorization bypass when using method security. An unauthorized malicious user can gain unauthorized access to methods that should be restricted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1258|2024-08-05T03:51:49.125Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1279|2024-08-05T03:59:37.260Z -- pivotal -- rabbitmq%20for%20pcf
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1279</link>
      <description>Pivotal RabbitMQ for PCF, all versions, uses a deterministically generated cookie that is shared between all machines when configured in a multi-tenant cluster. A remote attacker who can gain information about the network topology can guess this cookie and, if they have access to the right ports on any server in the MQ cluster can use this cookie to gain full control over the entire cluster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1279|2024-08-05T03:59:37.260Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1257|2024-08-05T03:51:49.126Z -- pivotal -- spring%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1257</link>
      <description>Spring Framework, versions 5.0.x prior to 5.0.6, versions 4.3.x prior to 4.3.17, and older unsupported versions allows applications to expose STOMP over WebSocket endpoints with a simple, in-memory STOMP broker through the spring-messaging module. A malicious user (or attacker) can craft a message to the broker that can lead to a regular expression, denial of service attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1257|2024-08-05T03:51:49.126Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1280|2024-08-05T03:59:37.283Z -- pivotal -- greenplum%20command%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1280</link>
      <description>Pivotal Greenplum Command Center versions 2.x prior to 2.5.1 contains a blind SQL injection vulnerability. An unauthenticated user can perform a SQL injection in the command center which results in disclosure of database contents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1280|2024-08-05T03:59:37.283Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1256|2024-08-05T03:51:49.033Z -- pivotal -- spring%20cloud%20sso%20connector
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1256</link>
      <description>Spring Cloud SSO Connector, version 2.1.2, contains a regression which disables issuer validation in resource servers that are not bound to the SSO service. In PCF deployments with multiple SSO service plans, a remote attacker can authenticate to unbound resource servers which use this version of the SSO Connector with tokens generated from another service plan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1256|2024-08-05T03:51:49.033Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1198|2024-08-05T03:51:49.023Z -- pivotal -- cloud%20cache
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1198</link>
      <description>Pivotal Cloud Cache, versions prior to 1.3.1, prints a superuser password in plain text during BOSH deployment logs. A malicious user with access to the logs could escalate their privileges using this password.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1198|2024-08-05T03:51:49.023Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1259|2024-08-05T03:51:48.968Z -- pivotal -- spring%20data%20commons
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1259</link>
      <description>Spring Data Commons, versions 1.13 prior to 1.13.12 and 2.0 prior to 2.0.7, used in combination with XMLBeam 1.4.14 or earlier versions, contains a property binder vulnerability caused by improper restriction of XML external entity references as underlying library XMLBeam does not restrict external reference expansion. An unauthenticated remote malicious user can supply specially crafted request parameters against Spring Data's projection-based request payload binding to access arbitrary files on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1259|2024-08-05T03:51:48.968Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
