<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Pivotal -- Cloud Foundry</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/pivotal/cloud%20foundry.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Pivotal -- Cloud Foundry</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:21:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2015-3190|2024-08-06T05:39:31.774Z -- pivotal -- cloud%20foundry
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-3190</link>
      <description>With Cloud Foundry Runtime cf-release versions v209 or earlier, UAA Standalone versions 2.2.6 or earlier and Pivotal Cloud Foundry Runtime 1.4.5 or earlier the UAA logout link is susceptible to an open redirect which allows an attacker to insert malicious web page as a redirect parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2015-3190|2024-08-06T05:39:31.774Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-4435|2024-08-06T00:32:24.614Z -- pivotal -- cloud%20foundry
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-4435</link>
      <description>An endpoint of the Agent running on the BOSH Director VM with stemcell versions prior to 3232.6 and 3146.13 may allow unauthenticated clients to read or write blobs or cause a denial of service attack on the Director VM. This vulnerability requires that the unauthenticated clients guess or find a URL matching an existing GUID.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-4435|2024-08-06T00:32:24.614Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2015-3191|2024-08-06T05:39:31.578Z -- pivotal -- cloud%20foundry
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-3191</link>
      <description>With Cloud Foundry Runtime cf-release versions v209 or earlier, UAA Standalone versions 2.2.6 or earlier and Pivotal Cloud Foundry Runtime 1.4.5 or earlier the change_email form in UAA is vulnerable to a CSRF attack. This allows an attacker to trigger an e-mail change for a user logged into a cloud foundry instance via a malicious link on a attacker controlled site. This vulnerability is applicable only when using the UAA internal user store for authentication. Deployments enabled for integration via SAML or LDAP are not affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2015-3191|2024-08-06T05:39:31.578Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2015-1834|2024-08-06T04:54:16.330Z -- pivotal -- cloud%20foundry
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-1834</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability was identified in the Cloud Foundry component Cloud Controller that affects cf-release versions prior to v208 and Pivotal Cloud Foundry Elastic Runtime versions prior to 1.4.2. Path traversal is the 'outbreak' of a given directory structure through relative file paths in the user input. It aims at accessing files and directories that are stored outside the web root folder, for disallowed reading or even executing arbitrary system commands. An attacker could use a certain parameter of the file path for instance to inject '../' sequences in order to navigate through the file system. In this particular case a remote authenticated attacker can exploit the identified vulnerability in order to upload arbitrary files to the server running a Cloud Controller instance - outside the isolated application container.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2015-1834|2024-08-06T04:54:16.330Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2015-3189|2024-08-06T05:39:32.005Z -- pivotal -- cloud%20foundry
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-3189</link>
      <description>With Cloud Foundry Runtime cf-release versions v208 or earlier, UAA Standalone versions 2.2.5 or earlier and Pivotal Cloud Foundry Runtime 1.4.5 or earlier, old Password Reset Links are not expired after the user changes their current email address to a new one. This vulnerability is applicable only when using the UAA internal user store for authentication. Deployments enabled for integration via SAML or LDAP are not affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2015-3189|2024-08-06T05:39:32.005Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
