<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for McAfee LLC -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/mcafee%20llc/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for McAfee LLC -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 20:23:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7276|2024-09-17T01:01:18.516Z -- mcafee%20llc -- mcafee%20endpoint%20security%20%28ens%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7276</link>
      <description>Authentication bypass vulnerability in MfeUpgradeTool in McAfee Endpoint Security (ENS) for Windows prior to 10.7.0 April 2020 Update allows administrator users to access policy settings via running this tool.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7276|2024-09-17T01:01:18.516Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 11:20:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23883|2024-09-17T01:41:53.554Z -- mcafee%20llc -- endpoint%20security%20%28ens%29%20for%20windows
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23883</link>
      <description>A Null Pointer Dereference vulnerability in McAfee Endpoint Security (ENS) for Windows prior to 10.7.0 February 2021 Update allows a local administrator to cause Windows to crash via a specific system call which is not handled correctly. This varies by machine and had partial protection prior to this update.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23883|2024-09-17T01:41:53.554Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 09:25:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23881|2024-09-17T01:41:33.007Z -- mcafee%20llc -- endpoint%20security%20%28ens%29%20for%20windows
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23881</link>
      <description>A stored cross site scripting vulnerability in ePO extension of McAfee Endpoint Security (ENS) prior to 10.7.0 February 2021 Update allows an ENS ePO administrator to add a script to a policy event which will trigger the script to be run through a browser block page when a local non-administrator user triggers the policy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23881|2024-09-17T01:41:33.007Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 10:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7312|2024-09-17T02:31:47.777Z -- mcafee%20llc -- ma%20for%20windows
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7312</link>
      <description>DLL Search Order Hijacking Vulnerability in the installer in McAfee Agent (MA) for Windows prior to 5.6.6 allows local users to execute arbitrary code and escalate privileges via execution from a compromised folder.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7312|2024-09-17T02:31:47.777Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 09:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7259|2024-09-17T00:31:04.559Z -- mcafee%20llc -- mcafee%20endpoint%20security%20%28ens%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7259</link>
      <description>Exploitation of Privilege/Trust vulnerability in file in McAfee Endpoint Security (ENS) Prior to 10.7.0 February 2020 Update allows local users to bypass local security protection via a carefully crafted input file</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7259|2024-09-17T00:31:04.559Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 11:55:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7323|2024-09-17T01:26:01.081Z -- mcafee%20llc -- endpoint%20security%20for%20windows
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7323</link>
      <description>Authentication Protection Bypass vulnerability in McAfee Endpoint Security (ENS) for Windows prior to 10.7.0 September 2020 Update allows physical local users to bypass the Windows lock screen via triggering certain detection events while the computer screen is locked and the McTray.exe is running with elevated privileges. This issue is timing dependent and requires physical access to the machine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7323|2024-09-17T01:26:01.081Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 09:35:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7277|2024-09-17T00:05:40.086Z -- mcafee%20llc -- mcafee%20endpoint%20security%20%28ens%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7277</link>
      <description>Protection mechanism failure in all processes in McAfee Endpoint Security (ENS) for Windows prior to 10.7.0 April 2020 Update allows local users to stop certain McAfee ENS processes, reducing the protection offered.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7277|2024-09-17T00:05:40.086Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 11:20:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7275|2024-09-17T00:05:29.685Z -- mcafee%20llc -- mcafee%20endpoint%20security%20%28ens%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7275</link>
      <description>Accessing, modifying or executing executable files vulnerability in the uninstaller in McAfee Endpoint Security (ENS) for Windows Prior to 10.7.0 April 2020 Update allows local users to execute arbitrary code via a carefully crafted input file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7275|2024-09-17T00:05:29.685Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 11:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7314|2024-09-17T00:16:24.860Z -- mcafee%20llc -- mcafee%20dxl%20for%20mac%20shipped%20with%20ma
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7314</link>
      <description>Privilege Escalation Vulnerability in the installer in McAfee Data Exchange Layer (DXL) Client for Mac shipped with McAfee Agent (MA) for Mac prior to MA 5.6.6 allows local users to run commands as root via incorrectly applied permissions on temporary files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7314|2024-09-17T00:16:24.860Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 09:50:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7325|2024-09-17T01:46:26.348Z -- mcafee%20llc -- mvision%20endpoint
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7325</link>
      <description>Privilege Escalation vulnerability in McAfee MVISION Endpoint prior to 20.9 Update allows local users to access files which the user otherwise would not have access to via manipulating symbolic links to redirect McAfee file operations to an unintended file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7325|2024-09-17T01:46:26.348Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 09:45:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7311|2024-09-17T01:31:44.215Z -- mcafee%20llc -- ma%20for%20windows
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7311</link>
      <description>Privilege Escalation vulnerability in the installer in McAfee Agent (MA) for Windows prior to 5.6.6 allows local users to assume SYSTEM rights during the installation of MA via manipulation of log files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7311|2024-09-17T01:31:44.215Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 09:45:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
