<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for McAfee LLC -- Endpoint Security for Windows</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/mcafee%20llc/endpoint%20security%20for%20windows.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for McAfee LLC -- Endpoint Security for Windows</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 14:23:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7320|2024-08-04T09:25:48.971Z -- mcafee%20llc -- endpoint%20security%20for%20windows
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7320</link>
      <description>Protection Mechanism Failure vulnerability in McAfee Endpoint Security (ENS) for Windows prior to 10.7.0 September 2020 Update allows local administrator to temporarily reduce the detection capability allowing otherwise detected malware to run via stopping certain Microsoft services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7320|2024-08-04T09:25:48.971Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7323|2024-08-04T09:25:48.981Z -- mcafee%20llc -- endpoint%20security%20for%20windows
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7323</link>
      <description>Authentication Protection Bypass vulnerability in McAfee Endpoint Security (ENS) for Windows prior to 10.7.0 September 2020 Update allows physical local users to bypass the Windows lock screen via triggering certain detection events while the computer screen is locked and the McTray.exe is running with elevated privileges. This issue is timing dependent and requires physical access to the machine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7323|2024-08-04T09:25:48.981Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7319|2024-08-04T09:25:49.098Z -- mcafee%20llc -- endpoint%20security%20for%20windows
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7319</link>
      <description>Improper Access Control vulnerability in McAfee Endpoint Security (ENS) for Windows prior to 10.7.0 September 2020 Update allows local users to access files which the user otherwise would not have access to via manipulating symbolic links to redirect McAfee file operations to an unintended file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7319|2024-08-04T09:25:49.098Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7322|2024-08-04T09:25:48.949Z -- mcafee%20llc -- endpoint%20security%20for%20windows
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7322</link>
      <description>Information Disclosure Vulnerability in McAfee Endpoint Security (ENS) for Windows prior to 10.7.0 September 2020 Update allows local users to gain access to sensitive information via incorrectly logging of sensitive information in debug logs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7322|2024-08-04T09:25:48.949Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
