<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for McAfee LLC -- McAfee Endpoint Security (ENS)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/mcafee%20llc/mcafee%20endpoint%20security%20%28ens%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for McAfee LLC -- McAfee Endpoint Security (ENS)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 20:22:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7261|2024-08-04T09:25:48.522Z -- mcafee%20llc -- mcafee%20endpoint%20security%20%28ens%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7261</link>
      <description>Buffer Overflow via Environment Variables vulnerability in AMSI component in McAfee Endpoint Security (ENS) Prior to 10.7.0 February 2020 Update allows local users to disable Endpoint Security via a carefully crafted user input.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7261|2024-08-04T09:25:48.522Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7250|2024-08-04T09:25:48.498Z -- mcafee%20llc -- mcafee%20endpoint%20security%20%28ens%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7250</link>
      <description>Symbolic link manipulation vulnerability in McAfee Endpoint Security (ENS) for Windows prior to 10.7.0 February 2020 Update allows authenticated local user to potentially gain an escalation of privileges by pointing the link to files which the user which not normally have permission to alter via carefully creating symbolic links from the ENS log file directory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7250|2024-08-04T09:25:48.498Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7276|2024-08-04T09:25:48.636Z -- mcafee%20llc -- mcafee%20endpoint%20security%20%28ens%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7276</link>
      <description>Authentication bypass vulnerability in MfeUpgradeTool in McAfee Endpoint Security (ENS) for Windows prior to 10.7.0 April 2020 Update allows administrator users to access policy settings via running this tool.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7276|2024-08-04T09:25:48.636Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7259|2024-08-04T09:25:48.575Z -- mcafee%20llc -- mcafee%20endpoint%20security%20%28ens%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7259</link>
      <description>Exploitation of Privilege/Trust vulnerability in file in McAfee Endpoint Security (ENS) Prior to 10.7.0 February 2020 Update allows local users to bypass local security protection via a carefully crafted input file</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7259|2024-08-04T09:25:48.575Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7273|2024-08-04T09:25:48.957Z -- mcafee%20llc -- mcafee%20endpoint%20security%20%28ens%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7273</link>
      <description>Accessing functionality not properly constrained by ACLs vulnerability in the autorun start-up protection in McAfee Endpoint Security (ENS) for Windows Prior to 10.7.0 April 2020 Update allows local users to delete or rename programs in the autorun key via manipulation of some parameters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7273|2024-08-04T09:25:48.957Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7274|2024-08-04T09:25:48.432Z -- mcafee%20llc -- mcafee%20endpoint%20security%20%28ens%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7274</link>
      <description>Privilege escalation vulnerability in McTray.exe in McAfee Endpoint Security (ENS) for Windows Prior to 10.7.0 April 2020 Update allows local users to spawn unrelated processes with elevated privileges via the system administrator granting McTray.exe elevated privileges (by default it runs with the current user's privileges).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7274|2024-08-04T09:25:48.432Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7275|2024-08-04T09:25:48.886Z -- mcafee%20llc -- mcafee%20endpoint%20security%20%28ens%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7275</link>
      <description>Accessing, modifying or executing executable files vulnerability in the uninstaller in McAfee Endpoint Security (ENS) for Windows Prior to 10.7.0 April 2020 Update allows local users to execute arbitrary code via a carefully crafted input file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7275|2024-08-04T09:25:48.886Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7277|2024-08-04T09:25:48.499Z -- mcafee%20llc -- mcafee%20endpoint%20security%20%28ens%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7277</link>
      <description>Protection mechanism failure in all processes in McAfee Endpoint Security (ENS) for Windows prior to 10.7.0 April 2020 Update allows local users to stop certain McAfee ENS processes, reducing the protection offered.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7277|2024-08-04T09:25:48.499Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7278|2024-08-04T09:25:48.499Z -- mcafee%20llc -- mcafee%20endpoint%20security%20%28ens%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7278</link>
      <description>Exploiting incorrectly configured access control security levels vulnerability in ENS Firewall in McAfee Endpoint Security (ENS) for Windows prior to 10.7.0 April 2020 and 10.6.1 April 2020 updates allows remote attackers and local users to allow or block unauthorized traffic via pre-existing rules not being handled correctly when updating to the February 2020 updates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7278|2024-08-04T09:25:48.499Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7255|2024-08-04T09:25:48.605Z -- mcafee%20llc -- mcafee%20endpoint%20security%20%28ens%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7255</link>
      <description>Privilege escalation vulnerability in the administrative user interface in McAfee Endpoint Security (ENS) for Windows prior to 10.7.0 February 2020 Update allows local users to gain elevated privileges via ENS not checking user permissions when editing configuration in the ENS client interface. Administrators can lock the ENS client interface through ePO to prevent users being able to edit the configuration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7255|2024-08-04T09:25:48.605Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7257|2024-08-04T09:25:48.988Z -- mcafee%20llc -- mcafee%20endpoint%20security%20%28ens%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7257</link>
      <description>Privilege escalation vulnerability in McAfee Endpoint Security (ENS) for Windows prior to 10.7.0 February 2020 Update allows local users to cause the deletion and creation of files they would not normally have permission to through altering the target of symbolic links whilst an anti-virus scan was in progress. This is timing dependent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7257|2024-08-04T09:25:48.988Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
