<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for PaulPrinting -- CMS</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/paulprinting/cms.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for PaulPrinting -- CMS</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3785|2023-10-23T17:41:17.463Z -- paulprinting -- cms
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3785</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PaulPrinting CMS 2018. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality. The manipulation of the argument firstname/lastname/address/city/state leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-235052.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in PaulPrinting CMS 2018 ausgemacht. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil. Durch Manipulation des Arguments firstname/lastname/address/city/state mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3785|2023-10-23T17:41:17.463Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 10:34:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3789|2023-10-23T17:46:10.136Z -- paulprinting -- cms
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3789</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in PaulPrinting CMS 2018. Affected is an unknown function of the file /account/delivery of the component Search. The manipulation of the argument s leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-235056.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in PaulPrinting CMS 2018 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei /account/delivery der Komponente Search. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments s mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3789|2023-10-23T17:46:10.136Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 16:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
