<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for containerd -- containerd</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/containerd/containerd.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for containerd -- containerd</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 04:24:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41103|2024-08-04T02:59:31.538Z -- containerd -- containerd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41103</link>
      <description>containerd is an open source container runtime with an emphasis on simplicity, robustness and portability. A bug was found in containerd where container root directories and some plugins had insufficiently restricted permissions, allowing otherwise unprivileged Linux users to traverse directory contents and execute programs. When containers included executable programs with extended permission bits (such as setuid), unprivileged Linux users could discover and execute those programs. When the UID of an unprivileged Linux user on the host collided with the file owner or group inside a container, the unprivileged Linux user on the host could discover, read, and modify those files. This vulnerability has been fixed in containerd 1.4.11 and containerd 1.5.7. Users should update to these version when they are released and may restart containers or update directory permissions to mitigate the vulnerability. Users unable to update should limit access to the host to trusted users. Update directory permission on container bundles directories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41103|2024-08-04T02:59:31.538Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43816|2024-08-04T04:03:08.904Z -- containerd -- containerd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43816</link>
      <description>containerd is an open source container runtime. On installations using SELinux, such as EL8 (CentOS, RHEL), Fedora, or SUSE MicroOS, with containerd since v1.5.0-beta.0 as the backing container runtime interface (CRI), an unprivileged pod scheduled to the node may bind mount, via hostPath volume, any privileged, regular file on disk for complete read/write access (sans delete). Such is achieved by placing the in-container location of the hostPath volume mount at either `/etc/hosts`, `/etc/hostname`, or `/etc/resolv.conf`. These locations are being relabeled indiscriminately to match the container process-label which effectively elevates permissions for savvy containers that would not normally be able to access privileged host files. This issue has been resolved in version 1.5.9. Users are advised to upgrade as soon as possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43816|2024-08-04T04:03:08.904Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 18:55:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
