<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Tenda -- AC10U</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tenda/ac10u.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Tenda -- AC10U</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0930|2024-01-26T16:00:07.582Z -- tenda -- ac10u
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0930</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49_multi_TDE01. This affects the function fromSetWirelessRepeat. The manipulation of the argument wpapsk_crypto leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252135. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49_multi_TDE01 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es betrifft die Funktion fromSetWirelessRepeat. Durch Manipulation des Arguments wpapsk_crypto mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0930|2024-01-26T16:00:07.582Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 16:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0926|2024-01-26T15:00:06.338Z -- tenda -- ac10u
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0926</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49_multi_TDE01 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function formWifiWpsOOB. The manipulation of the argument index leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252131. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49_multi_TDE01 gefunden. Es geht hierbei um die Funktion formWifiWpsOOB. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments index mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0926|2024-01-26T15:00:06.338Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 15:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0927|2024-01-26T15:00:07.625Z -- tenda -- ac10u
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0927</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49_multi_TDE01. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function fromAddressNat. The manipulation of the argument entrys/mitInterface/page leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252132. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49_multi_TDE01 ausgemacht. Es geht dabei um die Funktion fromAddressNat. Dank Manipulation des Arguments entrys/mitInterface/page mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0927|2024-01-26T15:00:07.625Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 15:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0931|2024-01-26T16:31:03.937Z -- tenda -- ac10u
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0931</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49_multi_TDE01. This vulnerability affects the function saveParentControlInfo. The manipulation of the argument deviceId/time/urls leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252136. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49_multi_TDE01 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Das betrifft die Funktion saveParentControlInfo. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments deviceId/time/urls mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0931|2024-01-26T16:31:03.937Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 16:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0924|2024-01-26T14:31:04.491Z -- tenda -- ac10u
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0924</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49_multi_TDE01. This affects the function formSetPPTPServer. The manipulation of the argument startIp leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252129 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49_multi_TDE01 gefunden. Betroffen hiervon ist die Funktion formSetPPTPServer. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments startIp mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0924|2024-01-26T14:31:04.491Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 14:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0932|2024-01-26T16:31:04.983Z -- tenda -- ac10u
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0932</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49_multi_TDE01. This issue affects the function setSmartPowerManagement. The manipulation of the argument time leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252137 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49_multi_TDE01 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft die Funktion setSmartPowerManagement. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments time mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0932|2024-01-26T16:31:04.983Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 16:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0928|2024-01-26T15:31:03.551Z -- tenda -- ac10u
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0928</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49_multi_TDE01. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function fromDhcpListClient. The manipulation of the argument page/listN leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252133 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49_multi_TDE01 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Dabei geht es um die Funktion fromDhcpListClient. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments page/listN mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0928|2024-01-26T15:31:03.551Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 15:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0929|2024-01-26T16:00:06.481Z -- tenda -- ac10u
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0929</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49_multi_TDE01. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function fromNatStaticSetting. The manipulation of the argument page leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252134 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49_multi_TDE01 ausgemacht. Hierbei geht es um die Funktion fromNatStaticSetting. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments page mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0929|2024-01-26T16:00:06.481Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 16:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0925|2024-01-26T14:31:05.583Z -- tenda -- ac10u
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0925</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49_multi_TDE01 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function formSetVirtualSer. The manipulation of the argument list leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252130 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49_multi_TDE01 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle gefunden. Es geht um die Funktion formSetVirtualSer. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments list mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0925|2024-01-26T14:31:05.583Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 14:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0922|2024-01-26T13:31:05.291Z -- tenda -- ac10u
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0922</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49_multi_TDE01. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formQuickIndex. The manipulation of the argument PPPOEPassword leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252127. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49_multi_TDE01 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Betroffen ist die Funktion formQuickIndex. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments PPPOEPassword mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0922|2024-01-26T13:31:05.291Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 13:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0923|2024-01-26T14:00:06.385Z -- tenda -- ac10u
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0923</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49_multi_TDE01. Affected by this issue is the function formSetDeviceName. The manipulation of the argument devName leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252128. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49_multi_TDE01 entdeckt. Betroffen davon ist die Funktion formSetDeviceName. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments devName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0923|2024-01-26T14:00:06.385Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 14:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2710|2024-03-20T18:00:07.175Z -- tenda -- ac10u
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2710</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setSchedWifi of the file /goform/openSchedWifi. The manipulation of the argument schedStartTime leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257461 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Das betrifft die Funktion setSchedWifi der Datei /goform/openSchedWifi. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments schedStartTime mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2710|2024-03-20T18:00:07.175Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 18:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2706|2024-03-20T16:31:05.842Z -- tenda -- ac10u
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2706</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49. This affects the function formWifiWpsStart of the file /goform/WifiWpsStart. The manipulation of the argument index leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257457 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49 gefunden. Es geht dabei um die Funktion formWifiWpsStart der Datei /goform/WifiWpsStart. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments index mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2706|2024-03-20T16:31:05.842Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 16:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2707|2024-03-20T17:00:07.795Z -- tenda -- ac10u
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2707</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function formWriteFacMac of the file /goform/WriteFacMac. The manipulation of the argument mac leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-257458 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle gefunden. Dabei geht es um die Funktion formWriteFacMac der Datei /goform/WriteFacMac. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments mac mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2707|2024-03-20T17:00:07.795Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 17:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2711|2024-03-20T18:00:08.616Z -- tenda -- ac10u
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2711</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.48. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function addWifiMacFilter of the file /goform/addWifiMacFilter. The manipulation of the argument deviceMac leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-257462 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.48 ausgemacht. Dies betrifft die Funktion addWifiMacFilter der Datei /goform/addWifiMacFilter. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments deviceMac mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2711|2024-03-20T18:00:08.616Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 18:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2853|2024-03-24T05:00:06.892Z -- tenda -- ac10u
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2853</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.48/15.03.06.49. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function formSetSambaConf of the file /goform/setsambacfg. The manipulation of the argument usbName leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257777 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.48/15.03.06.49 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft die Funktion formSetSambaConf der Datei /goform/setsambacfg. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments usbName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2853|2024-03-24T05:00:06.892Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 05:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2763|2024-03-21T20:31:03.792Z -- tenda -- ac10u
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2763</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.48. Affected by this issue is the function formSetCfm of the file goform/setcfm. The manipulation of the argument funcpara1 leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257600. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.48 entdeckt. Davon betroffen ist die Funktion formSetCfm der Datei goform/setcfm. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments funcpara1 mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2763|2024-03-21T20:31:03.792Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 20:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2703|2024-03-20T16:00:06.080Z -- tenda -- ac10u
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2703</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49. Affected is the function formSetDeviceName of the file /goform/SetOnlineDevName. The manipulation of the argument mac leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-257454 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49 entdeckt. Betroffen hiervon ist die Funktion formSetDeviceName der Datei /goform/SetOnlineDevName. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments mac mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2703|2024-03-20T16:00:06.080Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 16:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2704|2024-03-20T16:00:07.684Z -- tenda -- ac10u
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2704</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formSetFirewallCfg of the file /goform/SetFirewallCfg. The manipulation of the argument firewallEn leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257455. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Es geht um die Funktion formSetFirewallCfg der Datei /goform/SetFirewallCfg. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments firewallEn mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2704|2024-03-20T16:00:07.684Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 16:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2708|2024-03-20T17:31:04.520Z -- tenda -- ac10u
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2708</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function formexeCommand of the file /goform/execCommand. The manipulation of the argument cmdinput leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257459. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49 gefunden. Hierbei geht es um die Funktion formexeCommand der Datei /goform/execCommand. Durch Manipulation des Arguments cmdinput mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2708|2024-03-20T17:31:04.520Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 17:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2709|2024-03-20T17:31:05.924Z -- tenda -- ac10u
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2709</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function fromSetRouteStatic of the file /goform/SetStaticRouteCfg. The manipulation of the argument list leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257460. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.49 ausgemacht. Es betrifft die Funktion fromSetRouteStatic der Datei /goform/SetStaticRouteCfg. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments list mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2709|2024-03-20T17:31:05.924Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 17:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2764|2024-03-21T20:31:05.130Z -- tenda -- ac10u
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2764</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.48. This affects the function formSetPPTPServer of the file /goform/SetPptpServerCfg. The manipulation of the argument endIP leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257601 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Tenda AC10U 15.03.06.48 gefunden. Hiervon betroffen ist die Funktion formSetPPTPServer der Datei /goform/SetPptpServerCfg. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments endIP mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2764|2024-03-21T20:31:05.130Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 20:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2705|2024-03-20T16:31:04.186Z -- tenda -- ac10u
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2705</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tenda AC10U 1.0/15.03.06.49. Affected by this issue is the function formSetQosBand of the file /goform/SetNetControlList. The manipulation of the argument list leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257456. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Tenda AC10U 1.0/15.03.06.49 entdeckt. Es geht hierbei um die Funktion formSetQosBand der Datei /goform/SetNetControlList. Dank Manipulation des Arguments list mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2705|2024-03-20T16:31:04.186Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 16:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
