<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for Tenda -- AC18</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tenda/ac18.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for Tenda -- AC18</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 22:02:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-2546|2024-03-17T01:31:04.350Z -- Tenda -- AC18
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2546</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda AC18 15.13.07.09 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function fromSetWirelessRepeat. The manipulation of the argument wpapsk_crypto5g leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256999. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Tenda AC18 15.13.07.09 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es die Funktion fromSetWirelessRepeat. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments wpapsk_crypto5g mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2546|2024-03-17T01:31:04.350Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 01:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2854|2024-03-24T05:31:04.168Z -- Tenda -- AC18
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2854</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05. Affected is the function formSetSambaConf of the file /goform/setsambacfg. The manipulation of the argument usbName leads to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-257778 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05 entdeckt. Dabei betrifft es die Funktion formSetSambaConf der Datei /goform/setsambacfg. Durch Manipulation des Arguments usbName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2854|2024-03-24T05:31:04.168Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 05:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2547|2024-03-17T03:31:03.829Z -- Tenda -- AC18
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2547</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function R7WebsSecurityHandler. The manipulation of the argument password leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257000. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist die Funktion R7WebsSecurityHandler. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2547|2024-03-17T03:31:03.829Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 03:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2560|2024-03-17T10:31:04.158Z -- Tenda -- AC18
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2560</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05. Affected by this vulnerability is the function fromSysToolRestoreSet of the file /goform/SysToolRestoreSet. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257059. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Hierbei betrifft es die Funktion fromSysToolRestoreSet der Datei /goform/SysToolRestoreSet. Dank der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross-site request forgery-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2560|2024-03-17T10:31:04.158Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 10:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2487|2024-03-15T08:31:04.506Z -- Tenda -- AC18
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2487</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function formSetDeviceName of the file /goform/SetOnlineDevName. The manipulation of the argument devName/mac leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256894 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es die Funktion formSetDeviceName der Datei /goform/SetOnlineDevName. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments devName/mac mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2487|2024-03-15T08:31:04.506Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 08:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2490|2024-03-15T09:31:04.121Z -- Tenda -- AC18
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2490</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setSchedWifi of the file /goform/openSchedWifi. The manipulation of the argument schedStartTime/schedEndTime leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256897 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Betroffen ist die Funktion setSchedWifi der Datei /goform/openSchedWifi. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments schedStartTime/schedEndTime mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2490|2024-03-15T09:31:04.121Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 09:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2486|2024-03-15T08:00:06.524Z -- Tenda -- AC18
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2486</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function formQuickIndex of the file /goform/QuickIndex. The manipulation of the argument PPPOEPassword leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256893 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es die Funktion formQuickIndex der Datei /goform/QuickIndex. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments PPPOEPassword mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2486|2024-03-15T08:00:06.524Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 08:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2558|2024-03-17T09:00:07.516Z -- Tenda -- AC18
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2558</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function formexeCommand of the file /goform/execCommand. The manipulation of the argument cmdinput leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257057 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft die Funktion formexeCommand der Datei /goform/execCommand. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments cmdinput mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2558|2024-03-17T09:00:07.516Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 09:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2489|2024-03-15T09:00:10.441Z -- Tenda -- AC18
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2489</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05. Affected is the function formSetQosBand of the file /goform/SetNetControlList. The manipulation of the argument list leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256896. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05 entdeckt. Hiervon betroffen ist die Funktion formSetQosBand der Datei /goform/SetNetControlList. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments list mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2489|2024-03-15T09:00:10.441Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 09:00:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2485|2024-03-15T07:00:08.196Z -- Tenda -- AC18
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2485</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function formSetSpeedWan of the file /goform/SetSpeedWan. The manipulation of the argument speed_dir leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256892. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft die Funktion formSetSpeedWan der Datei /goform/SetSpeedWan. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments speed_dir mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2485|2024-03-15T07:00:08.196Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 07:00:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2488|2024-03-15T09:00:08.823Z -- Tenda -- AC18
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2488</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function formSetPPTPServer of the file /goform/SetPptpServerCfg. The manipulation of the argument startIP leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256895. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist die Funktion formSetPPTPServer der Datei /goform/SetPptpServerCfg. Dank Manipulation des Arguments startIP mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2488|2024-03-15T09:00:08.823Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 09:00:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2559|2024-03-17T09:31:04.514Z -- Tenda -- AC18
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2559</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05. Affected is the function fromSysToolReboot of the file /goform/SysToolReboot. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-257058 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05 entdeckt. Dabei betrifft es die Funktion fromSysToolReboot der Datei /goform/SysToolReboot. Durch Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross-site request forgery-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2559|2024-03-17T09:31:04.514Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 09:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>