<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for Tenda -- F1202</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tenda/f1202.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for Tenda -- F1202</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 16:28:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-3875|2024-04-16T18:00:05.455Z -- Tenda -- F1202
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3875</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda F1202 1.2.0.20(408). It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function fromNatlimit of the file /goform/Natlimit. The manipulation of the argument page leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-260909 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Tenda F1202 1.2.0.20(408) ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei geht es um die Funktion fromNatlimit der Datei /goform/Natlimit. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments page mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3875|2024-04-16T18:00:05.455Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 18:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3878|2024-04-16T18:31:05.460Z -- Tenda -- F1202
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3878</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tenda F1202 1.2.0.20(408). Affected by this issue is the function fromwebExcptypemanFilter of the file /goform/webExcptypemanFilter. The manipulation of the argument page leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-260912. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Tenda F1202 1.2.0.20(408) entdeckt. Dies betrifft die Funktion fromwebExcptypemanFilter der Datei /goform/webExcptypemanFilter. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments page mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3878|2024-04-16T18:31:05.460Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 18:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3877|2024-04-16T18:31:04.090Z -- Tenda -- F1202
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3877</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tenda F1202 1.2.0.20(408). Affected by this vulnerability is the function fromqossetting of the file /goform/fromqossetting. The manipulation of the argument qos leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-260911. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Tenda F1202 1.2.0.20(408) wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Das betrifft die Funktion fromqossetting der Datei /goform/fromqossetting. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments qos mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3877|2024-04-16T18:31:04.090Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 18:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3876|2024-04-16T18:00:07.035Z -- Tenda -- F1202
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3876</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tenda F1202 1.2.0.20(408). Affected is the function fromVirtualSer of the file /goform/VirtualSer. The manipulation of the argument page leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-260910 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Tenda F1202 1.2.0.20(408) entdeckt. Es betrifft die Funktion fromVirtualSer der Datei /goform/VirtualSer. Dank Manipulation des Arguments page mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3876|2024-04-16T18:00:07.035Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 18:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>