<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Tenda -- FH1205</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tenda/fh1205.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Tenda -- FH1205</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3009|2024-03-27T23:31:03.733Z -- tenda -- fh1205
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3009</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda FH1205 2.0.0.7(775) and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formWriteFacMac of the file /goform/WriteFacMac. The manipulation of the argument mac leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-258295. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Tenda FH1205 2.0.0.7(775) wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht um die Funktion formWriteFacMac der Datei /goform/WriteFacMac. Durch Manipulation des Arguments mac mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3009|2024-03-27T23:31:03.733Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 23:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3008|2024-03-27T23:00:06.978Z -- tenda -- fh1205
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3008</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tenda FH1205 2.0.0.7(775). Affected is the function formexeCommand of the file /goform/execCommand. The manipulation of the argument cmdinput leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-258294 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Tenda FH1205 2.0.0.7(775) gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist die Funktion formexeCommand der Datei /goform/execCommand. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments cmdinput mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3008|2024-03-27T23:00:06.978Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 23:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3012|2024-03-28T00:00:06.995Z -- tenda -- fh1205
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3012</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda FH1205 2.0.0.7(775). It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function GetParentControlInfo of the file /goform/GetParentControlInfo. The manipulation of the argument mac leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-258298 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Tenda FH1205 2.0.0.7(775) wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei geht es um die Funktion GetParentControlInfo der Datei /goform/GetParentControlInfo. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments mac mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3012|2024-03-28T00:00:06.995Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 00:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3007|2024-03-27T23:00:05.599Z -- tenda -- fh1205
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3007</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tenda FH1205 2.0.0.7(775). This issue affects the function fromNatStaticSetting of the file /goform/NatStaticSetting. The manipulation of the argument page leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-258293 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Tenda FH1205 2.0.0.7(775) entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist die Funktion fromNatStaticSetting der Datei /goform/NatStaticSetting. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments page mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3007|2024-03-27T23:00:05.599Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 23:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3011|2024-03-28T00:00:05.446Z -- tenda -- fh1205
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3011</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda FH1205 2.0.0.7(775). It has been classified as critical. This affects the function formQuickIndex of the file /goform/QuickIndex. The manipulation of the argument PPPOEPassword leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-258297 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Tenda FH1205 2.0.0.7(775) ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um die Funktion formQuickIndex der Datei /goform/QuickIndex. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments PPPOEPassword mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3011|2024-03-28T00:00:05.446Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 00:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3010|2024-03-27T23:31:05.075Z -- tenda -- fh1205
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3010</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda FH1205 2.0.0.7(775) and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function formSetCfm of the file /goform/setcfm. The manipulation of the argument funcpara1 leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-258296. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Tenda FH1205 2.0.0.7(775) gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um die Funktion formSetCfm der Datei /goform/setcfm. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments funcpara1 mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3010|2024-03-27T23:31:05.075Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 23:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3006|2024-03-27T22:31:05.391Z -- tenda -- fh1205
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3006</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tenda FH1205 2.0.0.7(775). This vulnerability affects the function fromSetRouteStatic of the file /goform/fromRouteStatic. The manipulation of the argument entrys leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-258292. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Tenda FH1205 2.0.0.7(775) wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist die Funktion fromSetRouteStatic der Datei /goform/fromRouteStatic. Dank Manipulation des Arguments entrys mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3006|2024-03-27T22:31:05.391Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 22:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
