<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Tenda -- W6</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tenda/w6.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Tenda -- W6</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 22:22:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0995|2024-08-01T18:26:30.371Z -- tenda -- w6
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0995</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda W6 1.0.0.9(4122). It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function formwrlSSIDset of the file /goform/wifiSSIDset of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument index leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252260. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Tenda W6 1.0.0.9(4122) ausgemacht. Davon betroffen ist die Funktion formwrlSSIDset der Datei /goform/wifiSSIDset der Komponente httpd. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments index mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0995|2024-08-01T18:26:30.371Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 02:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0994|2024-08-01T18:26:30.342Z -- tenda -- w6
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0994</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda W6 1.0.0.9(4122). It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formSetCfm of the file /goform/setcfm of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument funcpara1 leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252259. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Tenda W6 1.0.0.9(4122) wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Hierbei betrifft es die Funktion formSetCfm der Datei /goform/setcfm der Komponente httpd. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments funcpara1 mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0994|2024-08-01T18:26:30.342Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 01:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
