<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Tongda -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tongda/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Tongda -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 23:22:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5682|2024-10-11T18:08:53.553Z -- tongda -- oa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5682</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Tongda OA 2017 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file general/hr/training/record/delete.php. The manipulation of the argument RECORD_ID leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 11.10 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-243058 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Tongda OA 2017 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle gefunden. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei general/hr/training/record/delete.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments RECORD_ID mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 11.10 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5682|2024-10-11T18:08:53.553Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 20:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4903|2024-06-07T20:01:36.811Z -- tongda -- oa</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4903</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Tongda OA 2017. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /general/meeting/manage/delete.php. The manipulation of the argument M_ID_STR leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-264436. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Tongda OA 2017 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei /general/meeting/manage/delete.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments M_ID_STR mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4903|2024-06-07T20:01:36.811Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 15:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4903|2024-08-01T20:55:10.260Z -- tongda -- oa</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4903</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Tongda OA 2017. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /general/meeting/manage/delete.php. The manipulation of the argument M_ID_STR leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-264436. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Tongda OA 2017 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei /general/meeting/manage/delete.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments M_ID_STR mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4903|2024-08-01T20:55:10.260Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 15:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
