<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Tongda -- OA 2017</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tongda/oa%202017.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Tongda -- OA 2017</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 08:24:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5267|2024-08-02T07:52:08.572Z -- tongda -- oa%202017
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5267</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Tongda OA 2017 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file general/hr/recruit/hr_pool/delete.php. The manipulation of the argument EXPERT_ID leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 11.10 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-240880.
In Tongda OA 2017 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle gefunden. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei general/hr/recruit/hr_pool/delete.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments EXPERT_ID mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 11.10 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5267|2024-08-02T07:52:08.572Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 15:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5261|2024-08-02T07:52:08.544Z -- tongda -- oa%202017
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5261</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tongda OA 2017. Affected is an unknown function of the file general/hr/manage/staff_title_evaluation/delete.php. The manipulation of the argument EVALUATION_ID leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 11.10 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-240870 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Tongda OA 2017 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei general/hr/manage/staff_title_evaluation/delete.php. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments EVALUATION_ID mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 11.10 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5261|2024-08-02T07:52:08.544Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 12:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5497|2024-08-02T07:59:44.773Z -- tongda -- oa%202017
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5497</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tongda OA 2017 11.10. Affected is an unknown function of the file general/hr/salary/welfare_manage/delete.php. The manipulation of the argument WELFARE_ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-241650 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Tongda OA 2017 11.10 entdeckt. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei general/hr/salary/welfare_manage/delete.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments WELFARE_ID mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5497|2024-08-02T07:59:44.773Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 17:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5285|2024-08-02T07:52:08.716Z -- tongda -- oa%202017
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5285</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tongda OA 2017. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file general/hr/recruit/recruitment/delete.php. The manipulation of the argument RECRUITMENT_ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 11.10 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-240913 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In Tongda OA 2017 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei general/hr/recruit/recruitment/delete.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments RECRUITMENT_ID mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 11.10 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5285|2024-08-02T07:52:08.716Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 19:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5298|2024-08-02T07:52:08.574Z -- tongda -- oa%202017
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5298</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Tongda OA 2017. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file general/hr/recruit/requirements/delete.php. The manipulation of the argument REQUIREMENTS_ID leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 11.10 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-240938 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Tongda OA 2017 ausgemacht. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei general/hr/recruit/requirements/delete.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments REQUIREMENTS_ID mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 11.10 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5298|2024-08-02T07:52:08.574Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 05:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5265|2024-08-02T07:52:08.524Z -- tongda -- oa%202017
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5265</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tongda OA 2017. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file general/hr/manage/staff_transfer/delete.php. The manipulation of the argument TRANSFER_ID leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 11.10 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-240878 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Tongda OA 2017 entdeckt. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei general/hr/manage/staff_transfer/delete.php. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments TRANSFER_ID mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 11.10 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5265|2024-08-02T07:52:08.524Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 14:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1252|2024-02-06T16:31:03.742Z -- tongda -- oa%202017</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1252</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.9. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /general/attendance/manage/ask_duty/delete.php. The manipulation of the argument ASK_DUTY_ID leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 11.10 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252991.
In Tongda OA 2017 bis 11.9 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei /general/attendance/manage/ask_duty/delete.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments ASK_DUTY_ID mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 11.10 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1252|2024-02-06T16:31:03.742Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 16:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1251|2024-02-06T16:00:06.750Z -- tongda -- oa%202017</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1251</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.10. Affected is an unknown function of the file /general/email/outbox/delete.php. The manipulation of the argument DELETE_STR leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252990 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Tongda OA 2017 bis 11.10 entdeckt. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei /general/email/outbox/delete.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments DELETE_STR mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1251|2024-02-06T16:00:06.750Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 16:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1252|2024-08-01T18:33:25.153Z -- tongda -- oa%202017</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1252</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.9. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /general/attendance/manage/ask_duty/delete.php. The manipulation of the argument ASK_DUTY_ID leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 11.10 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252991.
In Tongda OA 2017 bis 11.9 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei /general/attendance/manage/ask_duty/delete.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments ASK_DUTY_ID mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 11.10 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1252|2024-08-01T18:33:25.153Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 16:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1251|2024-08-01T18:33:25.323Z -- tongda -- oa%202017</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1251</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.10. Affected is an unknown function of the file /general/email/outbox/delete.php. The manipulation of the argument DELETE_STR leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252990 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Tongda OA 2017 bis 11.10 entdeckt. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei /general/email/outbox/delete.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments DELETE_STR mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1251|2024-08-01T18:33:25.323Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 16:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
