<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for D-Link -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/D-Link/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for D-Link -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 22:21:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-5297|2024-05-23T21:30:05.538Z -- D-Link -- D-View
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5297</link><description>D-Link D-View executeWmicCmd Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link D-View. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the executeWmicCmd method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21821.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5297|2024-05-23T21:30:05.538Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 21:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5294|2024-05-23T21:29:48.169Z -- D-Link -- DIR-3040
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5294</link><description>D-Link DIR-3040 prog.cgi websSecurityHandler Memory Leak Denial-of-Service Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to create a denial-of-service condition on affected installations of D-Link DIR-3040 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi program, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper memory management when processing HTTP cookie values. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to create a denial-of-service condition on the system.
. Was ZDI-CAN-21668.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5294|2024-05-23T21:29:48.169Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 21:29:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5292|2024-05-23T21:29:37.136Z -- D-Link -- Network Assistant
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5292</link><description>D-Link Network Assistant Uncontrolled Search Path Element Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of D-Link Network Assistant. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DNACore service. The service loads a file from an unsecured location. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-21426.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5292|2024-05-23T21:29:37.136Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 21:29:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5293|2024-05-23T21:29:44.062Z -- D-Link -- DIR-2640
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5293</link><description>D-Link DIR-2640 HTTP Referer Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-2640-US routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within prog.cgi, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21853.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5293|2024-05-23T21:29:44.062Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 21:29:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5295|2024-05-23T21:29:52.609Z -- D-Link -- G416
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5295</link><description>D-Link G416 flupl self Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 wireless routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21294.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5295|2024-05-23T21:29:52.609Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 21:29:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5296|2024-05-23T21:29:58.566Z -- D-Link -- D-View
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5296</link><description>D-Link D-View Use of Hard-coded Cryptographic Key Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of D-Link D-View. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the TokenUtils class. The issue results from a hard-coded cryptographic key. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-21991.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5296|2024-05-23T21:29:58.566Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 21:29:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5291|2024-05-23T21:29:29.301Z -- D-Link -- DIR-2150
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5291</link><description>D-Link DIR-2150 GetDeviceSettings Target Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-2150 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the SOAP API interface, which listens on TCP port 80 by default. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21235.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5291|2024-05-23T21:29:29.301Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 21:29:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5299|2024-05-23T21:30:14.551Z -- D-Link -- D-View
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5299</link><description>D-Link D-View execMonitorScript Exposed Dangerous Method Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link D-View. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the execMonitorScript method. The issue results from an exposed dangerous method. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21828.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5299|2024-05-23T21:30:14.551Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 21:30:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5298|2024-05-23T21:30:10.037Z -- D-Link -- D-View
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5298</link><description>D-Link D-View queryDeviceCustomMonitorResult Exposed Dangerous Method Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link D-View. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the queryDeviceCustomMonitorResult method. The issue results from an exposed dangerous method. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21842.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5298|2024-05-23T21:30:10.037Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 21:30:10 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>