<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for D-Link -- DAP-1330</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/d-link/dap-1330.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for D-Link -- DAP-1330</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 07:20:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34828|2024-08-04T00:26:54.047Z -- d-link -- dap-1330
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34828</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1330 1.13B01 BETA routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the SOAPAction HTTP header. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the device. Was ZDI-CAN-12066.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34828|2024-08-04T00:26:54.047Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 17:35:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34830|2024-08-04T00:26:54.067Z -- d-link -- dap-1330
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34830</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1330 1.13B01 BETA routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the Cookie HTTP header. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the device. Was ZDI-CAN-12028.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34830|2024-08-04T00:26:54.067Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 17:35:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34827|2024-08-04T00:26:54.090Z -- d-link -- dap-1330
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34827</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1330 1.13B01 BETA routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the SOAPAction HTTP header. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the device. Was ZDI-CAN-12029.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34827|2024-08-04T00:26:54.090Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 17:35:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34829|2024-08-04T00:26:54.060Z -- d-link -- dap-1330
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34829</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1330 1.13B01 BETA routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the HNAP_AUTH HTTP header. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the device. Was ZDI-CAN-12065.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34829|2024-08-04T00:26:54.060Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 17:35:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
