<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for D-Link -- DAP-2622</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/d-link/dap-2622.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for D-Link -- DAP-2622</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 22:22:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35749|2024-08-21T21:08:54.185Z -- d-link -- dap-2622
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35749</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Firmware Upgrade Filename Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20077.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35749|2024-08-21T21:08:54.185Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:55:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41215|2024-08-02T18:54:04.455Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41215</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set Date-Time Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20086.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41215|2024-08-02T18:54:04.455Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35728|2024-08-02T16:30:44.558Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35728</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Reboot Auth Password Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20055.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35728|2024-08-02T16:30:44.558Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35747|2024-08-02T16:30:44.362Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35747</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Firmware Upgrade Auth Password Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20075.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35747|2024-08-02T16:30:44.362Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35741|2024-08-02T16:30:44.319Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35741</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Configuration Backup Filename Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20068.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35741|2024-08-02T16:30:44.319Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35730|2024-08-02T16:30:44.283Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35730</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Reset Auth Password Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20057.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35730|2024-08-02T16:30:44.283Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35733|2024-08-02T16:30:44.412Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35733</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Change ID Password Auth Username Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20060.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35733|2024-08-02T16:30:44.412Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35757|2024-08-02T16:30:44.613Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35757</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set Date-Time NTP Server Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20085.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35757|2024-08-02T16:30:44.613Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:55:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35736|2024-08-02T16:30:44.848Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35736</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Change ID Password New Password Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20063.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35736|2024-08-02T16:30:44.848Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35756|2024-08-02T16:30:44.632Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35756</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set Date-Time Auth Password Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20084.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35756|2024-08-02T16:30:44.632Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35739|2024-08-02T16:30:44.600Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35739</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Configuration Backup Server IPv6 Address Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20066.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35739|2024-08-02T16:30:44.600Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35751|2024-08-02T16:30:44.580Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35751</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set AG Profile Auth Username Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20079.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35751|2024-08-02T16:30:44.580Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35744|2024-08-02T16:30:44.634Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35744</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Configuration Restore Server IPv6 Address Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20071.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35744|2024-08-02T16:30:44.634Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35731|2024-08-02T16:30:44.531Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35731</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Reset Factory Auth Username Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20058.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35731|2024-08-02T16:30:44.531Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35750|2024-08-02T16:30:44.658Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35750</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Get SSID List WPA PSK Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of authentication prior to allowing access to functionality. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose stored credentials, leading to further compromise. Was ZDI-CAN-20078.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35750|2024-08-02T16:30:44.658Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35732|2024-08-02T16:30:44.296Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35732</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Reset Factory Auth Password Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20059.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35732|2024-08-02T16:30:44.296Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35743|2024-08-02T16:30:44.217Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35743</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Configuration Restore Auth Password Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root.
. Was ZDI-CAN-20070.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35743|2024-08-02T16:30:44.217Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35740|2024-08-02T16:30:44.561Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35740</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Configuration Backup Server Address Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20067.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35740|2024-08-02T16:30:44.561Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35726|2024-08-02T16:30:44.560Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35726</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP User Verification Auth Password Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20053.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35726|2024-08-02T16:30:44.560Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35738|2024-08-02T16:30:44.570Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35738</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Configuration Backup Auth Password Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20065.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35738|2024-08-02T16:30:44.570Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35742|2024-08-02T16:30:44.254Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35742</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Configuration Restore Auth Username Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20069.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35742|2024-08-02T16:30:44.254Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35749|2024-08-02T16:30:44.775Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35749</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Firmware Upgrade Filename Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20077.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35749|2024-08-02T16:30:44.775Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:55:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35724|2024-08-02T16:30:44.432Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35724</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 Telnet CLI Use of Hardcoded Credentials Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the CLI service, which listens on TCP port 23. The server program contains hard-coded credentials. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-20050.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35724|2024-08-02T16:30:44.432Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35737|2024-08-02T16:30:44.359Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35737</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Configuration Backup Auth Username Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20064.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35737|2024-08-02T16:30:44.359Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35753|2024-08-02T16:30:44.887Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35753</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set AG Profile UUID Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20081.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35753|2024-08-02T16:30:44.887Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35746|2024-08-02T16:30:44.954Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35746</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Firmware Upgrade Auth Username Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20074.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35746|2024-08-02T16:30:44.954Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35755|2024-08-02T16:30:44.709Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35755</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set Date-Time Auth Username Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20083.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35755|2024-08-02T16:30:44.709Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35735|2024-08-02T16:30:44.514Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35735</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Change ID Password New Username Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20062.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35735|2024-08-02T16:30:44.514Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35752|2024-08-02T16:30:44.601Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35752</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set AG Profile Auth Password Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20080.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35752|2024-08-02T16:30:44.601Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35725|2024-08-02T16:30:44.268Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35725</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP User Verification Auth Username Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20052.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35725|2024-08-02T16:30:44.268Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35718|2024-08-02T16:30:44.538Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35718</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Change ID Password Auth Password Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20061.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35718|2024-08-02T16:30:44.538Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35729|2024-08-02T16:30:43.974Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35729</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Reset Auth Username Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20056.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35729|2024-08-02T16:30:43.974Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35727|2024-08-02T16:30:44.594Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35727</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Reboot Auth Username Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20054.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35727|2024-08-02T16:30:44.594Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35754|2024-08-02T16:30:44.676Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35754</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set AG Profile NMS URL Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20082.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35754|2024-08-02T16:30:44.676Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35745|2024-08-02T16:30:44.596Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35745</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Configuration Restore Filename Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20073.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35745|2024-08-02T16:30:44.596Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35748|2024-08-02T16:30:44.374Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35748</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Firmware Upgrade Server IPv6 Address Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20076.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35748|2024-08-02T16:30:44.374Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:55:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35741|2024-06-05T20:03:50.957Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35741</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Configuration Backup Filename Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20068.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35741|2024-06-05T20:03:50.957Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35757|2024-06-04T17:18:10.104Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35757</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set Date-Time NTP Server Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20085.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35757|2024-06-04T17:18:10.104Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:55:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35736|2024-06-05T19:51:11.836Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35736</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Change ID Password New Password Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20063.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35736|2024-06-05T19:51:11.836Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35737|2024-06-05T19:51:25.756Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35737</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Configuration Backup Auth Username Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20064.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35737|2024-06-05T19:51:25.756Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35756|2024-06-05T20:10:29.880Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35756</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set Date-Time Auth Password Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20084.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35756|2024-06-05T20:10:29.880Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35740|2024-06-04T17:18:12.859Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35740</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Configuration Backup Server Address Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20067.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35740|2024-06-04T17:18:12.859Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35726|2024-06-05T19:48:44.561Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35726</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP User Verification Auth Password Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20053.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35726|2024-06-05T19:48:44.561Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35730|2024-06-04T17:18:14.156Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35730</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Reset Auth Password Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20057.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35730|2024-06-04T17:18:14.156Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35747|2024-06-05T20:07:02.453Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35747</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Firmware Upgrade Auth Password Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20075.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35747|2024-06-05T20:07:02.453Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35751|2024-06-05T20:07:45.883Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35751</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set AG Profile Auth Username Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20079.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35751|2024-06-05T20:07:45.883Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35750|2024-06-05T20:07:52.464Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35750</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Get SSID List WPA PSK Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of authentication prior to allowing access to functionality. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose stored credentials, leading to further compromise. Was ZDI-CAN-20078.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35750|2024-06-05T20:07:52.464Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35746|2024-06-05T20:06:02.003Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35746</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Firmware Upgrade Auth Username Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20074.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35746|2024-06-05T20:06:02.003Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35731|2024-06-04T17:18:19.547Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35731</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Reset Factory Auth Username Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20058.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35731|2024-06-04T17:18:19.547Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35727|2024-06-05T19:49:12.754Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35727</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Reboot Auth Username Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20054.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35727|2024-06-05T19:49:12.754Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35732|2024-06-05T19:50:16.849Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35732</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Reset Factory Auth Password Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20059.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35732|2024-06-05T19:50:16.849Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35724|2024-06-05T19:47:46.215Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35724</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 Telnet CLI Use of Hardcoded Credentials Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the CLI service, which listens on TCP port 23. The server program contains hard-coded credentials. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-20050.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35724|2024-06-05T19:47:46.215Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35749|2024-05-07T22:55:03.505Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35749</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Firmware Upgrade Filename Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20077.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35749|2024-05-07T22:55:03.505Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:55:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35728|2024-06-05T19:49:31.529Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35728</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Reboot Auth Password Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20055.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35728|2024-06-05T19:49:31.529Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35753|2024-06-05T20:08:38.357Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35753</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set AG Profile UUID Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20081.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35753|2024-06-05T20:08:38.357Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35745|2024-06-05T20:05:44.226Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35745</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Configuration Restore Filename Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20073.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35745|2024-06-05T20:05:44.226Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35744|2024-06-05T20:05:27.912Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35744</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Configuration Restore Server IPv6 Address Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20071.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35744|2024-06-05T20:05:27.912Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35752|2024-06-05T20:08:24.906Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35752</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set AG Profile Auth Password Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20080.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35752|2024-06-05T20:08:24.906Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35729|2024-06-05T19:49:52.683Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35729</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Reset Auth Username Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20056.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35729|2024-06-05T19:49:52.683Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35748|2024-06-04T17:18:29.653Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35748</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Firmware Upgrade Server IPv6 Address Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20076.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35748|2024-06-04T17:18:29.653Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:55:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35725|2024-06-05T19:48:04.521Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35725</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP User Verification Auth Username Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20052.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35725|2024-06-05T19:48:04.521Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35733|2024-06-05T19:50:34.081Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35733</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Change ID Password Auth Username Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20060.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35733|2024-06-05T19:50:34.081Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35738|2024-06-05T20:01:49.352Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35738</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Configuration Backup Auth Password Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20065.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35738|2024-06-05T20:01:49.352Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35755|2024-06-05T20:09:35.156Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35755</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set Date-Time Auth Username Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20083.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35755|2024-06-05T20:09:35.156Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35743|2024-06-05T20:05:13.189Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35743</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Configuration Restore Auth Password Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root.
. Was ZDI-CAN-20070.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35743|2024-06-05T20:05:13.189Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35718|2024-06-05T19:47:20.887Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35718</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Change ID Password Auth Password Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20061.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35718|2024-06-05T19:47:20.887Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35735|2024-06-05T19:50:56.820Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35735</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Change ID Password New Username Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20062.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35735|2024-06-05T19:50:56.820Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35742|2024-06-05T20:04:12.748Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35742</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Configuration Restore Auth Username Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20069.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35742|2024-06-05T20:04:12.748Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35754|2024-06-05T20:09:01.063Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35754</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set AG Profile NMS URL Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20082.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35754|2024-06-05T20:09:01.063Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35739|2024-06-05T20:03:25.235Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35739</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Configuration Backup Server IPv6 Address Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20066.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35739|2024-06-05T20:03:25.235Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44417|2024-06-06T12:33:23.409Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-44417</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set IPv4 Address Auth Password Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20091.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44417|2024-06-06T12:33:23.409Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44416|2024-06-06T12:33:06.623Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-44416</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 Telnet CLI Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the CLI service, which listens on TCP port 23. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20051.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44416|2024-06-06T12:33:06.623Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41215|2024-06-05T20:51:48.321Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41215</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set Date-Time Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20086.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41215|2024-06-05T20:51:48.321Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37316|2024-06-05T20:12:17.609Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37316</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set IPv6 Address Default Gateway Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20094.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37316|2024-06-05T20:12:17.609Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37320|2024-06-05T20:13:21.729Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37320</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set SSID List SSID Name Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20098.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37320|2024-06-05T20:13:21.729Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37321|2024-06-05T20:13:39.639Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37321</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set SSID List RADIUS Secret Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20099.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37321|2024-06-05T20:13:39.639Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37317|2024-06-05T20:12:34.390Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37317</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set IPv6 Address Primary DNS Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20095.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37317|2024-06-05T20:12:34.390Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37326|2024-06-05T20:14:44.155Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37326</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set Wireless Info Auth Password Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20103.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37326|2024-06-05T20:14:44.155Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37310|2024-06-05T20:10:46.030Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37310</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set Device Info Auth Username Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20087.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37310|2024-06-05T20:10:46.030Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37311|2024-06-05T20:10:59.912Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37311</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set Device Info Auth Password Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20088.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37311|2024-06-05T20:10:59.912Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37324|2024-06-05T20:14:21.664Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37324</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set Wireless Info Auth Username Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20102.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37324|2024-06-05T20:14:21.664Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37312|2024-06-05T20:11:13.920Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37312</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set Device Info Device Name Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20089.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37312|2024-06-05T20:11:13.920Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37313|2024-06-05T20:11:28.467Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37313</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set IPv4 Address Auth Username Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20090.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37313|2024-06-05T20:11:28.467Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37325|2024-06-05T20:16:26.646Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37325</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set SSID List Missing Authentication Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to make unauthorized changes to device configuration on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of authentication prior to allowing access to functionality. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to manipulate wireless authentication settings. Was ZDI-CAN-20104.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37325|2024-06-05T20:16:26.646Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:55:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37314|2024-06-05T20:11:46.513Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37314</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set IPv6 Address Auth Username Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20092.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37314|2024-06-05T20:11:46.513Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37318|2024-06-05T20:12:53.748Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37318</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set IPv6 Address Secondary DNS Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20096.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37318|2024-06-05T20:12:53.748Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37322|2024-06-05T20:13:51.908Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37322</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set SSID List RADIUS Server Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20100.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37322|2024-06-05T20:13:51.908Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37323|2024-06-05T20:14:08.984Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37323</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set SSID List PSK Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20101.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37323|2024-06-05T20:14:08.984Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37319|2024-06-05T20:13:09.499Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37319</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set IPv6 Address Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20097.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37319|2024-06-05T20:13:09.499Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37315|2024-06-05T20:12:03.476Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37315</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set IPv6 Address Auth Password Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20093.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37315|2024-06-05T20:12:03.476Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37310|2024-08-02T17:09:34.013Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37310</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set Device Info Auth Username Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20087.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37310|2024-08-02T17:09:34.013Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37315|2024-08-02T17:09:34.174Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37315</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set IPv6 Address Auth Password Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20093.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37315|2024-08-02T17:09:34.174Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37323|2024-08-02T17:09:34.183Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37323</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set SSID List PSK Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20101.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37323|2024-08-02T17:09:34.183Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37312|2024-08-02T17:09:34.099Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37312</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set Device Info Device Name Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20089.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37312|2024-08-02T17:09:34.099Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37319|2024-08-02T17:09:34.021Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37319</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set IPv6 Address Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20097.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37319|2024-08-02T17:09:34.021Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37311|2024-08-02T17:09:34.082Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37311</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set Device Info Auth Password Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20088.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37311|2024-08-02T17:09:34.082Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37320|2024-08-02T17:09:34.045Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37320</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set SSID List SSID Name Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20098.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37320|2024-08-02T17:09:34.045Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37318|2024-08-02T17:09:34.216Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37318</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set IPv6 Address Secondary DNS Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20096.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37318|2024-08-02T17:09:34.216Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37314|2024-08-02T17:09:34.195Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37314</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set IPv6 Address Auth Username Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20092.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37314|2024-08-02T17:09:34.195Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37321|2024-08-02T17:09:34.106Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37321</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set SSID List RADIUS Secret Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20099.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37321|2024-08-02T17:09:34.106Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37313|2024-08-02T17:09:34.170Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37313</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set IPv4 Address Auth Username Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20090.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37313|2024-08-02T17:09:34.170Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37322|2024-08-02T17:09:34.119Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37322</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set SSID List RADIUS Server Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20100.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37322|2024-08-02T17:09:34.119Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37317|2024-08-02T17:09:34.062Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37317</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set IPv6 Address Primary DNS Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20095.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37317|2024-08-02T17:09:34.062Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37326|2024-08-02T17:09:34.090Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37326</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set Wireless Info Auth Password Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20103.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37326|2024-08-02T17:09:34.090Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37325|2024-08-02T17:09:34.023Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37325</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set SSID List Missing Authentication Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to make unauthorized changes to device configuration on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of authentication prior to allowing access to functionality. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to manipulate wireless authentication settings. Was ZDI-CAN-20104.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37325|2024-08-02T17:09:34.023Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:55:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37324|2024-08-02T17:09:34.016Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37324</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set Wireless Info Auth Username Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20102.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37324|2024-08-02T17:09:34.016Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37316|2024-08-02T17:09:34.060Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37316</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set IPv6 Address Default Gateway Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20094.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37316|2024-08-02T17:09:34.060Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44416|2024-08-02T20:07:33.178Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44416</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 Telnet CLI Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the CLI service, which listens on TCP port 23. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20051.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44416|2024-08-02T20:07:33.178Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44417|2024-08-02T20:07:32.889Z -- d-link -- dap-2622</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44417</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set IPv4 Address Auth Password Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20091.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44417|2024-08-02T20:07:32.889Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
