<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for D-Link -- DAP-1325</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/d-link/dap-1325.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for D-Link -- DAP-1325</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 21:22:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44408|2024-08-02T20:07:33.192Z -- d-link -- dap-1325
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44408</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 SetAPLanSettings IPAddr Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18827.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44408|2024-08-02T20:07:33.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44409|2024-08-02T20:07:33.009Z -- d-link -- dap-1325
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44409</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 SetSetupWizardStatus Enabled Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18838.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44409|2024-08-02T20:07:33.009Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44406|2024-08-02T20:07:32.830Z -- d-link -- dap-1325
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44406</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 SetAPLanSettings DeviceName Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18825.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44406|2024-08-02T20:07:32.830Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44407|2024-08-02T20:07:33.123Z -- d-link -- dap-1325
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44407</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 SetAPLanSettings Gateway Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18826.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44407|2024-08-02T20:07:33.123Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44405|2024-08-02T20:07:32.994Z -- d-link -- dap-1325
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44405</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 get_value_of_key Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18824.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44405|2024-08-02T20:07:32.994Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44404|2024-08-02T20:07:33.151Z -- d-link -- dap-1325
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44404</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 get_value_from_app Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18823.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44404|2024-08-02T20:07:33.151Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44403|2024-08-02T20:07:32.905Z -- d-link -- dap-1325
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44403</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 HNAP SetWLanRadioSettings Channel Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of a request parameter provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18822.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44403|2024-08-02T20:07:32.905Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41213|2024-06-04T17:22:01.691Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41213</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 setDhcpAssignRangeUpdate lan_ipaddr Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18840.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41213|2024-06-04T17:22:01.691Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41194|2024-06-04T17:22:00.834Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41194</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 HNAP SetAPLanSettings SubnetMask Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of a request parameter provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18814.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41194|2024-06-04T17:22:00.834Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41205|2024-06-04T17:22:00.411Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41205</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 SetAPLanSettings SubnetMask Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18831.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41205|2024-06-04T17:22:00.411Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41198|2024-06-04T17:21:58.707Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41198</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 HNAP SetHostIPv6StaticSettings StaticDNS1 Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of a request parameter provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18818.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41198|2024-06-04T17:21:58.707Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41209|2024-06-04T17:21:58.276Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41209</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 SetHostIPv6StaticSettings StaticDNS1 Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18835.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41209|2024-06-04T17:21:58.276Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41208|2024-06-04T17:21:54.922Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41208</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 SetHostIPv6StaticSettings StaticDefaultGateway Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18834.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41208|2024-06-04T17:21:54.922Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41199|2024-06-04T17:21:54.515Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41199</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 HNAP SetHostIPv6StaticSettings StaticDNS2 Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of a request parameter provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18819.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41199|2024-06-04T17:21:54.515Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41204|2024-06-04T17:21:53.249Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41204</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 SetAPLanSettings SecondaryDNS Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18830.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41204|2024-06-04T17:21:53.249Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41195|2024-06-04T17:21:52.836Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41195</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 HNAP SetHostIPv6Settings IPv6Mode Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of a request parameter provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18815.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41195|2024-06-04T17:21:52.836Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41212|2024-06-04T17:21:52.013Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41212</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 SetTriggerAPValidate Key Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18839.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41212|2024-06-04T17:21:52.013Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41188|2024-06-04T17:21:50.763Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41188</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 HNAP SetAPLanSettings DeviceName Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of a request parameter provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18808.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41188|2024-06-04T17:21:50.763Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41192|2024-06-04T17:21:48.560Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41192</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 HNAP SetAPLanSettings PrimaryDNS Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of a request parameter provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18812.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41192|2024-06-04T17:21:48.560Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41203|2024-06-04T17:21:47.716Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41203</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 SetAPLanSettings PrimaryDNS Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18829.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41203|2024-06-04T17:21:47.716Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41202|2024-06-04T17:21:46.066Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41202</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 SetAPLanSettings Mode Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18828.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41202|2024-06-04T17:21:46.066Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41193|2024-06-04T17:21:45.248Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41193</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 HNAP SetAPLanSettings SecondaryDNS Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of a request parameter provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18813.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41193|2024-06-04T17:21:45.248Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41214|2024-06-04T17:21:43.864Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41214</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 setDhcpAssignRangeUpdate lan_ipaddr Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18841.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41214|2024-06-04T17:21:43.864Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41189|2024-06-05T20:49:31.045Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41189</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 HNAP SetAPLanSettings Gateway Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of a request parameter provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18809.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41189|2024-06-05T20:49:31.045Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41201|2024-06-05T20:51:04.804Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41201</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 HNAP SetSetupWizardStatus Enabled Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of a request parameter provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18821.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41201|2024-06-05T20:51:04.804Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41190|2024-06-04T17:21:39.341Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41190</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 HNAP SetAPLanSettings IPAddr Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of a request parameter provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18810.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41190|2024-06-04T17:21:39.341Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41186|2024-06-05T17:25:42.875Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41186</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 CGI Missing Authentication Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to access various functionality on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the CGI interface. The issue results from the lack of authentication prior to allowing access to functionality. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose stored credentials, leading to further compromise. Was ZDI-CAN-18804.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41186|2024-06-05T17:25:42.875Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41187|2024-06-04T17:21:37.409Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41187</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 HNAP Missing Authentication Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the HNAP interface. The issue results from the lack of authentication prior to allowing access to functionality. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18807.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41187|2024-06-04T17:21:37.409Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41191|2024-06-04T17:21:37.012Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41191</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 HNAP SetAPLanSettings Mode Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of a request parameter provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18811.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41191|2024-06-04T17:21:37.012Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41200|2024-06-04T17:21:36.613Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41200</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 HNAP SetHostIPv6StaticSettings StaticPrefixLength Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of a request parameter provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18820.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41200|2024-06-04T17:21:36.613Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41207|2024-06-04T17:21:34.892Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41207</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 SetHostIPv6StaticSettings StaticAddress Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18833.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41207|2024-06-04T17:21:34.892Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41196|2024-06-04T17:21:34.463Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41196</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 HNAP SetHostIPv6StaticSettings StaticAddress Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of a request parameter provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18816.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41196|2024-06-04T17:21:34.463Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41211|2024-06-04T17:21:34.053Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41211</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 SetHostIPv6StaticSettings StaticPrefixLength Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18837.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41211|2024-06-04T17:21:34.053Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41210|2024-06-04T17:21:31.520Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41210</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 SetHostIPv6StaticSettings StaticDNS2 Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18836.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41210|2024-06-04T17:21:31.520Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41197|2024-06-04T17:21:30.662Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41197</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 HNAP SetHostIPv6StaticSettings StaticDefaultGateway Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of a request parameter provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18817.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41197|2024-06-04T17:21:30.662Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41206|2024-06-04T17:21:30.211Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41206</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 SetHostIPv6Settings IPv6Mode Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18832.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41206|2024-06-04T17:21:30.211Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44406|2024-06-04T17:19:34.134Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-44406</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 SetAPLanSettings DeviceName Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18825.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44406|2024-06-04T17:19:34.134Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44407|2024-06-04T17:19:32.862Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-44407</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 SetAPLanSettings Gateway Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18826.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44407|2024-06-04T17:19:32.862Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44408|2024-06-04T17:19:30.318Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-44408</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 SetAPLanSettings IPAddr Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18827.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44408|2024-06-04T17:19:30.318Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44404|2024-06-04T17:19:28.968Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-44404</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 get_value_from_app Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18823.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44404|2024-06-04T17:19:28.968Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44405|2024-06-04T17:19:26.873Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-44405</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 get_value_of_key Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18824.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44405|2024-06-04T17:19:26.873Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44409|2024-06-04T17:19:25.132Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-44409</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 SetSetupWizardStatus Enabled Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18838.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44409|2024-06-04T17:19:25.132Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44403|2024-06-04T17:19:18.045Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-44403</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 HNAP SetWLanRadioSettings Channel Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of a request parameter provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18822.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44403|2024-06-04T17:19:18.045Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41187|2024-08-02T18:54:04.255Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41187</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 HNAP Missing Authentication Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the HNAP interface. The issue results from the lack of authentication prior to allowing access to functionality. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18807.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41187|2024-08-02T18:54:04.255Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41188|2024-08-02T18:54:04.323Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41188</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 HNAP SetAPLanSettings DeviceName Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of a request parameter provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18808.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41188|2024-08-02T18:54:04.323Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41192|2024-08-02T18:54:04.376Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41192</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 HNAP SetAPLanSettings PrimaryDNS Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of a request parameter provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18812.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41192|2024-08-02T18:54:04.376Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41214|2024-08-02T18:54:04.382Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41214</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 setDhcpAssignRangeUpdate lan_ipaddr Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18841.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41214|2024-08-02T18:54:04.382Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41194|2024-08-02T18:54:04.351Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41194</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 HNAP SetAPLanSettings SubnetMask Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of a request parameter provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18814.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41194|2024-08-02T18:54:04.351Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41209|2024-08-02T18:54:04.419Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41209</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 SetHostIPv6StaticSettings StaticDNS1 Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18835.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41209|2024-08-02T18:54:04.419Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41208|2024-08-02T18:54:04.438Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41208</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 SetHostIPv6StaticSettings StaticDefaultGateway Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18834.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41208|2024-08-02T18:54:04.438Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41204|2024-08-02T18:54:04.371Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41204</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 SetAPLanSettings SecondaryDNS Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18830.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41204|2024-08-02T18:54:04.371Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41198|2024-08-02T18:54:04.331Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41198</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 HNAP SetHostIPv6StaticSettings StaticDNS1 Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of a request parameter provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18818.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41198|2024-08-02T18:54:04.331Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41199|2024-08-02T18:54:04.382Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41199</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 HNAP SetHostIPv6StaticSettings StaticDNS2 Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of a request parameter provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18819.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41199|2024-08-02T18:54:04.382Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41205|2024-08-02T18:54:04.592Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41205</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 SetAPLanSettings SubnetMask Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18831.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41205|2024-08-02T18:54:04.592Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41213|2024-08-02T18:54:04.423Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41213</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 setDhcpAssignRangeUpdate lan_ipaddr Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18840.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41213|2024-08-02T18:54:04.423Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41206|2024-08-02T18:54:04.310Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41206</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 SetHostIPv6Settings IPv6Mode Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18832.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41206|2024-08-02T18:54:04.310Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41207|2024-08-02T18:54:04.352Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41207</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 SetHostIPv6StaticSettings StaticAddress Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18833.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41207|2024-08-02T18:54:04.352Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41202|2024-08-02T18:54:04.356Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41202</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 SetAPLanSettings Mode Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18828.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41202|2024-08-02T18:54:04.356Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41200|2024-08-02T18:54:04.391Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41200</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 HNAP SetHostIPv6StaticSettings StaticPrefixLength Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of a request parameter provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18820.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41200|2024-08-02T18:54:04.391Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41196|2024-08-02T18:54:04.528Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41196</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 HNAP SetHostIPv6StaticSettings StaticAddress Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of a request parameter provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18816.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41196|2024-08-02T18:54:04.528Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41212|2024-08-02T18:54:05.062Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41212</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 SetTriggerAPValidate Key Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18839.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41212|2024-08-02T18:54:05.062Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41193|2024-08-02T18:54:04.470Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41193</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 HNAP SetAPLanSettings SecondaryDNS Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of a request parameter provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18813.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41193|2024-08-02T18:54:04.470Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41201|2024-08-02T18:54:04.445Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41201</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 HNAP SetSetupWizardStatus Enabled Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of a request parameter provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18821.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41201|2024-08-02T18:54:04.445Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41195|2024-08-02T18:54:04.356Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41195</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 HNAP SetHostIPv6Settings IPv6Mode Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of a request parameter provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18815.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41195|2024-08-02T18:54:04.356Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41211|2024-08-02T18:54:04.536Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41211</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 SetHostIPv6StaticSettings StaticPrefixLength Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18837.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41211|2024-08-02T18:54:04.536Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41190|2024-08-02T18:54:04.388Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41190</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 HNAP SetAPLanSettings IPAddr Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of a request parameter provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18810.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41190|2024-08-02T18:54:04.388Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41210|2024-08-02T18:54:04.359Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41210</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 SetHostIPv6StaticSettings StaticDNS2 Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18836.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41210|2024-08-02T18:54:04.359Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41191|2024-08-02T18:54:04.330Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41191</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 HNAP SetAPLanSettings Mode Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of a request parameter provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18811.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41191|2024-08-02T18:54:04.330Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41189|2024-08-02T18:54:04.595Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41189</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 HNAP SetAPLanSettings Gateway Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of a request parameter provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18809.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41189|2024-08-02T18:54:04.595Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41197|2024-08-02T18:54:04.868Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41197</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 HNAP SetHostIPv6StaticSettings StaticDefaultGateway Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of a request parameter provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18817.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41197|2024-08-02T18:54:04.868Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41186|2024-08-02T18:54:04.177Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41186</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 CGI Missing Authentication Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to access various functionality on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the CGI interface. The issue results from the lack of authentication prior to allowing access to functionality. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose stored credentials, leading to further compromise. Was ZDI-CAN-18804.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41186|2024-08-02T18:54:04.177Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41203|2024-08-02T18:54:04.536Z -- d-link -- dap-1325</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41203</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1325 SetAPLanSettings PrimaryDNS Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1325 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XML data provided to the HNAP1 SOAP endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18829.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41203|2024-08-02T18:54:04.536Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
