<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for D-Link -- DAP-1360</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/d-link/dap-1360.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for D-Link -- DAP-1360</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 19:21:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32143|2024-09-18T18:28:11.976Z -- d-link -- dap-1360
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32143</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1360 webupg UPGCGI_CheckAuth Numeric Truncation Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1360 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of requests to the /cgi-bin/webupg endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in an integer overflow before allocating a buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root.
. Was ZDI-CAN-18423.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32143|2024-09-18T18:28:11.976Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32142|2024-09-18T18:28:11.192Z -- d-link -- dap-1360
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32142</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1360 webproc var:page Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1360 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of requests to the /cgi-bin/webproc endpoint. When parsing the var:page parameter, the process does not properly validate the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root.
. Was ZDI-CAN-18422.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32142|2024-09-18T18:28:11.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32140|2024-09-18T18:28:09.741Z -- d-link -- dap-1360
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32140</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1360 webproc var:sys_Token Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1360 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling requests to the /cgi-bin/webproc endpoint. When parsing the var:sys_Token parameter, the process does not properly validate the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root.
. Was ZDI-CAN-18418.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32140|2024-09-18T18:28:09.741Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32136|2024-09-18T18:28:06.807Z -- d-link -- dap-1360
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32136</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1360 webproc var:menu Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1360 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling requests to the /cgi-bin/webproc endpoint. When parsing the var:menu parameter, the process does not properly validate the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root.
. Was ZDI-CAN-18414.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32136|2024-09-18T18:28:06.807Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32138|2024-09-18T18:28:08.264Z -- d-link -- dap-1360
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32138</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1360 webproc Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1360 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of requests to the /cgi-bin/webproc endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root.
. Was ZDI-CAN-18416.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32138|2024-09-18T18:28:08.264Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32141|2024-09-18T18:28:10.492Z -- d-link -- dap-1360
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32141</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1360 webproc WEB_DisplayPage Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1360 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of requests to the /cgi-bin/webproc endpoint. When parsing the getpage and errorpage parameters, the process does not properly validate the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root.
. Was ZDI-CAN-18419.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32141|2024-09-18T18:28:10.492Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32145|2024-09-18T18:28:13.398Z -- d-link -- dap-1360
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32145</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1360 Hardcoded Credentials Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1360 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the processing of login requests to the web-based user interface. The firmware contains hard-coded default credentials. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system.
. Was ZDI-CAN-18455.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32145|2024-09-18T18:28:13.398Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32144|2024-09-18T18:28:12.699Z -- d-link -- dap-1360
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32144</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1360 webproc COMM_MakeCustomMsg Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1360 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of requests to the /cgi-bin/webproc endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root.
. Was ZDI-CAN-18454.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32144|2024-09-18T18:28:12.699Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32137|2024-09-18T18:28:07.536Z -- d-link -- dap-1360
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32137</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1360 webproc WEB_DisplayPage Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1360 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of requests to the /cgi-bin/webproc endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of root.
. Was ZDI-CAN-18415.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32137|2024-09-18T18:28:07.536Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32146|2024-09-18T18:28:14.151Z -- d-link -- dap-1360
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32146</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1360 Multiple Parameters Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1360 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the /cgi-bin/webproc endpoint. When parsing the errorpage and nextpage parameters, the process does not properly validate the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root.
. Was ZDI-CAN-18746.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32146|2024-09-18T18:28:14.151Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32139|2024-09-18T18:28:08.994Z -- d-link -- dap-1360
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32139</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1360 webproc Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1360 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling requests to the /cgi-bin/webproc endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root.
. Was ZDI-CAN-18417.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32139|2024-09-18T18:28:08.994Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32138|2024-06-04T17:26:06.642Z -- d-link -- dap-1360</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32138</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1360 webproc Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1360 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of requests to the /cgi-bin/webproc endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18416.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32138|2024-06-04T17:26:06.642Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32143|2024-06-04T17:26:07.523Z -- d-link -- dap-1360</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32143</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1360 webupg UPGCGI_CheckAuth Numeric Truncation Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1360 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of requests to the /cgi-bin/webupg endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in an integer overflow before allocating a buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18423.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32143|2024-06-04T17:26:07.523Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32142|2024-06-11T17:46:15.813Z -- d-link -- dap-1360</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32142</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1360 webproc var:page Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1360 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of requests to the /cgi-bin/webproc endpoint. When parsing the var:page parameter, the process does not properly validate the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18422.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32142|2024-06-11T17:46:15.813Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32139|2024-06-04T17:26:10.088Z -- d-link -- dap-1360</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32139</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1360 webproc Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1360 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling requests to the /cgi-bin/webproc endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18417.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32139|2024-06-04T17:26:10.088Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32145|2024-06-04T17:26:13.942Z -- d-link -- dap-1360</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32145</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1360 Hardcoded Credentials Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1360 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the processing of login requests to the web-based user interface. The firmware contains hard-coded default credentials. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-18455.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32145|2024-06-04T17:26:13.942Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32144|2024-06-05T17:22:52.418Z -- d-link -- dap-1360</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32144</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1360 webproc COMM_MakeCustomMsg Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1360 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of requests to the /cgi-bin/webproc endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18454.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32144|2024-06-05T17:22:52.418Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32146|2024-06-04T17:26:23.139Z -- d-link -- dap-1360</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32146</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1360 Multiple Parameters Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1360 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the /cgi-bin/webproc endpoint. When parsing the errorpage and nextpage parameters, the process does not properly validate the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18746.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32146|2024-06-04T17:26:23.139Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32141|2024-06-05T19:35:45.730Z -- d-link -- dap-1360</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32141</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1360 webproc WEB_DisplayPage Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1360 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of requests to the /cgi-bin/webproc endpoint. When parsing the getpage and errorpage parameters, the process does not properly validate the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18419.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32141|2024-06-05T19:35:45.730Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32136|2024-06-05T17:25:13.064Z -- d-link -- dap-1360</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32136</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1360 webproc var:menu Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1360 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling requests to the /cgi-bin/webproc endpoint. When parsing the var:menu parameter, the process does not properly validate the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18414.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32136|2024-06-05T17:25:13.064Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32137|2024-06-06T15:10:19.566Z -- d-link -- dap-1360</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32137</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1360 webproc WEB_DisplayPage Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1360 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of requests to the /cgi-bin/webproc endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18415.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32137|2024-06-06T15:10:19.566Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32140|2024-06-04T17:26:30.132Z -- d-link -- dap-1360</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32140</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1360 webproc var:sys_Token Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1360 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling requests to the /cgi-bin/webproc endpoint. When parsing the var:sys_Token parameter, the process does not properly validate the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18418.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32140|2024-06-04T17:26:30.132Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32146|2024-08-02T15:03:28.933Z -- d-link -- dap-1360</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32146</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1360 Multiple Parameters Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1360 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the /cgi-bin/webproc endpoint. When parsing the errorpage and nextpage parameters, the process does not properly validate the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18746.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32146|2024-08-02T15:03:28.933Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32145|2024-08-02T15:03:29.212Z -- d-link -- dap-1360</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32145</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1360 Hardcoded Credentials Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1360 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the processing of login requests to the web-based user interface. The firmware contains hard-coded default credentials. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-18455.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32145|2024-08-02T15:03:29.212Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32142|2024-08-02T15:03:29.227Z -- d-link -- dap-1360</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32142</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1360 webproc var:page Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1360 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of requests to the /cgi-bin/webproc endpoint. When parsing the var:page parameter, the process does not properly validate the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18422.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32142|2024-08-02T15:03:29.227Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32141|2024-08-02T15:03:29.144Z -- d-link -- dap-1360</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32141</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1360 webproc WEB_DisplayPage Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1360 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of requests to the /cgi-bin/webproc endpoint. When parsing the getpage and errorpage parameters, the process does not properly validate the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18419.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32141|2024-08-02T15:03:29.144Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32139|2024-08-02T15:03:29.159Z -- d-link -- dap-1360</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32139</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1360 webproc Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1360 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling requests to the /cgi-bin/webproc endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18417.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32139|2024-08-02T15:03:29.159Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32137|2024-08-02T15:03:29.167Z -- d-link -- dap-1360</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32137</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1360 webproc WEB_DisplayPage Directory Traversal Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1360 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of requests to the /cgi-bin/webproc endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18415.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32137|2024-08-02T15:03:29.167Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32138|2024-08-02T15:03:29.270Z -- d-link -- dap-1360</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32138</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1360 webproc Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1360 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of requests to the /cgi-bin/webproc endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18416.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32138|2024-08-02T15:03:29.270Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32136|2024-08-02T15:03:28.985Z -- d-link -- dap-1360</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32136</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1360 webproc var:menu Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1360 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling requests to the /cgi-bin/webproc endpoint. When parsing the var:menu parameter, the process does not properly validate the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18414.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32136|2024-08-02T15:03:28.985Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32144|2024-08-02T15:03:29.178Z -- d-link -- dap-1360</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32144</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1360 webproc COMM_MakeCustomMsg Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1360 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of requests to the /cgi-bin/webproc endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18454.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32144|2024-08-02T15:03:29.178Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32140|2024-08-02T15:03:29.168Z -- d-link -- dap-1360</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32140</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1360 webproc var:sys_Token Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1360 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling requests to the /cgi-bin/webproc endpoint. When parsing the var:sys_Token parameter, the process does not properly validate the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18418.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32140|2024-08-02T15:03:29.168Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32143|2024-08-02T15:03:29.243Z -- d-link -- dap-1360</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32143</link>
      <description>D-Link DAP-1360 webupg UPGCGI_CheckAuth Numeric Truncation Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-1360 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of requests to the /cgi-bin/webupg endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in an integer overflow before allocating a buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18423.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32143|2024-08-02T15:03:29.243Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
