<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for D-Link -- DAP-2020</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/d-link/dap-2020.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for D-Link -- DAP-2020</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 21:22:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34860|2024-08-04T00:26:54.228Z -- d-link -- dap-2020
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34860</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2020 1.01rc001 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the getpage parameter provided to the webproc endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-12103.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34860|2024-08-04T00:26:54.228Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 17:10:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34863|2024-08-04T00:26:54.606Z -- d-link -- dap-2020
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34863</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2020 1.01rc001 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the var:page parameter provided to the webproc endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-13271.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34863|2024-08-04T00:26:54.606Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 17:10:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34861|2024-08-04T00:26:54.669Z -- d-link -- dap-2020
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34861</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2020 1.01rc001 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the webproc endpoint, which listens on TCP port 80 by default. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-12104.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34861|2024-08-04T00:26:54.669Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 17:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34862|2024-08-04T00:26:54.205Z -- d-link -- dap-2020
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34862</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2020 1.01rc001 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the var:menu parameter provided to the webproc endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-13270.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34862|2024-08-04T00:26:54.205Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 17:10:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
