<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for D-Link -- DAR-8000-10</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/d-link/dar-8000-10.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for D-Link -- DAR-8000-10</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 13:24:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4711|2024-08-02T07:37:59.572Z -- d-link -- dar-8000-10
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4711</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in D-Link DAR-8000-10 up to 20230819. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /log/decodmail.php. The manipulation of the argument file leads to os command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-238574 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in D-Link DAR-8000-10 bis 20230819 entdeckt. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei /log/decodmail.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments file mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Sie ist schwierig ausnutzbar. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4711|2024-08-02T07:37:59.572Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 19:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4542|2024-08-02T07:31:06.464Z -- d-link -- dar-8000-10
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4542</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DAR-8000-10 up to 20230809. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /app/sys1.php. The manipulation of the argument cmd with the input id leads to os command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-238047. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in D-Link DAR-8000-10 bis 20230809 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei /app/sys1.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments cmd mit der Eingabe id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4542|2024-08-02T07:31:06.464Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 21:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4699|2024-08-01T20:47:41.583Z -- d-link -- dar-8000-10</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4699</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in D-Link DAR-8000-10 up to 20230922. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /importhtml.php. The manipulation of the argument sql leads to deserialization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263747. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed immediately that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in D-Link DAR-8000-10 bis 20230922 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei /importhtml.php. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments sql mit unbekannten Daten kann eine deserialization-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4699|2024-08-01T20:47:41.583Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 00:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4699|2024-05-10T00:31:04.335Z -- d-link -- dar-8000-10</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4699</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in D-Link DAR-8000-10 up to 20230922. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /importhtml.php. The manipulation of the argument sql leads to deserialization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263747. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed immediately that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in D-Link DAR-8000-10 bis 20230922 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei /importhtml.php. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments sql mit unbekannten Daten kann eine deserialization-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4699|2024-05-10T00:31:04.335Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 00:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
