<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for D-Link -- DAR-7000</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/d-link/dar-7000.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for D-Link -- DAR-7000</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 18:24:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5144|2024-08-02T07:52:06.678Z -- d-link -- dar-7000
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5144</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in D-Link DAR-7000 and DAR-8000 up to 20151231. Affected is an unknown function of the file /sysmanage/updateos.php. The manipulation of the argument file_upload leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-240240. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in D-Link DAR-7000 and DAR-8000 bis 20151231 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei /sysmanage/updateos.php. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments file_upload mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5144|2024-08-02T07:52:06.678Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 23:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5148|2024-08-02T07:52:06.679Z -- d-link -- dar-7000
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5148</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in D-Link DAR-7000 and DAR-8000 up to 20151231. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /Tool/uploadfile.php. The manipulation of the argument file_upload leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-240244. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed immediately that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
In D-Link DAR-7000 and DAR-8000 bis 20151231 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei /Tool/uploadfile.php. Durch Manipulation des Arguments file_upload mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5148|2024-08-02T07:52:06.679Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 01:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6581|2024-08-02T08:35:14.482Z -- d-link -- dar-7000
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6581</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DAR-7000 up to 20231126 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /user/inc/workidajax.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-247162 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In D-Link DAR-7000 bis 20231126 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle gefunden. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei /user/inc/workidajax.php. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6581|2024-08-02T08:35:14.482Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 22:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5150|2024-08-02T07:52:07.309Z -- d-link -- dar-7000
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5150</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in D-Link DAR-7000 and DAR-8000 up to 20151231. Affected is an unknown function of the file /useratte/web.php. The manipulation of the argument file_upload leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-240246 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed immediately that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in D-Link DAR-7000 and DAR-8000 bis 20151231 entdeckt. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei /useratte/web.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments file_upload mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5150|2024-08-02T07:52:07.309Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 01:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5145|2024-08-02T07:52:07.509Z -- d-link -- dar-7000
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5145</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DAR-7000 up to 20151231 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /sysmanage/licence.php. The manipulation of the argument file_upload leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-240241 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed immediately that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
In D-Link DAR-7000 bis 20151231 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei /sysmanage/licence.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments file_upload mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5145|2024-08-02T07:52:07.509Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 23:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5152|2024-08-02T07:52:07.473Z -- d-link -- dar-7000
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5152</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in D-Link DAR-7000 and DAR-8000 up to 20151231. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /importexport.php. The manipulation of the argument sql leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-240248. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed immediately that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in D-Link DAR-7000 and DAR-8000 bis 20151231 entdeckt. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei /importexport.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments sql mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5152|2024-08-02T07:52:07.473Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 02:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5147|2024-08-02T07:52:07.301Z -- d-link -- dar-7000
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5147</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in D-Link DAR-7000 up to 20151231. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /sysmanage/updateos.php. The manipulation of the argument 1_file_upload leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-240243. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed immediately that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in D-Link DAR-7000 bis 20151231 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei /sysmanage/updateos.php. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments 1_file_upload mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5147|2024-08-02T07:52:07.301Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 00:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5143|2024-08-02T07:52:07.525Z -- d-link -- dar-7000
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5143</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in D-Link DAR-7000 up to 20151231. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /log/webmailattach.php. The manipulation of the argument table_name leads to an unknown weakness. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-240239. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed immediately that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in D-Link DAR-7000 bis 20151231 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei /log/webmailattach.php. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments table_name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unbekannte Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5143|2024-08-02T07:52:07.525Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 22:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5149|2024-08-02T07:52:07.574Z -- d-link -- dar-7000
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5149</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in D-Link DAR-7000 up to 20151231. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /useratte/userattestation.php. The manipulation of the argument web_img leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-240245 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed immediately that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in D-Link DAR-7000 bis 20151231 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei /useratte/userattestation.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments web_img mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5149|2024-08-02T07:52:07.574Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 01:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5322|2024-08-02T07:52:08.720Z -- d-link -- dar-7000
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5322</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in D-Link DAR-7000 up to 20151231. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /sysmanage/edit_manageadmin.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-240992. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed immediately that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in D-Link DAR-7000 bis 20151231 ausgemacht. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei /sysmanage/edit_manageadmin.php. Durch Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5322|2024-08-02T07:52:08.720Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 04:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5146|2024-08-02T07:52:07.568Z -- d-link -- dar-7000
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5146</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in D-Link DAR-7000 and DAR-8000 up to 20151231 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /sysmanage/updatelib.php. The manipulation of the argument file_upload leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-240242 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed immediately that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in D-Link DAR-7000 and DAR-8000 bis 20151231 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei /sysmanage/updatelib.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments file_upload mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5146|2024-08-02T07:52:07.568Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 00:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6525|2024-07-05T13:49:24.531Z -- d-link -- dar-7000</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6525</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in D-Link DAR-7000 up to 20230922. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /log/decodmail.php. The manipulation of the argument file leads to deserialization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-270368. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in D-Link DAR-7000 bis 20230922 ausgemacht. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei /log/decodmail.php. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments file mit unbekannten Daten kann eine deserialization-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6525|2024-07-05T13:49:24.531Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 13:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6525|2024-08-01T21:41:03.833Z -- d-link -- dar-7000</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6525</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in D-Link DAR-7000 up to 20230922. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /log/decodmail.php. The manipulation of the argument file leads to deserialization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-270368. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in D-Link DAR-7000 bis 20230922 ausgemacht. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei /log/decodmail.php. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments file mit unbekannten Daten kann eine deserialization-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6525|2024-08-01T21:41:03.833Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 13:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
