<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for D-Link -- DIR-3040</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/d-link/dir-3040.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for D-Link -- DIR-3040</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 15:23:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-43648|2024-08-03T13:40:06.208Z -- d-link -- dir-3040
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43648</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-3040 1.20B03 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the MiniDLNA service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the MiniDLNA service. Was ZDI-CAN-19910.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-43648|2024-08-03T13:40:06.208Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41224|2024-08-02T18:54:04.340Z -- d-link -- dir-3040</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41224</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-3040 prog.cgi SetDeviceSettings Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-3040 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-size stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21650.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41224|2024-08-02T18:54:04.340Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41222|2024-08-02T18:54:04.370Z -- d-link -- dir-3040</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41222</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-3040 prog.cgi SetWan2Settings Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-3040 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-size stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21622.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41222|2024-08-02T18:54:04.370Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:25:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41226|2024-08-02T18:54:04.420Z -- d-link -- dir-3040</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41226</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-3040 prog.cgi SetMyDLinkRegistration Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-3040 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-size stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21652.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41226|2024-08-02T18:54:04.420Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41228|2024-08-02T18:54:04.635Z -- d-link -- dir-3040</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41228</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-3040 prog.cgi SetUsersSettings Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-3040 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-size stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21654.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41228|2024-08-02T18:54:04.635Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41217|2024-08-02T18:54:04.592Z -- d-link -- dir-3040</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41217</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-3040 prog.cgi SetQuickVPNSettings Password Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-3040 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21617.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41217|2024-08-02T18:54:04.592Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41219|2024-08-02T18:54:04.372Z -- d-link -- dir-3040</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41219</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-3040 prog.cgi SetWanSettings Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-3040 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-size stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21619.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41219|2024-08-02T18:54:04.372Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41229|2024-08-02T18:54:04.384Z -- d-link -- dir-3040</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41229</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-3040 HTTP Request Processing Referer Heap-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-3040 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21671.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41229|2024-08-02T18:54:04.384Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41216|2024-08-02T18:54:04.582Z -- d-link -- dir-3040</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41216</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-3040 prog.cgi SetDynamicDNSSettings Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-3040 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21616.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41216|2024-08-02T18:54:04.582Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41221|2024-08-02T18:54:04.360Z -- d-link -- dir-3040</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41221</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-3040 prog.cgi SetWLanRadioSecurity Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-3040 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-size stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21621.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41221|2024-08-02T18:54:04.360Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41227|2024-08-02T18:54:04.431Z -- d-link -- dir-3040</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41227</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-3040 prog.cgi SetTriggerPPPoEValidate Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-3040 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-size stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21653.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41227|2024-08-02T18:54:04.431Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41220|2024-08-02T18:54:04.476Z -- d-link -- dir-3040</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41220</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-3040 prog.cgi SetSysEmailSettings Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-3040 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-size stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21620.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41220|2024-08-02T18:54:04.476Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41225|2024-08-02T18:54:04.446Z -- d-link -- dir-3040</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41225</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-3040 prog.cgi SetIPv6PppoeSettings Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-3040 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-size stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21651.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41225|2024-08-02T18:54:04.446Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41218|2024-08-02T18:54:04.429Z -- d-link -- dir-3040</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41218</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-3040 prog.cgi SetWan3Settings Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-3040 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-size stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21618.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41218|2024-08-02T18:54:04.429Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41230|2024-08-02T18:54:04.575Z -- d-link -- dir-3040</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41230</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-3040 HTTP Request Processing Referer Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-3040 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed size stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21674.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41230|2024-08-02T18:54:04.575Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41223|2024-08-02T18:54:04.585Z -- d-link -- dir-3040</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41223</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-3040 prog.cgi SetQuickVPNSettings PSK Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-3040 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-size stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21623.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41223|2024-08-02T18:54:04.585Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5294|2024-07-30T14:50:16.254Z -- d-link -- dir-3040</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5294</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-3040 prog.cgi websSecurityHandler Memory Leak Denial-of-Service Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to create a denial-of-service condition on affected installations of D-Link DIR-3040 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi program, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper memory management when processing HTTP cookie values. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to create a denial-of-service condition on the system.
. Was ZDI-CAN-21668.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5294|2024-07-30T14:50:16.254Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 21:29:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5294|2024-05-23T21:29:48.169Z -- d-link -- dir-3040</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5294</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-3040 prog.cgi websSecurityHandler Memory Leak Denial-of-Service Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to create a denial-of-service condition on affected installations of D-Link DIR-3040 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi program, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper memory management when processing HTTP cookie values. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to create a denial-of-service condition on the system.
. Was ZDI-CAN-21668.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5294|2024-05-23T21:29:48.169Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 21:29:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41230|2024-06-05T20:52:45.078Z -- d-link -- dir-3040</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41230</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-3040 HTTP Request Processing Referer Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-3040 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed size stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21674.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41230|2024-06-05T20:52:45.078Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41226|2024-06-04T17:21:32.362Z -- d-link -- dir-3040</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41226</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-3040 prog.cgi SetMyDLinkRegistration Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-3040 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-size stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21652.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41226|2024-06-04T17:21:32.362Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41227|2024-06-04T17:21:33.207Z -- d-link -- dir-3040</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41227</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-3040 prog.cgi SetTriggerPPPoEValidate Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-3040 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-size stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21653.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41227|2024-06-04T17:21:33.207Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41220|2024-06-04T17:21:35.361Z -- d-link -- dir-3040</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41220</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-3040 prog.cgi SetSysEmailSettings Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-3040 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-size stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21620.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41220|2024-06-04T17:21:35.361Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41216|2024-06-04T17:21:38.499Z -- d-link -- dir-3040</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41216</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-3040 prog.cgi SetDynamicDNSSettings Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-3040 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21616.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41216|2024-06-04T17:21:38.499Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41217|2024-06-04T17:21:38.920Z -- d-link -- dir-3040</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41217</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-3040 prog.cgi SetQuickVPNSettings Password Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-3040 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21617.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41217|2024-06-04T17:21:38.920Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41221|2024-06-04T17:21:41.386Z -- d-link -- dir-3040</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41221</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-3040 prog.cgi SetWLanRadioSecurity Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-3040 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-size stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21621.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41221|2024-06-04T17:21:41.386Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41218|2024-06-04T17:21:41.780Z -- d-link -- dir-3040</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41218</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-3040 prog.cgi SetWan3Settings Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-3040 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-size stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21618.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41218|2024-06-04T17:21:41.780Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41222|2024-06-04T17:21:43.033Z -- d-link -- dir-3040</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41222</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-3040 prog.cgi SetWan2Settings Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-3040 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-size stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21622.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41222|2024-06-04T17:21:43.033Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:25:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41223|2024-06-04T17:21:50.328Z -- d-link -- dir-3040</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41223</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-3040 prog.cgi SetQuickVPNSettings PSK Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-3040 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-size stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21623.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41223|2024-06-04T17:21:50.328Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41219|2024-06-04T17:21:51.610Z -- d-link -- dir-3040</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41219</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-3040 prog.cgi SetWanSettings Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-3040 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-size stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21619.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41219|2024-06-04T17:21:51.610Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41228|2024-06-05T20:51:44.796Z -- d-link -- dir-3040</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41228</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-3040 prog.cgi SetUsersSettings Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-3040 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-size stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21654.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41228|2024-06-05T20:51:44.796Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41224|2024-06-04T17:21:56.177Z -- d-link -- dir-3040</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41224</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-3040 prog.cgi SetDeviceSettings Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-3040 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-size stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21650.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41224|2024-06-04T17:21:56.177Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41225|2024-06-04T17:21:57.402Z -- d-link -- dir-3040</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41225</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-3040 prog.cgi SetIPv6PppoeSettings Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-3040 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-size stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21651.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41225|2024-06-04T17:21:57.402Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41229|2024-06-04T17:21:59.546Z -- d-link -- dir-3040</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41229</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-3040 HTTP Request Processing Referer Heap-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-3040 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21671.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41229|2024-06-04T17:21:59.546Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5294|2024-08-01T21:11:12.440Z -- d-link -- dir-3040</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5294</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-3040 prog.cgi websSecurityHandler Memory Leak Denial-of-Service Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to create a denial-of-service condition on affected installations of D-Link DIR-3040 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi program, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper memory management when processing HTTP cookie values. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to create a denial-of-service condition on the system.
. Was ZDI-CAN-21668.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5294|2024-08-01T21:11:12.440Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 21:29:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
