<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for D-Link -- DIR-859</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/d-link/dir-859.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for D-Link -- DIR-859</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 20:23:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0769|2024-08-01T18:18:18.263Z -- d-link -- dir-859
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0769</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-859 1.06B01. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /hedwig.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument service with the input ../../../../htdocs/webinc/getcfg/DHCPS6.BRIDGE-1.xml leads to path traversal. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-251666 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed immediately that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in D-Link DIR-859 1.06B01 ausgemacht. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei /hedwig.cgi der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments service mit der Eingabe ../../../../htdocs/webinc/getcfg/DHCPS6.BRIDGE-1.xml mit unbekannten Daten kann eine path traversal-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0769|2024-08-01T18:18:18.263Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 08:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
