<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for D-Link -- DIR-X3260</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/d-link/dir-x3260.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for D-Link -- DIR-X3260</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51614|2024-06-04T17:21:02.665Z -- d-link -- dir-x3260
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51614</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-X3260 prog.cgi SetQuickVPNSettings Password Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-X3260 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21591.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51614|2024-06-04T17:21:02.665Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51618|2024-06-04T17:20:57.453Z -- d-link -- dir-x3260
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51618</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-X3260 prog.cgi SetWLanRadioSecurity Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-X3260 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21595.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51618|2024-06-04T17:20:57.453Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51622|2024-06-04T17:20:56.202Z -- d-link -- dir-x3260
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51622</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-X3260 prog.cgi SetTriggerPPPoEValidate Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-X3260 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-size stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21672.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51622|2024-06-04T17:20:56.202Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51623|2024-06-04T17:20:54.486Z -- d-link -- dir-x3260
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51623</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-X3260 prog.cgi SetAPClientSettings Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-X3260 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-size stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21673.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51623|2024-06-04T17:20:54.486Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51619|2024-06-04T17:20:54.076Z -- d-link -- dir-x3260
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51619</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-X3260 prog.cgi SetMyDLinkRegistration Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-X3260 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-size stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21667.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51619|2024-06-04T17:20:54.076Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51615|2024-06-04T17:20:51.628Z -- d-link -- dir-x3260
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51615</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-X3260 prog.cgi SetQuickVPNSettings PSK Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-X3260 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21592.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51615|2024-06-04T17:20:51.628Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51613|2024-06-04T17:20:39.268Z -- d-link -- dir-x3260
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51613</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-X3260 prog.cgi SetDynamicDNSSettings Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-X3260 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21590.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51613|2024-06-04T17:20:39.268Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51631|2024-06-04T17:20:24.304Z -- d-link -- dir-x3260
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51631</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-X3260 prog.cgi SetUsersSettings Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-X3260 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-size stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21675.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51631|2024-06-04T17:20:24.304Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 23:16:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51616|2024-06-04T17:20:20.803Z -- d-link -- dir-x3260
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51616</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-X3260 prog.cgi SetSysEmailSettings Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-X3260 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21593.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51616|2024-06-04T17:20:20.803Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51620|2024-06-04T17:20:19.525Z -- d-link -- dir-x3260
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51620</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-X3260 prog.cgi SetIPv6PppoeSettings Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-X3260 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-size stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21669.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51620|2024-06-04T17:20:19.525Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51621|2024-06-04T17:20:16.572Z -- d-link -- dir-x3260
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51621</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-X3260 prog.cgi SetDeviceSettings Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-X3260 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-size stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21670.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51621|2024-06-04T17:20:16.572Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51617|2024-06-04T17:20:14.476Z -- d-link -- dir-x3260
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51617</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-X3260 prog.cgi SetWanSettings Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-X3260 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21594.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51617|2024-06-04T17:20:14.476Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44420|2024-06-04T17:19:39.311Z -- d-link -- dir-x3260
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-44420</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-X3260 prog.cgi Incorrect Implementation of Authentication Algorithm Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of D-Link DIR-X3260 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi executable. The issue results from an incorrect implementation of the authentication algorithm. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the device. Was ZDI-CAN-21100.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44420|2024-06-04T17:19:39.311Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44421|2024-06-04T17:19:38.015Z -- d-link -- dir-x3260
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-44421</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-X3260 SetTriggerPPPoEValidate Username Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-X3260 routers. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi program, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21101.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44421|2024-06-04T17:19:38.015Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44426|2024-06-04T17:19:36.288Z -- d-link -- dir-x3260
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-44426</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-X3260 SetSysEmailSettings AccountPassword Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-X3260 routers. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within prog.cgi, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21160.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44426|2024-06-04T17:19:36.288Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44427|2024-06-04T17:19:31.577Z -- d-link -- dir-x3260
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-44427</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-X3260 SetSysEmailSettings SMTPServerAddress Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-X3260 routers. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within prog.cgi, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21222.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44427|2024-06-04T17:19:31.577Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44424|2024-06-04T17:19:30.745Z -- d-link -- dir-x3260
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-44424</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-X3260 SetSysEmailSettings EmailTo Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-X3260 routers. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within prog.cgi, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21158.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44424|2024-06-04T17:19:30.745Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44425|2024-06-04T17:19:23.804Z -- d-link -- dir-x3260
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-44425</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-X3260 SetSysEmailSettings AccountName Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-X3260 routers. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within prog.cgi, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21159.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44425|2024-06-04T17:19:23.804Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44422|2024-06-04T17:19:20.714Z -- d-link -- dir-x3260
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-44422</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-X3260 SetSysEmailSettings EmailFrom Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-X3260 routers. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi program, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21102.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44422|2024-06-04T17:19:20.714Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44418|2024-06-04T17:19:20.262Z -- d-link -- dir-x3260
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-44418</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-X3260 Prog.cgi Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-X3260 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length an user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20727.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44418|2024-06-04T17:19:20.262Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44419|2024-06-04T17:19:19.821Z -- d-link -- dir-x3260
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-44419</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-X3260 Prog.cgi Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-X3260 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi binary, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length an user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20774.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44419|2024-06-04T17:19:19.821Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44423|2024-06-04T17:19:19.365Z -- d-link -- dir-x3260
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-44423</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-X3260 SetTriggerPPPoEValidate Password Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-X3260 routers. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the prog.cgi program, which handles HNAP requests made to the lighttpd webserver listening on TCP ports 80 and 443. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21157.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44423|2024-06-04T17:19:19.365Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35723|2024-06-04T17:18:38.588Z -- d-link -- dir-x3260
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35723</link>
      <description>D-Link DIR-X3260 prog.cgi SOAPAction Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DIR-X3260 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of the SOAPAction request header provided to the prog.cgi endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20983.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35723|2024-06-04T17:18:38.588Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
