<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for D-Link -- DNS-120</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/d-link/dns-120.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for D-Link -- DNS-120</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:23:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7828|2024-08-15T12:31:03.787Z -- d-link -- dns-120
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7828</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability classified as critical was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. This vulnerability affects the function cgi_set_cover of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument album_name leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
In D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240814 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Das betrifft die Funktion cgi_set_cover der Datei /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. Dank Manipulation des Arguments album_name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7828|2024-08-15T12:31:03.787Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 12:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7829|2024-08-15T12:31:05.244Z -- d-link -- dns-120
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7829</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. This issue affects the function cgi_del_photo of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument current_path leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240814 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft die Funktion cgi_del_photo der Datei /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments current_path mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7829|2024-08-15T12:31:05.244Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 12:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7715|2024-08-13T06:31:04.655Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7715</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240812. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function sprintf of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument filter leads to command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240812 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist die Funktion sprintf der Datei /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments filter mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7715|2024-08-13T06:31:04.655Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 06:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7715|2024-08-14T20:54:51.331Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7715</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240812. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function sprintf of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument filter leads to command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240812 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist die Funktion sprintf der Datei /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments filter mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7715|2024-08-14T20:54:51.331Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 06:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
