<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for D-Link -- DNS-120</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/d-link/dns-120.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for D-Link -- DNS-120</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 21:21:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8131|2024-08-26T20:30:42.009Z -- d-link -- dns-120
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8131</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function module_enable_disable of the file /cgi-bin/apkg_mgr.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument f_module_name leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240814 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft die Funktion module_enable_disable der Datei /cgi-bin/apkg_mgr.cgi der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments f_module_name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8131|2024-08-26T20:30:42.009Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 17:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8132|2024-08-26T15:54:41.469Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8132</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function webdav_mgr of the file /cgi-bin/webdav_mgr.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument f_path leads to command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240814 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es die Funktion webdav_mgr der Datei /cgi-bin/webdav_mgr.cgi der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments f_path mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8132|2024-08-26T15:54:41.469Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 18:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8133|2024-08-26T13:15:17.599Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8133</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function cgi_FMT_R5_SpareDsk_DiskMGR of the file /cgi-bin/hd_config.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument f_source_dev leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
In D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240814 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es die Funktion cgi_FMT_R5_SpareDsk_DiskMGR der Datei /cgi-bin/hd_config.cgi der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments f_source_dev mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8133|2024-08-26T13:15:17.599Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 19:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8129|2024-08-26T13:13:02.376Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8129</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. Affected is the function cgi_s3_modify of the file /cgi-bin/s3.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument f_job_name leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240814 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es betrifft die Funktion cgi_s3_modify der Datei /cgi-bin/s3.cgi der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments f_job_name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8129|2024-08-26T13:13:02.376Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 15:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8132|2024-08-24T18:00:05.836Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8132</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function webdav_mgr of the file /cgi-bin/webdav_mgr.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument f_path leads to command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240814 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es die Funktion webdav_mgr der Datei /cgi-bin/webdav_mgr.cgi der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments f_path mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8132|2024-08-24T18:00:05.836Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 18:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8130|2024-08-24T16:31:05.950Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8130</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function cgi_s3 of the file /cgi-bin/s3.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument f_a_key leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
In D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240814 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Das betrifft die Funktion cgi_s3 der Datei /cgi-bin/s3.cgi der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments f_a_key mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8130|2024-08-24T16:31:05.950Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 16:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8128|2024-08-24T11:31:05.389Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8128</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. This issue affects the function cgi_add_zip of the file /cgi-bin/webfile_mgr.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument path leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240814 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei geht es um die Funktion cgi_add_zip der Datei /cgi-bin/webfile_mgr.cgi der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments path mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8128|2024-08-24T11:31:05.389Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 11:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7922|2024-08-19T18:23:40.353Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7922</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function cgi_audio_search/cgi_create_playlist/cgi_get_album_all_tracks/cgi_get_alltracks_editlist/cgi_get_artist_all_album/cgi_get_genre_all_tracks/cgi_get_tracks_list/cgi_set_airplay_content/cgi_write_playlist of the file /cgi-bin/myMusic.cgi. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240814 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist die Funktion cgi_audio_search/cgi_create_playlist/cgi_get_album_all_tracks/cgi_get_alltracks_editlist/cgi_get_artist_all_album/cgi_get_genre_all_tracks/cgi_get_tracks_list/cgi_set_airplay_content/cgi_write_playlist der Datei /cgi-bin/myMusic.cgi. Durch das Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7922|2024-08-19T18:23:40.353Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 15:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7849|2024-08-16T17:21:43.257Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7849</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. This affects the function cgi_create_album of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument current_path leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240814 gefunden. Es betrifft die Funktion cgi_create_album der Datei /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments current_path mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7849|2024-08-16T17:21:43.257Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 23:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7830|2024-08-15T16:01:15.692Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7830</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. Affected is the function cgi_move_photo of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument photo_name leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240814 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es die Funktion cgi_move_photo der Datei /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments photo_name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7830|2024-08-15T16:01:15.692Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7828|2024-08-15T16:01:00.352Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7828</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability classified as critical was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. This vulnerability affects the function cgi_set_cover of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument album_name leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
In D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240814 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Das betrifft die Funktion cgi_set_cover der Datei /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. Dank Manipulation des Arguments album_name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7828|2024-08-15T16:01:00.352Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 12:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7832|2024-08-15T16:01:19.900Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7832</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function cgi_get_fullscreen_photos of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument user leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240814 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist die Funktion cgi_get_fullscreen_photos der Datei /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments user mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7832|2024-08-15T16:01:19.900Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7829|2024-08-15T16:01:13.603Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7829</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. This issue affects the function cgi_del_photo of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument current_path leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240814 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft die Funktion cgi_del_photo der Datei /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments current_path mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7829|2024-08-15T16:01:13.603Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 12:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7831|2024-08-15T16:01:17.786Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7831</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function cgi_get_cooliris of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument path leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
In D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240814 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es die Funktion cgi_get_cooliris der Datei /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. Durch Manipulation des Arguments path mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7831|2024-08-15T16:01:17.786Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7830|2024-08-15T13:00:06.188Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7830</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. Affected is the function cgi_move_photo of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument photo_name leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240814 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es die Funktion cgi_move_photo der Datei /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments photo_name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7830|2024-08-15T13:00:06.188Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7832|2024-08-15T13:31:04.175Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7832</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function cgi_get_fullscreen_photos of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument user leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240814 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist die Funktion cgi_get_fullscreen_photos der Datei /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments user mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7832|2024-08-15T13:31:04.175Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7829|2024-08-15T13:51:06.579Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7829</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. This issue affects the function cgi_del_photo of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument current_path leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240814 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft die Funktion cgi_del_photo der Datei /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments current_path mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7829|2024-08-15T13:51:06.579Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 12:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7831|2024-08-15T13:00:08.266Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7831</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function cgi_get_cooliris of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument path leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
In D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240814 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es die Funktion cgi_get_cooliris der Datei /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. Durch Manipulation des Arguments path mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7831|2024-08-15T13:00:08.266Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7715|2024-08-14T20:54:51.331Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7715</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240812. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function sprintf of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument filter leads to command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240812 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist die Funktion sprintf der Datei /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments filter mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7715|2024-08-14T20:54:51.331Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 06:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7715|2024-08-13T06:31:04.655Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7715</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240812. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function sprintf of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument filter leads to command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240812 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist die Funktion sprintf der Datei /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments filter mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7715|2024-08-13T06:31:04.655Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 06:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7829|2024-08-15T12:31:05.244Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7829</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. This issue affects the function cgi_del_photo of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument current_path leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240814 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft die Funktion cgi_del_photo der Datei /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments current_path mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7829|2024-08-15T12:31:05.244Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 12:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7828|2024-08-15T12:31:03.787Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7828</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability classified as critical was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. This vulnerability affects the function cgi_set_cover of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument album_name leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
In D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240814 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Das betrifft die Funktion cgi_set_cover der Datei /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. Dank Manipulation des Arguments album_name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7828|2024-08-15T12:31:03.787Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 12:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7831|2024-08-15T14:32:51.171Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7831</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function cgi_get_cooliris of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument path leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
In D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240814 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es die Funktion cgi_get_cooliris der Datei /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. Durch Manipulation des Arguments path mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7831|2024-08-15T14:32:51.171Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7715|2024-08-15T14:28:38.576Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7715</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240812. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function sprintf of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument filter leads to command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240812 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist die Funktion sprintf der Datei /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments filter mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7715|2024-08-15T14:28:38.576Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 06:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7830|2024-08-15T14:42:39.873Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7830</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. Affected is the function cgi_move_photo of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument photo_name leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240814 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es die Funktion cgi_move_photo der Datei /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments photo_name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7830|2024-08-15T14:42:39.873Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7832|2024-08-16T15:09:53.544Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7832</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function cgi_get_fullscreen_photos of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument user leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240814 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist die Funktion cgi_get_fullscreen_photos der Datei /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments user mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7832|2024-08-16T15:09:53.544Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7828|2024-08-16T15:14:16.066Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7828</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability classified as critical was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. This vulnerability affects the function cgi_set_cover of the file /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. The manipulation of the argument album_name leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
In D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240814 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Das betrifft die Funktion cgi_set_cover der Datei /cgi-bin/photocenter_mgr.cgi. Dank Manipulation des Arguments album_name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7828|2024-08-16T15:14:16.066Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 12:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7922|2024-08-19T15:00:06.847Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7922</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function cgi_audio_search/cgi_create_playlist/cgi_get_album_all_tracks/cgi_get_alltracks_editlist/cgi_get_artist_all_album/cgi_get_genre_all_tracks/cgi_get_tracks_list/cgi_set_airplay_content/cgi_write_playlist of the file /cgi-bin/myMusic.cgi. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240814 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist die Funktion cgi_audio_search/cgi_create_playlist/cgi_get_album_all_tracks/cgi_get_alltracks_editlist/cgi_get_artist_all_album/cgi_get_genre_all_tracks/cgi_get_tracks_list/cgi_set_airplay_content/cgi_write_playlist der Datei /cgi-bin/myMusic.cgi. Durch das Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7922|2024-08-19T15:00:06.847Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 15:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8127|2024-08-24T09:31:05.244Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8127</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. This vulnerability affects the function cgi_unzip of the file /cgi-bin/webfile_mgr.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument path leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
In D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240814 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei geht es um die Funktion cgi_unzip der Datei /cgi-bin/webfile_mgr.cgi der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments path mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8127|2024-08-24T09:31:05.244Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 09:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8129|2024-08-24T15:31:05.810Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8129</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. Affected is the function cgi_s3_modify of the file /cgi-bin/s3.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument f_job_name leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240814 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es betrifft die Funktion cgi_s3_modify der Datei /cgi-bin/s3.cgi der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments f_job_name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8129|2024-08-24T15:31:05.810Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 15:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8131|2024-08-24T17:31:05.870Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8131</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function module_enable_disable of the file /cgi-bin/apkg_mgr.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument f_module_name leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240814 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft die Funktion module_enable_disable der Datei /cgi-bin/apkg_mgr.cgi der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments f_module_name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8131|2024-08-24T17:31:05.870Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 17:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8134|2024-08-24T20:00:06.287Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8134</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function cgi_FMT_Std2R5_1st_DiskMGR of the file /cgi-bin/hd_config.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument f_source_dev leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240814 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist die Funktion cgi_FMT_Std2R5_1st_DiskMGR der Datei /cgi-bin/hd_config.cgi der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Dank Manipulation des Arguments f_source_dev mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8134|2024-08-24T20:00:06.287Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 20:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8133|2024-08-24T19:00:06.248Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8133</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function cgi_FMT_R5_SpareDsk_DiskMGR of the file /cgi-bin/hd_config.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument f_source_dev leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
In D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240814 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es die Funktion cgi_FMT_R5_SpareDsk_DiskMGR der Datei /cgi-bin/hd_config.cgi der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments f_source_dev mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8133|2024-08-24T19:00:06.248Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 19:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8134|2024-08-26T14:41:17.128Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8134</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function cgi_FMT_Std2R5_1st_DiskMGR of the file /cgi-bin/hd_config.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument f_source_dev leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240814 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist die Funktion cgi_FMT_Std2R5_1st_DiskMGR der Datei /cgi-bin/hd_config.cgi der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Dank Manipulation des Arguments f_source_dev mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8134|2024-08-26T14:41:17.128Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 20:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8127|2024-08-26T16:05:13.557Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8127</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814. This vulnerability affects the function cgi_unzip of the file /cgi-bin/webfile_mgr.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument path leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
In D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240814 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei geht es um die Funktion cgi_unzip der Datei /cgi-bin/webfile_mgr.cgi der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments path mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8127|2024-08-26T16:05:13.557Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 09:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8130|2024-08-26T16:24:18.306Z -- d-link -- dns-120</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8130</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 up to 20240814 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function cgi_s3 of the file /cgi-bin/s3.cgi of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument f_a_key leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the product is end-of-life. It should be retired and replaced.
In D-Link DNS-120, DNR-202L, DNS-315L, DNS-320, DNS-320L, DNS-320LW, DNS-321, DNR-322L, DNS-323, DNS-325, DNS-326, DNS-327L, DNR-326, DNS-340L, DNS-343, DNS-345, DNS-726-4, DNS-1100-4, DNS-1200-05 and DNS-1550-04 bis 20240814 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Das betrifft die Funktion cgi_s3 der Datei /cgi-bin/s3.cgi der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments f_a_key mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8130|2024-08-26T16:24:18.306Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 16:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
