<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for D-Link -- G416</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/d-link/g416.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for D-Link -- G416</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 23:22:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50214|2024-08-02T22:09:49.766Z -- d-link -- g416
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50214</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 nodered tar File Handling Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21808.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50214|2024-08-02T22:09:49.766Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50208|2024-08-02T22:09:49.805Z -- d-link -- g416
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50208</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 ovpncfg Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21441.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50208|2024-08-02T22:09:49.805Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50199|2024-08-02T22:09:49.664Z -- d-link -- g416
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50199</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 httpd Missing Authentication for Critical Function Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of D-Link G416 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of authentication prior to allowing access to functionality. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to gain access to critical functions on the device. Was ZDI-CAN-21287.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50199|2024-08-02T22:09:49.664Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50209|2024-08-02T22:09:49.942Z -- d-link -- g416
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50209</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 cfgsave Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 wireless routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21442.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50209|2024-08-02T22:09:49.942Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50206|2024-08-02T22:09:49.650Z -- d-link -- g416
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50206</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 flupl query_type edit Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21299.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50206|2024-08-02T22:09:49.650Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50216|2024-08-02T22:09:49.786Z -- d-link -- g416
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50216</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 awsfile tar File Handling Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21810.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50216|2024-08-02T22:09:49.786Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50202|2024-08-02T22:09:49.716Z -- d-link -- g416
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50202</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 flupl pythonmodules Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 wireless routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21295.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50202|2024-08-02T22:09:49.716Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50200|2024-08-02T22:09:49.786Z -- d-link -- g416
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50200</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 cfgsave backusb Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21288.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50200|2024-08-02T22:09:49.786Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50207|2024-08-02T22:09:49.656Z -- d-link -- g416
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50207</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 flupl filename Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21300.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50207|2024-08-02T22:09:49.656Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50215|2024-08-02T22:09:49.869Z -- d-link -- g416
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50215</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 nodered gz File Handling Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21809.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50215|2024-08-02T22:09:49.869Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50217|2024-08-02T22:09:49.709Z -- d-link -- g416
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50217</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 awsfile rm Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21811.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50217|2024-08-02T22:09:49.709Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50213|2024-08-02T22:09:49.838Z -- d-link -- g416
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50213</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 nodered File Handling Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21807.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50213|2024-08-02T22:09:49.838Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50205|2024-08-02T22:09:49.835Z -- d-link -- g416
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50205</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 awsfile chmod Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21298.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50205|2024-08-02T22:09:49.835Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50198|2024-08-02T22:09:49.648Z -- d-link -- g416
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50198</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 cfgsave Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 wireless routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21286.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50198|2024-08-02T22:09:49.648Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50204|2024-08-02T22:09:49.772Z -- d-link -- g416
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50204</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 flupl pythonapp Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 wireless routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21297.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50204|2024-08-02T22:09:49.772Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50212|2024-08-02T22:09:49.690Z -- d-link -- g416
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50212</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 httpd Improper Handling of Exceptional Conditions Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of D-Link G416 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper handling of error conditions. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21664.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50212|2024-08-02T22:09:49.690Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50210|2024-08-02T22:09:50.019Z -- d-link -- g416
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50210</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 httpd API-AUTH Digest Processing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21662.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50210|2024-08-02T22:09:50.019Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50211|2024-08-02T22:09:50.001Z -- d-link -- g416
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50211</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 httpd API-AUTH Timestamp Processing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21663.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50211|2024-08-02T22:09:50.001Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50201|2024-08-02T22:09:49.701Z -- d-link -- g416
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50201</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 cfgsave upusb Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21289.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50201|2024-08-02T22:09:49.701Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50203|2024-08-02T22:09:49.778Z -- d-link -- g416
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50203</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 nodered chmod Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21296.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50203|2024-08-02T22:09:49.778Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50204|2024-06-04T17:18:07.819Z -- d-link -- g416</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50204</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 flupl pythonapp Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 wireless routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21297.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50204|2024-06-04T17:18:07.819Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50212|2024-06-04T17:18:07.406Z -- d-link -- g416</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50212</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 httpd Improper Handling of Exceptional Conditions Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of D-Link G416 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper handling of error conditions. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21664.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50212|2024-06-04T17:18:07.406Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50199|2024-06-04T17:18:05.749Z -- d-link -- g416</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50199</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 httpd Missing Authentication for Critical Function Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of D-Link G416 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of authentication prior to allowing access to functionality. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to gain access to critical functions on the device. Was ZDI-CAN-21287.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50199|2024-06-04T17:18:05.749Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50208|2024-06-04T17:18:04.865Z -- d-link -- g416</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50208</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 ovpncfg Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21441.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50208|2024-06-04T17:18:04.865Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50209|2024-06-04T17:18:03.950Z -- d-link -- g416</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50209</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 cfgsave Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 wireless routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21442.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50209|2024-06-04T17:18:03.950Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50198|2024-06-04T17:18:03.496Z -- d-link -- g416</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50198</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 cfgsave Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 wireless routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21286.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50198|2024-06-04T17:18:03.496Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50213|2024-06-04T17:18:02.190Z -- d-link -- g416</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50213</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 nodered File Handling Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21807.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50213|2024-06-04T17:18:02.190Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50205|2024-06-04T17:18:01.714Z -- d-link -- g416</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50205</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 awsfile chmod Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21298.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50205|2024-06-04T17:18:01.714Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50202|2024-06-04T17:17:56.224Z -- d-link -- g416</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50202</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 flupl pythonmodules Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 wireless routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21295.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50202|2024-06-04T17:17:56.224Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50214|2024-06-04T17:17:55.321Z -- d-link -- g416</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50214</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 nodered tar File Handling Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21808.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50214|2024-06-04T17:17:55.321Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50215|2024-06-04T17:17:54.028Z -- d-link -- g416</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50215</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 nodered gz File Handling Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21809.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50215|2024-06-04T17:17:54.028Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50203|2024-06-04T17:17:53.609Z -- d-link -- g416</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50203</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 nodered chmod Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21296.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50203|2024-06-04T17:17:53.609Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50216|2024-06-04T17:17:49.171Z -- d-link -- g416</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50216</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 awsfile tar File Handling Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21810.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50216|2024-06-04T17:17:49.171Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50200|2024-06-04T17:17:48.731Z -- d-link -- g416</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50200</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 cfgsave backusb Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21288.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50200|2024-06-04T17:17:48.731Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50201|2024-06-04T17:17:45.250Z -- d-link -- g416</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50201</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 cfgsave upusb Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21289.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50201|2024-06-04T17:17:45.250Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50217|2024-06-04T17:17:44.813Z -- d-link -- g416</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50217</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 awsfile rm Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21811.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50217|2024-06-04T17:17:44.813Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50210|2024-06-04T17:17:43.500Z -- d-link -- g416</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50210</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 httpd API-AUTH Digest Processing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21662.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50210|2024-06-04T17:17:43.500Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50206|2024-06-04T17:17:43.069Z -- d-link -- g416</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50206</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 flupl query_type edit Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21299.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50206|2024-06-04T17:17:43.069Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50207|2024-06-04T17:17:38.237Z -- d-link -- g416</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50207</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 flupl filename Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21300.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50207|2024-06-04T17:17:38.237Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50211|2024-06-04T17:17:37.818Z -- d-link -- g416</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50211</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 httpd API-AUTH Timestamp Processing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21663.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50211|2024-06-04T17:17:37.818Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5295|2024-06-04T18:02:59.195Z -- d-link -- g416</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5295</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 flupl self Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 wireless routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21294.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5295|2024-06-04T18:02:59.195Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 21:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5295|2024-08-01T21:11:12.437Z -- d-link -- g416</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5295</link>
      <description>D-Link G416 flupl self Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link G416 wireless routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the HTTP service listening on TCP port 80. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21294.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5295|2024-08-01T21:11:12.437Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 21:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
