<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Arno0x -- TwoFactorAuth</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/arno0x/twofactorauth.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Arno0x -- TwoFactorAuth</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 16:24:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-15030|2024-08-06T03:47:34.840Z -- arno0x -- twofactorauth
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-15030</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Arno0x TwoFactorAuth. This affects an unknown part of the file login/login.php. The manipulation of the argument from leads to open redirect. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The patch is named 8549ad3cf197095f783643e41333586d6a4d0e54. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-223803.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Arno0x TwoFactorAuth entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei login/login.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments from mit unbekannten Daten kann eine open redirect-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Dieses Produkt setzt Rolling Releases ein. Aus diesem Grund sind Details zu betroffenen oder zu aktualisierende Versionen nicht verfügbar. Der Patch wird als 8549ad3cf197095f783643e41333586d6a4d0e54 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-15030|2024-08-06T03:47:34.840Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 17:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
