<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for seccome -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/seccome/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for seccome -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 21:21:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3729|2024-08-03T01:20:57.204Z -- seccome -- ehoney
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3729</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in seccome Ehoney. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /api/v1/attack. The manipulation of the argument AttackIP leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-212411.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3729|2024-08-03T01:20:57.204Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3731|2024-08-03T01:20:57.612Z -- seccome -- ehoney
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3731</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in seccome Ehoney and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /api/v1/attack/token. The manipulation of the argument Payload leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The identifier VDB-212413 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3731|2024-08-03T01:20:57.612Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3735|2024-08-03T01:20:57.695Z -- seccome -- ehoney
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3735</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in seccome Ehoney. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /api/public/signup. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The identifier VDB-212417 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3735|2024-08-03T01:20:57.695Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3730|2024-08-03T01:20:57.526Z -- seccome -- ehoney
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3730</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in seccome Ehoney. Affected is an unknown function of the file /api/v1/attack/falco. The manipulation of the argument Payload leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-212412.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3730|2024-08-03T01:20:57.526Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3732|2024-08-03T01:20:57.567Z -- seccome -- ehoney
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3732</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in seccome Ehoney and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /api/v1/bait/set. The manipulation of the argument Payload leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. VDB-212414 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3732|2024-08-03T01:20:57.567Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
