<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for sc0ttkclark -- Pods – Custom Content Types and Fields</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sc0ttkclark/pods%20%E2%80%93%20custom%20content%20types%20and%20fields.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for sc0ttkclark -- Pods – Custom Content Types and Fields</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6965|2024-06-04T17:17:14.268Z -- sc0ttkclark -- pods%20%E2%80%93%20custom%20content%20types%20and%20fields
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6965</link>
      <description>The Pods – Custom Content Types and Fields plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.10 (with the exception of 2.7.31.2, 2.8.23.2, 2.9.19.2). This is due to the fact that the plugin allows the use of a file inclusion feature via shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to create pods and users (with default role).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6965|2024-06-04T17:17:14.268Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:59:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6967|2024-04-09T18:58:35.411Z -- sc0ttkclark -- pods%20%E2%80%93%20custom%20content%20types%20and%20fields
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6967</link>
      <description>The Pods – Custom Content Types and Fields plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.10 (with the exception of 2.7.31.2, 2.8.23.2, 2.9.19.2) due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor level access or higher, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6967|2024-04-09T18:58:35.411Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:58:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6999|2024-04-09T18:59:26.244Z -- sc0ttkclark -- pods%20%E2%80%93%20custom%20content%20types%20and%20fields
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6999</link>
      <description>The Pods – Custom Content Types and Fields plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Exxecution via shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.10 (with the exception of 2.7.31.2, 2.8.23.2, 2.9.19.2). This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor level access or higher, to execute code on the server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6999|2024-04-09T18:59:26.244Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:59:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3956|2024-06-04T17:32:22.346Z -- sc0ttkclark -- pods%20%E2%80%93%20custom%20content%20types%20and%20fields
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3956</link>
      <description>The Pods – Custom Content Types and Fields plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Pod Form widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3956|2024-06-04T17:32:22.346Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 08:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
