<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cloudflare -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cloudflare/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cloudflare -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1862|2023-06-20T08:28:12.578Z -- cloudflare -- warp%20client
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1862</link>
      <description>Cloudflare WARP client for Windows (up to v2023.3.381.0) allowed a malicious actor to remotely access the warp-svc.exe binary due to an insufficient access control policy on an IPC Named Pipe. This would have enabled an attacker to trigger WARP connect and disconnect commands, as well as obtaining network diagnostics and application configuration from the target's device. It is important to note that in order to exploit this, a set of requirements would need to be met, such as the target's device must've been reachable on port 445, allowed authentication with NULL sessions or otherwise having knowledge of the target's credentials.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1862|2023-06-20T08:28:12.578Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 08:28:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1412|2023-04-05T15:22:56.317Z -- cloudflare -- warp
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1412</link>
      <description>An unprivileged (non-admin) user can exploit an Improper Access Control vulnerability in the Cloudflare WARP Client for Windows (&lt;= 2022.12.582.0) to perform privileged operations with SYSTEM context by working with a combination of opportunistic locks (oplock) and symbolic links (which can both be created by an unprivileged user).

After installing the Cloudflare WARP Client (admin privileges required), an MSI-Installer is placed under C:\Windows\Installer. The vulnerability lies in the repair function of this MSI.

ImpactAn unprivileged (non-admin) user can exploit this vulnerability to perform privileged operations with SYSTEM context, including deleting arbitrary files and reading arbitrary file content. This can lead to a variety of attacks, including the manipulation of system files and privilege escalation.

PatchesA new installer with a fix that addresses this vulnerability was released in version 2023.3.381.0. While the WARP Client itself is not vulnerable (only the installer), users are encouraged to upgrade to the latest version and delete any older installers present in their systems.




</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1412|2023-04-05T15:22:56.317Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 15:22:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1314|2023-03-21T11:01:14.062Z -- cloudflare -- cloudflared
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1314</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been discovered in cloudflared's installer (&lt;= 2023.3.0) for Windows 32-bits devices that allows a local attacker with no administrative permissions to escalate their privileges on the affected device. This vulnerability exists because the MSI installer used by cloudflared relied on a world-writable directory.

An attacker with local access to the device (without Administrator rights) can use symbolic links to trick the MSI installer into deleting files in locations that the attacker would otherwise have no access to. By creating a symlink from the world-writable directory to the target file, the attacker can manipulate the MSI installer's repair functionality to delete the target file during the repair process.

Exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an attacker to delete important system files or replace them with malicious files, potentially leading to the affected device being compromised.

The cloudflared client itself is not affected by this vulnerability, only the installer for 32-bit Windows devices.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1314|2023-03-21T11:01:14.062Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 11:01:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1732|2023-05-10T11:41:53.902Z -- cloudflare -- circl
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1732</link>
      <description>When sampling randomness for a shared secret, the implementation of Kyber and FrodoKEM, did not check whether crypto/rand.Read() returns an error. In rare deployment cases (error thrown by the Read() function), this could lead to a predictable shared secret.

The tkn20 and blindrsa components did not check whether enough randomness was returned from the user provided randomness source. Typically the user provides crypto/rand.Reader, which in the vast majority of cases will always return the right number random bytes. In the cases where it does not, or the user provides a source that does not, the blinding for blindrsa is weak and integrity of the plaintext is not ensured in tkn20.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1732|2023-05-10T11:41:53.902Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 11:41:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0654|2023-08-29T15:05:19.623Z -- cloudflare -- warp%20client
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0654</link>
      <description>Due to a misconfiguration, the WARP Mobile Client (&lt; 6.29) for Android was susceptible to a tapjacking attack. In the event that an attacker built a malicious application and managed to install it on a victim's device, the attacker would be able to trick the user into believing that the app shown on the screen was the WARP client when in reality it was the attacker's app.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0654|2023-08-29T15:05:19.623Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 15:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0652|2023-04-06T09:48:14.685Z -- cloudflare -- warp
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0652</link>
      <description>Due to a hardlink created in the ProgramData folder during the repair process of the software, the installer (MSI) of WARP Client for Windows (&lt;= 2022.12.582.0) allowed a malicious attacker to forge the destination of the hardlink and escalate privileges, overwriting SYSTEM protected files.
As Cloudflare WARP client for Windows (up to version 2022.5.309.0) allowed creation of mount points from its ProgramData folder, during installation of the WARP client, it was possible to escalate privileges and overwrite SYSTEM protected files.


</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0652|2023-04-06T09:48:14.685Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 09:42:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0238|2023-08-29T14:56:50.791Z -- cloudflare -- warp%20client
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0238</link>
      <description>Due to lack of a security policy, the WARP Mobile Client (&lt;=6.29) for Android was susceptible to this vulnerability which allowed a malicious app installed on a victim's device to exploit a peculiarity in an Android function, wherein under certain conditions, the malicious app could dictate the task behaviour of the WARP app.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0238|2023-08-29T14:56:50.791Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 14:56:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4241|2023-08-16T10:13:12.564Z -- cloudflare -- lol-html
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4241</link>
      <description>lol-html can cause panics on certain HTML inputs. Anyone processing arbitrary 3rd party HTML with the library is affected.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4241|2023-08-16T10:13:12.564Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 10:13:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3747|2023-09-07T12:11:01.435Z -- cloudflare -- warp%20client
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3747</link>
      <description>Zero Trust Administrators have the ability to disallow end users from disabling WARP on their devices. Override codes can also be created by the Administrators to allow a device to temporarily be disconnected from WARP, however, due to lack of server side validation, an attacker with local access to the device, could extend the maximum allowed disconnected time of WARP client granted by an override code by changing the date &amp; time on the local device where WARP is running.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3747|2023-09-07T12:11:01.435Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 12:11:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3766|2023-08-03T13:49:46.751Z -- cloudflare -- odoh-rs
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3766</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was discovered in the odoh-rs rust crate that stems from faulty logic during the parsing of encrypted queries. This issue specifically occurs when processing encrypted query data received from remote clients and enables an attacker with knowledge of this vulnerability to craft and send specially designed encrypted queries to targeted ODOH servers running with odoh-rs. Upon successful exploitation, the server will crash abruptly, disrupting its normal operation and rendering the service temporarily unavailable.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3766|2023-08-03T13:49:46.751Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 13:49:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3348|2023-08-29T09:17:49.419Z -- cloudflare -- wrangler
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3348</link>
      <description>The Wrangler command line tool  (&lt;=wrangler@3.1.0 or &lt;=wrangler@2.20.1) was affected by a directory traversal vulnerability when running a local development server for Pages (wrangler pages dev command). This vulnerability enabled an attacker in the same network as the victim to connect to the local development server and access the victim's files present outside of the directory for the development server.



</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3348|2023-08-29T09:17:49.419Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 13:47:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3036|2023-06-14T11:08:28.361Z -- cloudflare -- cfnts
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3036</link>
      <description>An unchecked read in NTP server in github.com/cloudflare/cfnts prior to commit  783490b https://github.com/cloudflare/cfnts/commit/783490b913f05e508a492cd7b02e3c4ec2297b71  enabled a remote attacker to trigger a panic by sending an NTSAuthenticator packet with extension length longer than the packet contents.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3036|2023-06-14T11:08:28.361Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 11:08:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3040|2023-06-14T11:55:19.181Z -- cloudflare -- lua-resty-json
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3040</link>
      <description>A debug function in the lua-resty-json package, up to commit id 3ef9492bd3a44d9e51301d6adc3cd1789c8f534a (merged in PR #14) contained an out of bounds access bug that could have allowed an attacker to launch a DoS if the function was used to parse untrusted input data. It is important to note that because this debug function was only used in tests and demos, it was not exploitable in a normal environment.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3040|2023-06-14T11:55:19.181Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 11:54:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7079|2023-12-29T12:08:49.883Z -- cloudflare -- wrangler
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-7079</link>
      <description>Sending specially crafted HTTP requests and inspector messages to Wrangler's dev server could result in any file on the user's computer being accessible over the local network. An attacker that could trick any user on the local network into opening a malicious website could also read any file.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7079|2023-12-29T12:08:49.883Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 11:54:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7080|2023-12-29T12:08:25.935Z -- cloudflare -- wrangler
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-7080</link>
      <description>The V8 inspector intentionally allows arbitrary code execution within the Workers sandbox for debugging. wrangler dev would previously start an inspector server listening on all network interfaces. This would allow an attacker on the local network to connect to the inspector and run arbitrary code. Additionally, the inspector server did not validate Origin/Host headers, granting an attacker that can trick any user on the local network into opening a malicious website the ability to run code. If wrangler dev --remote was being used, an attacker could access production resources if they were bound to the worker.

This issue was fixed in wrangler@3.19.0 and wrangler@2.20.2. Whilst wrangler dev's inspector server listens on local interfaces by default as of wrangler@3.16.0, an  SSRF vulnerability in miniflare https://github.com/cloudflare/workers-sdk/security/advisories/GHSA-fwvg-2739-22v7  (CVE-2023-7078) allowed access from the local network until wrangler@3.18.0. wrangler@3.19.0 and wrangler@2.20.2 introduced validation for the Origin/Host headers.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7080|2023-12-29T12:08:25.935Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 11:58:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7078|2023-12-29T12:09:03.496Z -- cloudflare -- miniflare
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-7078</link>
      <description>Sending specially crafted HTTP requests to Miniflare's server could result in arbitrary HTTP and WebSocket requests being sent from the server. If Miniflare was configured to listen on external network interfaces (as was the default in wrangler until 3.19.0), an attacker on the local network could access other local servers.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7078|2023-12-29T12:09:03.496Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 11:53:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6180|2023-12-05T15:02:40.007Z -- cloudflare -- tokio-boring
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6180</link>
      <description>The tokio-boring library in version 4.0.0 is affected by a memory leak issue that can lead to excessive resource consumption and potential DoS by resource exhaustion. The set_ex_data function used by the library did not deallocate memory used by pre-existing data in memory each time after completing a TLS connection causing the program to consume more resources with each new connection.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6180|2023-12-05T15:02:40.007Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 15:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6992|2024-01-04T11:14:15.933Z -- cloudflare -- zlib
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6992</link>
      <description>Cloudflare version of zlib library was found to be vulnerable to memory corruption issues affecting the deflation algorithm implementation (deflate.c). The issues resulted from improper input validation and heap-based buffer overflow.
A local attacker could exploit the problem during compression using a crafted malicious file potentially leading to denial of service of the software.
Patches: The issue has been patched in commit  8352d10 https://github.com/cloudflare/zlib/commit/8352d108c05db1bdc5ac3bdf834dad641694c13c . The upstream repository is not affected.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6992|2024-01-04T11:14:15.933Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 11:11:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6193|2023-12-12T13:32:03.183Z -- cloudflare -- quiche
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6193</link>
      <description>quiche v. 0.15.0 through 0.19.0 was discovered to be vulnerable to unbounded queuing of path validation messages, which could lead to excessive resource consumption.
QUIC path validation (RFC 9000 Section 8.2) requires that the recipient of a PATH_CHALLENGE frame responds by sending a PATH_RESPONSE. An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit the vulnerability by sending PATH_CHALLENGE frames and manipulating the connection (e.g. by restricting the peer's congestion window size) so that PATH_RESPONSE frames can only be sent at the slower rate than they are received; leading to storage of path validation data in an unbounded queue. 
Quiche versions greater than 0.19.0 address this problem.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6193|2023-12-12T13:32:03.183Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 13:32:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2512|2023-05-12T10:10:21.870Z -- cloudflare -- workerd
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-2512</link>
      <description>Prior to version v1.20230419.0, the FormData API implementation was subject to an integer overflow. If a FormData instance contained more than 2^31 elements, the forEach() method could end up reading from the wrong location in memory while iterating over elements. This would most likely lead to a segmentation fault, but could theoretically allow arbitrary undefined behavior.


In order for the bug to be exploitable, the process would need to be able to allocate 160GB of RAM. Due to this, the bug was never exploitable on the Cloudflare Workers platform, but could theoretically be exploitable on deployments of workerd running on machines with a huge amount of memory. Moreover, in order to be remotely exploited, an attacker would have to upload a single form-encoded HTTP request of at least tens of gigabytes in size. The application code would then have to use request.formData() to parse the request and formData.forEach() to iterate over this data. Due to these limitations, the exploitation likelihood was considered Low.

A fix that addresses this vulnerability has been released in version v1.20230419.0 and users are encouraged to update to the latest version available.


</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2512|2023-05-12T10:10:21.870Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 10:09:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2754|2023-08-03T13:53:00.634Z -- cloudflare -- warp
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-2754</link>
      <description>The Cloudflare WARP client for Windows assigns loopback IPv4 addresses for the DNS Servers, since WARP acts as local DNS server that performs DNS queries in a secure manner, however, if a user is connected to WARP over an IPv6-capable network, te WARP client did not assign loopback IPv6 addresses but Unique Local Addresses, which under certain conditions could point towards unknown devices in the same local network which enables an Attacker to view DNS queries made by the device.


</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2754|2023-08-03T13:53:00.634Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 13:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1765|2024-06-04T18:00:25.467Z -- cloudflare -- quiche
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1765</link>
      <description>Cloudflare Quiche (through version 0.19.1/0.20.0) was affected by an unlimited resource allocation vulnerability causing rapid increase of memory usage of the system running quiche server or client.
A remote attacker could take advantage of this vulnerability by repeatedly sending an unlimited number of 1-RTT CRYPTO frames after previously completing the QUIC handshake.
Exploitation was possible for the duration of the connection which could be extended by the attacker. 
quiche 0.19.2 and 0.20.1 are the earliest versions containing the fix for this issue.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1765|2024-06-04T18:00:25.467Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 18:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1410|2024-06-04T17:59:28.523Z -- cloudflare -- quiche
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1410</link>
      <description>Cloudflare quiche was discovered to be vulnerable to unbounded storage of information related to connection ID retirement, which could lead to excessive resource consumption. Each QUIC connection possesses a set of connection Identifiers (IDs); see  RFC 9000 Section 5.1 https://datatracker.ietf.org/doc/html/rfc9000#section-5.1 . Endpoints declare the number of active connection IDs they are willing to support using the active_connection_id_limit transport parameter. The peer can create new IDs using a NEW_CONNECTION_ID frame but must stay within the active ID limit. This is done by retirement of old IDs, the endpoint sends NEW_CONNECTION_ID includes a value in the retire_prior_to field, which elicits a RETIRE_CONNECTION_ID frame as confirmation. An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit the vulnerability by sending NEW_CONNECTION_ID frames and manipulating the connection (e.g. by restricting the peer's congestion window size) so that RETIRE_CONNECTION_ID frames can only be sent at a slower rate than they are received, leading to storage of information related to connection IDs in an unbounded queue. Quiche versions 0.19.2 and 0.20.1 are the earliest to address this problem. There is no workaround for affected versions.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1410|2024-06-04T17:59:28.523Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 18:06:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0212|2024-01-29T09:13:44.939Z -- cloudflare -- cloudflare-wordpress
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0212</link>
      <description>The Cloudflare Wordpress plugin was found to be vulnerable to improper authentication. The vulnerability enables attackers with a lower privileged account to access data from the Cloudflare API.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0212|2024-01-29T09:13:44.939Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 09:13:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
