<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cloudflare -- WARP</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cloudflare/warp.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cloudflare -- WARP</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 11:20:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1412|2024-08-02T05:49:11.409Z -- cloudflare -- warp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1412</link>
      <description>An unprivileged (non-admin) user can exploit an Improper Access Control vulnerability in the Cloudflare WARP Client for Windows (&lt;= 2022.12.582.0) to perform privileged operations with SYSTEM context by working with a combination of opportunistic locks (oplock) and symbolic links (which can both be created by an unprivileged user).

After installing the Cloudflare WARP Client (admin privileges required), an MSI-Installer is placed under C:\Windows\Installer. The vulnerability lies in the repair function of this MSI.

ImpactAn unprivileged (non-admin) user can exploit this vulnerability to perform privileged operations with SYSTEM context, including deleting arbitrary files and reading arbitrary file content. This can lead to a variety of attacks, including the manipulation of system files and privilege escalation.

PatchesA new installer with a fix that addresses this vulnerability was released in version 2023.3.381.0. While the WARP Client itself is not vulnerable (only the installer), users are encouraged to upgrade to the latest version and delete any older installers present in their systems.




</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1412|2024-08-02T05:49:11.409Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 15:22:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2754|2024-08-02T06:33:05.480Z -- cloudflare -- warp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2754</link>
      <description>The Cloudflare WARP client for Windows assigns loopback IPv4 addresses for the DNS Servers, since WARP acts as local DNS server that performs DNS queries in a secure manner, however, if a user is connected to WARP over an IPv6-capable network, te WARP client did not assign loopback IPv6 addresses but Unique Local Addresses, which under certain conditions could point towards unknown devices in the same local network which enables an Attacker to view DNS queries made by the device.


</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2754|2024-08-02T06:33:05.480Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 13:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0652|2024-08-02T05:17:50.356Z -- cloudflare -- warp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0652</link>
      <description>Due to a hardlink created in the ProgramData folder during the repair process of the software, the installer (MSI) of WARP Client for Windows (&lt;= 2022.12.582.0) allowed a malicious attacker to forge the destination of the hardlink and escalate privileges, overwriting SYSTEM protected files.
As Cloudflare WARP client for Windows (up to version 2022.5.309.0) allowed creation of mount points from its ProgramData folder, during installation of the WARP client, it was possible to escalate privileges and overwrite SYSTEM protected files.


</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0652|2024-08-02T05:17:50.356Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 09:42:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
