<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Opencaching Deutschland -- oc-server3</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/opencaching%20deutschland/oc-server3.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Opencaching Deutschland -- oc-server3</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 20:22:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4514|2024-08-03T01:41:45.630Z -- opencaching%20deutschland -- oc-server3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4514</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Opencaching Deutschland oc-server3. Affected is an unknown function of the file htdocs/lang/de/ocstyle/varset.inc.php. The manipulation of the argument varvalue leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The name of the patch is 4bdd6a0e7b7760cea03b91812cbb80d7b16e3b5f. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. VDB-215886 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4514|2024-08-03T01:41:45.630Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4586|2024-08-03T01:41:45.808Z -- opencaching%20deutschland -- oc-server3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4586</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Opencaching Deutschland oc-server3. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file htdocs/templates2/ocstyle/cachelists.tpl of the component Cachelist Handler. The manipulation of the argument name_filter/by_filter leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The name of the patch is a9f79c7da78cd24a7ef1d298e6bc86006972ea73. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-216172.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4586|2024-08-03T01:41:45.808Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4585|2024-08-03T01:41:45.693Z -- opencaching%20deutschland -- oc-server3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4585</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Opencaching Deutschland oc-server3. This affects an unknown part of the file htdocs/templates2/ocstyle/start.tpl of the component Cookie Handler. The manipulation of the argument usercountryCode leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The name of the patch is c720f2777a452186c67ef30db3679dd409556544. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-216171.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4585|2024-08-03T01:41:45.693Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4587|2024-08-03T01:41:45.792Z -- opencaching%20deutschland -- oc-server3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4587</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Opencaching Deutschland oc-server3. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file htdocs/templates2/ocstyle/login.tpl of the component Login Page. The manipulation of the argument username leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The name of the patch is 3296ebd61e7fe49e93b5755d5d7766d6e94a7667. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier VDB-216173 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4587|2024-08-03T01:41:45.792Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
