<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for The libssh2 Project -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/the%20libssh2%20project/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for The libssh2 Project -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 20:23:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3860|2024-08-04T19:19:18.589Z -- the%20libssh2%20project -- libssh2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3860</link>
      <description>An out of bounds read flaw was discovered in libssh2 before 1.8.1 in the way SFTP packets with empty payloads are parsed. A remote attacker who compromises a SSH server may be able to cause a Denial of Service or read data in the client memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3860|2024-08-04T19:19:18.589Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 18:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3862|2024-08-04T19:19:18.615Z -- the%20libssh2%20project -- libssh2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3862</link>
      <description>An out of bounds read flaw was discovered in libssh2 before 1.8.1 in the way SSH_MSG_CHANNEL_REQUEST packets with an exit status message and no payload are parsed. A remote attacker who compromises a SSH server may be able to cause a Denial of Service or read data in the client memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3862|2024-08-04T19:19:18.615Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 21:39:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3855|2024-08-04T19:19:18.675Z -- the%20libssh2%20project -- libssh2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3855</link>
      <description>An integer overflow flaw which could lead to an out of bounds write was discovered in libssh2 before 1.8.1 in the way packets are read from the server. A remote attacker who compromises a SSH server may be able to execute code on the client system when a user connects to the server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3855|2024-08-04T19:19:18.675Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 20:13:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3859|2024-08-04T19:19:18.624Z -- the%20libssh2%20project -- libssh2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3859</link>
      <description>An out of bounds read flaw was discovered in libssh2 before 1.8.1 in the _libssh2_packet_require and _libssh2_packet_requirev functions. A remote attacker who compromises a SSH server may be able to cause a Denial of Service or read data in the client memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3859|2024-08-04T19:19:18.624Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 21:18:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3861|2024-08-04T19:19:18.629Z -- the%20libssh2%20project -- libssh2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3861</link>
      <description>An out of bounds read flaw was discovered in libssh2 before 1.8.1 in the way SSH packets with a padding length value greater than the packet length are parsed. A remote attacker who compromises a SSH server may be able to cause a Denial of Service or read data in the client memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3861|2024-08-04T19:19:18.629Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 18:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3858|2024-08-04T19:19:18.593Z -- the%20libssh2%20project -- libssh2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3858</link>
      <description>An out of bounds read flaw was discovered in libssh2 before 1.8.1 when a specially crafted SFTP packet is received from the server. A remote attacker who compromises a SSH server may be able to cause a Denial of Service or read data in the client memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3858|2024-08-04T19:19:18.593Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 20:22:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3856|2024-08-04T19:19:18.557Z -- the%20libssh2%20project -- libssh2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3856</link>
      <description>An integer overflow flaw, which could lead to an out of bounds write, was discovered in libssh2 before 1.8.1 in the way keyboard prompt requests are parsed. A remote attacker who compromises a SSH server may be able to execute code on the client system when a user connects to the server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3856|2024-08-04T19:19:18.557Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 18:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3857|2024-08-04T19:19:18.668Z -- the%20libssh2%20project -- libssh2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3857</link>
      <description>An integer overflow flaw which could lead to an out of bounds write was discovered in libssh2 before 1.8.1 in the way SSH_MSG_CHANNEL_REQUEST packets with an exit signal are parsed. A remote attacker who compromises a SSH server may be able to execute code on the client system when a user connects to the server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3857|2024-08-04T19:19:18.668Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 18:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3863|2024-08-04T19:19:18.614Z -- the%20libssh2%20project -- libssh2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3863</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in libssh2 before 1.8.1. A server could send a multiple keyboard interactive response messages whose total length are greater than unsigned char max characters. This value is used as an index to copy memory causing in an out of bounds memory write error.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3863|2024-08-04T19:19:18.614Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 17:52:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
