<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Fujian Kelixin Communication -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/fujian%20kelixin%20communication/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Fujian Kelixin Communication -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2566|2024-03-17T15:00:06.050Z -- fujian%20kelixin%20communication -- command%20and%20dispatch%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2566</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Fujian Kelixin Communication Command and Dispatch Platform up to 20240313. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file api/client/get_extension_yl.php. The manipulation of the argument imei leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257065 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In Fujian Kelixin Communication Command and Dispatch Platform bis 20240313 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei api/client/get_extension_yl.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments imei mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2566|2024-03-17T15:00:06.050Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 15:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2622|2024-03-19T02:00:07.258Z -- fujian%20kelixin%20communication -- command%20and%20dispatch%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2622</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Fujian Kelixin Communication Command and Dispatch Platform up to 20240318. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /api/client/editemedia.php. The manipulation of the argument number/enterprise_uuid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257199.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Fujian Kelixin Communication Command and Dispatch Platform bis 20240318 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei /api/client/editemedia.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments number/enterprise_uuid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2622|2024-03-19T02:00:07.258Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 02:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2620|2024-03-19T01:00:06.531Z -- fujian%20kelixin%20communication -- command%20and%20dispatch%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2620</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Fujian Kelixin Communication Command and Dispatch Platform up to 20240318 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file api/client/down_file.php. The manipulation of the argument uuid leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257197 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In Fujian Kelixin Communication Command and Dispatch Platform bis 20240318 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei api/client/down_file.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments uuid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2620|2024-03-19T01:00:06.531Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 01:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2621|2024-03-19T01:00:08.253Z -- fujian%20kelixin%20communication -- command%20and%20dispatch%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2621</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Fujian Kelixin Communication Command and Dispatch Platform up to 20240318 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file api/client/user/pwd_update.php. The manipulation of the argument uuid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-257198 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Fujian Kelixin Communication Command and Dispatch Platform bis 20240318 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei api/client/user/pwd_update.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments uuid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2621|2024-03-19T01:00:08.253Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 01:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
