<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cloud Foundry -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cloud%20foundry/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cloud Foundry -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:25:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5420|2024-09-17T02:06:44.110Z -- cloud%20foundry -- routing
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5420</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry Routing (Gorouter) versions prior to 0.206.0 allow a malicious developer with "cf push" access to cause denial-of-service to the CF cluster by pushing an app that returns specially crafted HTTP responses that crash the Gorouters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5420|2024-09-17T02:06:44.110Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 01:10:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11047|2024-09-17T02:41:49.974Z -- cloud%20foundry -- cloud%20foundry%20uaa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11047</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry UAA, versions 4.19 prior to 4.19.2 and 4.12 prior to 4.12.4 and 4.10 prior to 4.10.2 and 4.7 prior to 4.7.6 and 4.5 prior to 4.5.7, incorrectly authorizes requests to admin endpoints by accepting a valid refresh token in lieu of an access token. Refresh tokens by design have a longer expiration time than access tokens, allowing the possessor of a refresh token to authenticate longer than expected. This affects the administrative endpoints of the UAA. i.e. /Users, /Groups, etc. However, if the user has been deleted or had groups removed, or the client was deleted, the refresh token will no longer be valid.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11047|2024-09-17T02:41:49.974Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3785|2024-09-17T01:56:39.503Z -- cloud%20foundry -- capi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3785</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry Cloud Controller, versions prior to 1.78.0, contain an endpoint with improper authorization. A remote authenticated malicious user with read permissions can request package information and receive a signed bit-service url that grants the user write permissions to the bit-service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3785|2024-09-17T01:56:39.503Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11270|2024-09-17T04:19:01.006Z -- cloud%20foundry -- uaa%20release%20%28oss%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11270</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry UAA versions prior to v73.4.0 contain a vulnerability where a malicious client possessing the 'clients.write' authority or scope can bypass the restrictions imposed on clients created via 'clients.write' and create clients with arbitrary scopes that the creator does not possess.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11270|2024-09-17T04:19:01.006Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 16:21:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1193|2024-09-17T03:47:48.896Z -- cloud%20foundry -- cloud%20foundry%20router
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1193</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry routing-release, versions prior to 0.175.0, lacks sanitization for user-provided X-Forwarded-Proto headers. A remote user can set the X-Forwarded-Proto header in a request to potentially bypass an application requirement to only respond over secure connections.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1193|2024-09-17T03:47:48.896Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11268|2024-09-17T03:13:54.242Z -- cloud%20foundry -- uaa%20release%20%28oss%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11268</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry UAA version prior to 73.3.0, contain endpoints that contains improper escaping. An authenticated malicious user with basic read privileges for one identity zone can extend those reading privileges to all other identity zones and obtain private information on users, clients, and groups in all other identity zones.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11268|2024-09-17T03:13:54.242Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 18:11:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11271|2024-09-17T00:37:19.176Z -- cloud%20foundry -- bosh
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11271</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry BOSH 270.x versions prior to v270.1.1, contain a BOSH Director that does not properly redact credentials when configured to use a MySQL database. A local authenticated malicious user may read any credentials that are contained in a BOSH manifest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11271|2024-09-17T00:37:19.176Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 23:38:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11294|2024-09-17T02:27:12.722Z -- cloud%20foundry -- capi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11294</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry Cloud Controller API (CAPI), version 1.88.0, allows space developers to list all global service brokers, including service broker URLs and GUIDs, which should only be accessible to admins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11294|2024-09-17T02:27:12.722Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 19:35:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1269|2024-09-17T04:05:15.217Z -- cloud%20foundry -- loggregator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1269</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry Loggregator, versions 89.x prior to 89.5 or 96.x prior to 96.1 or 99.x prior to 99.1 or 101.x prior to 101.9 or 102.x prior to 102.2, does not handle errors thrown while constructing certain http requests. A remote authenticated user may construct malicious requests to cause the traffic controller to leave dangling TCP connections, which could cause denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1269|2024-09-17T04:05:15.217Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1268|2024-09-17T04:25:07.541Z -- cloud%20foundry -- loggregator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1268</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry Loggregator, versions 89.x prior to 89.5 or 96.x prior to 96.1 or 99.x prior to 99.1 or 101.x prior to 101.9 or 102.x prior to 102.2, does not validate app GUID structure in requests. A remote authenticated malicious user knowing the GUID of an app may construct malicious requests to read from or write to the logs of that app.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1268|2024-09-17T04:25:07.541Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15755|2024-09-17T00:31:36.023Z -- cloud%20foundry -- cf%20networking%20release
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15755</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry CF Networking Release, versions 2.11.0 prior to 2.16.0, contain an internal api endpoint vulnerable to SQL injection between Diego cells and the policy server. A remote authenticated malicious user with mTLS certs can issue arbitrary SQL queries and gain access to the policy server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15755|2024-09-17T00:31:36.023Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5400|2024-09-17T02:47:41.645Z -- cloud%20foundry -- capi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5400</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry Cloud Controller (CAPI), versions prior to 1.91.0, logs properties of background jobs when they are run, which may include sensitive information such as credentials if provided to the job. A malicious user with access to those logs may gain unauthorized access to resources protected by such credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5400|2024-09-17T02:47:41.645Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 19:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3798|2024-09-17T04:09:11.026Z -- cloud%20foundry -- capi-release
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3798</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry Cloud Controller API Release, versions prior to 1.79.0, contains improper authentication when validating user permissions. A remote authenticated malicious user with the ability to create UAA clients and knowledge of the email of a victim in the foundation may escalate their privileges to that of the victim by creating a client with a name equal to the guid of their victim.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3798|2024-09-17T04:09:11.026Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 13:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3800|2024-09-17T04:29:08.973Z -- cloud%20foundry -- cf%20cli%20release
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3800</link>
      <description>CF CLI version prior to v6.45.0 (bosh release version 1.16.0) writes the client id and secret to its config file when the user authenticates with --client-credentials flag. A local authenticated malicious user with access to the CF CLI config file can act as that client, who is the owner of the leaked credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3800|2024-09-17T04:29:08.973Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 16:38:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15761|2024-09-17T00:46:20.654Z -- cloud%20foundry -- uaa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15761</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry UAA release, versions prior to v64.0, and UAA, versions prior to 4.23.0, contains a validation error which allows for privilege escalation. A remote authenticated user may modify the url and content of a consent page to gain a token with arbitrary scopes that escalates their privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15761|2024-09-17T00:46:20.654Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3789|2024-09-17T04:14:31.804Z -- cloud%20foundry -- cf%20routing
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3789</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry Routing Release, all versions prior to 0.188.0, contains a vulnerability that can hijack the traffic to route services hosted outside the platform. A user with space developer permissions can create a private domain that shadows the external domain of the route service, and map that route to an app. When the gorouter receives traffic destined for the external route service, this traffic will instead be directed to the internal app using the shadow route.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3789|2024-09-17T04:14:31.804Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 15:21:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11082|2024-09-17T02:00:59.932Z -- cloud%20foundry -- uaa%20release
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11082</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry UAA, all versions prior to 4.20.0 and Cloud Foundry UAA Release, all versions prior to 61.0, allows brute forcing of MFA codes. A remote unauthenticated malicious user in possession of a valid username and password can brute force MFA to login as the targeted user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11082|2024-09-17T02:00:59.932Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5423|2024-09-17T03:43:03.193Z -- cloud%20foundry -- capi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5423</link>
      <description>CAPI (Cloud Controller) versions prior to 1.101.0 are vulnerable to a denial-of-service attack in which an unauthenticated malicious attacker can send specially-crafted YAML files to certain endpoints, causing the YAML parser to consume excessive CPU and RAM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5423|2024-09-17T03:43:03.193Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 01:55:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1265|2024-09-17T02:21:31.743Z -- cloud%20foundry -- diego
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1265</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry Diego, release versions prior to 2.8.0, does not properly sanitize file paths in tar and zip files headers. A remote attacker with CF admin privileges can upload a malicious buildpack that will allow a complete takeover of a Diego Cell VM and access to all apps running on that Diego Cell.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1265|2024-09-17T02:21:31.743Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3801|2024-09-17T02:56:41.904Z -- cloud%20foundry -- credhub
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3801</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry cf-deployment, versions prior to 7.9.0, contain java components that are using an insecure protocol to fetch dependencies when building. A remote unauthenticated malicious attacker could hijack the DNS entry for the dependency, and inject malicious code into the component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3801|2024-09-17T02:56:41.904Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 20:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1277|2024-09-17T00:16:40.209Z -- cloud%20foundry -- garden-runc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1277</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry Garden-runC, versions prior to 1.13.0, does not correctly enforce disc quotas for Docker image layers. A remote authenticated user may push an app with a malicious Docker image that will consume more space on a Diego cell than allocated in their quota, potentially causing a DoS against the cell.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1277|2024-09-17T00:16:40.209Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15800|2024-09-17T03:34:23.465Z -- cloud%20foundry -- bits%20service%20release
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15800</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry Bits Service, versions prior to 2.18.0, includes an information disclosure vulnerability. A remote malicious user may execute a timing attack to brute-force the signing key, allowing them complete read and write access to the the Bits Service storage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15800|2024-09-17T03:34:23.465Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11279|2024-09-17T02:36:57.958Z -- cloud%20foundry -- uaa%20release%20%28oss%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11279</link>
      <description>CF UAA versions prior to 74.1.0 can request scopes for a client that shouldn't be allowed by submitting an array of requested scopes. A remote malicious user can escalate their own privileges to any scope, allowing them to take control of UAA and the resources it controls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11279|2024-09-17T02:36:57.958Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2019 21:15:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11283|2024-09-17T02:01:09.354Z -- cloud%20foundry -- smb%20volume
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11283</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry SMB Volume, versions prior to v2.0.3, accidentally outputs sensitive information to the logs. A remote user with access to the SMB Volume logs can discover the username and password for volumes that have been recently created, allowing the user to take control of the SMB Volume.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11283|2024-09-17T02:01:09.354Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 15:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5422|2024-09-17T04:25:30.136Z -- cloud%20foundry -- bosh%20system%20metrics%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5422</link>
      <description>BOSH System Metrics Server releases prior to 0.1.0 exposed the UAA password as a flag to a process running on the BOSH director. It exposed the password to any user or process with access to the same VM (through ps or looking at process details).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5422|2024-09-17T04:25:30.136Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 17:10:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3786|2024-09-17T02:15:38.765Z -- cloud%20foundry -- bosh%20backup%20and%20restore
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3786</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry BOSH Backup and Restore CLI, all versions prior to 1.5.0, does not check the authenticity of backup scripts in BOSH. A remote authenticated malicious user can modify the metadata file of a Bosh Backup and Restore job to request extra backup files from different jobs upon restore. The exploited hooks in this metadata script were only maintained in the cfcr-etcd-release, so clusters deployed with the BBR job for etcd in this release are vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3786|2024-09-17T02:15:38.765Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 15:21:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1191|2024-09-17T04:10:09.194Z -- cloud%20foundry -- garden-runc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1191</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry Garden-runC, versions prior to 1.11.0, contains an information exposure vulnerability. A user with access to Garden logs may be able to obtain leaked credentials and perform authenticated actions using those credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1191|2024-09-17T04:10:09.194Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37082|2024-08-02T03:43:51.046Z -- cloud%20foundry -- haproxy-boshrelease</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37082</link>
      <description>When deploying Cloud Foundry together with the haproxy-boshrelease and using a non default configuration, it might be possible to craft HTTP requests that bypass mTLS authentication to Cloud Foundry applications. 

You are affected if you have route-services enabled in routing-release and have configured the haproxy-boshrelease property “ha_proxy.forwarded_client_cert” to “forward_only_if_route_service”.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37082|2024-08-02T03:43:51.046Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 06:08:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37082|2024-07-17T20:25:39.258Z -- cloud%20foundry -- haproxy-boshrelease</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37082</link>
      <description>When deploying Cloud Foundry together with the haproxy-boshrelease and using a non default configuration, it might be possible to craft HTTP requests that bypass mTLS authentication to Cloud Foundry applications. 

You are affected if you have route-services enabled in routing-release and have configured the haproxy-boshrelease property “ha_proxy.forwarded_client_cert” to “forward_only_if_route_service”.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37082|2024-07-17T20:25:39.258Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 06:08:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37082|2024-07-12T15:38:05.256Z -- cloud%20foundry -- haproxy-boshrelease</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37082</link>
      <description>When deploying Cloud Foundry together with the haproxy-boshrelease and using a non default configuration, it might be possible to craft HTTP requests that bypass mTLS authentication to Cloud Foundry applications. 

You are affected if you have route-services enabled in routing-release and have configured the haproxy-boshrelease property “ha_proxy.forwarded_client_cert” to “forward_only_if_route_service”.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37082|2024-07-12T15:38:05.256Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 06:08:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22279|2024-06-11T17:23:34.311Z -- cloud%20foundry -- routing%20release</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22279</link>
      <description>Improper handling of requests in Routing Release &gt; v0.273.0 and &lt;= v0.297.0 allows an unauthenticated attacker to degrade
 the service availability of the Cloud Foundry deployment if performed at scale.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22279|2024-06-11T17:23:34.311Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 19:47:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37082|2024-07-12T16:22:02.363Z -- cloud%20foundry -- haproxy-boshrelease</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37082</link>
      <description>When deploying Cloud Foundry together with the haproxy-boshrelease and using a non default configuration, it might be possible to craft HTTP requests that bypass mTLS authentication to Cloud Foundry applications. 

You are affected if you have route-services enabled in routing-release and have configured the haproxy-boshrelease property “ha_proxy.forwarded_client_cert” to “forward_only_if_route_service”.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37082|2024-07-12T16:22:02.363Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 06:08:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22279|2024-08-01T22:43:34.216Z -- cloud%20foundry -- routing%20release</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22279</link>
      <description>Improper handling of requests in Routing Release &gt; v0.273.0 and &lt;= v0.297.0 allows an unauthenticated attacker to degrade
 the service availability of the Cloud Foundry deployment if performed at scale.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22279|2024-08-01T22:43:34.216Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 19:47:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
