<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cloud Foundry -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cloud%20foundry/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cloud Foundry -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:22:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5399|2024-08-04T08:30:23.929Z -- cloud%20foundry -- credhub
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5399</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry CredHub, versions prior to 2.5.10, connects to a MySQL database without TLS even when configured to use TLS. A malicious user with access to the network between CredHub and its MySQL database may eavesdrop on database connections and thereby gain unauthorized access to CredHub and other components.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5399|2024-08-04T08:30:23.929Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5420|2024-08-04T08:30:24.367Z -- cloud%20foundry -- routing
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5420</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry Routing (Gorouter) versions prior to 0.206.0 allow a malicious developer with "cf push" access to cause denial-of-service to the CF cluster by pushing an app that returns specially crafted HTTP responses that crash the Gorouters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5420|2024-08-04T08:30:24.367Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3780|2024-08-04T19:19:18.425Z -- cloud%20foundry -- cloud%20foundry%20container%20runtime%20%28cfcr%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3780</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry Container Runtime, versions prior to 0.28.0, deploys K8s worker nodes that contains a configuration file with IAAS credentials. A malicious user with access to the k8s nodes can obtain IAAS credentials allowing the user to escalate privileges to gain access to the IAAS account.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3780|2024-08-04T19:19:18.425Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3782|2024-08-04T19:19:18.541Z -- cloud%20foundry -- credhub%20cli
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3782</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry CredHub CLI, versions prior to 2.2.1, inadvertently writes authentication credentials provided via environment variables to its persistent config file. A local authenticated malicious user with access to the CredHub CLI config file can use these credentials to retrieve and modify credentials stored in CredHub that are authorized to the targeted user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3782|2024-08-04T19:19:18.541Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3785|2024-08-04T19:19:18.253Z -- cloud%20foundry -- capi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3785</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry Cloud Controller, versions prior to 1.78.0, contain an endpoint with improper authorization. A remote authenticated malicious user with read permissions can request package information and receive a signed bit-service url that grants the user write permissions to the bit-service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3785|2024-08-04T19:19:18.253Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5418|2024-08-04T08:30:23.953Z -- cloud%20foundry -- capi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5418</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry CAPI (Cloud Controller) versions prior to 1.98.0 allow authenticated users having only the "cloud_controller.read" scope, but no roles in any spaces, to list all droplets in all spaces (whereas they should see none).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5418|2024-08-04T08:30:23.953Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3787|2024-08-04T19:19:18.288Z -- cloud%20foundry -- uaa%20release%20%28oss%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3787</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry UAA, versions prior to 73.0.0, falls back to appending “unknown.org” to a user's email address when one is not provided and the user name does not contain an @ character. This domain is held by a private company, which leads to attack vectors including password recovery emails sent to a potentially fraudulent address. This would allow the attacker to gain complete control of the user's account.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3787|2024-08-04T19:19:18.288Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5417|2024-08-04T08:30:23.944Z -- cloud%20foundry -- capi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5417</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry CAPI (Cloud Controller), versions prior to 1.97.0, when used in a deployment where an app domain is also the system domain (which is true in the default CF Deployment manifest), were vulnerable to developers maliciously or accidentally claiming certain sensitive routes, potentially resulting in the developer's app handling some requests that were expected to go to certain system components.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5417|2024-08-04T08:30:23.944Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5402|2024-08-04T08:30:23.930Z -- cloud%20foundry -- uaa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5402</link>
      <description>In Cloud Foundry UAA, versions prior to 74.14.0, a CSRF vulnerability exists due to the OAuth2 state parameter not being checked in the callback function when authenticating with external identity providers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5402|2024-08-04T08:30:23.930Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5400|2024-08-04T08:30:23.863Z -- cloud%20foundry -- capi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5400</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry Cloud Controller (CAPI), versions prior to 1.91.0, logs properties of background jobs when they are run, which may include sensitive information such as credentials if provided to the job. A malicious user with access to those logs may gain unauthorized access to resources protected by such credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5400|2024-08-04T08:30:23.863Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3789|2024-08-04T19:19:18.263Z -- cloud%20foundry -- cf%20routing
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3789</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry Routing Release, all versions prior to 0.188.0, contains a vulnerability that can hijack the traffic to route services hosted outside the platform. A user with space developer permissions can create a private domain that shadows the external domain of the route service, and map that route to an app. When the gorouter receives traffic destined for the external route service, this traffic will instead be directed to the internal app using the shadow route.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3789|2024-08-04T19:19:18.263Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3788|2024-08-04T19:19:18.261Z -- cloud%20foundry -- uaa%20release%20%28oss%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3788</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry UAA Release, versions prior to 71.0, allows clients to be configured with an insecure redirect uri. Given a UAA client was configured with a wildcard in the redirect uri's subdomain, a remote malicious unauthenticated user can craft a phishing link to get a UAA access code from the victim.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3788|2024-08-04T19:19:18.261Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3798|2024-08-04T19:19:18.358Z -- cloud%20foundry -- capi-release
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3798</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry Cloud Controller API Release, versions prior to 1.79.0, contains improper authentication when validating user permissions. A remote authenticated malicious user with the ability to create UAA clients and knowledge of the email of a victim in the foundation may escalate their privileges to that of the victim by creating a client with a name equal to the guid of their victim.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3798|2024-08-04T19:19:18.358Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3779|2024-08-04T19:19:18.402Z -- cloud%20foundry -- cloud%20foundry%20container%20runtime%20%28cfcr%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3779</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry Container Runtime, versions prior to 0.29.0, deploys Kubernetes clusters utilize the same CA (Certificate Authority) to sign and trust certs for ETCD as used by the Kubernetes API. This could allow a user authenticated with a cluster to request a signed certificate leveraging the Kubernetes CSR capability to obtain a credential that could escalate privilege access to ETCD.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3779|2024-08-04T19:19:18.402Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3784|2024-08-04T19:19:18.219Z -- cloud%20foundry -- stratos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3784</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry Stratos, versions prior to 2.3.0, contains an insecure session that can be spoofed. When deployed on cloud foundry with multiple instances using the default embedded SQLite database, a remote authenticated malicious user can switch sessions to another user with the same session id.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3784|2024-08-04T19:19:18.219Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5416|2024-08-04T08:30:24.212Z -- cloud%20foundry -- routing
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5416</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry Routing (Gorouter), versions prior to 0.204.0, when used in a deployment with NGINX reverse proxies in front of the Gorouters, is potentially vulnerable to denial-of-service attacks in which an unauthenticated malicious attacker can send specially-crafted HTTP requests that may cause the Gorouters to be dropped from the NGINX backend pool.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5416|2024-08-04T08:30:24.212Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3801|2024-08-04T19:19:18.469Z -- cloud%20foundry -- credhub
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3801</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry cf-deployment, versions prior to 7.9.0, contain java components that are using an insecure protocol to fetch dependencies when building. A remote unauthenticated malicious attacker could hijack the DNS entry for the dependency, and inject malicious code into the component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3801|2024-08-04T19:19:18.469Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5401|2024-08-04T08:30:23.785Z -- cloud%20foundry -- routing
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5401</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry Routing Release, versions prior to 0.197.0, contains GoRouter, which allows malicious clients to send invalid headers, causing caching layers to reject subsequent legitimate clients trying to access the app.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5401|2024-08-04T08:30:23.785Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5423|2024-08-04T08:30:24.267Z -- cloud%20foundry -- capi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5423</link>
      <description>CAPI (Cloud Controller) versions prior to 1.101.0 are vulnerable to a denial-of-service attack in which an unauthenticated malicious attacker can send specially-crafted YAML files to certain endpoints, causing the YAML parser to consume excessive CPU and RAM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5423|2024-08-04T08:30:24.267Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3786|2024-08-04T19:19:18.389Z -- cloud%20foundry -- bosh%20backup%20and%20restore
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3786</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry BOSH Backup and Restore CLI, all versions prior to 1.5.0, does not check the authenticity of backup scripts in BOSH. A remote authenticated malicious user can modify the metadata file of a Bosh Backup and Restore job to request extra backup files from different jobs upon restore. The exploited hooks in this metadata script were only maintained in the cfcr-etcd-release, so clusters deployed with the BBR job for etcd in this release are vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3786|2024-08-04T19:19:18.389Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3794|2024-08-04T19:19:18.460Z -- cloud%20foundry -- uaa%20release%20%28oss%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3794</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry UAA, versions prior to v73.4.0, does not set an X-FRAME-OPTIONS header on various endpoints. A remote user can perform clickjacking attacks on UAA's frontend sites.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3794|2024-08-04T19:19:18.460Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3781|2024-08-04T19:19:18.462Z -- cloud%20foundry -- cf%20cli
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3781</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry CLI, versions prior to v6.43.0, improperly exposes passwords when verbose/trace/debugging is turned on. A local unauthenticated or remote authenticated malicious user with access to logs may gain part or all of a users password.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3781|2024-08-04T19:19:18.462Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3800|2024-08-04T19:19:18.463Z -- cloud%20foundry -- cf%20cli%20release
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3800</link>
      <description>CF CLI version prior to v6.45.0 (bosh release version 1.16.0) writes the client id and secret to its config file when the user authenticates with --client-credentials flag. A local authenticated malicious user with access to the CF CLI config file can act as that client, who is the owner of the leaked credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3800|2024-08-04T19:19:18.463Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5422|2024-08-04T08:30:24.539Z -- cloud%20foundry -- bosh%20system%20metrics%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5422</link>
      <description>BOSH System Metrics Server releases prior to 0.1.0 exposed the UAA password as a flag to a process running on the BOSH director. It exposed the password to any user or process with access to the same VM (through ps or looking at process details).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5422|2024-08-04T08:30:24.539Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3775|2024-08-04T19:19:18.080Z -- cloud%20foundry -- uaa%20release%20%28oss%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3775</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry UAA, versions prior to v70.0, allows a user to update their own email address. A remote authenticated user can impersonate a different user by changing their email address to that of a different user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3775|2024-08-04T19:19:18.080Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3783|2024-08-04T19:19:18.281Z -- cloud%20foundry -- stratos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3783</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry Stratos, versions prior to 2.3.0, deploys with a public default session store secret. A malicious user with default session store secret can brute force another user's current Stratos session, and act on behalf of that user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3783|2024-08-04T19:19:18.281Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37082|2024-08-02T03:43:51.046Z -- cloud%20foundry -- haproxy-boshrelease</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37082</link>
      <description>When deploying Cloud Foundry together with the haproxy-boshrelease and using a non default configuration, it might be possible to craft HTTP requests that bypass mTLS authentication to Cloud Foundry applications. 

You are affected if you have route-services enabled in routing-release and have configured the haproxy-boshrelease property “ha_proxy.forwarded_client_cert” to “forward_only_if_route_service”.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37082|2024-08-02T03:43:51.046Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 06:08:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37082|2024-07-17T20:25:39.258Z -- cloud%20foundry -- haproxy-boshrelease</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37082</link>
      <description>When deploying Cloud Foundry together with the haproxy-boshrelease and using a non default configuration, it might be possible to craft HTTP requests that bypass mTLS authentication to Cloud Foundry applications. 

You are affected if you have route-services enabled in routing-release and have configured the haproxy-boshrelease property “ha_proxy.forwarded_client_cert” to “forward_only_if_route_service”.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37082|2024-07-17T20:25:39.258Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 06:08:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37082|2024-07-12T15:38:05.256Z -- cloud%20foundry -- haproxy-boshrelease</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37082</link>
      <description>When deploying Cloud Foundry together with the haproxy-boshrelease and using a non default configuration, it might be possible to craft HTTP requests that bypass mTLS authentication to Cloud Foundry applications. 

You are affected if you have route-services enabled in routing-release and have configured the haproxy-boshrelease property “ha_proxy.forwarded_client_cert” to “forward_only_if_route_service”.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37082|2024-07-12T15:38:05.256Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 06:08:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22279|2024-06-11T17:23:34.311Z -- cloud%20foundry -- routing%20release</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22279</link>
      <description>Improper handling of requests in Routing Release &gt; v0.273.0 and &lt;= v0.297.0 allows an unauthenticated attacker to degrade
 the service availability of the Cloud Foundry deployment if performed at scale.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22279|2024-06-11T17:23:34.311Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 19:47:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37082|2024-07-12T16:22:02.363Z -- cloud%20foundry -- haproxy-boshrelease</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37082</link>
      <description>When deploying Cloud Foundry together with the haproxy-boshrelease and using a non default configuration, it might be possible to craft HTTP requests that bypass mTLS authentication to Cloud Foundry applications. 

You are affected if you have route-services enabled in routing-release and have configured the haproxy-boshrelease property “ha_proxy.forwarded_client_cert” to “forward_only_if_route_service”.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37082|2024-07-12T16:22:02.363Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 06:08:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22279|2024-08-01T22:43:34.216Z -- cloud%20foundry -- routing%20release</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22279</link>
      <description>Improper handling of requests in Routing Release &gt; v0.273.0 and &lt;= v0.297.0 allows an unauthenticated attacker to degrade
 the service availability of the Cloud Foundry deployment if performed at scale.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22279|2024-08-01T22:43:34.216Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 19:47:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
