<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cloud Foundry -- CAPI</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cloud%20foundry/capi.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cloud Foundry -- CAPI</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 11:20:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5418|2024-08-04T08:30:23.953Z -- cloud%20foundry -- capi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5418</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry CAPI (Cloud Controller) versions prior to 1.98.0 allow authenticated users having only the "cloud_controller.read" scope, but no roles in any spaces, to list all droplets in all spaces (whereas they should see none).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5418|2024-08-04T08:30:23.953Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5417|2024-08-04T08:30:23.944Z -- cloud%20foundry -- capi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5417</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry CAPI (Cloud Controller), versions prior to 1.97.0, when used in a deployment where an app domain is also the system domain (which is true in the default CF Deployment manifest), were vulnerable to developers maliciously or accidentally claiming certain sensitive routes, potentially resulting in the developer's app handling some requests that were expected to go to certain system components.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5417|2024-08-04T08:30:23.944Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5400|2024-08-04T08:30:23.863Z -- cloud%20foundry -- capi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5400</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry Cloud Controller (CAPI), versions prior to 1.91.0, logs properties of background jobs when they are run, which may include sensitive information such as credentials if provided to the job. A malicious user with access to those logs may gain unauthorized access to resources protected by such credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5400|2024-08-04T08:30:23.863Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5423|2024-08-04T08:30:24.267Z -- cloud%20foundry -- capi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5423</link>
      <description>CAPI (Cloud Controller) versions prior to 1.101.0 are vulnerable to a denial-of-service attack in which an unauthenticated malicious attacker can send specially-crafted YAML files to certain endpoints, causing the YAML parser to consume excessive CPU and RAM.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5423|2024-08-04T08:30:24.267Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
