<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cloud Foundry -- Cloud Foundry UAA</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cloud%20foundry/cloud%20foundry%20uaa.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cloud Foundry -- Cloud Foundry UAA</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 20:22:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11047|2024-08-05T07:54:36.497Z -- cloud%20foundry -- cloud%20foundry%20uaa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11047</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry UAA, versions 4.19 prior to 4.19.2 and 4.12 prior to 4.12.4 and 4.10 prior to 4.10.2 and 4.7 prior to 4.7.6 and 4.5 prior to 4.5.7, incorrectly authorizes requests to admin endpoints by accepting a valid refresh token in lieu of an access token. Refresh tokens by design have a longer expiration time than access tokens, allowing the possessor of a refresh token to authenticate longer than expected. This affects the administrative endpoints of the UAA. i.e. /Users, /Groups, etc. However, if the user has been deleted or had groups removed, or the client was deleted, the refresh token will no longer be valid.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11047|2024-08-05T07:54:36.497Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11041|2024-08-05T07:54:36.475Z -- cloud%20foundry -- cloud%20foundry%20uaa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11041</link>
      <description>Cloud Foundry UAA, versions later than 4.6.0 and prior to 4.19.0 except 4.10.1 and 4.7.5 and uaa-release versions later than v48 and prior to v60 except v55.1 and v52.9, does not validate redirect URL values on a form parameter used for internal UAA redirects on the login page, allowing open redirects. A remote attacker can craft a malicious link that, when clicked, will redirect users to arbitrary websites after a successful login attempt.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11041|2024-08-05T07:54:36.475Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
