<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Nanning Ontall -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/nanning%20ontall/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Nanning Ontall -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 19:20:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5828|2024-08-02T08:14:24.004Z -- nanning%20ontall -- longxing%20industrial%20development%20zone%20project%20construction%20and%20installation%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5828</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Nanning Ontall Longxing Industrial Development Zone Project Construction and Installation Management System up to 20231026. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file login.aspx. The manipulation of the argument tbxUserName leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-243727.
In Nanning Ontall Longxing Industrial Development Zone Project Construction and Installation Management System bis 20231026 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei login.aspx. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments tbxUserName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5828|2024-08-02T08:14:24.004Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 19:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
