<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for BoldGrid -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/boldgrid/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for BoldGrid -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 21:54:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-1692|2024-03-30T04:31:07.070Z -- boldgrid -- BoldGrid Easy SEO – Simple and Effective SEO
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1692</link><description>The BoldGrid Easy SEO – Simple and Effective SEO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the meta description field in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.13 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1692|2024-03-30T04:31:07.070Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 04:31:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0386|2024-03-12T21:34:34.174Z -- boldgrid -- weForms – Easy Drag &amp; Drop Contact Form Builder For WordPress
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0386</link><description>The weForms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'Referer' HTTP header in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.21 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0386|2024-03-12T21:34:34.174Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 21:34:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4400|2024-05-16T11:05:29.134Z -- boldgrid -- Post and Page Builder by BoldGrid – Visual Drag and Drop Editor
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4400</link><description>The Post and Page Builder by BoldGrid – Visual Drag and Drop Editor plguin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via an unknown parameter in versions up to, and including, 1.26.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4400|2024-05-16T11:05:29.134Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 11:05:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24869|2024-05-17T08:48:22.714Z -- BoldGrid -- Total Upkeep
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-24869</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in BoldGrid Total Upkeep allows Relative Path Traversal.This issue affects Total Upkeep: from n/a through 1.15.8.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24869|2024-05-17T08:48:22.714Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 08:48:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2950|2024-04-06T03:24:44.633Z -- boldgrid -- BoldGrid Easy SEO – Simple and Effective SEO
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2950</link><description>The BoldGrid Easy SEO – Simple and Effective SEO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.14 via meta information (og:description) This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view the first 130 characters of a password protected post which can contain sensitive information.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2950|2024-04-06T03:24:44.633Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 03:24:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2888|2024-03-26T05:41:02.491Z -- BoldGrid -- Post and Page Builder by BoldGrid – Visual Drag and Drop Editor
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2888</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in BoldGrid Post and Page Builder by BoldGrid – Visual Drag and Drop Editor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Post and Page Builder by BoldGrid – Visual Drag and Drop Editor: from n/a through 1.26.2.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2888|2024-03-26T05:41:02.491Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 05:41:02 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>