<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Academy -- LMS</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/academy/lms.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Academy -- LMS</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 21:22:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4973|2024-08-02T07:44:53.370Z -- academy -- lms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4973</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Academy LMS 6.2 on Windows. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /academy/tutor/filter of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument searched_word/searched_tution_class_type[]/searched_price_type[]/searched_duration[] leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The identifier VDB-239749 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Academy LMS 6.2 für Windows wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei /academy/tutor/filter der Komponente GET Parameter Handler. Durch Manipulation des Arguments searched_word/searched_tution_class_type[]/searched_price_type[]/searched_duration[] mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4973|2024-08-02T07:44:53.370Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 02:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4119|2024-08-02T07:17:12.130Z -- academy -- lms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4119</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Academy LMS 6.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /academy/home/courses. The manipulation of the argument query/sort_by leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. VDB-235966 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Academy LMS 6.0 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle gefunden. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei /academy/home/courses. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments query/sort_by mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4119|2024-08-02T07:17:12.130Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 08:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4974|2024-08-02T07:44:52.666Z -- academy -- lms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4974</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Academy LMS 6.2. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /academy/tutor/filter of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument price_min/price_max leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. VDB-239750 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Academy LMS 6.2 ausgemacht. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei /academy/tutor/filter der Komponente GET Parameter Handler. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments price_min/price_max mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4974|2024-08-02T07:44:52.666Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 02:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
