<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for zulip -- zulip</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/zulip/zulip.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for zulip -- zulip</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 21:24:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-27286|2024-03-20T19:35:59.164Z -- zulip -- zulip
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27286</link><description>Zulip is an open-source team collaboration. When a user moves a Zulip message, they have the option to move all messages in the topic, move only subsequent messages as well, or move just a single message.  If the user chose to just move one message, and was moving it from a public stream to a private stream, Zulip would successfully move the message, -- but active users who did not have access to the private stream, but whose client had already received the message, would continue to see the message in the public stream until they reloaded their client.  Additionally, Zulip did not remove view permissions on the message from recently-active users, allowing the message to show up in the "All messages" view or in search results, but not in "Inbox" or "Recent conversations" views. While the bug has been present since moving messages between streams was first introduced in version 3.0, this option became much more common starting in Zulip 8.0, when the default option in the picker for moving the very last message in a conversation was changed. This issue is fixed in Zulip Server 8.3. No known workarounds are available.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27286|2024-03-20T19:35:59.164Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 19:35:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21630|2024-01-25T19:30:09.106Z -- zulip -- zulip
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21630</link><description>Zulip is an open-source team collaboration tool. A vulnerability in version 8.0 is similar to CVE-2023-32677, but applies to multi-use invitations, not single-use invitation links as in the prior CVE. Specifically, it applies when the installation has configured non-admins to be able to invite users and create multi-use invitations, and has also configured only admins to be able to invite users to streams. As in CVE-2023-32677, this does not let users invite new users to arbitrary streams, only to streams that the inviter can already see. Version 8.1 fixes this issue. As a workaround, administrators can limit sending of invitations down to users who also have the permission to add users to streams.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21630|2024-01-25T19:30:09.106Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 19:30:09 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>