<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Control iD -- Gerencia Web</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/control%20id/gerencia%20web.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Control iD -- Gerencia Web</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0125|2024-02-13T07:43:49.952Z -- control%20id -- gerencia%20web
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0125</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Control iD Gerencia Web 1.30. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Web Interface. The manipulation of the argument Nome leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-217717 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In Control iD Gerencia Web 1.30 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Komponente Web Interface. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments Nome mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0125|2024-02-13T07:43:49.952Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 20:51:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4392|2023-10-24T08:55:10.604Z -- control%20id -- gerencia%20web
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4392</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Control iD Gerencia Web 1.30 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Cookie Handler. The manipulation leads to cleartext storage of sensitive information. The attack may be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-237380. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Control iD Gerencia Web 1.30 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Komponente Cookie Handler. Dank der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cleartext storage of sensitive information-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Sie ist schwierig ausnutzbar. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4392|2023-10-24T08:55:10.604Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 02:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
