<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Control iD -- iDSecure</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/control%20id/idsecure.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Control iD -- iDSecure</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 21:22:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6329|2024-08-02T08:28:21.191Z -- control%20id -- idsecure
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6329</link>
      <description>An authentication bypass vulnerability exists in Control iD iDSecure v4.7.32.0. The login routine used by iDS-Core.dll contains a "passwordCustom" option that allows an unauthenticated attacker to compute valid credentials that can be used to bypass authentication and act as an administrative user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6329|2024-08-02T08:28:21.191Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 16:34:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2044|2024-08-02T06:12:19.935Z -- control%20id -- idsecure
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2044</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Control iD iDSecure 4.7.29.1 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Dispositivos Page. The manipulation of the argument IP-DNS leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. VDB-225922 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Control iD iDSecure 4.7.29.1 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle gefunden. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Komponente Dispositivos Page. Durch Manipulation des Arguments IP-DNS mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2044|2024-08-02T06:12:19.935Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 10:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
