<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Control iD -- RHiD</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/control%20id/rhid.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Control iD -- RHiD</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 15:23:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2043|2024-08-02T06:12:19.899Z -- control%20id -- rhid
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2043</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Control iD RHiD 23.3.19.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /v2/customerdb/operator.svc/a of the component Edit Handler. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The identifier VDB-225921 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in Control iD RHiD 23.3.19.0 gefunden. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei /v2/customerdb/operator.svc/a der Komponente Edit Handler. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments email mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2043|2024-08-02T06:12:19.899Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 09:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2524|2024-08-02T06:26:09.364Z -- control%20id -- rhid
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2524</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Control iD RHiD 23.3.19.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /v2/#/. The manipulation leads to direct request. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-228015. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Control iD RHiD 23.3.19.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei /v2/#/. Durch das Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine direct request-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2524|2024-08-02T06:26:09.364Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 18:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2421|2024-08-02T06:19:15.227Z -- control%20id -- rhid
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2421</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Control iD RHiD 23.3.19.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /v2/#/add/department. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. VDB-227718 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in Control iD RHiD 23.3.19.0 entdeckt. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei /v2/#/add/department. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments Name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2421|2024-08-02T06:19:15.227Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 01:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
