<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Nvidia Corporation -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/nvidia%20corporation/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Nvidia Corporation -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 10:23:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6262|2024-08-05T06:01:48.321Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- geforce%20experience
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6262</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GeForce Experience prior to 3.15 contains a vulnerability when GameStream is enabled where limited sensitive user information may be available to users with system access, which may lead to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6262|2024-08-05T06:01:48.321Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6265|2024-08-05T06:01:48.079Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- geforce%20experience
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6265</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GeForce Experience contains a vulnerability in all versions prior to 3.16 during application installation on Windows 7 in elevated privilege mode, where a local user who initiates a browser session may obtain escalation of privileges on the browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6265|2024-08-05T06:01:48.079Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6242|2024-08-05T06:01:47.693Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- some%20nvidia%20tegra%20mobile%20processors
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6242</link>
      <description>Some NVIDIA Tegra mobile processors released prior to 2016 contain a buffer overflow vulnerability in BootROM Recovery Mode (RCM). An attacker with physical access to the device's USB and the ability to force the device to reboot into RCM could exploit the vulnerability to execute unverified code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6242|2024-08-05T06:01:47.693Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6267|2024-08-05T06:01:48.925Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6267</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Tegra OpenMax driver (libnvomx) contains a vulnerability in which the software does not validate or incorrectly validates input that can affect the control flow or data flow of a program, which may lead to denial of service or escalation of privileges. Android ID: A-70857947.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6267|2024-08-05T06:01:48.925Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6268|2024-08-05T06:01:48.306Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6268</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Tegra library contains a vulnerability in libnvmmlite_video.so, where referencing memory after it has been freed may lead to denial of service or possible escalation of privileges. Android ID: A-80433161.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6268|2024-08-05T06:01:48.306Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6259|2024-08-05T06:01:48.184Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- nvidia%20geforce%20experience
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6259</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GeForce Experience all versions prior to 3.14.1 contains a potential vulnerability when GameStream is enabled, an attacker has system access, and certain system features are enabled, where limited information disclosure may be possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6259|2024-08-05T06:01:48.184Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6261|2024-08-05T06:01:48.008Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- geforce%20experience
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6261</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GeForce Experience prior to 3.15 contains a vulnerability when GameStream is enabled which sets incorrect permissions on a file, which may to code execution, denial of service, or escalation of privileges by users with system access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6261|2024-08-05T06:01:48.008Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6247|2024-08-05T06:01:48.297Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- gpu%20display%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6247</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Windows GPU Display Driver contains a vulnerability in the kernel mode layer (nvlddmkm.sys) handler for DxgkDdiEscape where a NULL pointer dereference may lead to denial of service or possible escalation of privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6247|2024-08-05T06:01:48.297Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6252|2024-08-05T06:01:48.554Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- gpu%20display%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6252</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Windows GPU Display Driver contains a vulnerability in the kernel mode layer handler for DxgkDdiEscape where the software allows an actor access to restricted functionality that is unnecessary to production usage, and which may result in denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6252|2024-08-05T06:01:48.554Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6266|2024-08-05T06:01:48.243Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- geforce%20experience
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6266</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GeForce Experience contains a vulnerability in all versions prior to 3.16 on Windows where a local user may obtain third party integration parameters, which may lead to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6266|2024-08-05T06:01:48.243Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6257|2024-08-05T06:01:48.316Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- nvidia%20geforce%20experience
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6257</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GeForce Experience all versions prior to 3.14.1 contains a potential vulnerability when GameStream is enabled where improper access control may lead to a denial of service, escalation of privileges, or both.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6257|2024-08-05T06:01:48.316Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6241|2024-08-05T06:01:47.984Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6241</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Tegra Gralloc module contains a vulnerability in driver in which it does not validate input parameter of the registerbuffer API, which may lead to arbitrary code execution, denial of service, or escalation of privileges. Android ID: A-62540032 Severity Rating: High Version: N/A.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6241|2024-08-05T06:01:47.984Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6258|2024-08-05T06:01:48.304Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- nvidia%20geforce%20experience
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6258</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GeForce Experience all versions prior to 3.14.1 contains a potential vulnerability during GameStream installation where an attacker who has system access can potentially conduct a Man-in-the-Middle (MitM) attack to obtain sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6258|2024-08-05T06:01:48.304Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6250|2024-08-05T06:01:47.683Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- gpu%20display%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6250</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Windows GPU Display Driver contains a vulnerability in the kernel mode layer (nvlddmkm.sys) handler for DxgkDdiEscape where a NULL pointer dereference occurs which may lead to denial of service or possible escalation of privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6250|2024-08-05T06:01:47.683Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6254|2024-08-05T06:01:48.584Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6254</link>
      <description>In Android before the 2018-05-05 security patch level, NVIDIA Media Server contains an out-of-bounds read (due to improper input validation) vulnerability which could lead to local information disclosure. This issue is rated as moderate. Android: A-64340684. Reference: N-CVE-2018-6254.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6254|2024-08-05T06:01:48.584Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6263|2024-08-05T06:01:48.476Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- geforce%20experience
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6263</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GeForce Experience contains a vulnerability in all versions prior to 3.16 on Windows in which an attacker who has access to a local user account can plant a malicious dynamic link library (DLL) during application installation, which may lead to escalation of privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6263|2024-08-05T06:01:48.476Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6271|2024-08-05T06:01:48.550Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6271</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Tegra OpenMax driver (libnvomx) contains a vulnerability in which the software delivers extra data with the buffer and does not properly validated the extra data, which may lead to denial of service or escalation of privileges. Android ID: A-80198474.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6271|2024-08-05T06:01:48.550Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6260|2024-08-05T06:01:47.983Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- gpu%20graphics%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6260</link>
      <description>NVIDIA graphics driver contains a vulnerability that may allow access to application data processed on the GPU through a side channel exposed by the GPU performance counters. Local user access is required. This is not a network or remote attack vector.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6260|2024-08-05T06:01:47.983Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6246|2024-08-05T06:01:48.607Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6246</link>
      <description>In Android before the 2018-05-05 security patch level, NVIDIA Widevine Trustlet contains a vulnerability in Widevine TA where the software reads data past the end, or before the beginning, of the intended buffer, which may lead to Information Disclosure. This issue is rated as moderate. Android: A-69383916. Reference: N-CVE-2018-6246.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6246|2024-08-05T06:01:48.607Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6251|2024-08-05T06:01:48.666Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- gpu%20display%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6251</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Windows GPU Display Driver contains a vulnerability in the DirectX 10 Usermode driver, where a specially crafted pixel shader can cause writing to unallocated memory, leading to denial of service or potential code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6251|2024-08-05T06:01:48.666Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6253|2024-08-05T06:01:47.995Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- gpu%20display%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6253</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver contains a vulnerability in the DirectX and OpenGL Usermode drivers where a specially crafted pixel shader can cause infinite recursion leading to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6253|2024-08-05T06:01:47.995Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6248|2024-08-05T06:01:48.291Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- gpu%20display%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6248</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Windows GPU Display Driver contains a vulnerability in the kernel mode layer handler for DxgkDdiEscape where the software uses a sequential operation to read or write a buffer, but it uses an incorrect length value that causes it to access memory that is outside of the bounds of the buffer which may lead to denial of service or possible escalation of privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6248|2024-08-05T06:01:48.291Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6249|2024-08-05T06:01:47.664Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- gpu%20display%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6249</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver contains a vulnerability in kernel mode layer handler where a NULL pointer dereference may lead to denial of service or potential escalation of privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6249|2024-08-05T06:01:47.664Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
