<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Nvidia Corporation -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/nvidia%20corporation/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Nvidia Corporation -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 18:25:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6247|2024-09-16T16:43:24.503Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6247</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the NVIDIA sound driver could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of the kernel. This issue is rated as High due to the possibility of local arbitrary code execution in a privileged process in the kernel. Product: Android. Versions: N/A. Android ID: A-34386301. References: N-CVE-2017-6247.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6247|2024-09-16T16:43:24.503Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6294|2024-09-16T17:15:30.614Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- gpu%20display%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6294</link>
      <description>In Android before the 2018-06-05 security patch level, NVIDIA Tegra X1 TZ contains a possible out of bounds write due to missing bounds check which could lead to escalation of privilege from the kernel to the TZ. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. This issue is rated as high. Version: N/A. Android: A-69316825. Reference: N-CVE-2017-6294.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6294|2024-09-16T17:15:30.614Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6292|2024-09-16T17:59:19.251Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- gpu%20display%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6292</link>
      <description>In Android before the 2018-06-05 security patch level, NVIDIA TLZ TrustZone contains a possible out of bounds write due to integer overflow which could lead to local escalation of privilege in the TrustZone with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. This issue is rated as high. Version: N/A. Android: A-69480285. Reference: N-CVE-2017-6292.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6292|2024-09-16T17:59:19.251Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-0340|2024-09-16T17:15:09.133Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-0340</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the NVIDIA Libnvparser component due to a memcpy into a fixed sized buffer with a user-controlled size could lead to a memory corruption and possible remote code execution. This issue is rated as High. Product: Android. Version: N/A. Android ID: A-33968204. References: N-CVE-2017-0340.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-0340|2024-09-16T17:15:09.133Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6257|2024-09-16T17:43:39.449Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- nvidia%20geforce%20experience
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6257</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GeForce Experience all versions prior to 3.14.1 contains a potential vulnerability when GameStream is enabled where improper access control may lead to a denial of service, escalation of privileges, or both.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6257|2024-09-16T17:43:39.449Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6252|2024-09-16T17:33:03.260Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- nvidia%20windows%20gpu%20display%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6252</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Windows GPU Display Driver contains a vulnerability in the kernel mode layer handler where a NULL pointer dereference may lead to a denial of service or potential escalation of privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6252|2024-09-16T17:33:03.260Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6252|2024-09-16T17:24:03.220Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- gpu%20display%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6252</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Windows GPU Display Driver contains a vulnerability in the kernel mode layer handler for DxgkDdiEscape where the software allows an actor access to restricted functionality that is unnecessary to production usage, and which may result in denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6252|2024-09-16T17:24:03.220Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6267|2024-09-16T16:22:46.175Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- gpu%20display%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6267</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver contains a vulnerability in the kernel mode layer handler where an incorrect initialization of internal objects can cause an infinite loop which may lead to a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6267|2024-09-16T16:22:46.175Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6293|2024-09-16T17:48:07.072Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6293</link>
      <description>In Android before the 2018-05-05 security patch level, NVIDIA Tegra X1 TZ contains a vulnerability in Widevine TA where the software writes data past the end, or before the beginning, of the intended buffer, which may lead to escalation of Privileges. This issue is rated as high. Android: A-69377364. Reference: N-CVE-2017-6293.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6293|2024-09-16T17:48:07.072Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6262|2024-09-16T16:59:01.642Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- geforce%20experience
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6262</link>
      <description>NVIDIA GeForce Experience prior to 3.15 contains a vulnerability when GameStream is enabled where limited sensitive user information may be available to users with system access, which may lead to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6262|2024-09-16T16:59:01.642Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5670|2024-09-16T16:17:58.743Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- nvidia%20gpu%20graphics%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5670</link>
      <description>NVIDIA Windows GPU Display Driver contains a vulnerability in the kernel mode layer handler for DxgkDdiEscape in which the software uses a sequential operation to read from or write to a buffer, but it uses an incorrect length value that causes it to access memory that is outside of the bounds of the buffer which may lead to denial of service, escalation of privileges, code execution or information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5670|2024-09-16T16:17:58.743Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6288|2024-09-16T17:49:26.292Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6288</link>
      <description>NVIDIA libnvrm contains a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check which could lead to local information disclosure. This issue is rated as moderate. Product: Android. Version: N/A. Android: A-65482562. Reference: N-CVE-2017-6288.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6288|2024-09-16T17:49:26.292Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6286|2024-09-16T17:03:06.148Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6286</link>
      <description>NVIDIA libnvomx contains a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check which could lead to local escalation of privilege. This issue is rated as high. Product: Android. Version: N/A. Android: A-64893247. Reference: N-CVE-2017-6286.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6286|2024-09-16T17:03:06.148Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6254|2024-09-16T17:08:29.755Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6254</link>
      <description>In Android before the 2018-05-05 security patch level, NVIDIA Media Server contains an out-of-bounds read (due to improper input validation) vulnerability which could lead to local information disclosure. This issue is rated as moderate. Android: A-64340684. Reference: N-CVE-2018-6254.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6254|2024-09-16T17:08:29.755Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6242|2024-09-16T16:53:48.144Z -- nvidia%20corporation -- some%20nvidia%20tegra%20mobile%20processors
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6242</link>
      <description>Some NVIDIA Tegra mobile processors released prior to 2016 contain a buffer overflow vulnerability in BootROM Recovery Mode (RCM). An attacker with physical access to the device's USB and the ability to force the device to reboot into RCM could exploit the vulnerability to execute unverified code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6242|2024-09-16T16:53:48.144Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
