<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for ASUS -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/asus/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for ASUS -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28703|2023-06-02T00:00:00 -- asus -- rt-ac86u
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-28703</link>
      <description>ASUS RT-AC86U’s specific cgi function has a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability due to insufficient validation for network packet header length. A remote attacker with administrator privileges can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary system commands, disrupt system or terminate service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28703|2023-06-02T00:00:00</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28702|2023-06-02T00:00:00 -- asus -- rt-ac86u
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-28702</link>
      <description>ASUS RT-AC86U does not filter special characters for parameters in specific web URLs. A remote attacker with normal user privileges can exploit this vulnerability to perform command injection attack to execute arbitrary system commands, disrupt system or terminate service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28702|2023-06-02T00:00:00</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5716|2024-01-19T07:09:54.691Z -- asus -- armoury%20crate
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5716</link>
      <description>ASUS Armoury Crate has a vulnerability in arbitrary file write and allows remote attackers to access or modify arbitrary files by sending specific HTTP requests without permission.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5716|2024-01-19T07:09:54.691Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 03:07:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38033|2023-09-07T06:42:16.805Z -- asus -- rt-ac86u
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38033</link>
      <description>
ASUS RT-AC86U unused Traffic Analyzer legacy Statistic function has insufficient filtering of special character. A remote attacker with regular user privilege can exploit this vulnerability to perform command injection attack to execute arbitrary commands, disrupt system or terminate services.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38033|2023-09-07T06:42:16.805Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 06:42:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38032|2023-09-07T06:30:47.345Z -- asus -- rt-ac86u
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38032</link>
      <description>
ASUS RT-AC86U AiProtection security- related function has insufficient filtering of special character. A remote attacker with regular user privilege can exploit this vulnerability to perform command injection attack to execute arbitrary commands, disrupt system or terminate services.



</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38032|2023-09-07T06:30:47.345Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 06:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38031|2023-09-07T03:24:38.199Z -- asus -- rt-ac86u
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38031</link>
      <description>
ASUS RT-AC86U Adaptive QoS - Web History function has insufficient filtering of special character. A remote attacker with regular user privilege can exploit this vulnerability to perform command injection attack to execute arbitrary commands, disrupt system or terminate services.



</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38031|2023-09-07T03:24:38.199Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 03:24:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39239|2024-03-27T07:14:38.193Z -- asus -- rt-ax55
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39239</link>
      <description>
It is identified a format string vulnerability in ASUS RT-AX56U V2’s General function API. This vulnerability is caused by lacking validation for a specific value within its  apply.cgi module. A remote attacker with administrator privilege can exploit this vulnerability to perform remote arbitrary code execution, arbitrary system operation or disrupt service.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39239|2024-03-27T07:14:38.193Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 07:18:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39238|2024-03-27T07:06:35.024Z -- asus -- rt-ax55
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39238</link>
      <description>
It is identified a format string vulnerability in ASUS RT-AX56U V2. This vulnerability is caused by lacking validation for a specific value within its set_iperf3_svr.cgi module. A remote attacker with administrator privilege can exploit this vulnerability to perform remote arbitrary code execution, arbitrary system operation or disrupt service.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39238|2024-03-27T07:06:35.024Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 07:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39237|2023-09-07T06:53:39.760Z -- asus -- rt-ac86u
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39237</link>
      <description>
ASUS RT-AC86U Traffic Analyzer - Apps analysis function has insufficient filtering of special character. A remote attacker with regular user privilege can exploit this vulnerability to perform command injection attack to execute arbitrary commands, disrupt system or terminate services.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39237|2023-09-07T06:53:39.760Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 06:53:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39240|2024-03-27T07:02:04.782Z -- asus -- rt-ax55
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39240</link>
      <description>
It is identified a format string vulnerability in ASUS RT-AX56U V2’s iperf client function API. This vulnerability is caused by lacking validation for a specific value within its set_iperf3_cli.cgi module. A remote attacker with administrator privilege can exploit this vulnerability to perform remote arbitrary code execution, arbitrary system operation or disrupt service.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39240|2024-03-27T07:02:04.782Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 07:25:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39236|2023-09-07T06:49:26.746Z -- asus -- rt-ac86u
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39236</link>
      <description>
ASUS RT-AC86U Traffic Analyzer - Statistic function has insufficient filtering of special character. A remote attacker with regular user privilege can exploit this vulnerability to perform command injection attack to execute arbitrary commands, disrupt system or terminate services.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39236|2023-09-07T06:49:26.746Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 06:49:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41346|2023-11-03T07:15:22.787Z -- asus -- rt-ax55
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41346</link>
      <description>ASUS RT-AX55’s authentication-related function has a vulnerability of insufficient filtering of special characters within its token-refresh module. An authenticated remote attacker can exploit this vulnerability to perform a Command Injection attack to execute arbitrary commands, disrupt the system or terminate services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41346|2023-11-03T07:15:22.787Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 04:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41347|2023-11-03T07:15:54.767Z -- asus -- rt-ax55
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41347</link>
      <description>ASUS RT-AX55’s authentication-related function has a vulnerability of insufficient filtering of special characters within its check token module. An authenticated remote attacker can exploit this vulnerability to perform a Command Injection attack to execute arbitrary commands, disrupt the system or terminate services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41347|2023-11-03T07:15:54.767Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 04:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41348|2023-11-03T07:16:13.129Z -- asus -- rt-ax55
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41348</link>
      <description>ASUS RT-AX55’s authentication-related function has a vulnerability of insufficient filtering of special characters within its code-authentication module. An authenticated remote attacker can exploit this vulnerability to perform a Command Injection attack to execute arbitrary commands, disrupt the system or terminate services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41348|2023-11-03T07:16:13.129Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 04:32:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41345|2023-11-03T07:14:55.631Z -- asus -- rt-ax55
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41345</link>
      <description>ASUS RT-AX55’s authentication-related function has a vulnerability of insufficient filtering of special characters within its token-generated module. An authenticated remote attacker can exploit this vulnerability to perform a Command Injection attack to execute arbitrary commands, disrupt the system, or terminate services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41345|2023-11-03T07:14:55.631Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 04:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41349|2023-09-18T02:36:30.234Z -- asus -- rt-ax88u
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41349</link>
      <description>
ASUS router RT-AX88U has a vulnerability of using externally controllable format strings within its Advanced Open VPN function. An authenticated remote attacker can exploit the exported OpenVPN configuration to execute an externally-controlled format string attack, resulting in sensitivity information leakage, or forcing the device to reset and permanent denial of service.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41349|2023-09-18T02:36:30.234Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 02:36:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34358|2023-07-31T04:09:05.030Z -- asus -- rt-ax88u
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34358</link>
      <description>ASUS RT-AX88U's httpd is subject to an unauthenticated DoS condition. A remote attacker can send a specially crafted request to a device which contains a specific user agent, causing the httpd binary to crash during a string comparison performed within web.c, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34358|2023-07-31T04:09:05.030Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 04:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34359|2023-07-31T04:32:14.068Z -- asus -- rt-ax88u
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34359</link>
      <description>ASUS RT-AX88U's httpd is subject to an unauthenticated DoS condition. A remote attacker can send a specially crafted request to the device which causes the httpd binary to crash within the "do_json_decode()" function of ej.c, resulting in a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34359|2023-07-31T04:32:14.068Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 04:31:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34360|2023-07-31T05:32:14.662Z -- asus -- rt-ax88u
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34360</link>
      <description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) issue was discovered within the Custom User Icons functionality of ASUS RT-AX88U running firmware versions 3.0.0.4.388.23110 and prior.  After a remote attacker logging in device with regular user privilege, the remote attacker can perform a Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) attack by uploading image which containing JavaScript code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34360|2023-07-31T05:32:14.662Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 05:32:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35087|2023-07-21T07:11:03.792Z -- asus -- rt-ax56u%20v2
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35087</link>
      <description>
It is identified a format string vulnerability in ASUS RT-AX56U V2 &amp; RT-AC86U. This vulnerability is caused by lacking validation for a specific value when calling cm_processChangedConfigMsg in ccm_processREQ_CHANGED_CONFIG function in AiMesh system. An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit this vulnerability without privilege to perform remote arbitrary code execution, arbitrary system operation or disrupt service.
This issue affects RT-AX56U V2: 3.0.0.4.386_50460; RT-AC86U: 3.0.0.4_386_51529.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35087|2023-07-21T07:11:03.792Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 07:11:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35086|2024-03-27T07:21:52.292Z -- asus -- rt-ax56u%20v2
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35086</link>
      <description>
It is identified a format string vulnerability in ASUS RT-AX56U V2 &amp; RT-AC86U. This vulnerability is caused by directly using input as a format string when calling syslog in logmessage_normal function, in the do_detwan_cgi module of httpd. A remote attacker with administrator privilege can exploit this vulnerability to perform remote arbitrary code execution, arbitrary system operation or disrupt service.

This issue affects RT-AX56U V2: 3.0.0.4.386_50460; RT-AC86U: 3.0.0.4_386_51529.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35086|2024-03-27T07:21:52.292Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 06:32:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35720|2024-06-04T17:18:10.530Z -- asus -- rt-ax92u
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35720</link>
      <description>ASUS RT-AX92U lighttpd mod_webdav.so SQL Injection Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected ASUS RT-AX92U routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. 

The specific flaw exists within the mod_webdav.so module. When parsing a request, the process does not properly validate a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-16078.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35720|2024-06-04T17:18:10.530Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1655|2024-04-15T06:21:37.900Z -- asus -- expertwifi%20ebm63
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1655</link>
      <description>Certain ASUS WiFi routers models has an OS Command Injection vulnerability, allowing an authenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary system commands by sending a specially crafted request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1655|2024-04-15T06:21:37.900Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 04:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0401|2024-06-04T17:58:40.749Z -- asus -- expertwifi
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0401</link>
      <description>ASUS routers supporting custom OpenVPN profiles are vulnerable to a code execution vulnerability. An authenticated and remote attacker can execute arbitrary operating system commands by uploading a crafted OVPN profile. Known affected routers include ASUS ExpertWiFi, ASUS RT-AX55, ASUS RT-AX58U, ASUS RT-AC67U, ASUS RT-AC68R, ASUS RT-AC68U, ASUS RT-AX86, ASUS RT-AC86U, ASUS RT-AX88U, and ASUS RT-AX3000.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0401|2024-06-04T17:58:40.749Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 16:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
