<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for ASUS -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/asus/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for ASUS -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 23:22:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26674|2024-08-03T05:11:44.783Z -- asus -- rt-ax88u
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26674</link>
      <description>ASUS RT-AX88U has a Format String vulnerability, which allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to write to arbitrary memory address and perform remote arbitrary code execution, arbitrary system operation or disrupt service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26674|2024-08-03T05:11:44.783Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26672|2024-08-03T05:11:43.431Z -- asus -- webstorage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26672</link>
      <description>ASUS WebStorage has a hardcoded API Token in the APP source code. An unauthenticated remote attacker can use this token to establish connections with the server and carry out login attempts to general user accounts. A successful login to a general user account allows the attacker to access, modify or delete this user account information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26672|2024-08-03T05:11:43.431Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28183|2024-08-03T21:40:12.197Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28183</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Web License configuration setting) does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28183|2024-08-03T21:40:12.197Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28180|2024-08-03T21:40:12.215Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28180</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Audit log configuration setting) does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28180|2024-08-03T21:40:12.215Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-35401|2024-08-03T09:36:44.178Z -- asus -- rt-ax82u
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-35401</link>
      <description>An authentication bypass vulnerability exists in the get_IFTTTTtoken.cgi functionality of Asus RT-AX82U 3.0.0.4.386_49674-ge182230. A specially-crafted HTTP request can lead to full administrative access to the device. An attacker would need to send a series of HTTP requests to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-35401|2024-08-03T09:36:44.178Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 20:44:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28208|2024-08-03T21:40:12.868Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28208</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Get video file function) does not filter the specific parameter. As obtaining the administrator permission, remote attackers can use the means of path traversal to access system files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28208|2024-08-03T21:40:12.868Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38393|2024-08-03T10:54:03.747Z -- asus -- rt-ax82u
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38393</link>
      <description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in the cfg_server cm_processConnDiagPktList opcode of Asus RT-AX82U 3.0.0.4.386_49674-ge182230 router's configuration service. A specially-crafted network packet can lead to denial of service. An attacker can send a malicious packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38393|2024-08-03T10:54:03.747Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 20:37:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28191|2024-08-03T21:40:12.722Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28191</link>
      <description>The Firmware update function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28191|2024-08-03T21:40:12.722Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28184|2024-08-03T21:40:12.920Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28184</link>
      <description>The Active Directory configuration function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28184|2024-08-03T21:40:12.920Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26668|2024-08-03T05:11:43.535Z -- asus -- control%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26668</link>
      <description>ASUS Control Center API has a broken access control vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker can call privileged API functions to perform partial system operations or cause partial disrupt of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26668|2024-08-03T05:11:43.535Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28181|2024-08-03T21:40:12.220Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28181</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Remote video configuration setting) does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28181|2024-08-03T21:40:12.220Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28178|2024-08-03T21:40:12.308Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28178</link>
      <description>The UEFI configuration function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28178|2024-08-03T21:40:12.308Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-25596|2024-08-03T04:42:50.013Z -- asus -- rt-ac86u
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-25596</link>
      <description>ASUS RT-AC56U’s configuration function has a heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability due to insufficient validation for the decryption parameter length, which allows an unauthenticated LAN attacker to execute arbitrary code, perform arbitrary operations and disrupt service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-25596|2024-08-03T04:42:50.013Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28175|2024-08-03T21:40:12.190Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28175</link>
      <description>The Radius configuration function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28175|2024-08-03T21:40:12.190Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28199|2024-08-03T21:40:12.939Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28199</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Modify user’s information function) does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28199|2024-08-03T21:40:12.939Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28179|2024-08-03T21:40:12.296Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28179</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Media support configuration setting) does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28179|2024-08-03T21:40:12.296Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28209|2024-08-03T21:40:13.105Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28209</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Delete video file function) does not filter the specific parameter. As obtaining the administrator permission, remote attackers can use the means of path traversal to access system files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28209|2024-08-03T21:40:13.105Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28201|2024-08-03T21:40:13.737Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28201</link>
      <description>The Service configuration-1 function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28201|2024-08-03T21:40:13.737Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28206|2024-08-03T21:40:14.066Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28206</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Record video file function) does not filter the specific parameter. As obtaining the administrator permission, remote attackers can use the means of path traversal to access system files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28206|2024-08-03T21:40:14.066Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26673|2024-08-03T05:11:44.364Z -- asus -- rt-ax88u
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26673</link>
      <description>ASUS RT-AX88U has insufficient filtering for special characters in the HTTP header parameter. A remote attacker with general user privilege can exploit this vulnerability to inject JavaScript and perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26673|2024-08-03T05:11:44.364Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28177|2024-08-03T21:40:12.192Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28177</link>
      <description>The LDAP configuration function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28177|2024-08-03T21:40:12.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28185|2024-08-03T21:40:12.204Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28185</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (ActiveX configuration-1 acquisition) does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28185|2024-08-03T21:40:12.204Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28203|2024-08-03T21:40:12.667Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28203</link>
      <description>The Web Set Media Image function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not filter the specific parameter. As obtaining the administrator permission, remote attackers can launch command injection to execute command arbitrary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28203|2024-08-03T21:40:12.667Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28182|2024-08-03T21:40:12.219Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28182</link>
      <description>The Web Service configuration function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28182|2024-08-03T21:40:12.219Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28207|2024-08-03T21:40:12.874Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28207</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Get Help file function) does not filter the specific parameter. As obtaining the administrator permission, remote attackers can use the means of path traversal to access system files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28207|2024-08-03T21:40:12.874Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28200|2024-08-03T21:40:12.953Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28200</link>
      <description>The CD media configuration function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28200|2024-08-03T21:40:12.953Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23970|2024-08-03T03:59:23.252Z -- asus -- rt-ax56u
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23970</link>
      <description>ASUS RT-AX56U’s update_json function has a path traversal vulnerability due to insufficient filtering for special characters in the URL parameter. An unauthenticated LAN attacker can overwrite a system file by uploading another file with the same file name, which results in service disruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23970|2024-08-03T03:59:23.252Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28192|2024-08-03T21:40:12.695Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28192</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Remote video storage function) does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28192|2024-08-03T21:40:12.695Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22054|2024-08-03T03:00:55.327Z -- asus -- rt-ax56u
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22054</link>
      <description>ASUS RT-AX56U’s login function contains a path traversal vulnerability due to its inadequate filtering for special characters in URL parameters, which allows an unauthenticated local area network attacker to access restricted system paths and download arbitrary files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22054|2024-08-03T03:00:55.327Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26669|2024-08-03T05:11:44.296Z -- asus -- control%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26669</link>
      <description>ASUS Control Center is vulnerable to SQL injection. An authenticated remote attacker with general user privilege can inject SQL command to specific API parameters to acquire database schema or access data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26669|2024-08-03T05:11:44.296Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23972|2024-08-03T03:59:22.869Z -- asus -- rt-ax56u
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23972</link>
      <description>ASUS RT-AX56U’s SQL handling function has an SQL injection vulnerability due to insufficient user input validation. An unauthenticated LAN attacker to inject arbitrary SQL code to read, modify and delete database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23972|2024-08-03T03:59:22.869Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28194|2024-08-03T21:40:13.880Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28194</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Remote image configuration setting) does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28194|2024-08-03T21:40:13.880Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23973|2024-08-03T03:59:23.337Z -- asus -- rt-ax56u
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23973</link>
      <description>ASUS RT-AX56U’s user profile configuration function is vulnerable to stack-based buffer overflow due to insufficient validation for parameter length. An unauthenticated LAN attacker can execute arbitrary code to perform arbitrary operations or disrupt service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23973|2024-08-03T03:59:23.337Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28190|2024-08-03T21:40:13.334Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28190</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Generate new certificate function) does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28190|2024-08-03T21:40:13.334Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28204|2024-08-03T21:40:12.669Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28204</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Modify user’s information function) does not filter the specific parameter. As obtaining the administrator permission, remote attackers can launch command injection to execute command arbitrary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28204|2024-08-03T21:40:12.669Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28197|2024-08-03T21:40:12.773Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28197</link>
      <description>The Active Directory configuration function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28197|2024-08-03T21:40:12.773Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28202|2024-08-03T21:40:14.013Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28202</link>
      <description>The Service configuration-2 function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28202|2024-08-03T21:40:14.013Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4221|2024-08-03T01:34:49.843Z -- asus -- nas-m25
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4221</link>
      <description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in Asus NAS-M25 allows an unauthenticated attacker to inject arbitrary OS commands via unsanitized cookie values.This issue affects NAS-M25: through 1.0.1.7.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4221|2024-08-03T01:34:49.843Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:26:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-25595|2024-08-03T04:42:49.985Z -- asus -- rt-ac86u
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-25595</link>
      <description>ASUS RT-AC86U has improper user request handling, which allows an unauthenticated LAN attacker to cause a denial of service by sending particular request a server-to-client reply attempt.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-25595|2024-08-03T04:42:49.985Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28193|2024-08-03T21:40:12.689Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28193</link>
      <description>The SMTP configuration function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28193|2024-08-03T21:40:12.689Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23971|2024-08-03T03:59:23.305Z -- asus -- rt-ax56u
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23971</link>
      <description>ASUS RT-AX56U’s update_PLC/PORT file has a path traversal vulnerability due to insufficient filtering for special characters in the URL parameter. An unauthenticated LAN attacker can overwrite a system file by uploading another PLC/PORT file with the same file name, which results in service disruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23971|2024-08-03T03:59:23.305Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22262|2024-08-03T03:07:50.316Z -- asus -- armoury%20crate%20%26%20aura%20creator%20installer%20%28rog%20live%20service%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22262</link>
      <description>ROG Live Service’s function for deleting temp files created by installation has an improper link resolution before file access vulnerability. Since this function does not validate the path before deletion, an unauthenticated local attacker can create an unexpected symbolic link to system file path, to delete arbitrary system files and disrupt system service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22262|2024-08-03T03:07:50.316Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21933|2024-08-03T03:00:54.898Z -- asus -- vc65-c1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21933</link>
      <description>ASUS VivoMini/Mini PC device has an improper input validation vulnerability. A local attacker with system privilege can use system management interrupt (SMI) to modify memory, resulting in arbitrary code execution for controlling the system or disrupting service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21933|2024-08-03T03:00:54.898Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28186|2024-08-03T21:40:13.558Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28186</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (ActiveX configuration-2 acquisition) does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28186|2024-08-03T21:40:13.558Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38105|2024-08-03T10:45:52.594Z -- asus -- rt-ax82u
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38105</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability exists in the cm_processREQ_NC opcode of Asus RT-AX82U 3.0.0.4.386_49674-ge182230 router's configuration service. A specially-crafted network packets can lead to a disclosure of sensitive information. An attacker can send a network request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38105|2024-08-03T10:45:52.594Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 20:44:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28205|2024-08-03T21:40:13.302Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28205</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Delete SOL video file function) does not filter the specific parameter. As obtaining the administrator permission, remote attackers can use the means of path traversal to access system files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28205|2024-08-03T21:40:13.302Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28196|2024-08-03T21:40:12.986Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28196</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Generate SSL certificate function) does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28196|2024-08-03T21:40:12.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28189|2024-08-03T21:40:12.875Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28189</link>
      <description>The SMTP configuration function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28189|2024-08-03T21:40:12.875Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28176|2024-08-03T21:40:12.256Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28176</link>
      <description>The DNS configuration function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28176|2024-08-03T21:40:12.256Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28198|2024-08-03T21:40:12.653Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28198</link>
      <description>The Firmware protocol configuration function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28198|2024-08-03T21:40:12.653Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38699|2024-08-03T11:02:14.548Z -- asus -- armoury%20crate%20service
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38699</link>
      <description>Armoury Crate Service’s logging function has insufficient validation to check if the log file is a symbolic link. A physical attacker with general user privilege can modify the log file property to a symbolic link that points to arbitrary system file, causing the logging function to overwrite the system file and disrupt the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38699|2024-08-03T11:02:14.548Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-25597|2024-08-03T04:42:50.062Z -- asus -- rt-ac86u
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-25597</link>
      <description>ASUS RT-AC86U’s LPD service has insufficient filtering for special characters in the user request, which allows an unauthenticated LAN attacker to perform command injection attack, execute arbitrary commands and disrupt or terminate service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-25597|2024-08-03T04:42:50.062Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28187|2024-08-03T21:40:12.312Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28187</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Generate new SSL certificate) does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28187|2024-08-03T21:40:12.312Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28195|2024-08-03T21:40:12.683Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28195</link>
      <description>The Radius configuration function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28195|2024-08-03T21:40:12.683Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28188|2024-08-03T21:40:12.235Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28188</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Modify user’s information function) does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28188|2024-08-03T21:40:12.235Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35720|2024-08-02T16:30:44.421Z -- asus -- rt-ax92u</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35720</link>
      <description>ASUS RT-AX92U lighttpd mod_webdav.so SQL Injection Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected ASUS RT-AX92U routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. 

The specific flaw exists within the mod_webdav.so module. When parsing a request, the process does not properly validate a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-16078.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35720|2024-08-02T16:30:44.421Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3912|2024-08-01T20:26:57.193Z -- asus -- dsl-n17u</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3912</link>
      <description>Certain models of ASUS routers have an arbitrary firmware upload vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary system commands on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3912|2024-08-01T20:26:57.193Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 09:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0401|2024-08-01T18:04:49.502Z -- asus -- expertwifi</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0401</link>
      <description>ASUS routers supporting custom OpenVPN profiles are vulnerable to a code execution vulnerability. An authenticated and remote attacker can execute arbitrary operating system commands by uploading a crafted OVPN profile. Known affected routers include ASUS ExpertWiFi, ASUS RT-AX55, ASUS RT-AX58U, ASUS RT-AC67U, ASUS RT-AC68R, ASUS RT-AC68U, ASUS RT-AX86, ASUS RT-AC86U, ASUS RT-AX88U, and ASUS RT-AX3000.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0401|2024-08-01T18:04:49.502Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 16:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1655|2024-08-01T18:48:21.610Z -- asus -- expertwifi%20ebm63</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1655</link>
      <description>Certain ASUS WiFi routers models has an OS Command Injection vulnerability, allowing an authenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary system commands by sending a specially crafted request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1655|2024-08-01T18:48:21.610Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 04:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31161|2024-07-16T17:06:54.254Z -- asus -- download%20master</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31161</link>
      <description>The upload functionality of ASUS Download Master does not properly filter user input. Remote attackers with administrative privilege can exploit this vulnerability to upload any file to any location. They may even upload malicious web page files to the website directory, allowing arbitrary system commands to be executed upon browsing the webpage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31161|2024-07-16T17:06:54.254Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:53:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31162|2024-06-18T20:43:05.443Z -- asus -- download%20master</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31162</link>
      <description>The specific function parameter of ASUS Download Master does not properly filter user input. An unauthenticated remote attacker with administrative privileges can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary system commands on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31162|2024-06-18T20:43:05.443Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 06:35:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3079|2024-06-17T19:28:48.754Z -- asus -- zenwifi%20xt8</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3079</link>
      <description>Certain models of ASUS routers have buffer overflow vulnerabilities, allowing remote attackers with administrative privileges to execute arbitrary commands on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3079|2024-06-17T19:28:48.754Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3080|2024-06-17T13:36:27.202Z -- asus -- zenwifi%20xt8</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3080</link>
      <description>Certain ASUS router models have authentication bypass vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to log in the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3080|2024-06-17T13:36:27.202Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3912|2024-06-14T17:40:50.459Z -- asus -- dsl-n17u</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3912</link>
      <description>Certain models of ASUS routers have an arbitrary firmware upload vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary system commands on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3912|2024-06-14T17:40:50.459Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 09:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3912|2024-06-14T10:57:26.604Z -- asus -- dsl-n17u</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3912</link>
      <description>Certain models of ASUS routers have an arbitrary firmware upload vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary system commands on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3912|2024-06-14T10:57:26.604Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 09:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31162|2024-06-14T06:35:07.192Z -- asus -- download%20master</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31162</link>
      <description>The specific function parameter of ASUS Download Master does not properly filter user input. An unauthenticated remote attacker with administrative privileges can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary system commands on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31162|2024-06-14T06:35:07.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 06:35:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31163|2024-06-14T06:52:50.331Z -- asus -- download%20master</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31163</link>
      <description>ASUS Download Master has a buffer overflow vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker with administrative privileges can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary system commands on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31163|2024-06-14T06:52:50.331Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 06:52:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3079|2024-06-14T02:32:21.718Z -- asus -- zenwifi%20xt8</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3079</link>
      <description>Certain models of ASUS routers have buffer overflow vulnerabilities, allowing remote attackers with administrative privileges to execute arbitrary commands on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3079|2024-06-14T02:32:21.718Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3080|2024-06-14T02:57:27.002Z -- asus -- zenwifi%20xt8</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3080</link>
      <description>Certain ASUS router models have authentication bypass vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to log in the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3080|2024-06-14T02:57:27.002Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0401|2024-06-04T17:58:40.749Z -- asus -- expertwifi</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0401</link>
      <description>ASUS routers supporting custom OpenVPN profiles are vulnerable to a code execution vulnerability. An authenticated and remote attacker can execute arbitrary operating system commands by uploading a crafted OVPN profile. Known affected routers include ASUS ExpertWiFi, ASUS RT-AX55, ASUS RT-AX58U, ASUS RT-AC67U, ASUS RT-AC68R, ASUS RT-AC68U, ASUS RT-AX86, ASUS RT-AC86U, ASUS RT-AX88U, and ASUS RT-AX3000.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0401|2024-06-04T17:58:40.749Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 16:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1655|2024-04-15T06:21:37.900Z -- asus -- expertwifi%20ebm63</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1655</link>
      <description>Certain ASUS WiFi routers models has an OS Command Injection vulnerability, allowing an authenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary system commands by sending a specially crafted request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1655|2024-04-15T06:21:37.900Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 04:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35720|2024-06-04T17:18:10.530Z -- asus -- rt-ax92u</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35720</link>
      <description>ASUS RT-AX92U lighttpd mod_webdav.so SQL Injection Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected ASUS RT-AX92U routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. 

The specific flaw exists within the mod_webdav.so module. When parsing a request, the process does not properly validate a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-16078.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35720|2024-06-04T17:18:10.530Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3080|2024-06-14T02:59:53.642Z -- asus -- zenwifi%20xt8</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3080</link>
      <description>Certain ASUS router models have authentication bypass vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to log in the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3080|2024-06-14T02:59:53.642Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31159|2024-06-14T03:25:03.735Z -- asus -- download%20master</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31159</link>
      <description>The parameter used in the certain page of ASUS Download Master is not properly filtered for user input. A remote attacker with administrative privilege can insert JavaScript code to the parameter for Reflected Cross-site scripting attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31159|2024-06-14T03:25:03.735Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:25:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3079|2024-06-14T02:59:31.013Z -- asus -- zenwifi%20xt8</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3079</link>
      <description>Certain models of ASUS routers have buffer overflow vulnerabilities, allowing remote attackers with administrative privileges to execute arbitrary commands on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3079|2024-06-14T02:59:31.013Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31161|2024-06-14T03:53:51.560Z -- asus -- download%20master</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31161</link>
      <description>The upload functionality of ASUS Download Master does not properly filter user input. Remote attackers with administrative privilege can exploit this vulnerability to upload any file to any location. They may even upload malicious web page files to the website directory, allowing arbitrary system commands to be executed upon browsing the webpage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31161|2024-06-14T03:53:51.560Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:53:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31160|2024-06-14T03:41:21.402Z -- asus -- download%20master</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31160</link>
      <description>The parameter used in the certain page of ASUS Download Master is not properly filtered for user input. A remote attacker with administrative privilege can insert JavaScript code to the parameter for Stored Cross-site scripting attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31160|2024-06-14T03:41:21.402Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:41:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3912|2024-06-14T09:35:32.401Z -- asus -- dsl-n17u</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3912</link>
      <description>Certain models of ASUS routers have an arbitrary firmware upload vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary system commands on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3912|2024-06-14T09:35:32.401Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 09:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31163|2024-06-14T15:41:17.475Z -- asus -- download%20master</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31163</link>
      <description>ASUS Download Master has a buffer overflow vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker with administrative privileges can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary system commands on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31163|2024-06-14T15:41:17.475Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 06:52:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31159|2024-06-14T18:14:45.924Z -- asus -- download%20master</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31159</link>
      <description>The parameter used in the certain page of ASUS Download Master is not properly filtered for user input. A remote attacker with administrative privilege can insert JavaScript code to the parameter for Reflected Cross-site scripting attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31159|2024-06-14T18:14:45.924Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:25:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3080|2024-06-17T14:38:06.904Z -- asus -- zenwifi%20xt8</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3080</link>
      <description>Certain ASUS router models have authentication bypass vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to log in the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3080|2024-06-17T14:38:06.904Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1655|2024-06-18T17:40:25.275Z -- asus -- expertwifi%20ebm63</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1655</link>
      <description>Certain ASUS WiFi routers models has an OS Command Injection vulnerability, allowing an authenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary system commands by sending a specially crafted request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1655|2024-06-18T17:40:25.275Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 04:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3912|2024-06-28T03:55:21.068Z -- asus -- dsl-n17u</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3912</link>
      <description>Certain models of ASUS routers have an arbitrary firmware upload vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary system commands on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3912|2024-06-28T03:55:21.068Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 09:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3080|2024-06-28T03:55:18.969Z -- asus -- zenwifi%20xt8</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3080</link>
      <description>Certain ASUS router models have authentication bypass vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to log in the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3080|2024-06-28T03:55:18.969Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3079|2024-06-28T03:55:20.013Z -- asus -- zenwifi%20xt8</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3079</link>
      <description>Certain models of ASUS routers have buffer overflow vulnerabilities, allowing remote attackers with administrative privileges to execute arbitrary commands on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3079|2024-06-28T03:55:20.013Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31160|2024-07-19T18:45:33.807Z -- asus -- download%20master</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31160</link>
      <description>The parameter used in the certain page of ASUS Download Master is not properly filtered for user input. A remote attacker with administrative privilege can insert JavaScript code to the parameter for Stored Cross-site scripting attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31160|2024-07-19T18:45:33.807Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:41:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3079|2024-08-01T19:32:42.604Z -- asus -- zenwifi%20xt8</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3079</link>
      <description>Certain models of ASUS routers have buffer overflow vulnerabilities, allowing remote attackers with administrative privileges to execute arbitrary commands on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3079|2024-08-01T19:32:42.604Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3080|2024-08-01T19:32:42.618Z -- asus -- zenwifi%20xt8</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3080</link>
      <description>Certain ASUS router models have authentication bypass vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to log in the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3080|2024-08-01T19:32:42.618Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31160|2024-08-02T01:46:04.470Z -- asus -- download%20master</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31160</link>
      <description>The parameter used in the certain page of ASUS Download Master is not properly filtered for user input. A remote attacker with administrative privilege can insert JavaScript code to the parameter for Stored Cross-site scripting attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31160|2024-08-02T01:46:04.470Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:41:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31159|2024-08-02T01:46:04.534Z -- asus -- download%20master</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31159</link>
      <description>The parameter used in the certain page of ASUS Download Master is not properly filtered for user input. A remote attacker with administrative privilege can insert JavaScript code to the parameter for Reflected Cross-site scripting attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31159|2024-08-02T01:46:04.534Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:25:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31163|2024-08-02T01:46:04.321Z -- asus -- download%20master</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31163</link>
      <description>ASUS Download Master has a buffer overflow vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker with administrative privileges can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary system commands on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31163|2024-08-02T01:46:04.321Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 06:52:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31162|2024-08-02T01:46:04.365Z -- asus -- download%20master</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31162</link>
      <description>The specific function parameter of ASUS Download Master does not properly filter user input. An unauthenticated remote attacker with administrative privileges can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary system commands on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31162|2024-08-02T01:46:04.365Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 06:35:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31161|2024-08-02T01:46:04.773Z -- asus -- download%20master</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31161</link>
      <description>The upload functionality of ASUS Download Master does not properly filter user input. Remote attackers with administrative privilege can exploit this vulnerability to upload any file to any location. They may even upload malicious web page files to the website directory, allowing arbitrary system commands to be executed upon browsing the webpage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31161|2024-08-02T01:46:04.773Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:53:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
