<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for ASUS -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/asus/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for ASUS -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 06:24:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41289|2024-09-17T00:36:55.811Z -- asus -- p453uj%20bios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41289</link>
      <description>ASUS P453UJ contains the Improper Restriction of Operations within the Bounds of a Memory Buffer vulnerability. With a general user’s permission, local attackers can modify the BIOS by replacing or filling in the content of the designated Memory DataBuffer, which causing a failure of integrity verification and further resulting in a failure to boot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41289|2024-09-17T00:36:55.811Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 09:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26668|2024-09-17T02:42:54.277Z -- asus -- control%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26668</link>
      <description>ASUS Control Center API has a broken access control vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker can call privileged API functions to perform partial system operations or cause partial disrupt of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26668|2024-09-17T02:42:54.277Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 05:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28202|2024-09-17T02:12:15.278Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28202</link>
      <description>The Service configuration-2 function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28202|2024-09-17T02:12:15.278Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 05:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28189|2024-09-17T02:21:09.330Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28189</link>
      <description>The SMTP configuration function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28189|2024-09-17T02:21:09.330Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 05:02:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26669|2024-09-17T02:42:16.801Z -- asus -- control%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26669</link>
      <description>ASUS Control Center is vulnerable to SQL injection. An authenticated remote attacker with general user privilege can inject SQL command to specific API parameters to acquire database schema or access data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26669|2024-09-17T02:42:16.801Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 05:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28194|2024-09-17T04:09:52.489Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28194</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Remote image configuration setting) does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28194|2024-09-17T04:09:52.489Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 05:02:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22054|2024-09-17T01:01:37.824Z -- asus -- rt-ax56u
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22054</link>
      <description>ASUS RT-AX56U’s login function contains a path traversal vulnerability due to its inadequate filtering for special characters in URL parameters, which allows an unauthenticated local area network attacker to access restricted system paths and download arbitrary files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22054|2024-09-17T01:01:37.824Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 04:50:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28192|2024-09-17T03:28:44.149Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28192</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Remote video storage function) does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28192|2024-09-17T03:28:44.149Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 05:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28181|2024-09-17T00:31:42.608Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28181</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Remote video configuration setting) does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28181|2024-09-17T00:31:42.608Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 05:02:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28176|2024-09-17T01:41:07.100Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28176</link>
      <description>The DNS configuration function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28176|2024-09-17T01:41:07.100Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 05:01:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28201|2024-09-17T01:31:19.486Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28201</link>
      <description>The Service configuration-1 function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28201|2024-09-17T01:31:19.486Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 05:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22262|2024-09-17T01:45:46.992Z -- asus -- armoury%20crate%20%26%20aura%20creator%20installer%20%28rog%20live%20service%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22262</link>
      <description>ROG Live Service’s function for deleting temp files created by installation has an improper link resolution before file access vulnerability. Since this function does not validate the path before deletion, an unauthenticated local attacker can create an unexpected symbolic link to system file path, to delete arbitrary system files and disrupt system service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22262|2024-09-17T01:45:46.992Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 01:55:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28205|2024-09-17T02:21:06.092Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28205</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Delete SOL video file function) does not filter the specific parameter. As obtaining the administrator permission, remote attackers can use the means of path traversal to access system files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28205|2024-09-17T02:21:06.092Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 05:02:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23973|2024-09-17T01:35:51.997Z -- asus -- rt-ax56u
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23973</link>
      <description>ASUS RT-AX56U’s user profile configuration function is vulnerable to stack-based buffer overflow due to insufficient validation for parameter length. An unauthenticated LAN attacker can execute arbitrary code to perform arbitrary operations or disrupt service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23973|2024-09-17T01:35:51.997Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 18:22:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28204|2024-09-17T03:38:49.311Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28204</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Modify user’s information function) does not filter the specific parameter. As obtaining the administrator permission, remote attackers can launch command injection to execute command arbitrary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28204|2024-09-17T03:38:49.311Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 05:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-25596|2024-09-17T00:46:09.147Z -- asus -- rt-ac86u
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-25596</link>
      <description>ASUS RT-AC56U’s configuration function has a heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability due to insufficient validation for the decryption parameter length, which allows an unauthenticated LAN attacker to execute arbitrary code, perform arbitrary operations and disrupt service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-25596|2024-09-17T00:46:09.147Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 18:22:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28179|2024-09-17T01:05:48.147Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28179</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Media support configuration setting) does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28179|2024-09-17T01:05:48.147Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 05:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28193|2024-09-17T03:48:35.862Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28193</link>
      <description>The SMTP configuration function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28193|2024-09-17T03:48:35.862Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 05:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26673|2024-09-17T01:41:18.038Z -- asus -- rt-ax88u
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26673</link>
      <description>ASUS RT-AX88U has insufficient filtering for special characters in the HTTP header parameter. A remote attacker with general user privilege can exploit this vulnerability to inject JavaScript and perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26673|2024-09-17T01:41:18.038Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 06:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28183|2024-09-17T03:48:00.979Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28183</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Web License configuration setting) does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28183|2024-09-17T03:48:00.979Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 05:02:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23970|2024-09-17T01:55:53.709Z -- asus -- rt-ax56u
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23970</link>
      <description>ASUS RT-AX56U’s update_json function has a path traversal vulnerability due to insufficient filtering for special characters in the URL parameter. An unauthenticated LAN attacker can overwrite a system file by uploading another file with the same file name, which results in service disruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23970|2024-09-17T01:55:53.709Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 18:22:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23971|2024-09-17T04:04:05.439Z -- asus -- rt-ax56u
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23971</link>
      <description>ASUS RT-AX56U’s update_PLC/PORT file has a path traversal vulnerability due to insufficient filtering for special characters in the URL parameter. An unauthenticated LAN attacker can overwrite a system file by uploading another PLC/PORT file with the same file name, which results in service disruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23971|2024-09-17T04:04:05.439Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 18:22:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31161|2024-08-02T01:46:04.773Z -- asus -- download%20master</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31161</link>
      <description>The upload functionality of ASUS Download Master does not properly filter user input. Remote attackers with administrative privilege can exploit this vulnerability to upload any file to any location. They may even upload malicious web page files to the website directory, allowing arbitrary system commands to be executed upon browsing the webpage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31161|2024-08-02T01:46:04.773Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:53:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31162|2024-08-02T01:46:04.365Z -- asus -- download%20master</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31162</link>
      <description>The specific function parameter of ASUS Download Master does not properly filter user input. An unauthenticated remote attacker with administrative privileges can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary system commands on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31162|2024-08-02T01:46:04.365Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 06:35:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31163|2024-08-02T01:46:04.321Z -- asus -- download%20master</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31163</link>
      <description>ASUS Download Master has a buffer overflow vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker with administrative privileges can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary system commands on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31163|2024-08-02T01:46:04.321Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 06:52:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31159|2024-08-02T01:46:04.534Z -- asus -- download%20master</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31159</link>
      <description>The parameter used in the certain page of ASUS Download Master is not properly filtered for user input. A remote attacker with administrative privilege can insert JavaScript code to the parameter for Reflected Cross-site scripting attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31159|2024-08-02T01:46:04.534Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:25:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31160|2024-08-02T01:46:04.470Z -- asus -- download%20master</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31160</link>
      <description>The parameter used in the certain page of ASUS Download Master is not properly filtered for user input. A remote attacker with administrative privilege can insert JavaScript code to the parameter for Stored Cross-site scripting attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31160|2024-08-02T01:46:04.470Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:41:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3080|2024-08-01T19:32:42.618Z -- asus -- zenwifi%20xt8</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3080</link>
      <description>Certain ASUS router models have authentication bypass vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to log in the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3080|2024-08-01T19:32:42.618Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3079|2024-08-01T19:32:42.604Z -- asus -- zenwifi%20xt8</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3079</link>
      <description>Certain models of ASUS routers have buffer overflow vulnerabilities, allowing remote attackers with administrative privileges to execute arbitrary commands on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3079|2024-08-01T19:32:42.604Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31160|2024-07-19T18:45:33.807Z -- asus -- download%20master</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31160</link>
      <description>The parameter used in the certain page of ASUS Download Master is not properly filtered for user input. A remote attacker with administrative privilege can insert JavaScript code to the parameter for Stored Cross-site scripting attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31160|2024-07-19T18:45:33.807Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:41:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3079|2024-06-28T03:55:20.013Z -- asus -- zenwifi%20xt8</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3079</link>
      <description>Certain models of ASUS routers have buffer overflow vulnerabilities, allowing remote attackers with administrative privileges to execute arbitrary commands on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3079|2024-06-28T03:55:20.013Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3080|2024-06-28T03:55:18.969Z -- asus -- zenwifi%20xt8</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3080</link>
      <description>Certain ASUS router models have authentication bypass vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to log in the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3080|2024-06-28T03:55:18.969Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3912|2024-06-28T03:55:21.068Z -- asus -- dsl-n17u</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3912</link>
      <description>Certain models of ASUS routers have an arbitrary firmware upload vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary system commands on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3912|2024-06-28T03:55:21.068Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 09:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1655|2024-06-18T17:40:25.275Z -- asus -- expertwifi%20ebm63</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1655</link>
      <description>Certain ASUS WiFi routers models has an OS Command Injection vulnerability, allowing an authenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary system commands by sending a specially crafted request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1655|2024-06-18T17:40:25.275Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 04:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3080|2024-06-17T14:38:06.904Z -- asus -- zenwifi%20xt8</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3080</link>
      <description>Certain ASUS router models have authentication bypass vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to log in the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3080|2024-06-17T14:38:06.904Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31159|2024-06-14T18:14:45.924Z -- asus -- download%20master</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31159</link>
      <description>The parameter used in the certain page of ASUS Download Master is not properly filtered for user input. A remote attacker with administrative privilege can insert JavaScript code to the parameter for Reflected Cross-site scripting attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31159|2024-06-14T18:14:45.924Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:25:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31163|2024-06-14T15:41:17.475Z -- asus -- download%20master</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31163</link>
      <description>ASUS Download Master has a buffer overflow vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker with administrative privileges can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary system commands on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31163|2024-06-14T15:41:17.475Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 06:52:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3912|2024-06-14T09:35:32.401Z -- asus -- dsl-n17u</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3912</link>
      <description>Certain models of ASUS routers have an arbitrary firmware upload vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary system commands on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3912|2024-06-14T09:35:32.401Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 09:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31160|2024-06-14T03:41:21.402Z -- asus -- download%20master</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31160</link>
      <description>The parameter used in the certain page of ASUS Download Master is not properly filtered for user input. A remote attacker with administrative privilege can insert JavaScript code to the parameter for Stored Cross-site scripting attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31160|2024-06-14T03:41:21.402Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:41:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31161|2024-06-14T03:53:51.560Z -- asus -- download%20master</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31161</link>
      <description>The upload functionality of ASUS Download Master does not properly filter user input. Remote attackers with administrative privilege can exploit this vulnerability to upload any file to any location. They may even upload malicious web page files to the website directory, allowing arbitrary system commands to be executed upon browsing the webpage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31161|2024-06-14T03:53:51.560Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:53:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3079|2024-06-14T02:59:31.013Z -- asus -- zenwifi%20xt8</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3079</link>
      <description>Certain models of ASUS routers have buffer overflow vulnerabilities, allowing remote attackers with administrative privileges to execute arbitrary commands on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3079|2024-06-14T02:59:31.013Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31159|2024-06-14T03:25:03.735Z -- asus -- download%20master</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31159</link>
      <description>The parameter used in the certain page of ASUS Download Master is not properly filtered for user input. A remote attacker with administrative privilege can insert JavaScript code to the parameter for Reflected Cross-site scripting attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31159|2024-06-14T03:25:03.735Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:25:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3080|2024-06-14T02:59:53.642Z -- asus -- zenwifi%20xt8</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3080</link>
      <description>Certain ASUS router models have authentication bypass vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to log in the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3080|2024-06-14T02:59:53.642Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35720|2024-06-04T17:18:10.530Z -- asus -- rt-ax92u</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35720</link>
      <description>ASUS RT-AX92U lighttpd mod_webdav.so SQL Injection Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected ASUS RT-AX92U routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. 

The specific flaw exists within the mod_webdav.so module. When parsing a request, the process does not properly validate a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-16078.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35720|2024-06-04T17:18:10.530Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1655|2024-04-15T06:21:37.900Z -- asus -- expertwifi%20ebm63</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1655</link>
      <description>Certain ASUS WiFi routers models has an OS Command Injection vulnerability, allowing an authenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary system commands by sending a specially crafted request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1655|2024-04-15T06:21:37.900Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 04:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0401|2024-06-04T17:58:40.749Z -- asus -- expertwifi</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0401</link>
      <description>ASUS routers supporting custom OpenVPN profiles are vulnerable to a code execution vulnerability. An authenticated and remote attacker can execute arbitrary operating system commands by uploading a crafted OVPN profile. Known affected routers include ASUS ExpertWiFi, ASUS RT-AX55, ASUS RT-AX58U, ASUS RT-AC67U, ASUS RT-AC68R, ASUS RT-AC68U, ASUS RT-AX86, ASUS RT-AC86U, ASUS RT-AX88U, and ASUS RT-AX3000.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0401|2024-06-04T17:58:40.749Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 16:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3080|2024-06-14T02:57:27.002Z -- asus -- zenwifi%20xt8</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3080</link>
      <description>Certain ASUS router models have authentication bypass vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to log in the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3080|2024-06-14T02:57:27.002Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3079|2024-06-14T02:32:21.718Z -- asus -- zenwifi%20xt8</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3079</link>
      <description>Certain models of ASUS routers have buffer overflow vulnerabilities, allowing remote attackers with administrative privileges to execute arbitrary commands on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3079|2024-06-14T02:32:21.718Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31163|2024-06-14T06:52:50.331Z -- asus -- download%20master</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31163</link>
      <description>ASUS Download Master has a buffer overflow vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker with administrative privileges can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary system commands on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31163|2024-06-14T06:52:50.331Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 06:52:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31162|2024-06-14T06:35:07.192Z -- asus -- download%20master</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31162</link>
      <description>The specific function parameter of ASUS Download Master does not properly filter user input. An unauthenticated remote attacker with administrative privileges can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary system commands on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31162|2024-06-14T06:35:07.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 06:35:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3912|2024-06-14T10:57:26.604Z -- asus -- dsl-n17u</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3912</link>
      <description>Certain models of ASUS routers have an arbitrary firmware upload vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary system commands on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3912|2024-06-14T10:57:26.604Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 09:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3912|2024-06-14T17:40:50.459Z -- asus -- dsl-n17u</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3912</link>
      <description>Certain models of ASUS routers have an arbitrary firmware upload vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary system commands on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3912|2024-06-14T17:40:50.459Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 09:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3080|2024-06-17T13:36:27.202Z -- asus -- zenwifi%20xt8</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3080</link>
      <description>Certain ASUS router models have authentication bypass vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to log in the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3080|2024-06-17T13:36:27.202Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3079|2024-06-17T19:28:48.754Z -- asus -- zenwifi%20xt8</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3079</link>
      <description>Certain models of ASUS routers have buffer overflow vulnerabilities, allowing remote attackers with administrative privileges to execute arbitrary commands on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3079|2024-06-17T19:28:48.754Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31162|2024-06-18T20:43:05.443Z -- asus -- download%20master</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31162</link>
      <description>The specific function parameter of ASUS Download Master does not properly filter user input. An unauthenticated remote attacker with administrative privileges can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary system commands on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31162|2024-06-18T20:43:05.443Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 06:35:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31161|2024-07-16T17:06:54.254Z -- asus -- download%20master</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31161</link>
      <description>The upload functionality of ASUS Download Master does not properly filter user input. Remote attackers with administrative privilege can exploit this vulnerability to upload any file to any location. They may even upload malicious web page files to the website directory, allowing arbitrary system commands to be executed upon browsing the webpage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31161|2024-07-16T17:06:54.254Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 03:53:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1655|2024-08-01T18:48:21.610Z -- asus -- expertwifi%20ebm63</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1655</link>
      <description>Certain ASUS WiFi routers models has an OS Command Injection vulnerability, allowing an authenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary system commands by sending a specially crafted request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1655|2024-08-01T18:48:21.610Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 04:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0401|2024-08-01T18:04:49.502Z -- asus -- expertwifi</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0401</link>
      <description>ASUS routers supporting custom OpenVPN profiles are vulnerable to a code execution vulnerability. An authenticated and remote attacker can execute arbitrary operating system commands by uploading a crafted OVPN profile. Known affected routers include ASUS ExpertWiFi, ASUS RT-AX55, ASUS RT-AX58U, ASUS RT-AC67U, ASUS RT-AC68R, ASUS RT-AC68U, ASUS RT-AX86, ASUS RT-AC86U, ASUS RT-AX88U, and ASUS RT-AX3000.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0401|2024-08-01T18:04:49.502Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 16:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3912|2024-08-01T20:26:57.193Z -- asus -- dsl-n17u</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3912</link>
      <description>Certain models of ASUS routers have an arbitrary firmware upload vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary system commands on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3912|2024-08-01T20:26:57.193Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 09:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35720|2024-08-02T16:30:44.421Z -- asus -- rt-ax92u</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35720</link>
      <description>ASUS RT-AX92U lighttpd mod_webdav.so SQL Injection Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected ASUS RT-AX92U routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. 

The specific flaw exists within the mod_webdav.so module. When parsing a request, the process does not properly validate a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-16078.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35720|2024-08-02T16:30:44.421Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
