<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for ASUS -- BMC firmware for Z10PR-D16</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/asus/bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for ASUS -- BMC firmware for Z10PR-D16</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 22:22:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28188|2024-09-16T16:22:42.826Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28188</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Modify user’s information function) does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28188|2024-09-16T16:22:42.826Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 05:02:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28177|2024-09-16T19:10:49.934Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28177</link>
      <description>The LDAP configuration function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28177|2024-09-16T19:10:49.934Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 05:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28187|2024-09-16T17:03:45.222Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28187</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Generate new SSL certificate) does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28187|2024-09-16T17:03:45.222Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 05:02:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28184|2024-09-16T20:31:30.262Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28184</link>
      <description>The Active Directory configuration function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28184|2024-09-16T20:31:30.262Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 05:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28178|2024-09-16T17:38:58.664Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28178</link>
      <description>The UEFI configuration function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28178|2024-09-16T17:38:58.664Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 05:02:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28182|2024-09-16T21:07:24.302Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28182</link>
      <description>The Web Service configuration function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28182|2024-09-16T21:07:24.302Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 05:02:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
