<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for ASUS -- BMC firmware for ASMB9-iKVM</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/asus/bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for ASUS -- BMC firmware for ASMB9-iKVM</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:22:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28208|2024-08-03T21:40:12.868Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28208</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Get video file function) does not filter the specific parameter. As obtaining the administrator permission, remote attackers can use the means of path traversal to access system files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28208|2024-08-03T21:40:12.868Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28191|2024-08-03T21:40:12.722Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28191</link>
      <description>The Firmware update function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28191|2024-08-03T21:40:12.722Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28199|2024-08-03T21:40:12.939Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28199</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Modify user’s information function) does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28199|2024-08-03T21:40:12.939Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28209|2024-08-03T21:40:13.105Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28209</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Delete video file function) does not filter the specific parameter. As obtaining the administrator permission, remote attackers can use the means of path traversal to access system files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28209|2024-08-03T21:40:13.105Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28201|2024-08-03T21:40:13.737Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28201</link>
      <description>The Service configuration-1 function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28201|2024-08-03T21:40:13.737Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28206|2024-08-03T21:40:14.066Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28206</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Record video file function) does not filter the specific parameter. As obtaining the administrator permission, remote attackers can use the means of path traversal to access system files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28206|2024-08-03T21:40:14.066Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28207|2024-08-03T21:40:12.874Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28207</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Get Help file function) does not filter the specific parameter. As obtaining the administrator permission, remote attackers can use the means of path traversal to access system files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28207|2024-08-03T21:40:12.874Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28200|2024-08-03T21:40:12.953Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28200</link>
      <description>The CD media configuration function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28200|2024-08-03T21:40:12.953Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28192|2024-08-03T21:40:12.695Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28192</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Remote video storage function) does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28192|2024-08-03T21:40:12.695Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28194|2024-08-03T21:40:13.880Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28194</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Remote image configuration setting) does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28194|2024-08-03T21:40:13.880Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28190|2024-08-03T21:40:13.334Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28190</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Generate new certificate function) does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28190|2024-08-03T21:40:13.334Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28197|2024-08-03T21:40:12.773Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28197</link>
      <description>The Active Directory configuration function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28197|2024-08-03T21:40:12.773Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28202|2024-08-03T21:40:14.013Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28202</link>
      <description>The Service configuration-2 function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28202|2024-08-03T21:40:14.013Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28193|2024-08-03T21:40:12.689Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28193</link>
      <description>The SMTP configuration function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28193|2024-08-03T21:40:12.689Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28196|2024-08-03T21:40:12.986Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28196</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Generate SSL certificate function) does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28196|2024-08-03T21:40:12.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28198|2024-08-03T21:40:12.653Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28198</link>
      <description>The Firmware protocol configuration function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28198|2024-08-03T21:40:12.653Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28195|2024-08-03T21:40:12.683Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20asmb9-ikvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28195</link>
      <description>The Radius configuration function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28195|2024-08-03T21:40:12.683Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
