<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for ASUS -- BMC firmware for Z10PR-D16</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/asus/bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for ASUS -- BMC firmware for Z10PR-D16</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 23:22:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28183|2024-08-03T21:40:12.197Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28183</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Web License configuration setting) does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28183|2024-08-03T21:40:12.197Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28180|2024-08-03T21:40:12.215Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28180</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Audit log configuration setting) does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28180|2024-08-03T21:40:12.215Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28184|2024-08-03T21:40:12.920Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28184</link>
      <description>The Active Directory configuration function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28184|2024-08-03T21:40:12.920Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28181|2024-08-03T21:40:12.220Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28181</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Remote video configuration setting) does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28181|2024-08-03T21:40:12.220Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28178|2024-08-03T21:40:12.308Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28178</link>
      <description>The UEFI configuration function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28178|2024-08-03T21:40:12.308Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28175|2024-08-03T21:40:12.190Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28175</link>
      <description>The Radius configuration function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28175|2024-08-03T21:40:12.190Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28179|2024-08-03T21:40:12.296Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28179</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Media support configuration setting) does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28179|2024-08-03T21:40:12.296Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28177|2024-08-03T21:40:12.192Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28177</link>
      <description>The LDAP configuration function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28177|2024-08-03T21:40:12.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28185|2024-08-03T21:40:12.204Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28185</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (ActiveX configuration-1 acquisition) does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28185|2024-08-03T21:40:12.204Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28203|2024-08-03T21:40:12.667Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28203</link>
      <description>The Web Set Media Image function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not filter the specific parameter. As obtaining the administrator permission, remote attackers can launch command injection to execute command arbitrary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28203|2024-08-03T21:40:12.667Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28182|2024-08-03T21:40:12.219Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28182</link>
      <description>The Web Service configuration function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28182|2024-08-03T21:40:12.219Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28204|2024-08-03T21:40:12.669Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28204</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Modify user’s information function) does not filter the specific parameter. As obtaining the administrator permission, remote attackers can launch command injection to execute command arbitrary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28204|2024-08-03T21:40:12.669Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28186|2024-08-03T21:40:13.558Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28186</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (ActiveX configuration-2 acquisition) does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28186|2024-08-03T21:40:13.558Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28205|2024-08-03T21:40:13.302Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28205</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Delete SOL video file function) does not filter the specific parameter. As obtaining the administrator permission, remote attackers can use the means of path traversal to access system files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28205|2024-08-03T21:40:13.302Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28189|2024-08-03T21:40:12.875Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28189</link>
      <description>The SMTP configuration function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28189|2024-08-03T21:40:12.875Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28176|2024-08-03T21:40:12.256Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28176</link>
      <description>The DNS configuration function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28176|2024-08-03T21:40:12.256Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28187|2024-08-03T21:40:12.312Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28187</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Generate new SSL certificate) does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28187|2024-08-03T21:40:12.312Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28188|2024-08-03T21:40:12.235Z -- asus -- bmc%20firmware%20for%20z10pr-d16
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28188</link>
      <description>The specific function in ASUS BMC’s firmware Web management page (Modify user’s information function) does not verify the string length entered by users, resulting in a Buffer overflow vulnerability. As obtaining the privileged permission, remote attackers use the leakage to abnormally terminate the Web service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28188|2024-08-03T21:40:12.235Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
