<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for wpdevteam -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/wpdevteam/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for wpdevteam -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 12:25:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2083|2024-08-02T06:12:19.900Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20blocks%20%E2%80%93%20page%20builder%20gutenberg%20blocks%2C%20patterns%20%26%20templates
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2083</link>
      <description>The Essential Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized use of functionality due to a missing capability check on the save function in versions up to, and including, 4.0.6. This makes it possible for subscriber-level attackers to save plugin settings. While a nonce check is present, it is only executed when a nonce is provided. Not providing a nonce results in the nonce verification to be skipped. There is no capability check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2083|2024-08-02T06:12:19.900Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 05:33:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7044|2024-08-02T08:50:07.819Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7044</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via custom ID in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor access and higher to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7044|2024-08-02T08:50:07.819Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 09:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3779|2024-08-02T07:08:49.685Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3779</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthenticated API key disclosure in versions up to, and including, 5.8.1 due to the plugin adding the API key to the source code of any page running the MailChimp block. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to obtain a site's MailChimp API key. We recommend resetting any MailChimp API keys if running a vulnerable version of this plugin with the MailChimp block enabled as the API key may have been compromised. This only affects sites running the premium version of the plugin and that have the Mailchimp block enabled on a page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3779|2024-08-02T07:08:49.685Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 05:38:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4386|2024-08-02T07:24:04.545Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20blocks%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4386</link>
      <description>The Essential Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in versions up to, and including, 4.2.0 via deserialization of untrusted input in the get_posts function. This allows unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. No POP chain is present in the vulnerable plugin. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4386|2024-08-02T07:24:04.545Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 07:29:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4282|2024-08-02T07:24:03.815Z -- wpdevteam -- embedpress%20%E2%80%93%20embed%20pdf%2C%20youtube%2C%20google%20docs%2C%20vimeo%2C%20wistia%20videos%2C%20audios%2C%20maps%20%26%20any%20documents%20in%20gutenberg%20%26%20elementor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4282</link>
      <description>The EmbedPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'admin_post_remove' and 'remove_private_data' functions in versions up to, and including, 3.8.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber privileges or above, to delete plugin settings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4282|2024-08-02T07:24:03.815Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 11:05:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3371|2024-08-02T06:55:03.189Z -- wpdevteam -- embedpress%20%E2%80%93%20embed%20pdf%2C%20youtube%2C%20google%20docs%2C%20vimeo%2C%20wistia%20videos%2C%20audios%2C%20maps%20%26%20any%20documents%20in%20gutenberg%20%26%20elementor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3371</link>
      <description>The User Registration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure due to hardcoded encryption key on the 'lock_content_form_handler' and 'display_password_form' function in versions up to, and including, 3.7.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to decrypt and view the password protected content.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3371|2024-08-02T06:55:03.189Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 01:55:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4402|2024-08-02T07:24:04.668Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20blocks%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4402</link>
      <description>The Essential Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in versions up to, and including, 4.2.0 via deserialization of untrusted input in the get_products function. This allows unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. No POP chain is present in the vulnerable plugin. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4402|2024-08-02T07:24:04.668Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 06:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2087|2024-08-02T06:12:20.473Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20blocks%20%E2%80%93%20page%20builder%20gutenberg%20blocks%2C%20patterns%20%26%20templates
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2087</link>
      <description>The Essential Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 4.0.6. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the save function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change plugin settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2087|2024-08-02T06:12:20.473Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 05:33:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2086|2024-08-02T06:12:20.173Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20blocks%20%E2%80%93%20page%20builder%20gutenberg%20blocks%2C%20patterns%20%26%20templates
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2086</link>
      <description>The Essential Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized use of functionality due to a missing capability check on the template_count function in versions up to, and including, 4.0.6. This makes it possible for subscriber-level attackers to obtain plugin template information. While a nonce check is present, it is only executed when a nonce is provided. Not providing a nonce results in the nonce verification to be skipped. There is no capability check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2086|2024-08-02T06:12:20.173Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 05:33:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7071|2024-08-02T08:50:07.847Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20blocks%20%E2%80%93%20page%20builder%20gutenberg%20blocks%2C%20patterns%20%26%20templates
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7071</link>
      <description>The Essential Blocks – Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks, Patterns &amp; Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Table of Contents block in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7071|2024-08-02T08:50:07.847Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:33:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6986|2024-08-02T08:50:07.948Z -- wpdevteam -- embedpress%20%E2%80%93%20embed%20pdf%2C%20youtube%2C%20google%20docs%2C%20vimeo%2C%20wistia%20videos%2C%20audios%2C%20maps%20%26%20any%20documents%20in%20gutenberg%20%26%20elementor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6986</link>
      <description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, YouTube, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's embed_oembed_html shortcode in all versions up to 3.9.5 (exclusive) due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6986|2024-08-02T08:50:07.948Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 06:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4283|2024-08-02T07:24:03.691Z -- wpdevteam -- embedpress%20%E2%80%93%20embed%20pdf%2C%20youtube%2C%20google%20docs%2C%20vimeo%2C%20wistia%20videos%2C%20audios%2C%20maps%20%26%20any%20documents%20in%20gutenberg%20%26%20elementor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4283</link>
      <description>The EmbedPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'embedpress_calendar' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 3.8.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4283|2024-08-02T07:24:03.691Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 11:05:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2084|2024-08-02T06:12:19.951Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20blocks%20%E2%80%93%20page%20builder%20gutenberg%20blocks%2C%20patterns%20%26%20templates
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2084</link>
      <description>The Essential Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized use of functionality due to a missing capability check on the get function in versions up to, and including, 4.0.6. This makes it possible for subscriber-level attackers to obtain plugin settings. While a nonce check is present, it is only executed when a nonce is provided. Not providing a nonce results in the nonce verification to be skipped. There is no capability check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2084|2024-08-02T06:12:19.951Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 05:33:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2085|2024-08-02T06:12:20.324Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20blocks%20%E2%80%93%20page%20builder%20gutenberg%20blocks%2C%20patterns%20%26%20templates
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2085</link>
      <description>The Essential Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized use of functionality due to a missing capability check on the templates function in versions up to, and including, 4.0.6. This makes it possible for subscriber-level attackers to obtain plugin template information. While a nonce check is present, it is only executed when a nonce is provided. Not providing a nonce results in the nonce verification to be skipped. There is no capability check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2085|2024-08-02T06:12:20.324Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 05:33:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2833|2024-08-02T06:33:05.515Z -- wpdevteam -- reviewx%20%E2%80%93%20multi-criteria%20rating%20%26%20reviews%20for%20woocommerce
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2833</link>
      <description>The ReviewX plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in versions up to, and including, 1.6.13 due to insufficient restriction on the 'rx_set_screen_options' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with minimal permissions such as a subscriber, to modify their user role by supplying the 'wp_screen_options[option]' and 'wp_screen_options[value]' parameters during a screen option update.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2833|2024-08-02T06:33:05.515Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 09:33:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5571|2024-08-01T21:18:06.783Z -- wpdevteam -- embedpress%20%E2%80%93%20embed%20pdf%2C%20google%20docs%2C%20vimeo%2C%20wistia%2C%20embed%20youtube%20videos%2C%20audios%2C%20maps%20%26%20embed%20any%20documents%20in%20gutenberg%20%26%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5571</link>
      <description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia, Embed YouTube Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Embed Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'url' attribute within the plugin's EmbedPress PDF widget in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5571|2024-08-01T21:18:06.783Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 08:33:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6557|2024-08-01T21:41:03.524Z -- wpdevteam -- schedulepress%20%E2%80%93%20auto%20post%20%26%20publish%2C%20auto%20social%20share%2C%20schedule%20posts%20with%20editorial%20calendar%20%26%20missed%20schedule%20post%20publisher</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6557</link>
      <description>The SchedulePress – Auto Post &amp; Publish, Auto Social Share, Schedule Posts with Editorial Calendar &amp; Missed Schedule Post Publisher plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.3. This is due the plugin utilizing the wpdeveloper library and leaving the demo files in place with display_errors on. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6557|2024-08-01T21:41:03.524Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 04:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5189|2024-08-01T21:03:10.977Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5189</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘custom_js’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.23 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5189|2024-08-01T21:03:10.977Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 13:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5073|2024-08-01T21:03:10.538Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5073</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Twitter Feed component in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.21 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5073|2024-08-01T21:03:10.538Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 06:48:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5188|2024-08-01T21:03:11.069Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5188</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'get_manual_calendar_events' function in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.22 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5188|2024-08-01T21:03:11.069Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 11:03:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2650|2024-08-01T19:18:48.063Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2650</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the alignment parameter in the Woo Product Carousel widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2650|2024-08-01T19:18:48.063Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:58:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3018|2024-08-01T19:32:42.518Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3018</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.13 via deserialization of untrusted input from the 'error_resetpassword' attribute of the "Login | Register Form" widget (disabled by default). This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3018|2024-08-01T19:32:42.518Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 11:17:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2128|2024-08-01T19:03:38.917Z -- wpdevteam -- embedpress%20%E2%80%93%20embed%20pdf%2C%20google%20docs%2C%20vimeo%2C%20wistia%2C%20embed%20youtube%20videos%2C%20audios%2C%20maps%20%26%20embed%20any%20documents%20in%20gutenberg%20%26%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2128</link>
      <description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia, Embed YouTube Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Embed Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's embed widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2128|2024-08-01T19:03:38.917Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 19:32:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2688|2024-08-01T19:18:48.169Z -- wpdevteam -- embedpress%20%E2%80%93%20embed%20pdf%2C%20google%20docs%2C%20vimeo%2C%20wistia%2C%20embed%20youtube%20videos%2C%20audios%2C%20maps%20%26%20embed%20any%20documents%20in%20gutenberg%20%26%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2688</link>
      <description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia, Embed YouTube Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Embed Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the EmbedPress document widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2688|2024-08-01T19:18:48.169Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 02:32:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2623|2024-08-01T19:18:47.963Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2623</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the countdown widget's message parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.11 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2623|2024-08-01T19:18:47.963Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:59:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2255|2024-08-01T19:03:39.286Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20blocks%20%E2%80%93%20page%20builder%20gutenberg%20blocks%2C%20patterns%20%26%20templates</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2255</link>
      <description>The Essential Blocks – Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks, Patterns &amp; Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's widgets in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes such as listStyle. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2255|2024-08-01T19:03:39.286Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 03:20:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2845|2024-08-01T19:25:42.134Z -- wpdevteam -- betterdocs%20%E2%80%93%20best%20documentation%2C%20faq%20%26%20knowledge%20base%20plugin%20with%20ai%20support%20%26%20instant%20answer%20for%20elementor%20%26%20gutenberg</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2845</link>
      <description>The BetterDocs – Best Documentation, FAQ &amp; Knowledge Base Plugin with AI Support &amp; Instant Answer For Elementor &amp; Gutenberg plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2845|2024-08-01T19:25:42.134Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:58:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2468|2024-08-01T19:11:53.521Z -- wpdevteam -- embedpress%20%E2%80%93%20embed%20pdf%2C%20google%20docs%2C%20vimeo%2C%20wistia%2C%20embed%20youtube%20videos%2C%20audios%2C%20maps%20%26%20embed%20any%20documents%20in%20gutenberg%20%26%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2468</link>
      <description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia, Embed YouTube Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Embed Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the EmbedPress widget 'embedpress_pro_twitch_theme ' attribute in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2468|2024-08-01T19:11:53.521Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 02:32:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2974|2024-08-01T19:32:42.482Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2974</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in versions up to, and including, 5.9.13 via the load_more function. This can allow unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including private and draft posts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2974|2024-08-01T19:32:42.482Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5073|2024-07-29T18:39:51.487Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5073</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Twitter Feed component in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.21 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5073|2024-07-29T18:39:51.487Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 06:48:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5188|2024-07-23T16:21:51.417Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5188</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'get_manual_calendar_events' function in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.22 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5188|2024-07-23T16:21:51.417Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 11:03:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6557|2024-07-16T14:01:53.973Z -- wpdevteam -- schedulepress%20%E2%80%93%20auto%20post%20%26%20publish%2C%20auto%20social%20share%2C%20schedule%20posts%20with%20editorial%20calendar%20%26%20missed%20schedule%20post%20publisher</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6557</link>
      <description>The SchedulePress – Auto Post &amp; Publish, Auto Social Share, Schedule Posts with Editorial Calendar &amp; Missed Schedule Post Publisher plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.3. This is due the plugin utilizing the wpdeveloper library and leaving the demo files in place with display_errors on. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6557|2024-07-16T14:01:53.973Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 04:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3333|2024-07-12T18:13:30.628Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3333</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the URL attributes of widgets in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3333|2024-07-12T18:13:30.628Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 11:34:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0585|2024-07-05T17:21:33.383Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0585</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Filterable Gallery widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the Image URL. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0585|2024-07-05T17:21:33.383Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:21:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0586|2024-06-27T21:00:51.076Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0586</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Login/Register Element in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the custom login URL. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0586|2024-06-27T21:00:51.076Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3245|2024-06-19T19:32:45.393Z -- wpdevteam -- embedpress%20%E2%80%93%20embed%20pdf%2C%20google%20docs%2C%20vimeo%2C%20wistia%2C%20embed%20youtube%20videos%2C%20audios%2C%20maps%20%26%20embed%20any%20documents%20in%20gutenberg%20%26%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3245</link>
      <description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia, Embed YouTube Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Embed Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Youtube block in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3245|2024-06-19T19:32:45.393Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 02:32:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1565|2024-06-13T08:31:31.631Z -- wpdevteam -- embedpress%20%E2%80%93%20embed%20pdf%2C%20google%20docs%2C%20vimeo%2C%20wistia%2C%20embed%20youtube%20videos%2C%20audios%2C%20maps%20%26%20embed%20any%20documents%20in%20gutenberg%20%26%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1565</link>
      <description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, YouTube, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the PDF Widget URL in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1565|2024-06-13T08:31:31.631Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 08:31:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5073|2024-05-30T06:48:08.882Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5073</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Twitter Feed component in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.21 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5073|2024-05-30T06:48:08.882Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 06:48:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5571|2024-06-05T08:33:15.749Z -- wpdevteam -- embedpress%20%E2%80%93%20embed%20pdf%2C%20google%20docs%2C%20vimeo%2C%20wistia%2C%20embed%20youtube%20videos%2C%20audios%2C%20maps%20%26%20embed%20any%20documents%20in%20gutenberg%20%26%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5571</link>
      <description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia, Embed YouTube Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Embed Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'url' attribute within the plugin's EmbedPress PDF widget in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5571|2024-06-05T08:33:15.749Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 08:33:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5188|2024-06-06T11:03:03.438Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5188</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'get_manual_calendar_events' function in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.22 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5188|2024-06-06T11:03:03.438Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 11:03:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5189|2024-06-11T17:25:03.761Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5189</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘custom_js’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.23 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5189|2024-06-11T17:25:03.761Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 13:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1537|2024-03-13T15:26:59.753Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1537</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Data Table widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1537|2024-03-13T15:26:59.753Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:26:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1425|2024-06-04T18:01:25.156Z -- wpdevteam -- embedpress%20%E2%80%93%20embed%20pdf%2C%20google%20docs%2C%20vimeo%2C%20wistia%2C%20embed%20youtube%20videos%2C%20audios%2C%20maps%20%26%20embed%20any%20documents%20in%20gutenberg%20%26%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1425</link>
      <description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, YouTube, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Google Calendar Widget Link in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1425|2024-06-04T18:01:25.156Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1171|2024-06-04T18:01:23.018Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1171</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Filterable Gallery Widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1171|2024-06-04T18:01:23.018Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:56:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1536|2024-06-04T18:01:13.429Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1536</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's event calendar widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1536|2024-06-04T18:01:13.429Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:26:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1803|2024-06-04T18:00:50.729Z -- wpdevteam -- embedpress%20%E2%80%93%20embed%20pdf%2C%20google%20docs%2C%20vimeo%2C%20wistia%2C%20embed%20youtube%20videos%2C%20audios%2C%20maps%20%26%20embed%20any%20documents%20in%20gutenberg%20%26%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1803</link>
      <description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia, Embed YouTube Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Embed Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of functionality due to insufficient authorization validation on the PDF embed block in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.12. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to embed PDF blocks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1803|2024-06-04T18:00:50.729Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 12:43:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1854|2024-06-04T18:00:48.304Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20blocks%20%E2%80%93%20page%20builder%20gutenberg%20blocks%2C%20patterns%20%26%20templates</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1854</link>
      <description>The Essential Blocks – Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks, Patterns &amp; Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the blockId parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1854|2024-06-04T18:00:48.304Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:27:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1802|2024-06-04T18:00:39.649Z -- wpdevteam -- embedpress%20%E2%80%93%20embed%20pdf%2C%20google%20docs%2C%20vimeo%2C%20wistia%2C%20embed%20youtube%20videos%2C%20audios%2C%20maps%20%26%20embed%20any%20documents%20in%20gutenberg%20%26%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1802</link>
      <description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia, Embed YouTube Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Embed Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Wistia embed block in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the user supplied url. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1802|2024-06-04T18:00:39.649Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 20:33:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1698|2024-02-27T05:33:12.316Z -- wpdevteam -- notificationx%20%E2%80%93%20best%20fomo%2C%20social%20proof%2C%20woocommerce%20sales%20popup%20%26%20notification%20bar%20plugin%20with%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1698</link>
      <description>The NotificationX – Best FOMO, Social Proof, WooCommerce Sales Popup &amp; Notification Bar Plugin With Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'type' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1698|2024-02-27T05:33:12.316Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 05:33:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1276|2024-06-04T17:59:43.562Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1276</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Content Ticker arrow attribute in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1276|2024-06-04T17:59:43.562Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1349|2024-06-04T17:59:36.123Z -- wpdevteam -- embedpress%20%E2%80%93%20embed%20pdf%2C%20google%20docs%2C%20vimeo%2C%20wistia%2C%20embed%20youtube%20videos%2C%20audios%2C%20maps%20%26%20embed%20any%20documents%20in%20gutenberg%20%26%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1349</link>
      <description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, YouTube, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1349|2024-06-04T17:59:36.123Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:56:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1172|2024-06-04T17:59:34.464Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1172</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Accordion widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1172|2024-06-04T17:59:34.464Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:56:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1236|2024-06-04T17:59:32.856Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1236</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Filterable Controls label icon parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1236|2024-06-04T17:59:32.856Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0585|2024-02-05T21:21:41.130Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0585</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Filterable Gallery widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the Image URL. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0585|2024-02-05T21:21:41.130Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:21:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0586|2024-02-05T21:22:00.819Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0586</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Login/Register Element in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the custom login URL. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0586|2024-02-05T21:22:00.819Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0954|2024-02-05T21:21:52.530Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0954</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting through editing context via the 'data-eael-wrapper-link' wrapper in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied protocols. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0954|2024-02-05T21:21:52.530Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:21:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4316|2024-06-04T17:54:34.411Z -- wpdevteam -- embedpress%20%E2%80%93%20embed%20pdf%2C%20google%20docs%2C%20vimeo%2C%20wistia%2C%20embed%20youtube%20videos%2C%20audios%2C%20maps%20%26%20embed%20any%20documents%20in%20gutenberg%20%26%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4316</link>
      <description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia, Embed YouTube Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Embed Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.16 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4316|2024-06-04T17:54:34.411Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 20:03:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4156|2024-06-04T17:54:23.960Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4156</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘eael_event_text_color’ parameter in versions up to, and including, 5.9.17 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4156|2024-06-04T17:54:23.960Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:51:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4003|2024-05-02T16:51:51.058Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4003</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the eael_team_members_image_rounded parameter in the Team Members widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.15 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4003|2024-05-02T16:51:51.058Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:51:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4275|2024-06-04T17:53:31.938Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4275</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Interactive Circle widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.19 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4275|2024-06-04T17:53:31.938Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 07:33:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4449|2024-05-10T07:33:37.890Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4449</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'Fancy Text', 'Filter Gallery', 'Sticky Video', 'Content Ticker', 'Woo Product Gallery', &amp; 'Twitter Feed' widgets in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.19 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4449|2024-05-10T07:33:37.890Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 07:33:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4448|2024-06-04T17:53:26.017Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4448</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'Dual Color Header', 'Event Calendar', &amp; 'Advanced Data Table' widgets in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.19 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4448|2024-06-04T17:53:26.017Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 07:33:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4624|2024-06-04T17:53:24.587Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4624</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugins for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘eael_ext_toc_title_tag’ parameter in versions up to, and including, 5.9.20 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4624|2024-06-04T17:53:24.587Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 11:33:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4891|2024-06-04T17:52:58.930Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20blocks%20%E2%80%93%20page%20builder%20gutenberg%20blocks%2C%20patterns%20%26%20templates</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4891</link>
      <description>The Essential Blocks – Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks, Patterns &amp; Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘tagName’ parameter in versions up to, and including, 4.5.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4891|2024-06-04T17:52:58.930Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 04:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3245|2024-04-06T02:32:04.151Z -- wpdevteam -- embedpress%20%E2%80%93%20embed%20pdf%2C%20google%20docs%2C%20vimeo%2C%20wistia%2C%20embed%20youtube%20videos%2C%20audios%2C%20maps%20%26%20embed%20any%20documents%20in%20gutenberg%20%26%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3245</link>
      <description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia, Embed YouTube Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Embed Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Youtube block in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3245|2024-04-06T02:32:04.151Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 02:32:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3818|2024-06-04T17:33:12.564Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20blocks%20%E2%80%93%20page%20builder%20gutenberg%20blocks%2C%20patterns%20%26%20templates</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3818</link>
      <description>The Essential Blocks – Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks, Patterns &amp; Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's "Social Icons" block in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3818|2024-06-04T17:33:12.564Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 02:34:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3244|2024-06-04T17:32:56.226Z -- wpdevteam -- embedpress%20%E2%80%93%20embed%20pdf%2C%20google%20docs%2C%20vimeo%2C%20wistia%2C%20embed%20youtube%20videos%2C%20audios%2C%20maps%20%26%20embed%20any%20documents%20in%20gutenberg%20%26%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3244</link>
      <description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia, Embed YouTube Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Embed Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 
'embedpress_calendar' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3244|2024-06-04T17:32:56.226Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:58:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3018|2024-06-04T17:32:12.178Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3018</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.13 via deserialization of untrusted input from the 'error_resetpassword' attribute of the "Login | Register Form" widget (disabled by default). This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3018|2024-06-04T17:32:12.178Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 11:17:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3333|2024-04-17T11:34:23.338Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3333</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the URL attributes of widgets in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3333|2024-04-17T11:34:23.338Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 11:34:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3733|2024-04-25T08:29:00.282Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3733</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.15 via the ajax_load_more() , eael_woo_pagination_product_ajax(), and ajax_eael_product_gallery() functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract posts that may be in private or draft status.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3733|2024-04-25T08:29:00.282Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 08:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3728|2024-06-04T17:31:04.149Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3728</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Filterable Gallery &amp; Interactive Circle widgets in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.15 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3728|2024-06-04T17:31:04.149Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:51:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2623|2024-06-04T17:30:41.144Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2623</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the countdown widget's message parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.11 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2623|2024-06-04T17:30:41.144Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:59:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2468|2024-06-04T17:30:19.562Z -- wpdevteam -- embedpress%20%E2%80%93%20embed%20pdf%2C%20google%20docs%2C%20vimeo%2C%20wistia%2C%20embed%20youtube%20videos%2C%20audios%2C%20maps%20%26%20embed%20any%20documents%20in%20gutenberg%20%26%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2468</link>
      <description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia, Embed YouTube Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Embed Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the EmbedPress widget 'embedpress_pro_twitch_theme ' attribute in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2468|2024-06-04T17:30:19.562Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 02:32:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2845|2024-06-04T17:30:09.900Z -- wpdevteam -- betterdocs%20%E2%80%93%20best%20documentation%2C%20faq%20%26%20knowledge%20base%20plugin%20with%20ai%20support%20%26%20instant%20answer%20for%20elementor%20%26%20gutenberg</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2845</link>
      <description>The BetterDocs – Best Documentation, FAQ &amp; Knowledge Base Plugin with AI Support &amp; Instant Answer For Elementor &amp; Gutenberg plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2845|2024-06-04T17:30:09.900Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:58:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2255|2024-03-20T03:20:32.539Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20blocks%20%E2%80%93%20page%20builder%20gutenberg%20blocks%2C%20patterns%20%26%20templates</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2255</link>
      <description>The Essential Blocks – Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks, Patterns &amp; Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's widgets in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes such as listStyle. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2255|2024-03-20T03:20:32.539Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 03:20:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2688|2024-06-04T17:29:55.033Z -- wpdevteam -- embedpress%20%E2%80%93%20embed%20pdf%2C%20google%20docs%2C%20vimeo%2C%20wistia%2C%20embed%20youtube%20videos%2C%20audios%2C%20maps%20%26%20embed%20any%20documents%20in%20gutenberg%20%26%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2688</link>
      <description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia, Embed YouTube Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Embed Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the EmbedPress document widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2688|2024-06-04T17:29:55.033Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 02:32:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2974|2024-06-04T17:29:52.844Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2974</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in versions up to, and including, 5.9.13 via the load_more function. This can allow unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including private and draft posts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2974|2024-06-04T17:29:52.844Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2128|2024-06-04T17:29:46.566Z -- wpdevteam -- embedpress%20%E2%80%93%20embed%20pdf%2C%20google%20docs%2C%20vimeo%2C%20wistia%2C%20embed%20youtube%20videos%2C%20audios%2C%20maps%20%26%20embed%20any%20documents%20in%20gutenberg%20%26%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2128</link>
      <description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia, Embed YouTube Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Embed Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's embed widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2128|2024-06-04T17:29:46.566Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 19:32:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2650|2024-06-04T17:29:43.630Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2650</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the alignment parameter in the Woo Product Carousel widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2650|2024-06-04T17:29:43.630Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:58:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4449|2024-06-12T19:16:34.983Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4449</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'Fancy Text', 'Filter Gallery', 'Sticky Video', 'Content Ticker', 'Woo Product Gallery', &amp; 'Twitter Feed' widgets in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.19 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4449|2024-06-12T19:16:34.983Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 07:33:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1565|2024-06-13T16:51:17.838Z -- wpdevteam -- embedpress%20%E2%80%93%20embed%20pdf%2C%20google%20docs%2C%20vimeo%2C%20wistia%2C%20embed%20youtube%20videos%2C%20audios%2C%20maps%20%26%20embed%20any%20documents%20in%20gutenberg%20%26%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1565</link>
      <description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, YouTube, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the PDF Widget URL in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1565|2024-06-13T16:51:17.838Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 08:31:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1537|2024-06-24T14:52:02.512Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1537</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Data Table widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1537|2024-06-24T14:52:02.512Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:26:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3733|2024-07-02T20:15:14.582Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3733</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.15 via the ajax_load_more() , eael_woo_pagination_product_ajax(), and ajax_eael_product_gallery() functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract posts that may be in private or draft status.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3733|2024-07-02T20:15:14.582Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 08:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4003|2024-07-05T21:12:15.779Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4003</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the eael_team_members_image_rounded parameter in the Team Members widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.15 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4003|2024-07-05T21:12:15.779Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:51:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6557|2024-07-16T04:31:29.223Z -- wpdevteam -- schedulepress%20%E2%80%93%20auto%20post%20%26%20publish%2C%20auto%20social%20share%2C%20schedule%20posts%20with%20editorial%20calendar%20%26%20missed%20schedule%20post%20publisher</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6557</link>
      <description>The SchedulePress – Auto Post &amp; Publish, Auto Social Share, Schedule Posts with Editorial Calendar &amp; Missed Schedule Post Publisher plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.3. This is due the plugin utilizing the wpdeveloper library and leaving the demo files in place with display_errors on. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6557|2024-07-16T04:31:29.223Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 04:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5571|2024-07-17T13:08:39.922Z -- wpdevteam -- embedpress%20%E2%80%93%20embed%20pdf%2C%20google%20docs%2C%20vimeo%2C%20wistia%2C%20embed%20youtube%20videos%2C%20audios%2C%20maps%20%26%20embed%20any%20documents%20in%20gutenberg%20%26%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5571</link>
      <description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia, Embed YouTube Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Embed Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'url' attribute within the plugin's EmbedPress PDF widget in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5571|2024-07-17T13:08:39.922Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 08:33:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0954|2024-07-24T16:10:49.539Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0954</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting through editing context via the 'data-eael-wrapper-link' wrapper in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied protocols. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0954|2024-07-24T16:10:49.539Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:21:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1698|2024-08-01T18:48:21.529Z -- wpdevteam -- notificationx%20%E2%80%93%20best%20fomo%2C%20social%20proof%2C%20woocommerce%20sales%20popup%20%26%20notification%20bar%20plugin%20with%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1698</link>
      <description>The NotificationX – Best FOMO, Social Proof, WooCommerce Sales Popup &amp; Notification Bar Plugin With Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'type' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1698|2024-08-01T18:48:21.529Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 05:33:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0586|2024-08-01T18:11:35.646Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0586</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Login/Register Element in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the custom login URL. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0586|2024-08-01T18:11:35.646Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1276|2024-08-01T18:33:25.368Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1276</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Content Ticker arrow attribute in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1276|2024-08-01T18:33:25.368Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1803|2024-08-01T18:48:22.041Z -- wpdevteam -- embedpress%20%E2%80%93%20embed%20pdf%2C%20google%20docs%2C%20vimeo%2C%20wistia%2C%20embed%20youtube%20videos%2C%20audios%2C%20maps%20%26%20embed%20any%20documents%20in%20gutenberg%20%26%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1803</link>
      <description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia, Embed YouTube Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Embed Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of functionality due to insufficient authorization validation on the PDF embed block in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.12. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to embed PDF blocks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1803|2024-08-01T18:48:22.041Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 12:43:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1349|2024-08-01T18:33:25.580Z -- wpdevteam -- embedpress%20%E2%80%93%20embed%20pdf%2C%20google%20docs%2C%20vimeo%2C%20wistia%2C%20embed%20youtube%20videos%2C%20audios%2C%20maps%20%26%20embed%20any%20documents%20in%20gutenberg%20%26%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1349</link>
      <description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, YouTube, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1349|2024-08-01T18:33:25.580Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:56:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1171|2024-08-01T18:33:24.711Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1171</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Filterable Gallery Widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1171|2024-08-01T18:33:24.711Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:56:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1236|2024-08-01T18:33:25.255Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1236</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Filterable Controls label icon parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1236|2024-08-01T18:33:25.255Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1425|2024-08-01T18:40:20.741Z -- wpdevteam -- embedpress%20%E2%80%93%20embed%20pdf%2C%20google%20docs%2C%20vimeo%2C%20wistia%2C%20embed%20youtube%20videos%2C%20audios%2C%20maps%20%26%20embed%20any%20documents%20in%20gutenberg%20%26%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1425</link>
      <description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, YouTube, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Google Calendar Widget Link in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1425|2024-08-01T18:40:20.741Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1854|2024-08-01T18:56:22.304Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20blocks%20%E2%80%93%20page%20builder%20gutenberg%20blocks%2C%20patterns%20%26%20templates</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1854</link>
      <description>The Essential Blocks – Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks, Patterns &amp; Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the blockId parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1854|2024-08-01T18:56:22.304Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:27:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0954|2024-08-01T18:26:30.279Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0954</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting through editing context via the 'data-eael-wrapper-link' wrapper in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied protocols. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0954|2024-08-01T18:26:30.279Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:21:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1802|2024-08-01T18:48:21.992Z -- wpdevteam -- embedpress%20%E2%80%93%20embed%20pdf%2C%20google%20docs%2C%20vimeo%2C%20wistia%2C%20embed%20youtube%20videos%2C%20audios%2C%20maps%20%26%20embed%20any%20documents%20in%20gutenberg%20%26%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1802</link>
      <description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia, Embed YouTube Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Embed Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Wistia embed block in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the user supplied url. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1802|2024-08-01T18:48:21.992Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 20:33:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1565|2024-08-01T18:40:21.532Z -- wpdevteam -- embedpress%20%E2%80%93%20embed%20pdf%2C%20google%20docs%2C%20vimeo%2C%20wistia%2C%20embed%20youtube%20videos%2C%20audios%2C%20maps%20%26%20embed%20any%20documents%20in%20gutenberg%20%26%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1565</link>
      <description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, YouTube, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the PDF Widget URL in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1565|2024-08-01T18:40:21.532Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 08:31:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1536|2024-08-01T18:40:21.339Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1536</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's event calendar widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1536|2024-08-01T18:40:21.339Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:26:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1172|2024-08-01T18:33:24.169Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1172</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Accordion widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1172|2024-08-01T18:33:24.169Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:56:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0585|2024-08-01T18:11:35.629Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0585</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Filterable Gallery widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the Image URL. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0585|2024-08-01T18:11:35.629Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:21:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1537|2024-08-01T18:40:21.396Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1537</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Data Table widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1537|2024-08-01T18:40:21.396Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:26:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3733|2024-08-01T20:20:01.126Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3733</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.15 via the ajax_load_more() , eael_woo_pagination_product_ajax(), and ajax_eael_product_gallery() functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract posts that may be in private or draft status.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3733|2024-08-01T20:20:01.126Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 08:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4156|2024-08-01T20:33:52.653Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4156</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘eael_event_text_color’ parameter in versions up to, and including, 5.9.17 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4156|2024-08-01T20:33:52.653Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:51:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4275|2024-08-01T20:33:53.190Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4275</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Interactive Circle widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.19 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4275|2024-08-01T20:33:53.190Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 07:33:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3728|2024-08-01T20:20:01.082Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3728</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Filterable Gallery &amp; Interactive Circle widgets in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.15 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3728|2024-08-01T20:20:01.082Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:51:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4891|2024-08-01T20:55:10.248Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20blocks%20%E2%80%93%20page%20builder%20gutenberg%20blocks%2C%20patterns%20%26%20templates</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4891</link>
      <description>The Essential Blocks – Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks, Patterns &amp; Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘tagName’ parameter in versions up to, and including, 4.5.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4891|2024-08-01T20:55:10.248Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 04:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3244|2024-08-01T20:05:08.314Z -- wpdevteam -- embedpress%20%E2%80%93%20embed%20pdf%2C%20google%20docs%2C%20vimeo%2C%20wistia%2C%20embed%20youtube%20videos%2C%20audios%2C%20maps%20%26%20embed%20any%20documents%20in%20gutenberg%20%26%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3244</link>
      <description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia, Embed YouTube Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Embed Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 
'embedpress_calendar' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3244|2024-08-01T20:05:08.314Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:58:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3245|2024-08-01T20:05:08.315Z -- wpdevteam -- embedpress%20%E2%80%93%20embed%20pdf%2C%20google%20docs%2C%20vimeo%2C%20wistia%2C%20embed%20youtube%20videos%2C%20audios%2C%20maps%20%26%20embed%20any%20documents%20in%20gutenberg%20%26%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3245</link>
      <description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia, Embed YouTube Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Embed Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Youtube block in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3245|2024-08-01T20:05:08.315Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 02:32:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4448|2024-08-01T20:40:47.216Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4448</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'Dual Color Header', 'Event Calendar', &amp; 'Advanced Data Table' widgets in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.19 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4448|2024-08-01T20:40:47.216Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 07:33:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4449|2024-08-01T20:40:47.184Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4449</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'Fancy Text', 'Filter Gallery', 'Sticky Video', 'Content Ticker', 'Woo Product Gallery', &amp; 'Twitter Feed' widgets in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.19 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4449|2024-08-01T20:40:47.184Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 07:33:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4316|2024-08-01T20:40:46.043Z -- wpdevteam -- embedpress%20%E2%80%93%20embed%20pdf%2C%20google%20docs%2C%20vimeo%2C%20wistia%2C%20embed%20youtube%20videos%2C%20audios%2C%20maps%20%26%20embed%20any%20documents%20in%20gutenberg%20%26%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4316</link>
      <description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia, Embed YouTube Videos, Audios, Maps &amp; Embed Any Documents in Gutenberg &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.16 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4316|2024-08-01T20:40:46.043Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 20:03:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4003|2024-08-01T20:26:57.273Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4003</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the eael_team_members_image_rounded parameter in the Team Members widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.15 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4003|2024-08-01T20:26:57.273Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:51:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3333|2024-08-01T20:05:08.380Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3333</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the URL attributes of widgets in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3333|2024-08-01T20:05:08.380Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 11:34:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4624|2024-08-01T20:47:41.209Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4624</link>
      <description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugins for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘eael_ext_toc_title_tag’ parameter in versions up to, and including, 5.9.20 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4624|2024-08-01T20:47:41.209Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 11:33:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3818|2024-08-01T20:20:02.056Z -- wpdevteam -- essential%20blocks%20%E2%80%93%20page%20builder%20gutenberg%20blocks%2C%20patterns%20%26%20templates</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3818</link>
      <description>The Essential Blocks – Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks, Patterns &amp; Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's "Social Icons" block in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3818|2024-08-01T20:20:02.056Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 02:34:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
