<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for wpdevteam -- Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/wpdevteam/essential%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%E2%80%93%20best%20elementor%20templates%2C%20widgets%2C%20kits%20%26%20woocommerce%20builders.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for wpdevteam -- Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 09:22:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-5073|2024-05-30T06:48:08.882Z -- wpdevteam -- Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5073</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Twitter Feed component in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.21 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5073|2024-05-30T06:48:08.882Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 06:48:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2650|2024-04-09T18:58:56.390Z -- wpdevteam -- Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2650</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the alignment parameter in the Woo Product Carousel widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2650|2024-04-09T18:58:56.390Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:58:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2974|2024-04-09T18:59:00.562Z -- wpdevteam -- Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2974</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in versions up to, and including, 5.9.13 via the load_more function. This can allow unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including private and draft posts.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2974|2024-04-09T18:59:00.562Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:59:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2623|2024-04-09T18:59:17.215Z -- wpdevteam -- Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2623</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the countdown widget's message parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.11 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2623|2024-04-09T18:59:17.215Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3728|2024-05-02T16:51:53.633Z -- wpdevteam -- Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3728</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Filterable Gallery &amp; Interactive Circle widgets in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.15 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3728|2024-05-02T16:51:53.633Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:51:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3733|2024-04-25T08:29:00.282Z -- wpdevteam -- Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3733</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.15 via the ajax_load_more() , eael_woo_pagination_product_ajax(), and ajax_eael_product_gallery() functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract posts that may be in private or draft status.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3733|2024-04-25T08:29:00.282Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 08:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3333|2024-04-17T11:34:23.338Z -- wpdevteam -- Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3333</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the URL attributes of widgets in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3333|2024-04-17T11:34:23.338Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 11:34:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3018|2024-03-30T11:17:25.675Z -- wpdevteam -- Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3018</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.13 via deserialization of untrusted input from the 'error_resetpassword' attribute of the "Login | Register Form" widget (disabled by default). This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3018|2024-03-30T11:17:25.675Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 11:17:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4624|2024-05-14T11:33:10.571Z -- wpdevteam -- Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4624</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugins for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘eael_ext_toc_title_tag’ parameter in versions up to, and including, 5.9.20 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4624|2024-05-14T11:33:10.571Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 11:33:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4448|2024-05-10T07:33:37.184Z -- wpdevteam -- Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4448</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'Dual Color Header', 'Event Calendar', &amp; 'Advanced Data Table' widgets in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.19 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4448|2024-05-10T07:33:37.184Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 07:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4449|2024-05-10T07:33:37.890Z -- wpdevteam -- Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4449</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'Fancy Text', 'Filter Gallery', 'Sticky Video', 'Content Ticker', 'Woo Product Gallery', &amp; 'Twitter Feed' widgets in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.19 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4449|2024-05-10T07:33:37.890Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 07:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4275|2024-05-10T07:33:38.841Z -- wpdevteam -- Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4275</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Interactive Circle widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.19 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4275|2024-05-10T07:33:38.841Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 07:33:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4003|2024-05-02T16:51:51.058Z -- wpdevteam -- Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4003</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the eael_team_members_image_rounded parameter in the Team Members widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.15 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4003|2024-05-02T16:51:51.058Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:51:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4156|2024-05-02T16:51:52.490Z -- wpdevteam -- Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4156</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘eael_event_text_color’ parameter in versions up to, and including, 5.9.17 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4156|2024-05-02T16:51:52.490Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:51:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0954|2024-02-05T21:21:52.530Z -- wpdevteam -- Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0954</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting through editing context via the 'data-eael-wrapper-link' wrapper in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied protocols. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0954|2024-02-05T21:21:52.530Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:21:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0586|2024-02-05T21:22:00.819Z -- wpdevteam -- Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0586</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Login/Register Element in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the custom login URL. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0586|2024-02-05T21:22:00.819Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0585|2024-02-05T21:21:41.130Z -- wpdevteam -- Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0585</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Filterable Gallery widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the Image URL. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0585|2024-02-05T21:21:41.130Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:21:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1236|2024-02-20T18:56:27.656Z -- wpdevteam -- Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1236</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Filterable Controls label icon parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1236|2024-02-20T18:56:27.656Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:56:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1172|2024-02-20T18:56:50.201Z -- wpdevteam -- Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1172</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Accordion widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1172|2024-02-20T18:56:50.201Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1276|2024-02-20T18:56:40.459Z -- wpdevteam -- Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1276</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Content Ticker arrow attribute in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1276|2024-02-20T18:56:40.459Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:56:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1536|2024-03-13T15:26:34.059Z -- wpdevteam -- Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1536</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's event calendar widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1536|2024-03-13T15:26:34.059Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:26:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1171|2024-02-20T18:56:51.143Z -- wpdevteam -- Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1171</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Filterable Gallery Widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1171|2024-02-20T18:56:51.143Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:56:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1537|2024-03-13T15:26:59.753Z -- wpdevteam -- Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1537</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Data Table widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1537|2024-03-13T15:26:59.753Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:26:59 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>