<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Poly -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/poly/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Poly -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 22:22:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4462|2024-08-02T07:31:05.383Z -- poly -- trio%208300
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4462</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Poly Trio 8300, Trio 8500, Trio 8800, Trio C60, CCX 350, CCX 400, CCX 500, CCX 505, CCX 600, CCX 700, EDGE E100, EDGE E220, EDGE E300, EDGE E320, EDGE E350, EDGE E400, EDGE E450, EDGE E500, EDGE E550, VVX 101, VVX 150, VVX 201, VVX 250, VVX 300, VVX 301, VVX 310, VVX 311, VVX 350, VVX 400, VVX 401, VVX 410, VVX 411, VVX 450, VVX 500, VVX 501, VVX 600 and VVX 601. This affects an unknown part of the component Web Configuration Application. The manipulation leads to insufficiently random values. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249255.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Poly Trio 8300, Trio 8500, Trio 8800, Trio C60, CCX 350, CCX 400, CCX 500, CCX 505, CCX 600, CCX 700, EDGE E100, EDGE E220, EDGE E300, EDGE E320, EDGE E350, EDGE E400, EDGE E450, EDGE E500, EDGE E550, VVX 101, VVX 150, VVX 201, VVX 250, VVX 300, VVX 301, VVX 310, VVX 311, VVX 350, VVX 400, VVX 401, VVX 410, VVX 411, VVX 450, VVX 500, VVX 501, VVX 600 and VVX 601 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Komponente Web Configuration Application. Mittels Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine insufficiently random values-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Sie ist schwierig auszunutzen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4462|2024-08-02T07:31:05.383Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 09:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4463|2024-08-02T07:31:05.440Z -- poly -- ccx%20400
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4463</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Poly CCX 400, CCX 600, Trio 8800 and Trio C60. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component HTTP Header Handler. The manipulation of the argument Cookie leads to denial of service. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249256.
In Poly CCX 400, CCX 600, Trio 8800 and Trio C60 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Komponente HTTP Header Handler. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments Cookie mit unbekannten Daten kann eine denial of service-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4463|2024-08-02T07:31:05.440Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 09:37:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4464|2024-08-02T07:31:05.501Z -- poly -- trio%208300
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4464</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Poly Trio 8300, Trio 8500, Trio 8800, Trio C60, CCX 350, CCX 400, CCX 500, CCX 505, CCX 600, CCX 700, EDGE E100, EDGE E220, EDGE E300, EDGE E320, EDGE E350, EDGE E400, EDGE E450, EDGE E500, EDGE E550, VVX 101, VVX 150, VVX 201, VVX 250, VVX 300, VVX 301, VVX 310, VVX 311, VVX 350, VVX 400, VVX 401, VVX 410, VVX 411, VVX 450, VVX 500, VVX 501, VVX 600 and VVX 601. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Diagnostic Telnet Mode. The manipulation leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-249257 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Poly Trio 8300, Trio 8500, Trio 8800, Trio C60, CCX 350, CCX 400, CCX 500, CCX 505, CCX 600, CCX 700, EDGE E100, EDGE E220, EDGE E300, EDGE E320, EDGE E350, EDGE E400, EDGE E450, EDGE E500, EDGE E550, VVX 101, VVX 150, VVX 201, VVX 250, VVX 300, VVX 301, VVX 310, VVX 311, VVX 350, VVX 400, VVX 401, VVX 410, VVX 411, VVX 450, VVX 500, VVX 501, VVX 600 and VVX 601 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Komponente Diagnostic Telnet Mode. Durch Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4464|2024-08-02T07:31:05.501Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 09:37:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4465|2024-08-02T07:31:05.490Z -- poly -- trio%208300
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4465</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Poly Trio 8300, Trio 8500, Trio 8800, Trio C60, CCX 350, CCX 400, CCX 500, CCX 505, CCX 600, CCX 700, EDGE E100, EDGE E220, EDGE E300, EDGE E320, EDGE E350, EDGE E400, EDGE E450, EDGE E500, EDGE E550, VVX 101, VVX 150, VVX 201, VVX 250, VVX 300, VVX 301, VVX 310, VVX 311, VVX 350, VVX 400, VVX 401, VVX 410, VVX 411, VVX 450, VVX 500, VVX 501, VVX 600 and VVX 601. Affected is an unknown function of the component Configuration File Import. The manipulation of the argument device.auth.localAdminPassword leads to unverified password change. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249258 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Poly Trio 8300, Trio 8500, Trio 8800, Trio C60, CCX 350, CCX 400, CCX 500, CCX 505, CCX 600, CCX 700, EDGE E100, EDGE E220, EDGE E300, EDGE E320, EDGE E350, EDGE E400, EDGE E450, EDGE E500, EDGE E550, VVX 101, VVX 150, VVX 201, VVX 250, VVX 300, VVX 301, VVX 310, VVX 311, VVX 350, VVX 400, VVX 401, VVX 410, VVX 411, VVX 450, VVX 500, VVX 501, VVX 600 and VVX 601 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Komponente Configuration File Import. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments device.auth.localAdminPassword mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unverified password change-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4465|2024-08-02T07:31:05.490Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 09:37:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4466|2024-08-02T07:31:05.363Z -- poly -- ccx%20400
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4466</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Poly CCX 400, CCX 600, Trio 8800 and Trio C60 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Web Interface. The manipulation leads to protection mechanism failure. The attack can be launched remotely. The vendor explains that they do not regard this as a vulnerability as this is a feature that they offer to their customers who have a variety of environmental needs that are met through different firmware builds. To avoid potential roll-back attacks, they remove vulnerable builds from the public servers as a remediation effort. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249259.
In Poly CCX 400, CCX 600, Trio 8800 and Trio C60 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Komponente Web Interface. Durch Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine protection mechanism failure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4466|2024-08-02T07:31:05.363Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 09:38:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4468|2024-08-02T07:31:05.502Z -- poly -- trio%208500
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4468</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Poly Trio 8500, Trio 8800 and Trio C60. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the component Poly Lens Management Cloud Registration. The manipulation leads to missing authorization. It is possible to launch the attack on the physical device. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249261 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Poly Trio 8500, Trio 8800 and Trio C60 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Komponente Poly Lens Management Cloud Registration. Dank Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine missing authorization-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Ein Angriff setzt physischen Zugriff auf dem Zielobjekt voraus. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4468|2024-08-02T07:31:05.502Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 09:38:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4467|2024-08-02T07:31:05.430Z -- poly -- trio%208800
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4467</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Poly Trio 8800 7.2.6.0019 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Test Automation Mode. The manipulation leads to backdoor. It is possible to launch the attack on the physical device. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249260.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Poly Trio 8800 7.2.6.0019 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Komponente Test Automation Mode. Dank der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine backdoor-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Ein Angriff setzt physischen Zugriff auf dem Zielobjekt voraus. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4467|2024-08-02T07:31:05.430Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 09:38:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6147|2024-06-26T19:40:03.741Z -- poly -- plantronics%20hub</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6147</link>
      <description>Poly Plantronics Hub Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Poly Plantronics Hub. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Spokes Update Service. By creating a symbolic link, an attacker can abuse the service to delete a file. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-18271.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6147|2024-06-26T19:40:03.741Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 20:11:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6147|2024-06-20T20:11:52.626Z -- poly -- plantronics%20hub</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6147</link>
      <description>Poly Plantronics Hub Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Poly Plantronics Hub. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Spokes Update Service. By creating a symbolic link, an attacker can abuse the service to delete a file. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-18271.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6147|2024-06-20T20:11:52.626Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 20:11:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6147|2024-08-01T21:33:04.947Z -- poly -- plantronics%20hub</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6147</link>
      <description>Poly Plantronics Hub Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Poly Plantronics Hub. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Spokes Update Service. By creating a symbolic link, an attacker can abuse the service to delete a file. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-18271.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6147|2024-08-01T21:33:04.947Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 20:11:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
