<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Poly -- CCX 400</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/poly/ccx%20400.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Poly -- CCX 400</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 11:20:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4466|2024-08-02T07:31:05.363Z -- poly -- ccx%20400
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4466</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Poly CCX 400, CCX 600, Trio 8800 and Trio C60 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Web Interface. The manipulation leads to protection mechanism failure. The attack can be launched remotely. The vendor explains that they do not regard this as a vulnerability as this is a feature that they offer to their customers who have a variety of environmental needs that are met through different firmware builds. To avoid potential roll-back attacks, they remove vulnerable builds from the public servers as a remediation effort. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249259.
In Poly CCX 400, CCX 600, Trio 8800 and Trio C60 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Komponente Web Interface. Durch Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine protection mechanism failure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4466|2024-08-02T07:31:05.363Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 09:38:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4463|2024-08-02T07:31:05.440Z -- poly -- ccx%20400
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4463</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Poly CCX 400, CCX 600, Trio 8800 and Trio C60. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component HTTP Header Handler. The manipulation of the argument Cookie leads to denial of service. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249256.
In Poly CCX 400, CCX 600, Trio 8800 and Trio C60 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Komponente HTTP Header Handler. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments Cookie mit unbekannten Daten kann eine denial of service-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4463|2024-08-02T07:31:05.440Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 09:37:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
