<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for Surya2Developer -- Hostel Management Service</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/surya2developer/hostel%20management%20service.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for Surya2Developer -- Hostel Management Service</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 16:28:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-2483|2024-03-15T07:00:06.663Z -- Surya2Developer -- Hostel Management Service
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2483</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Surya2Developer Hostel Management Service 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /change-password.php of the component Password Change Handler. The manipulation of the argument oldpassword leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-256889 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Surya2Developer Hostel Management Service 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei /change-password.php der Komponente Password Change Handler. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments oldpassword mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross-site request forgery-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2483|2024-03-15T07:00:06.663Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 07:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2482|2024-03-15T06:31:03.854Z -- Surya2Developer -- Hostel Management Service
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2482</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Surya2Developer Hostel Management Service 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /check_availability.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument oldpassword leads to observable response discrepancy. The attack can be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256891.
In Surya2Developer Hostel Management Service 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei /check_availability.php der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments oldpassword mit unbekannten Daten kann eine observable response discrepancy-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Sie gilt als schwierig ausnutzbar. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2482|2024-03-15T06:31:03.854Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 06:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>