<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Ahwxorg -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ahwxorg/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Ahwxorg -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 19:19:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41054|2024-09-30T17:47:34.079Z -- ahwxorg -- librey
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41054</link>
      <description>LibreY is a fork of LibreX, a framework-less and javascript-free privacy respecting meta search engine. LibreY is subject to a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in the `image_proxy.php` file of LibreY before commit 8f9b9803f231e2954e5b49987a532d28fe50a627. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to use the server as a proxy to send HTTP GET requests to arbitrary targets and retrieve information in the internal network or conduct Denial-of-Service (DoS) attacks via the `url` parameter. Remote attackers can use the server as a proxy to send HTTP GET requests and retrieve information in the internal network. Remote attackers can also request the server to download large files or chain requests among multiple instances to reduce the performance of the server or even deny access from legitimate users. This issue has been addressed in https://github.com/Ahwxorg/LibreY/pull/31. LibreY hosters are advised to use the latest commit. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41054|2024-09-30T17:47:34.079Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 17:32:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41055|2024-09-30T17:44:49.389Z -- ahwxorg -- librey
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41055</link>
      <description>LibreY is a fork of LibreX, a framework-less and javascript-free privacy respecting meta search engine. LibreY is subject to a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in the `engines/google/text.php` and `engines/duckduckgo/text.php` files in versions before commit be59098abd119cda70b15bf3faac596dfd39a744. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to request the server to send HTTP GET requests to arbitrary targets and conduct Denial-of-Service (DoS) attacks via the `wikipedia_language` cookie. Remote attackers can request the server to download large files to reduce the performance of the server or even deny access from legitimate users. This issue has been patched in https://github.com/Ahwxorg/LibreY/pull/9. LibreY hosters are advised to use the latest commit. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41055|2024-09-30T17:44:49.389Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 17:32:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
