<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Juniper Networks -- Juniper ATP</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/juniper%20networks/juniper%20atp.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Juniper Networks -- Juniper ATP</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:21:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0021|2024-09-16T20:48:00.968Z -- juniper%20networks -- juniper%20atp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0021</link>
      <description>On Juniper ATP, secret passphrase CLI inputs, such as "set mcm", are logged to /var/log/syslog in clear text, allowing authenticated local user to be able to view these secret information. This issue affects Juniper ATP 5.0 versions prior to 5.0.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0021|2024-09-16T20:48:00.968Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0024|2024-09-16T20:32:19.806Z -- juniper%20networks -- juniper%20atp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0024</link>
      <description>A persistent cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Email Collectors menu of Juniper ATP may allow authenticated user to inject arbitrary script and steal sensitive data and credentials from a web administration session, possibly tricking a follow-on administrative user to perform administrative actions on the device. This issue affects Juniper ATP 5.0 versions prior to 5.0.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0024|2024-09-16T20:32:19.806Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0020|2024-09-16T22:01:48.191Z -- juniper%20networks -- juniper%20atp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0020</link>
      <description>Juniper ATP ships with hard coded credentials in the Web Collector instance which gives an attacker the ability to take full control of any installation of the software. Affected releases are Juniper Networks Juniper ATP: 5.0 versions prior to 5.0.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0020|2024-09-16T22:01:48.191Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0023|2024-09-16T19:00:38.903Z -- juniper%20networks -- juniper%20atp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0023</link>
      <description>A persistent cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Golden VM menu of Juniper ATP may allow authenticated user to inject arbitrary script and steal sensitive data and credentials from a web administration session, possibly tricking a follow-on administrative user to perform administrative actions on the device. This issue affects Juniper ATP 5.0 versions prior to 5.0.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0023|2024-09-16T19:00:38.903Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0030|2024-09-16T17:17:54.376Z -- juniper%20networks -- juniper%20atp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0030</link>
      <description>Juniper ATP uses DES and a hardcoded salt for password hashing, allowing for trivial de-hashing of the password file contents. This issue affects Juniper ATP 5.0 versions prior to 5.0.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0030|2024-09-16T17:17:54.376Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0018|2024-09-16T18:39:46.049Z -- juniper%20networks -- juniper%20atp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0018</link>
      <description>A persistent cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the file upload menu of Juniper ATP may allow an authenticated user to inject arbitrary scripts and steal sensitive data and credentials from a web administration session, possibly tricking a follow-on administrative user to perform administrative actions on the device. This issue affects Juniper ATP 5.0 versions prior to 5.0.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0018|2024-09-16T18:39:46.049Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0026|2024-09-16T16:59:13.791Z -- juniper%20networks -- juniper%20atp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0026</link>
      <description>A persistent cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Zone configuration of Juniper ATP may allow authenticated user to inject arbitrary script and steal sensitive data and credentials from a web administration session, possibly tricking a follow-on administrative user to perform administrative actions on the device. This issue affects Juniper ATP 5.0 versions prior to 5.0.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0026|2024-09-16T16:59:13.791Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0004|2024-09-16T16:17:26.216Z -- juniper%20networks -- juniper%20atp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0004</link>
      <description>On Juniper ATP, the API key and the device key are logged in a file readable by authenticated local users. These keys are used for performing critical operations on the WebUI interface. This issue affects Juniper ATP 5.0 versions prior to 5.0.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0004|2024-09-16T16:17:26.216Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0029|2024-09-16T22:03:43.469Z -- juniper%20networks -- juniper%20atp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0029</link>
      <description>Juniper ATP Series Splunk credentials are logged in a file readable by authenticated local users. Using these credentials an attacker can access the Splunk server. This issue affects Juniper ATP 5.0 versions prior to 5.0.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0029|2024-09-16T22:03:43.469Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-0022|2024-09-16T21:03:47.862Z -- juniper%20networks -- juniper%20atp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-0022</link>
      <description>Juniper ATP ships with hard coded credentials in the Cyphort Core instance which gives an attacker the ability to take full control of any installation of the software. Affected releases are Juniper Networks Juniper ATP: 5.0 versions prior to 5.0.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-0022|2024-09-16T21:03:47.862Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
