<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Juniper Networks -- MIST Cloud UI</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/juniper%20networks/mist%20cloud%20ui.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Juniper Networks -- MIST Cloud UI</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 16:23:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1675|2024-08-04T06:46:30.238Z -- juniper%20networks -- mist%20cloud%20ui
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1675</link>
      <description>When Security Assertion Markup Language (SAML) authentication is enabled, Juniper Networks Mist Cloud UI might incorrectly process invalid authentication certificates which could allow a malicious network-based user to access unauthorized data. This issue affects all Juniper Networks Mist Cloud UI versions prior to September 2 2020.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1675|2024-08-04T06:46:30.238Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1676|2024-08-04T06:46:29.685Z -- juniper%20networks -- mist%20cloud%20ui
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1676</link>
      <description>When SAML authentication is enabled, Juniper Networks Mist Cloud UI might incorrectly handle SAML responses, allowing a remote attacker to modify a valid SAML response without invalidating its cryptographic signature to bypass SAML authentication security controls. This issue affects all Juniper Networks Mist Cloud UI versions prior to September 2 2020.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1676|2024-08-04T06:46:29.685Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1677|2024-08-04T06:46:29.708Z -- juniper%20networks -- mist%20cloud%20ui
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1677</link>
      <description>When SAML authentication is enabled, Juniper Networks Mist Cloud UI might incorrectly handle child elements in SAML responses, allowing a remote attacker to modify a valid SAML response without invalidating its cryptographic signature to bypass SAML authentication security controls. This issue affects all Juniper Networks Mist Cloud UI versions prior to September 2 2020.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1677|2024-08-04T06:46:29.708Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
