<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Juniper Networks -- NorthStar Controller Application</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/juniper%20networks/northstar%20controller%20application.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Juniper Networks -- NorthStar Controller Application</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 16:24:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2324|2024-08-05T13:48:05.327Z -- juniper%20networks -- northstar%20controller%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2324</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability in Juniper Networks NorthStar Controller Application prior to version 2.1.0 Service Pack 1 may allow a network-based malicious attacker to cause a denial of service condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2324|2024-08-05T13:48:05.327Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2332|2024-08-05T13:48:05.234Z -- juniper%20networks -- northstar%20controller%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2332</link>
      <description>An insufficient authentication vulnerability in Juniper Networks NorthStar Controller Application prior to version 2.1.0 Service Pack 1 may allow a malicious, network based, unauthenticated attacker to perform privileged actions to gain complete control over the environment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2332|2024-08-05T13:48:05.234Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2316|2024-08-05T13:48:05.421Z -- juniper%20networks -- northstar%20controller%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2316</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow vulnerability in Juniper Networks NorthStar Controller Application prior to version 2.1.0 Service Pack 1 may allow an authenticated malicious user to cause a buffer overflow leading to a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2316|2024-08-05T13:48:05.421Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2319|2024-08-05T13:48:05.244Z -- juniper%20networks -- northstar%20controller%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2319</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Juniper Networks NorthStar Controller Application prior to version 2.1.0 Service Pack 1 may allow a malicious attacker to compromise the systems confidentiality or integrity without authentication, leading to managed systems being compromised or services being denied to authentic end users and systems as a result.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2319|2024-08-05T13:48:05.244Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2321|2024-08-05T13:48:05.312Z -- juniper%20networks -- northstar%20controller%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2321</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Juniper Networks NorthStar Controller Application prior to version 2.1.0 Service Pack 1 may allow an unauthenticated, unprivileged, network-based attacker to cause various system services partial to full denials of services, modification of system states and files, and potential disclosure of sensitive information which may assist the attacker in further attacks on the system through the use of multiple attack vectors, including man-in-the-middle attacks, file injections, and malicious execution of commands causing out of bound memory conditions leading to other attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2321|2024-08-05T13:48:05.312Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2320|2024-08-05T13:48:05.267Z -- juniper%20networks -- northstar%20controller%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2320</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Juniper Networks NorthStar Controller Application prior to version 2.1.0 Service Pack 1 may allow an unauthenticated, unprivileged, network-based attacker to cause various denials of services leading to targeted information disclosure, modification of any component of the NorthStar system, including managed systems, and full denial of services to any systems under management which NorthStar interacts with using read-only or read-write credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2320|2024-08-05T13:48:05.267Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2328|2024-08-05T13:48:05.291Z -- juniper%20networks -- northstar%20controller%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2328</link>
      <description>An information leak vulnerability in Juniper Networks NorthStar Controller Application prior to version 2.1.0 Service Pack 1 may allow an unprivileged, authenticated, user to elevate their permissions through reading unprivileged information stored in the NorthStar controller.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2328|2024-08-05T13:48:05.291Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2318|2024-08-05T13:48:05.277Z -- juniper%20networks -- northstar%20controller%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2318</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Juniper Networks NorthStar Controller Application prior to version 2.1.0 Service Pack 1 may allow an authenticated malicious user to read log files which will compromise the integrity of the system, or provide elevation of privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2318|2024-08-05T13:48:05.277Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2326|2024-08-05T13:48:05.234Z -- juniper%20networks -- northstar%20controller%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2326</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability in Juniper Networks NorthStar Controller Application prior to version 2.1.0 Service Pack 1 may allow an unprivileged, authenticated, network-based attacker to replicate the underlying Junos OS VM and all data it maintains to their local system for future analysis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2326|2024-08-05T13:48:05.234Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2330|2024-08-05T13:48:05.232Z -- juniper%20networks -- northstar%20controller%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2330</link>
      <description>A denial of service vulnerability in Juniper Networks NorthStar Controller Application prior to version 2.1.0 Service Pack 1 may allow an unauthenticated, local user, to create a fork bomb scenario, also known as a rabbit virus, or wabbit, which will create processes that replicate themselves, until all resources are consumed on the system, leading to a denial of service to the entire system until it is restarted. Continued attacks by an unauthenticated, local user, can lead to persistent denials of services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2330|2024-08-05T13:48:05.232Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2331|2024-08-05T13:48:05.306Z -- juniper%20networks -- northstar%20controller%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2331</link>
      <description>A firewall bypass vulnerability in Juniper Networks NorthStar Controller Application prior to version 2.1.0 Service Pack 1 may allow a network-based malicious attacker to bypass firewall policies, leading to authentication bypass methods, information disclosure, modification of system files, and denials of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2331|2024-08-05T13:48:05.306Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2323|2024-08-05T13:48:05.268Z -- juniper%20networks -- northstar%20controller%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2323</link>
      <description>A denial of service vulnerability in Juniper Networks NorthStar Controller Application prior to version 2.1.0 Service Pack 1 may allow a malicious attacker crafting packets destined to the device to cause a persistent denial of service to the path computation server service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2323|2024-08-05T13:48:05.268Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2333|2024-08-05T13:48:05.267Z -- juniper%20networks -- northstar%20controller%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2333</link>
      <description>A persistent denial of service vulnerability in Juniper Networks NorthStar Controller Application prior to version 2.1.0 Service Pack 1 may allow a malicious, network-based, authenticated attacker to consume enough system resources to cause a persistent denial of service by visiting certain specific URLs on the server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2333|2024-08-05T13:48:05.267Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2329|2024-08-05T13:48:05.308Z -- juniper%20networks -- northstar%20controller%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2329</link>
      <description>An insufficient authentication vulnerability in Juniper Networks NorthStar Controller Application prior to version 2.1.0 Service Pack 1 may allow an unprivileged, authenticated, user to execute certain specific unprivileged system files capable of causing widespread denials of system services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2329|2024-08-05T13:48:05.308Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2322|2024-08-05T13:48:05.247Z -- juniper%20networks -- northstar%20controller%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2322</link>
      <description>A denial of service vulnerability in Juniper Networks NorthStar Controller Application prior to version 2.1.0 Service Pack 1, may allow an authenticated user to cause widespread denials of service to system services by consuming TCP and UDP ports which are normally reserved for other system services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2322|2024-08-05T13:48:05.247Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2334|2024-08-05T13:48:05.234Z -- juniper%20networks -- northstar%20controller%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2334</link>
      <description>An information leak vulnerability in Juniper Networks NorthStar Controller Application prior to version 2.1.0 Service Pack 1 may allow a network-based malicious attacker to perform a man-in-the-middle attack, thereby stealing authentic credentials from encrypted paths which are easily decrypted, and subsequently gain complete control of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2334|2024-08-05T13:48:05.234Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2325|2024-08-05T13:48:05.317Z -- juniper%20networks -- northstar%20controller%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2325</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow vulnerability in Juniper Networks NorthStar Controller Application prior to version 2.1.0 Service Pack 1 may allow an authenticated malicious user to cause a buffer overflow leading to a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2325|2024-08-05T13:48:05.317Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2317|2024-08-05T13:48:05.212Z -- juniper%20networks -- northstar%20controller%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2317</link>
      <description>A denial of service vulnerability in Juniper Networks NorthStar Controller Application prior to version 2.1.0 Service Pack 1 may allow an unauthenticated, unprivileged, network-based attacker to cause denials of services to underlying database tables leading to potential information disclosure, modification of system states, and partial to full denial of services relying upon data modified by an attacker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2317|2024-08-05T13:48:05.212Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2327|2024-08-05T13:48:05.271Z -- juniper%20networks -- northstar%20controller%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2327</link>
      <description>A denial of service vulnerability in Juniper Networks NorthStar Controller Application prior to version 2.1.0 Service Pack 1 may allow an authenticated malicious user to consume large amounts of system resources leading to a cascading denial of services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2327|2024-08-05T13:48:05.271Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
