<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for Nozomi Networks -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/nozomi%20networks/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for Nozomi Networks -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 22:21:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2023-32649|2024-05-28T12:10:02.631Z -- Nozomi Networks -- Guardian
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32649</link><description>A Denial of Service (Dos) vulnerability in Nozomi Networks Guardian and CMC, due to improper input validation in certain fields used in the Asset Intelligence functionality of our IDS, allows an unauthenticated attacker to crash the IDS module by sending specially crafted malformed network packets.

During the (limited) time window before the IDS module is automatically restarted, network traffic may not be analyzed.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32649|2024-05-28T12:10:02.631Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 10:06:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-26724|2024-05-28T10:17:39.175Z -- Nozomi Networks -- Guardian
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2021-26724</link><description>OS Command Injection vulnerability when changing date settings or hostname using web GUI of Nozomi Networks Guardian and CMC allows authenticated administrators to perform remote code execution. This issue affects: Nozomi Networks Guardian 20.0.7.3 version 20.0.7.3 and prior versions. Nozomi Networks CMC 20.0.7.3 version 20.0.7.3 and prior versions.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26724|2024-05-28T10:17:39.175Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5938|2024-05-28T12:24:10.797Z -- Nozomi Networks -- Arc
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5938</link><description>Multiple functions use archives without properly validating the filenames therein, rendering the application vulnerable to path traversal via 'zip slip' attacks.



An administrator able to provide tampered archives to be processed by the affected versions of Arc may be able to have arbitrary files extracted to arbitrary filesystem locations. Leveraging this issue, an attacker may be able to overwrite arbitrary files on the target filesystem and cause critical impacts on the system (e.g., arbitrary command execution on the victim’s machine).</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5938|2024-05-28T12:24:10.797Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 16:08:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-23903|2024-05-28T12:42:15.447Z -- Nozomi Networks -- Guardian
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-23903</link><description>An authenticated administrator can upload a SAML configuration file with the wrong format, with the application not checking the correct file format. Every subsequent application request will return an error.

The whole application in rendered unusable until a console intervention.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-23903|2024-05-28T12:42:15.447Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 09:12:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6916|2024-05-28T12:30:45.201Z -- Nozomi Networks -- Guardian
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6916</link><description>Audit records for OpenAPI requests may include sensitive information.



This could lead to unauthorized accesses and privilege escalation.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6916|2024-05-28T12:30:45.201Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 15:50:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29245|2024-05-28T12:12:24.900Z -- Nozomi Networks -- Guardian
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-29245</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability in Nozomi Networks Guardian and CMC, due to improper input validation in certain fields used in the Asset Intelligence functionality of our IDS, may allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary SQL statements on the DBMS used by the web application by sending specially crafted malicious network packets.

Malicious users with extensive knowledge on the underlying system may be able to extract arbitrary information from the DBMS in an uncontrolled way, or to alter its structure and data.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29245|2024-05-28T12:12:24.900Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 10:04:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-2567|2024-05-28T12:46:13.371Z -- Nozomi Networks -- Guardian
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-2567</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability in Nozomi Networks Guardian and CMC, due to improper input validation in certain parameters used in the Query functionality, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary SQL queries on the DBMS used by the web application.
Authenticated users can extract arbitrary information from the DBMS in an uncontrolled way.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2567|2024-05-28T12:46:13.371Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 10:03:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24015|2024-05-28T12:39:48.664Z -- Nozomi Networks -- Guardian
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-24015</link><description>A partial DoS vulnerability has been detected in the Reports section, exploitable by a malicious authenticated user forcing a report to be saved with its name set as null.

The reports section will be partially unavailable for all later attempts to use it, with the report list seemingly stuck on loading.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-24015|2024-05-28T12:39:48.664Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 09:05:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4259|2024-05-28T12:07:40.848Z -- Nozomi Networks -- CMC
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2022-4259</link><description>Due to improper input validation in the Alerts controller, a SQL injection vulnerability in Nozomi Networks Guardian and CMC allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary SQL queries on the DBMS used by the web application.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4259|2024-05-28T12:07:40.848Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 10:38:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22378|2024-05-28T12:28:51.336Z -- Nozomi Networks -- Guardian
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-22378</link><description>A blind SQL Injection vulnerability in Nozomi Networks Guardian and CMC, due to improper input validation in the sorting parameter, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary SQL queries on the DBMS used by the web application.

Authenticated users can extract arbitrary information from the DBMS in an uncontrolled way.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22378|2024-05-28T12:28:51.336Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 08:01:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22843|2024-05-28T12:35:11.445Z -- Nozomi Networks -- Guardian
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-22843</link><description>An authenticated attacker with administrative access to the appliance can inject malicious JavaScript code inside the definition of a Threat Intelligence rule, that will later be executed by another legitimate user viewing the details of such a rule.
An attacker may be able to perform unauthorized actions on behalf of legitimate users. JavaScript injection was possible in the content for Yara rules, while limited HTML injection has been proven for packet and STYX rules.
The injected code will be executed in the context of the authenticated victim's session.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22843|2024-05-28T12:35:11.445Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 08:46:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24471|2024-05-28T12:37:58.284Z -- Nozomi Networks -- Guardian
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-24471</link><description>An access control vulnerability was found, due to the restrictions that are applied on actual assertions not being enforced in their debug functionality.

An authenticated user with reduced visibility can obtain unauthorized information via the debug functionality, obtaining data that would normally be not accessible in the Query and Assertions functions.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-24471|2024-05-28T12:37:58.284Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5937|2024-05-28T12:22:30.882Z -- Nozomi Networks -- Arc
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5937</link><description>On Windows systems, the Arc configuration files resulted to be world-readable.



This can lead to information disclosure by local attackers, via exfiltration of sensitive data from configuration files.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5937|2024-05-28T12:22:30.882Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 16:06:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-0550|2024-05-28T10:34:04.028Z -- Nozomi Networks -- Guardian
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2022-0550</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in custom report logo upload in Nozomi Networks Guardian, and CMC allows an authenticated attacker with admin or report manager roles to execute unattended commands on the appliance using web server user privileges. This issue affects: Nozomi Networks Guardian versions prior to 22.0.0. Nozomi Networks CMC versions prior to 22.0.0.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-0550|2024-05-28T10:34:04.028Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 14:15:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-23574|2024-05-28T12:33:17.053Z -- Nozomi Networks -- Guardian
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-23574</link><description>A blind SQL Injection vulnerability in Nozomi Networks Guardian and CMC, due to improper input validation in the alerts_count component, allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary SQL queries on the DBMS used by the web application.

Authenticated users can extract arbitrary information from the DBMS in an uncontrolled way.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-23574|2024-05-28T12:33:17.053Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 08:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-0551|2024-05-28T10:43:03.215Z -- Nozomi Networks -- Guardian
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2022-0551</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in project file upload in Nozomi Networks Guardian and CMC allows an authenticated attacker with admin or import manager roles to execute unattended commands on the appliance using web server user privileges. This issue affects: Nozomi Networks Guardian versions prior to 22.0.0. Nozomi Networks CMC versions prior to 22.0.0.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-0551|2024-05-28T10:43:03.215Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 14:15:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-26725|2024-05-28T10:29:15.480Z -- Nozomi Networks -- Guardian
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2021-26725</link><description>Path Traversal vulnerability when changing timezone using web GUI of Nozomi Networks Guardian, CMC allows an authenticated administrator to read-protected system files. This issue affects: Nozomi Networks Guardian 20.0.7.3 version 20.0.7.3 and prior versions. Nozomi Networks CMC 20.0.7.3 version 20.0.7.3 and prior versions.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26725|2024-05-28T10:29:15.480Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24477|2024-05-28T12:44:23.640Z -- Nozomi Networks -- Guardian
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-24477</link><description>In certain conditions, depending on timing and the usage of the Chrome web browser, Guardian/CMC versions before 22.6.2 do not always completely invalidate the user session upon logout. Thus an authenticated local attacker may gain acces to the original user's session.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-24477|2024-05-28T12:44:23.640Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 07:50:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5253|2024-05-28T12:14:39.438Z -- Nozomi Networks -- Guardian
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5253</link><description>A missing authentication check in the WebSocket channel used for the Check Point IoT integration in Nozomi Networks Guardian and CMC, may allow an unauthenticated attacker to obtain assets data without authentication.



Malicious unauthenticated users with knowledge on the underlying system may be able to extract asset information.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5253|2024-05-28T12:14:39.438Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 10:53:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0218|2024-05-28T12:49:14.822Z -- Nozomi Networks -- Guardian
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0218</link><description>A Denial of Service (Dos) vulnerability in Nozomi Networks Guardian, caused by improper input validation in certain fields used in the Radius parsing functionality of our IDS, allows an unauthenticated attacker sending specially crafted malformed network packets to cause the IDS module to stop updating nodes, links, and assets.



Network traffic may not be analyzed until the IDS module is restarted.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0218|2024-05-28T12:49:14.822Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 15:55:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5936|2024-05-28T12:20:16.824Z -- Nozomi Networks -- Arc
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5936</link><description>On Unix systems (Linux, MacOS), Arc uses a temporary file with unsafe privileges.



By tampering with such file, a malicious local user in the system may be able to trigger arbitrary code execution with root privileges.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5936|2024-05-28T12:20:16.824Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 16:04:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5935|2024-05-28T12:18:17.874Z -- Nozomi Networks -- Arc
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5935</link><description>When configuring Arc (e.g. during the first setup), a local web interface is provided to ease the configuration process. Such web interface lacks authentication and may thus be abused by a local attacker or malware running on the machine itself.



A malicious local user or process, during a window of opportunity when the local web interface is active, may be able to extract sensitive information or change Arc's configuration. This could also lead to arbitrary code execution if a malicious update package is installed.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5935|2024-05-28T12:18:17.874Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 16:02:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0218|2024-04-10T15:55:59.971Z -- Nozomi Networks -- Guardian</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0218</link><description>A Denial of Service (Dos) vulnerability in Nozomi Networks Guardian, caused by improper input validation in certain fields used in the Radius parsing functionality of our IDS, allows an unauthenticated attacker sending specially crafted malformed network packets to cause the IDS module to stop updating nodes, links, and assets.

Network traffic may not be analyzed until the IDS module is restarted.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0218|2024-04-10T15:55:59.971Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 15:55:59 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>