<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for dhis2 -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/dhis2/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for dhis2 -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 23:22:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31139|2024-08-02T14:45:25.703Z -- dhis2 -- dhis2-core
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31139</link>
      <description>DHIS2 Core contains the service layer and Web API for DHIS2, an information system for data capture. Starting in the 2.37 branch and prior to versions 2.37.9.1, 2.38.3.1, and 2.39.1.2, Personal Access Tokens (PATs) generate unrestricted session cookies. This may lead to a bypass of other access restrictions (for example, based on allowed IP addresses or HTTP methods). DHIS2 implementers should upgrade to a supported version of DHIS2: 2.37.9.1, 2.38.3.1, or 2.39.1.2. Implementers can work around this issue by adding extra access control validations on a reverse proxy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31139|2024-08-02T14:45:25.703Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 14:27:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31138|2024-08-02T14:45:26.095Z -- dhis2 -- dhis2-core
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31138</link>
      <description>DHIS2 Core contains the service layer and Web API for DHIS2, an information system for data capture. Starting in the 2.36 branch and prior to versions 2.37.9.1, 2.38.3.1, and 2.39.1.2, using object model traversal in the payload of a PATCH request, authenticated users with write access to an object may be able to modify related objects that they should not have access to. DHIS2 implementers should upgrade to a supported version of DHIS2 to receive a patch: 2.37.9.1, 2.38.3.1, or 2.39.1.2. It is possible to work around this issue by blocking all PATCH requests on a reverse proxy, but this may cause some issues with the functionality of built-in applications using legacy PATCH requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31138|2024-08-02T14:45:26.095Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 14:11:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32060|2024-08-02T15:03:28.731Z -- dhis2 -- dhis2-core
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32060</link>
      <description>DHIS2 Core contains the service layer and Web API for DHIS2, an information system for data capture. Starting in the 2.35 branch and prior to versions 2.36.13, 2.37.8, 2.38.2, and 2.39.0, when the Category Option Combination Sharing settings are configured to control access to specific tracker program events or program stages, the `/trackedEntityInstances` and `/events` API endpoints may include all events regardless of the sharing settings applied to the category option combinations. When this specific configuration is present, users may have access to events which they should not be able to see based on the sharing settings of the category options.  The events will not appear in the user interface for web-based Tracker Capture or Capture applications, but if the Android Capture App is used they will be displayed to the user. Versions 2.36.13, 2.37.8, 2.38.2, and 2.39.0 contain a fix for this issue. No workaround is known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32060|2024-08-02T15:03:28.731Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 14:54:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
