<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for aerospike -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/aerospike/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for aerospike -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 13:23:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-9054|2024-08-06T02:42:09.764Z -- aerospike -- database%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-9054</link>
      <description>An exploitable stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the querying functionality of Aerospike Database Server 3.10.0.3. A specially crafted packet can cause a stack-based buffer overflow in the function as_sindex__simatch_list_by_set_binid resulting in remote code execution. An attacker can simply connect to the port to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-9054|2024-08-06T02:42:09.764Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-9053|2024-08-06T02:42:10.013Z -- aerospike -- database%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-9053</link>
      <description>An exploitable out-of-bounds indexing vulnerability exists within the RW fabric message particle type of Aerospike Database Server 3.10.0.3. A specially crafted packet can cause the server to fetch a function table outside the bounds of an array resulting in remote code execution. An attacker can simply connect to the port to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-9053|2024-08-06T02:42:10.013Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-9050|2024-08-06T02:42:09.930Z -- aerospike -- database%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-9050</link>
      <description>An exploitable out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in the client message-parsing functionality of Aerospike Database Server 3.10.0.3. A specially crafted packet can cause an out-of-bounds read resulting in disclosure of memory within the process, the same vulnerability can also be used to trigger a denial of service. An attacker can simply connect to the port and send the packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-9050|2024-08-06T02:42:09.930Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-9049|2024-08-06T02:42:09.798Z -- aerospike -- database%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-9049</link>
      <description>An exploitable denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the fabric-worker component of Aerospike Database Server 3.10.0.3. A specially crafted packet can cause the server process to dereference a null pointer. An attacker can simply connect to a TCP port in order to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-9049|2024-08-06T02:42:09.798Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-9051|2024-08-06T02:42:09.936Z -- aerospike -- database%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-9051</link>
      <description>An exploitable out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in the batch transaction field parsing functionality of Aerospike Database Server 3.10.0.3. A specially crafted packet can cause an out-of-bounds write resulting in memory corruption which can lead to remote code execution. An attacker can simply connect to the port to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-9051|2024-08-06T02:42:09.936Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
