<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Bosch -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/bosch/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Bosch -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 21:42:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23851|2024-09-16T18:39:12.509Z -- bosch -- cpp%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23851</link>
      <description>A specially crafted TCP/IP packet may cause the camera recovery image web interface to crash. It may also cause a buffer overflow which could enable remote code execution. The recovery image can only be booted with administrative rights or with physical access to the camera and allows the upload of a new firmware in case of a damaged firmware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23851|2024-09-16T18:39:12.509Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 16:03:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11895|2024-09-16T18:03:37.169Z -- bosch -- smart%20home%20controller
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11895</link>
      <description>A potential improper access control vulnerability exists in the JSON-RPC interface of the Bosch Smart Home Controller (SHC) before 9.8.905 that may result in a successful denial of service of the SHC and connected sensors and actuators. In order to exploit the vulnerability, the adversary needs to have successfully paired an app or service, which requires user interaction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11895|2024-09-16T18:03:37.169Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 20:07:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6767|2024-09-16T18:14:14.940Z -- bosch -- divar%20ip%203000
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6767</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability in the Bosch Video Management System (BVMS) FileTransferService allows an authenticated remote attacker to read arbitrary files from the Central Server. This affects Bosch BVMS versions 10.0 &lt;= 10.0.0.1225, 9.0 &lt;= 9.0.0.827, 8.0 &lt;= 8.0.329 and 7.5 and older. This affects Bosch BVMS Viewer versions 10.0 &lt;= 10.0.0.1225, 9.0 &lt;= 9.0.0.827, 8.0 &lt;= 8.0.329 and 7.5 and older. This affects Bosch DIVAR IP 3000, DIVAR IP 7000 and DIVAR IP all-in-one 5000 if a vulnerable BVMS version is installed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6767|2024-09-16T18:14:14.940Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 16:19:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6781|2024-09-16T17:14:05.717Z -- bosch -- smart%20home
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6781</link>
      <description>Improper certificate validation for certain connections in the Bosch Smart Home System App for iOS prior to version 9.17.1 potentially allows to intercept video contents by performing a man-in-the-middle attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6781|2024-09-16T17:14:05.717Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 18:10:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23859|2024-09-16T19:45:43.543Z -- bosch -- bvms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23859</link>
      <description>An unauthenticated attacker is able to send a special HTTP request, that causes a service to crash. In case of a standalone VRM or BVMS with VRM installation this crash also opens the possibility to send further unauthenticated commands to the service. On some products the interface is only local accessible lowering the CVSS base score. For a list of modified CVSS scores, please see the official Bosch Advisory Appendix chapter Modified CVSS Scores for CVE-2021-23859</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23859|2024-09-16T19:45:43.543Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 21:17:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6789|2024-09-16T19:29:59.857Z -- bosch -- monitor%20wall
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6789</link>
      <description>Loading a DLL through an Uncontrolled Search Path Element in the Bosch Monitor Wall installer up to and including version 10.00.0164 potentially allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code on a victim's system. A prerequisite is that the victim is tricked into placing a malicious DLL in the same directory where the installer is started from.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6789|2024-09-16T19:29:59.857Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 15:53:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23861|2024-09-16T17:49:16.784Z -- bosch -- bvms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23861</link>
      <description>By executing a special command, an user with administrative rights can get access to extended debug functionality on the VRM allowing an impact on integrity or availability of the installed software. This issue also affects installations of the DIVAR IP and BVMS with VRM installed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23861|2024-09-16T17:49:16.784Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 21:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11896|2024-09-16T19:24:49.342Z -- bosch -- smart%20home%20controller
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11896</link>
      <description>A potential incorrect privilege assignment vulnerability exists in the 3rd party pairing mechanism of the Bosch Smart Home Controller (SHC) before 9.8.907 that may result in a restricted app obtaining default app permissions. In order to exploit the vulnerability, the adversary needs to have successfully paired an app, which requires user interaction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11896|2024-09-16T19:24:49.342Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 20:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11892|2024-09-16T17:42:58.052Z -- bosch -- smart%20home%20controller
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11892</link>
      <description>A potential improper access control vulnerability exists in the JSON-RPC interface of the Bosch Smart Home Controller (SHC) before 9.8.905 that may result in reading or modification of the SHC's configuration or triggering and restoring backups. In order to exploit the vulnerability, the adversary needs to have successfully paired an app or service, which requires user interaction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11892|2024-09-16T17:42:58.052Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 19:55:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23849|2024-09-16T17:23:27.843Z -- bosch -- cpp%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23849</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based interface allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to trigger actions on an affected system on behalf of another user (CSRF - Cross Site Request Forgery). This requires the victim to be tricked into clicking a malicious link or opening a malicious website while being logged in into the camera.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23849|2024-09-16T17:23:27.843Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 19:23:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23848|2024-09-16T16:27:51.671Z -- bosch -- cpp%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23848</link>
      <description>An error in the URL handler Bosch IP cameras may lead to a reflected cross site scripting (XSS) in the web-based interface. An attacker with knowledge of the camera address can send a crafted link to a user, which will execute javascript code in the context of the user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23848|2024-09-16T16:27:51.671Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 14:18:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6786|2024-09-16T17:38:51.758Z -- bosch -- video%20recording%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6786</link>
      <description>Loading a DLL through an Uncontrolled Search Path Element in the Bosch Video Recording Manager installer up to and including version 3.82.0055 for 3.82, up to and including version 3.81.0064 for 3.81 and 3.71 and older potentially allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code on a victim's system. A prerequisite is that the victim is tricked into placing a malicious DLL in the same directory where the installer is started from.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6786|2024-09-16T17:38:51.758Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 15:51:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23854|2024-09-16T17:32:50.243Z -- bosch -- cpp%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23854</link>
      <description>An error in the handling of a page parameter in Bosch IP cameras may lead to a reflected cross site scripting (XSS) in the web-based interface. This issue only affects versions 7.7x and 7.6x. All other versions are not affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23854|2024-09-16T17:32:50.243Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 14:20:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6787|2024-09-16T16:17:43.323Z -- bosch -- video%20client
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6787</link>
      <description>Loading a DLL through an Uncontrolled Search Path Element in the Bosch Video Client installer up to and including version 1.7.6.079 potentially allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code on a victim's system. A prerequisite is that the victim is tricked into placing a malicious DLL in the same directory where the installer is started from.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6787|2024-09-16T16:17:43.323Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 15:51:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23862|2024-09-16T19:30:25.389Z -- bosch -- bvms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23862</link>
      <description>A crafted configuration packet sent by an authenticated administrative user can be used to execute arbitrary commands in system context. This issue also affects installations of the VRM, DIVAR IP, BVMS with VRM installed, the VIDEOJET decoder (VJD-7513 and VJD-8000).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23862|2024-09-16T19:30:25.389Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 21:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11891|2024-09-16T18:13:51.172Z -- bosch -- smart%20home%20controller
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11891</link>
      <description>A potential incorrect privilege assignment vulnerability exists in the app pairing mechanism of the Bosch Smart Home Controller (SHC) before 9.8.905 that may result in elevated privileges of the adversary's choosing. In order to exploit the vulnerability, the adversary needs physical access to the SHC during the attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11891|2024-09-16T18:13:51.172Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 19:40:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23846|2024-09-16T16:38:12.268Z -- bosch -- b426%C2%A0firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23846</link>
      <description>When using http protocol, the user password is transmitted as a clear text parameter for which it is possible to be obtained by an attacker through a MITM attack. This will be fixed starting from Firmware version 3.11.5, which will be released on the 30th of June, 2021.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23846|2024-09-16T16:38:12.268Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 13:38:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6771|2024-09-16T20:27:14.255Z -- bosch -- ip%20helper
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6771</link>
      <description>Loading a DLL through an Uncontrolled Search Path Element in Bosch IP Helper up to and including version 1.00.0008 potentially allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code on a victim's system. A prerequisite is that the victim is tricked into placing a malicious DLL in the same application directory as the portable IP Helper application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6771|2024-09-16T20:27:14.255Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 15:48:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25002|2024-03-25T13:55:15.344Z -- bosch -- network%20synchronizer%20enterprise</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25002</link>
      <description>Command Injection in the diagnostics interface of the Bosch Network Synchronizer allows unauthorized users full access to the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25002|2024-03-25T13:55:15.344Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 13:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32228|2024-06-04T17:26:31.054Z -- bosch -- ams</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32228</link>
      <description>A firmware bug which may lead to misinterpretation of data in the AMC2-4WCF and AMC2-2WCF allowing an adversary to grant access to the last authorized user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32228|2024-06-04T17:26:31.054Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 09:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32228|2024-08-02T15:10:25.010Z -- bosch -- ams</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32228</link>
      <description>A firmware bug which may lead to misinterpretation of data in the AMC2-4WCF and AMC2-2WCF allowing an adversary to grant access to the last authorized user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32228|2024-08-02T15:10:25.010Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 09:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25002|2024-08-09T16:21:18.523Z -- bosch -- network%20synchronizer%20enterprise</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25002</link>
      <description>Command Injection in the diagnostics interface of the Bosch Network Synchronizer allows unauthorized users full access to the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25002|2024-08-09T16:21:18.523Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 13:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
