<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Bosch -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/bosch/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Bosch -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:22:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-32535|2024-08-03T07:46:43.473Z -- bosch -- pra-es8p2s
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32535</link>
      <description>The Bosch Ethernet switch PRA-ES8P2S with software version 1.01.05 runs its web server with root privilege. In combination with CVE-2022-23534 this could give an attacker root access to the switch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-32535|2024-08-03T07:46:43.473Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 13:55:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23847|2024-08-03T19:14:09.274Z -- bosch -- cpp%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23847</link>
      <description>A Missing Authentication in Critical Function in Bosch IP cameras allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to extract sensitive information or change settings of the camera by sending crafted requests to the device. Only devices of the CPP6, CPP7 and CPP7.3 family with firmware 7.70, 7.72, and 7.80 prior to B128 are affected by this vulnerability. Versions 7.62 or lower and INTEOX cameras are not affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23847|2024-08-03T19:14:09.274Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23859|2024-08-03T19:14:09.402Z -- bosch -- bvms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23859</link>
      <description>An unauthenticated attacker is able to send a special HTTP request, that causes a service to crash. In case of a standalone VRM or BVMS with VRM installation this crash also opens the possibility to send further unauthenticated commands to the service. On some products the interface is only local accessible lowering the CVSS base score. For a list of modified CVSS scores, please see the official Bosch Advisory Appendix chapter Modified CVSS Scores for CVE-2021-23859</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23859|2024-08-03T19:14:09.402Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40183|2024-08-03T12:14:39.865Z -- bosch -- videojet%20multi%204000
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40183</link>
      <description>An error in the URL handler of the VIDEOJET multi 4000 may lead to a reflected cross site scripting (XSS) in the web-based interface. An attacker with knowledge of the encoder address can send a crafted link to a user, which will execute JavaScript code in the context of the user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40183|2024-08-03T12:14:39.865Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40184|2024-08-03T12:14:40.032Z -- bosch -- videojet%20multi%204000
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40184</link>
      <description>Incomplete filtering of JavaScript code in different configuration fields of the web based interface of the VIDEOJET multi 4000 allows an attacker with administrative credentials to store JavaScript code which will be executed for all administrators accessing the same configuration option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40184|2024-08-03T12:14:40.032Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41677|2024-08-03T12:49:43.473Z -- bosch -- camera%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41677</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability was discovered in Bosch IP camera devices allowing an unauthenticated attacker to retrieve information (like capabilities) about the device itself and network settings of the device, disclosing possibly internal network settings if the device is connected to the internet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41677|2024-08-03T12:49:43.473Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 13:02:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-32540|2024-08-03T07:46:43.635Z -- bosch -- bvms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32540</link>
      <description>Information Disclosure in Operator Client application in BVMS 10.1.1, 11.0 and 11.1.0 and VIDEOJET Decoder VJD-7513 versions 10.23 and 10.30 allows man-in-the-middle attacker to compromise confidential video stream. This is only applicable for UDP encryption when target system contains cameras with platform CPP13 or CPP14 and firmware version 8.x.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-32540|2024-08-03T07:46:43.635Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 16:38:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-32534|2024-08-03T07:46:43.351Z -- bosch -- pra-es8p2s
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32534</link>
      <description>The Bosch Ethernet switch PRA-ES8P2S with software version 1.01.05 and earlier was found to be vulnerable to command injection through its diagnostics web interface. This allows execution of shell commands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-32534|2024-08-03T07:46:43.351Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 13:55:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23851|2024-08-03T19:14:09.460Z -- bosch -- cpp%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23851</link>
      <description>A specially crafted TCP/IP packet may cause the camera recovery image web interface to crash. It may also cause a buffer overflow which could enable remote code execution. The recovery image can only be booted with administrative rights or with physical access to the camera and allows the upload of a new firmware in case of a damaged firmware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23851|2024-08-03T19:14:09.460Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23850|2024-08-03T19:14:09.385Z -- bosch -- cpp%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23850</link>
      <description>A specially crafted TCP/IP packet may cause a camera recovery image telnet interface to crash. It may also cause a buffer overflow which could enable remote code execution. The recovery image can only be booted with administrative rights or with physical access to the camera and allows the upload of a new firmware in case of a damaged firmware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23850|2024-08-03T19:14:09.385Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36301|2024-08-03T10:00:04.319Z -- bosch -- bf-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36301</link>
      <description>BF-OS version 3.x up to and including 3.83 do not enforce strong passwords which may allow a remote attacker to brute-force the device password.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36301|2024-08-03T10:00:04.319Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 14:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23843|2024-08-03T19:14:09.225Z -- bosch -- ams
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23843</link>
      <description>The Bosch software tools AccessIPConfig.exe and AmcIpConfig.exe are used to configure certains settings in AMC2 devices. The tool allows putting a password protection on configured devices to restrict access to the configuration of an AMC2. An attacker can circumvent this protection and make unauthorized changes to configuration data on the device. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability to manipulate the device\'s configuration or make it unresponsive in the local network. The attacker needs to have access to the local network, typically even the same subnet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23843|2024-08-03T19:14:09.225Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23854|2024-08-03T19:14:09.247Z -- bosch -- cpp%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23854</link>
      <description>An error in the handling of a page parameter in Bosch IP cameras may lead to a reflected cross site scripting (XSS) in the web-based interface. This issue only affects versions 7.7x and 7.6x. All other versions are not affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23854|2024-08-03T19:14:09.247Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23862|2024-08-03T19:14:09.805Z -- bosch -- bvms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23862</link>
      <description>A crafted configuration packet sent by an authenticated administrative user can be used to execute arbitrary commands in system context. This issue also affects installations of the VRM, DIVAR IP, BVMS with VRM installed, the VIDEOJET decoder (VJD-7513 and VJD-8000).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23862|2024-08-03T19:14:09.805Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36302|2024-08-03T10:00:04.271Z -- bosch -- bf-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36302</link>
      <description>File path manipulation vulnerability in BF-OS version 3.00 up to and including 3.83 allows an attacker to modify the file path to access different resources, which may contain sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36302|2024-08-03T10:00:04.271Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 14:03:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23853|2024-08-03T19:14:09.733Z -- bosch -- cpp%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23853</link>
      <description>In Bosch IP cameras, improper validation of the HTTP header allows an attacker to inject arbitrary HTTP headers through crafted URLs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23853|2024-08-03T19:14:09.733Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23842|2024-08-03T19:14:09.336Z -- bosch -- ams
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23842</link>
      <description>Communication to the AMC2 uses a state-of-the-art cryptographic algorithm for symmetric encryption called Blowfish. An attacker could retrieve the key from the firmware to decrypt network traffic between the AMC2 and the host system. Thus, an attacker can exploit this vulnerability to decrypt and modify network traffic, decrypt and further investigate the device\'s firmware file, and change the device configuration. The attacker needs to have access to the local network, typically even the same subnet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23842|2024-08-03T19:14:09.336Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23860|2024-08-03T19:14:09.832Z -- bosch -- bvms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23860</link>
      <description>An error in a page handler of the VRM may lead to a reflected cross site scripting (XSS) in the web-based interface. To exploit this vulnerability an attack must be able to modify the HTTP header that is sent. This issue also affects installations of the DIVAR IP and BVMS with VRM installed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23860|2024-08-03T19:14:09.832Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-32536|2024-08-03T07:46:43.564Z -- bosch -- pra-es8p2s
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32536</link>
      <description>The user access rights validation in the web server of the Bosch Ethernet switch PRA-ES8P2S with software version 1.01.05 was insufficient. This would allow a non-administrator user to obtain administrator user access rights.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-32536|2024-08-03T07:46:43.564Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 13:55:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23846|2024-08-03T19:14:09.219Z -- bosch -- b426%C2%A0firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23846</link>
      <description>When using http protocol, the user password is transmitted as a clear text parameter for which it is possible to be obtained by an attacker through a MITM attack. This will be fixed starting from Firmware version 3.11.5, which will be released on the 30th of June, 2021.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23846|2024-08-03T19:14:09.219Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23852|2024-08-03T19:14:09.365Z -- bosch -- cpp%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23852</link>
      <description>An authenticated attacker with administrator rights Bosch IP cameras can call an URL with an invalid parameter that causes the camera to become unresponsive for a few seconds and cause a Denial of Service (DoS).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23852|2024-08-03T19:14:09.365Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23861|2024-08-03T19:14:09.235Z -- bosch -- bvms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23861</link>
      <description>By executing a special command, an user with administrative rights can get access to extended debug functionality on the VRM allowing an impact on integrity or availability of the installed software. This issue also affects installations of the DIVAR IP and BVMS with VRM installed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23861|2024-08-03T19:14:09.235Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23849|2024-08-03T19:14:09.380Z -- bosch -- cpp%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23849</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based interface allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to trigger actions on an affected system on behalf of another user (CSRF - Cross Site Request Forgery). This requires the victim to be tricked into clicking a malicious link or opening a malicious website while being logged in into the camera.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23849|2024-08-03T19:14:09.380Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-47648|2024-08-03T15:02:36.511Z -- bosch -- b420
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-47648</link>
      <description>An Improper Access Control vulnerability allows an attacker to access the control panel of the B420 without requiring any sort of authorization or authentication due to the IP based authorization. If an authorized user has accessed a publicly available B420 product using valid credentials, an insider attacker can gain access to the same panel without requiring any sort of authorization. The B420 module was already obsolete at the time this vulnerability was found (The End of Life announcement was made in 2013).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-47648|2024-08-03T15:02:36.511Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23845|2024-08-03T19:14:09.174Z -- bosch -- b426%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23845</link>
      <description>This vulnerability could allow an attacker to hijack a session while a user is logged in the configuration web page. This vulnerability was discovered by a security researcher in B426 and found during internal product tests in B426-CN/B429-CN, and B426-M and has been fixed already starting from version 3.08 on, which was released on June 2019.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23845|2024-08-03T19:14:09.174Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23848|2024-08-03T19:14:09.760Z -- bosch -- cpp%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23848</link>
      <description>An error in the URL handler Bosch IP cameras may lead to a reflected cross site scripting (XSS) in the web-based interface. An attacker with knowledge of the camera address can send a crafted link to a user, which will execute javascript code in the context of the user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23848|2024-08-03T19:14:09.760Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32228|2024-08-02T15:10:25.010Z -- bosch -- ams</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32228</link>
      <description>A firmware bug which may lead to misinterpretation of data in the AMC2-4WCF and AMC2-2WCF allowing an adversary to grant access to the last authorized user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32228|2024-08-02T15:10:25.010Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 09:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32228|2024-06-04T17:26:31.054Z -- bosch -- ams</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32228</link>
      <description>A firmware bug which may lead to misinterpretation of data in the AMC2-4WCF and AMC2-2WCF allowing an adversary to grant access to the last authorized user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32228|2024-06-04T17:26:31.054Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 09:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25002|2024-03-25T13:55:15.344Z -- bosch -- network%20synchronizer%20enterprise</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25002</link>
      <description>Command Injection in the diagnostics interface of the Bosch Network Synchronizer allows unauthorized users full access to the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25002|2024-03-25T13:55:15.344Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 13:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
