<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Bosch -- PRAESIDEO</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/bosch/praesideo.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Bosch -- PRAESIDEO</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 11:21:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6776|2024-09-17T02:31:35.743Z -- bosch -- praesideo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6776</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Bosch PRAESIDEO until and including version 4.41 and Bosch PRAESENSA until and including version 1.10 allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to trigger actions on an affected system on behalf of another user (Cross-Site Request Forgery). This requires the victim to be tricked into clicking a malicious link or submitting a malicious form. A successful exploit allows the attacker to perform arbitrary actions with the privileges of the victim, e.g. creating and modifying user accounts, changing system configuration settings and cause DoS conditions. Note: For Bosch PRAESIDEO 4.31 and newer and Bosch PRAESENSA in all versions, the confidentiality impact is considered low because user credentials are not shown in the web interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6776|2024-09-17T02:31:35.743Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 15:51:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-6777|2024-09-17T01:51:38.379Z -- bosch -- praesideo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6777</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Bosch PRAESIDEO until and including version 4.41 and Bosch PRAESENSA until and including version 1.10 allows an authenticated remote attacker with admin privileges to mount a stored Cross-Site-Scripting (XSS) attack against another user. When the victim logs into the management interface, the stored script code is executed in the context of his browser. A successful exploit would allow an attacker to interact with the management interface with the privileges of the victim. However, as the attacker already needs admin privileges, there is no additional impact on the management interface itself.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-6777|2024-09-17T01:51:38.379Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 15:51:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
