<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Bosch -- Smart Home Controller</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/bosch/smart%20home%20controller.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Bosch -- Smart Home Controller</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 22:22:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11895|2024-09-16T18:03:37.169Z -- bosch -- smart%20home%20controller
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11895</link>
      <description>A potential improper access control vulnerability exists in the JSON-RPC interface of the Bosch Smart Home Controller (SHC) before 9.8.905 that may result in a successful denial of service of the SHC and connected sensors and actuators. In order to exploit the vulnerability, the adversary needs to have successfully paired an app or service, which requires user interaction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11895|2024-09-16T18:03:37.169Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 20:07:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11896|2024-09-16T19:24:49.342Z -- bosch -- smart%20home%20controller
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11896</link>
      <description>A potential incorrect privilege assignment vulnerability exists in the 3rd party pairing mechanism of the Bosch Smart Home Controller (SHC) before 9.8.907 that may result in a restricted app obtaining default app permissions. In order to exploit the vulnerability, the adversary needs to have successfully paired an app, which requires user interaction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11896|2024-09-16T19:24:49.342Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 20:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11892|2024-09-16T17:42:58.052Z -- bosch -- smart%20home%20controller
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11892</link>
      <description>A potential improper access control vulnerability exists in the JSON-RPC interface of the Bosch Smart Home Controller (SHC) before 9.8.905 that may result in reading or modification of the SHC's configuration or triggering and restoring backups. In order to exploit the vulnerability, the adversary needs to have successfully paired an app or service, which requires user interaction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11892|2024-09-16T17:42:58.052Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 19:55:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-11891|2024-09-16T18:13:51.172Z -- bosch -- smart%20home%20controller
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-11891</link>
      <description>A potential incorrect privilege assignment vulnerability exists in the app pairing mechanism of the Bosch Smart Home Controller (SHC) before 9.8.905 that may result in elevated privileges of the adversary's choosing. In order to exploit the vulnerability, the adversary needs physical access to the SHC during the attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-11891|2024-09-16T18:13:51.172Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 19:40:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
