<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for kiwitcms -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/kiwitcms/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for kiwitcms -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 12:25:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22451|2024-08-02T10:13:48.362Z -- kiwitcms -- kiwi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22451</link>
      <description>Kiwi TCMS is an open source test management system. In version 11.6 and prior, when users register new accounts and/or change passwords, there is no validation in place which would prevent them from picking an easy to guess password. This issue is resolved by providing defaults for the `AUTH_PASSWORD_VALIDATORS` configuration setting. As of version 11.7, the password can’t be too similar to other personal information, must contain at least 10 characters, can’t be a commonly used password, and can’t be entirely numeric. As a workaround, an administrator may reset all passwords in Kiwi TCMS if they think a weak password may have been chosen. </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22451|2024-08-02T10:13:48.362Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 15:56:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25156|2024-08-02T11:18:35.351Z -- kiwitcms -- kiwi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25156</link>
      <description>Kiwi TCMS, an open source test management system, does not impose rate limits in versions prior to 12.0. This makes it easier to attempt brute-force attacks against the login page. Users should upgrade to v12.0 or later to receive a patch. As a workaround, users may install and configure a rate-limiting proxy in front of Kiwi TCMS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25156|2024-08-02T11:18:35.351Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25171|2024-08-02T11:18:36.151Z -- kiwitcms -- kiwi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25171</link>
      <description>Kiwi TCMS, an open source test management system, does not impose rate limits in versions prior to 12.0. This makes it easier to attempt denial-of-service attacks against the Password reset page. An attacker could potentially send a large number of emails if they know the email addresses of users in Kiwi TCMS. Additionally that may strain SMTP resources. Users should upgrade to v12.0 or later to receive a patch. As potential workarounds, users may install and configure a rate-limiting proxy in front of Kiwi TCMS and/or configure rate limits on their email server when possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25171|2024-08-02T11:18:36.151Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
