<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Auto-Maskin -- DCU-210E</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/auto-maskin/dcu-210e.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Auto-Maskin -- DCU-210E</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:21:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5400|2024-09-16T18:08:45.736Z -- auto-maskin -- dcu-210e
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5400</link>
      <description>The Auto-Maskin products utilize an undocumented custom protocol to set up Modbus communications with other devices without validating those devices. The originating device sends a message in plaintext, 48:65:6c:6c:6f:20:57:6f:72:6c:64, "Hello World" over UDP ports 44444-44446 to the broadcast address for the LAN. Without verification devices respond to any of these broadcast messages on the LAN with a plaintext reply over UDP containing the device model and firmware version. Following this exchange the devices allow Modbus transmissions between the two devices on the standard Modbus port 502 TCP. Impact: An attacker can exploit this vulnerability to send arbitrary messages to any DCU or RP device through spoofing or replay attacks as long as they have access to the network. Affected releases are Auto-Maskin DCU-210E RP-210E: Versions prior to 3.7 on ARMv7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5400|2024-09-16T18:08:45.736Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5402|2024-09-16T17:28:38.924Z -- auto-maskin -- dcu-210e
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5402</link>
      <description>The Auto-Maskin DCU 210E, RP-210E, and Marine Pro Observer Android App use an embedded webserver that uses unencrypted plaintext for the transmission of the administrator PIN Impact: An attacker once authenticated can change configurations, upload new configuration files, and upload executable code via file upload for firmware updates. Requires access to the network. Affected releases are Auto-Maskin DCU-210E, RP-210E, and the Marine Pro Observer Android App. Versions prior to 3.7 on ARMv7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5402|2024-09-16T17:28:38.924Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
