<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Western Digital -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/western%20digital/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Western Digital -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22814|2023-06-30T23:05:43.130Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud%20os%205
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-22814</link>
      <description>An authentication bypass issue via spoofing was discovered in the token-based authentication mechanism that could allow an attacker to carry out an impersonation attack.


This issue affects My Cloud OS 5 devices: before 5.26.202.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22814|2023-06-30T23:05:43.130Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 23:05:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22819|2024-06-07T16:00:24.870Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud%20os%205
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-22819</link>
      <description>An uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability issue that could arise by sending crafted requests to a service to consume a large amount of memory, eventually resulting in the service being stopped and restarted was discovered in Western Digital My Cloud Home, My Cloud Home Duo, SanDisk ibi and Western Digital My Cloud OS 5 devices. This issue requires the attacker to already have root privileges in order to exploit this vulnerability. This issue affects My Cloud Home and My Cloud Home Duo: before 9.5.1-104; ibi: before 9.5.1-104; My Cloud OS 5: before 5.27.161.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22819|2024-06-07T16:00:24.870Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:26:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22815|2023-08-25T18:53:41.495Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud%20os%205
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-22815</link>
      <description>
Post-authentication remote command injection vulnerability in Western Digital My Cloud OS 5 devices that could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the root user on vulnerable CGI files. This vulnerability can only be exploited over the network and the attacker must already have admin/root privileges to carry out the exploit. An authentication bypass is required for this exploit, thereby making it more complex. The attack may not require user interaction. Since an attacker must already be authenticated, the confidentiality impact is low while the integrity and availability impact is high. 

This issue affects My Cloud OS 5 devices: before 5.26.300.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22815|2023-08-25T18:53:41.495Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 21:07:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22813|2023-05-10T21:57:39.906Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud%20os%205%20mobile%20app
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-22813</link>
      <description>









A device API
endpoint was missing access controls on Western Digital My Cloud OS 5 iOS and Anroid Mobile Apps, My Cloud Home iOS and Android Mobile Apps, SanDisk ibi iOS and Android Mobile Apps, My Cloud OS 5 Web App, My Cloud Home Web App and the SanDisk ibi Web App. Due to a permissive CORS policy
and missing authentication requirement for private IPs, a remote attacker on
the same network as the device could obtain device information by convincing a
victim user to visit an attacker-controlled server and issue a cross-site
request.



This issue affects
My Cloud OS 5 Mobile App: before 4.21.0; My Cloud Home Mobile App: before 4.21.0; ibi Mobile App: before 4.21.0; My
Cloud OS 5 Web App: before 4.26.0-6126; My Cloud Home Web App: before 4.26.0-6126;
ibi Web App: before 4.26.0-6126.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22813|2023-05-10T21:57:39.906Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 22:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22816|2023-06-30T21:01:16.209Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud%20os%205
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-22816</link>
      <description>A post-authentication remote command injection vulnerability in a CGI file in Western Digital My Cloud OS 5 devices that could allow an attacker to build files with redirects and execute larger payloads.
This issue affects My Cloud OS 5 devices: before 5.26.300.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22816|2023-06-30T21:01:16.209Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 21:01:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22817|2024-02-05T21:26:42.020Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud%20os%205
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-22817</link>
      <description>Server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability that could allow a rogue server on the local network to modify its URL using another DNS address to point back to the loopback adapter. This could then allow the URL to exploit other vulnerabilities on the local server. This was addressed by fixing DNS addresses that refer to loopback. This issue affects My Cloud OS 5 devices before 5.27.161, My Cloud Home, My Cloud Home Duo and SanDisk ibi devices before 9.5.1-104. 
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22817|2024-02-05T21:26:42.020Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:26:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
