<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Western Digital -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/western%20digital/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Western Digital -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 19:19:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22999|2024-08-03T03:28:42.794Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22999</link>
      <description>Western Digital My Cloud devices are vulnerable to a cross side scripting vulnerability that can allow a malicious user with elevated privileges access to drives being backed up to construct and inject JavaScript payloads into an authenticated user's browser. As a result, it may be possible to gain control over the authenticated session, steal data, modify settings, or redirect the user to malicious websites. The scope of impact can extend to other components.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22999|2024-08-03T03:28:42.794Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 18:47:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22990|2024-08-03T03:28:42.745Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22990</link>
      <description>A limited authentication bypass vulnerability was discovered that could allow an attacker to achieve remote code execution and escalate privileges on the My Cloud devices. Addressed this vulnerability by changing access token validation logic and rewriting rule logic on PHP scripts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22990|2024-08-03T03:28:42.745Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 20:27:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29844|2024-08-03T06:33:42.870Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29844</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the FTP service of Western Digital My Cloud OS 5 devices running firmware versions prior to 5.26.119 allows an attacker to read and write arbitrary files. This could lead to a full NAS compromise and would give remote execution capabilities to the attacker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29844|2024-08-03T06:33:42.870Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29842|2024-08-03T06:33:42.845Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud%20os%205
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29842</link>
      <description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command ('Command Injection') vulnerability that could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the root user on a vulnerable CGI file was discovered in Western Digital My Cloud OS 5 devicesThis issue affects My Cloud OS 5: before 5.26.119.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29842|2024-08-03T06:33:42.845Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 20:53:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29841|2024-08-03T06:33:42.812Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud%20os%205
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29841</link>
      <description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability that was caused by a command that read files from a privileged location and created a system command without sanitizing the read data. This command could be triggered by an attacker remotely to cause code execution and gain a reverse shell in Western Digital My Cloud OS 5 devices.This issue affects My Cloud OS 5: before 5.26.119.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29841|2024-08-03T06:33:42.812Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 21:04:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23003|2024-08-03T03:28:42.989Z -- western%20digital -- sweet%20b%20library
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23003</link>
      <description>When computing a shared secret or point multiplication on the NIST P-256 curve that results in an X coordinate of zero, the resulting output is not properly reduced modulo the P-256 field prime and is invalid. The resulting output may cause an error when used in other operations. This may be leveraged by an attacker to cause an error scenario or incorrect choice of session key in applications which use the library, resulting in a limited denial of service for an individual user. The scope of impact cannot extend to other components.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23003|2024-08-03T03:28:42.989Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 18:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29838|2024-08-03T06:33:42.806Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29838</link>
      <description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in the encrypted volumes and auto mount features of Western Digital My Cloud devices allows insecure direct access to the drive information in the case of a device reset. This issue affects: Western Digital My Cloud My Cloud versions prior to 5.25.124 on Linux.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29838|2024-08-03T06:33:42.806Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23001|2024-08-03T03:28:42.996Z -- western%20digital -- sweet%20b%20library
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23001</link>
      <description>When compressing or decompressing elliptic curve points using the Sweet B library, an incorrect choice of sign bit is used. An attacker with user level privileges and no other user's assistance can exploit this vulnerability with only knowledge of the public key and the library. The resulting output may cause an error when used in other operations; for instance, verification of a valid signature under a decompressed public key may fail. This may be leveraged by an attacker to cause an error scenario in applications which use the library, resulting in a limited denial of service for an individual user. The scope of impact cannot extend to other components.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23001|2024-08-03T03:28:42.996Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 18:51:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29837|2024-08-03T06:33:42.797Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud%20home
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29837</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability was addressed in Western Digital My Cloud Home, My Cloud Home Duo and SanDisk ibi which could allow an attacker to initiate installation of custom ZIP packages and overwrite system files. This could potentially lead to a code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29837|2024-08-03T06:33:42.797Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23000|2024-08-03T03:28:43.001Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23000</link>
      <description>The Western Digital My Cloud Web App [https://os5.mycloud.com/] uses a weak SSLContext when attempting to configure port forwarding rules. This was enabled to maintain compatibility with old or outdated home routers. By using an "SSL" context instead of "TLS" or specifying stronger validation, deprecated or insecure protocols are permitted. As a result, a local user with no privileges can exploit this vulnerability and jeopardize the integrity, confidentiality and authenticity of information transmitted. The scope of impact cannot extend to other components and no user input is required to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23000|2024-08-03T03:28:43.001Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 18:46:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36328|2024-08-03T10:00:04.308Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud%20home%20and%20my%20cloud%20home%20duo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36328</link>
      <description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability that could allow an attacker to create arbitrary shares on arbitrary directories and exfiltrate sensitive files, passwords, users and device configurations was discovered in Western Digital My Cloud Home, My Cloud Home Duo, SanDisk ibi and Western Digital My Cloud OS 5 devices. This can only be exploited once an attacker gains root privileges on the devices using an authentication bypass issue or another vulnerability.This issue affects My Cloud Home and My Cloud Home Duo: before 9.4.0-191; ibi: before 9.4.0-191; My Cloud OS 5: before 5.26.202.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36328|2024-08-03T10:00:04.308Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 17:55:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36330|2024-08-03T10:00:04.306Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud%20home%20and%20my%20cloud%20home%20duo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36330</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow vulnerability was discovered on firmware version validation that could lead to an unauthenticated remote code execution in Western Digital My Cloud Home, My Cloud Home Duo and SanDisk ibi devices. An attacker would require exploitation of another vulnerability to raise their privileges in order to exploit this buffer overflow vulnerability.

This issue affects My Cloud Home and My Cloud Home Duo: before 9.4.0-191; ibi: before 9.4.0-191. 



</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36330|2024-08-03T10:00:04.306Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 23:16:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29839|2024-08-03T06:33:42.792Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29839</link>
      <description>Insufficiently Protected Credentials vulnerability in the remote backups application on Western Digital My Cloud devices that could allow an attacker who has gained access to a relevant endpoint to use that information to access protected data. This issue affects: Western Digital My Cloud My Cloud versions prior to 5.25.124 on Linux.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29839|2024-08-03T06:33:42.792Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29843|2024-08-03T06:33:42.818Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29843</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability in the DDNS service configuration of Western Digital My Cloud OS 5 devices running firmware versions prior to 5.26.119 allows an attacker to execute code in the context of the root user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29843|2024-08-03T06:33:42.818Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29835|2024-08-03T06:33:42.851Z -- western%20digital -- wd%20discovery
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29835</link>
      <description>WD Discovery software executable files were signed with an unsafe SHA-1 hashing algorithm. An attacker could use this weakness to create forged certificate signatures due to the use of a hashing algorithm that is not collision-free. This could thereby impact the confidentiality of user content. This issue affects: Western Digital WD Discovery WD Discovery Desktop App versions prior to 4.4.396 on Mac; WD Discovery Desktop App versions prior to 4.4.396 on Windows.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29835|2024-08-03T06:33:42.851Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 19:43:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36326|2024-08-03T10:00:04.241Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud%20home%20and%20my%20cloud%20home%20duo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36326</link>
      <description>An uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability issue that could arise by sending crafted requests to a service to consume a large amount of memory, eventually resulting in the service being stopped and restarted was discovered in Western Digital My Cloud Home, My Cloud Home Duo, SanDisk ibi and Western Digital My Cloud OS 5 devices. This issue requires the attacker to already have root privileges in order to exploit this vulnerability.This issue affects My Cloud Home and My Cloud Home Duo: before 9.4.0-191; ibi: before 9.4.0-191; My Cloud OS 5: before 5.26.202.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36326|2024-08-03T10:00:04.241Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 17:53:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23002|2024-08-03T03:28:42.735Z -- western%20digital -- sweet%20b%20library
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23002</link>
      <description>When compressing or decompressing a point on the NIST P-256 elliptic curve with an X coordinate of zero, the resulting output is not properly reduced modulo the P-256 field prime and is invalid. The resulting output will cause an error when used in other operations. This may be leveraged by an attacker to cause an error scenario in applications which use the library, resulting in a limited denial of service for an individual user. The scope of impact cannot extend to other components.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23002|2024-08-03T03:28:42.735Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 18:52:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36331|2024-08-03T10:00:04.251Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud%20os%205
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36331</link>
      <description>Western Digital My Cloud, My Cloud Home, My Cloud Home Duo, and SanDisk ibi devices were vulnerable to an impersonation attack that could allow an unauthenticated attacker to gain access to user data.
This issue affects My Cloud OS 5 devices: before 5.25.132; My Cloud Home and My Cloud Home Duo: before 8.13.1-102; SanDisk ibi: before 8.13.1-102.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36331|2024-08-03T10:00:04.251Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 17:57:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22994|2024-08-03T03:28:42.734Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22994</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability was discovered on Western Digital My Cloud devices where an attacker could trick a NAS device into loading through an unsecured HTTP call. This was a result insufficient verification of calls to the device. The vulnerability was addressed by disabling checks for internet connectivity using HTTP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22994|2024-08-03T03:28:42.734Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 19:35:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22991|2024-08-03T03:28:42.988Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22991</link>
      <description>A malicious user on the same LAN could use DNS spoofing followed by a command injection attack to trick a NAS device into loading through an unsecured HTTP call. Addressed this vulnerability by disabling checks for internet connectivity using HTTP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22991|2024-08-03T03:28:42.988Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 20:27:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22993|2024-08-03T03:28:43.023Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22993</link>
      <description>A limited SSRF vulnerability was discovered on Western Digital My Cloud devices that could allow an attacker to impersonate a server and reach any page on the server by bypassing access controls. The vulnerability was addressed by creating a whitelist for valid parameters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22993|2024-08-03T03:28:43.023Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 19:09:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23006|2024-08-03T03:28:42.880Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud%20home
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23006</link>
      <description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability was found on Western Digital My Cloud Home, My Cloud Home Duo, and SanDisk ibi that could allow an attacker accessing the system locally to read information from /etc/version file. This vulnerability can only be exploited by chaining it with another issue. If an attacker is able to carry out a remote code execution attack, they can gain access to the vulnerable file, due to the presence of insecure functions in code. User interaction is required for exploitation. Exploiting the vulnerability could result in exposure of information, ability to modify files, memory access errors, or system crashes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23006|2024-08-03T03:28:42.880Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 13:53:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22989|2024-08-03T03:28:42.838Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22989</link>
      <description>My Cloud OS 5 was vulnerable to a pre-authenticated stack overflow vulnerability on the FTP service that could be exploited by unauthenticated attackers on the network. Addressed the vulnerability by adding defenses against stack overflow issues.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22989|2024-08-03T03:28:42.838Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 20:27:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29836|2024-08-03T06:33:42.762Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud%20home
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29836</link>
      <description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability was discovered via an HTTP API on Western Digital My Cloud Home; My Cloud Home Duo; and SanDisk ibi devices that could allow an attacker to abuse certain parameters to point to random locations on the file system. This could also allow the attacker to initiate the installation of custom packages at these locations. This can only be exploited once the attacker has been authenticated to the device. This issue affects: Western Digital My Cloud Home and My Cloud Home Duo versions prior to 8.11.0-113 on Linux; SanDisk ibi versions prior to 8.11.0-113 on Linux.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29836|2024-08-03T06:33:42.762Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36329|2024-08-03T10:00:04.370Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud%20home%20and%20my%20cloud%20home%20duo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36329</link>
      <description>An improper privilege management issue that could allow an attacker to cause a denial of service over the OTA mechanism was discovered in Western Digital My Cloud Home, My Cloud Home Duo and SanDisk ibi devices.This issue affects My Cloud Home and My Cloud Home Duo: before 9.4.0-191; ibi: before 9.4.0-191.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36329|2024-08-03T10:00:04.370Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 19:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22988|2024-08-03T03:28:42.755Z -- western%20digital -- edgerover
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22988</link>
      <description>File and directory permissions have been corrected to prevent unintended users from modifying or accessing resources. It would be more difficult for an authenticated attacker to now traverse through the files and directories. This can only be exploited once an attacker has already found a way to get authenticated access to the device. 

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22988|2024-08-03T03:28:42.755Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 20:27:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22997|2024-08-03T03:28:42.830Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud%20home
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22997</link>
      <description>Addressed a remote code execution vulnerability by resolving a command injection vulnerability and closing an AWS S3 bucket that potentially allowed an attacker to execute unsigned code on My Cloud Home devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22997|2024-08-03T03:28:42.830Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 20:22:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29840|2024-08-03T06:33:42.938Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud%20os%205
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29840</link>
      <description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability that could allow a rogue server on the local network to modify its URL to point back to the loopback adapter was addressed in Western Digital My Cloud OS 5 devices. This could allow the URL to exploit other vulnerabilities on the local server.This issue affects My Cloud OS 5 devices before 5.26.202.


</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29840|2024-08-03T06:33:42.938Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 22:09:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36327|2024-08-03T10:00:04.219Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud%20home%20and%20my%20cloud%20home%20duo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36327</link>
      <description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability that could allow an attacker to write files to locations with certain critical filesystem types leading to remote code execution was discovered in Western Digital My Cloud Home, My Cloud Home Duo, SanDisk ibi and Western Digital My Cloud OS 5 devices. This issue requires an authentication bypass issue to be triggered before this can be exploited. 
This issue affects My Cloud Home and My Cloud Home Duo: before 9.4.0-191; ibi: before 9.4.0-191; My Cloud OS 5: before 5.26.202.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36327|2024-08-03T10:00:04.219Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 17:54:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23004|2024-08-03T03:28:42.836Z -- western%20digital -- sweet%20b%20library
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23004</link>
      <description>When computing a shared secret or point multiplication on the NIST P-256 curve using a public key with an X coordinate of zero, an error is returned from the library, and an invalid unreduced value is written to the output buffer. This may be leveraged by an attacker to cause an error scenario, resulting in a limited denial of service for an individual user. The scope of impact cannot extend to other components.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23004|2024-08-03T03:28:42.836Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 18:55:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22998|2024-08-03T03:28:42.801Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud%20home
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22998</link>
      <description>Implemented protections on AWS credentials that were not properly protected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22998|2024-08-03T03:28:42.801Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 20:19:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22995|2024-08-03T03:28:42.925Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22995</link>
      <description>The combination of primitives offered by SMB and AFP in their default configuration allows the arbitrary writing of files. By exploiting these combination of primitives, an attacker can execute arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22995|2024-08-03T03:28:42.925Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22169|2024-08-02T18:31:11.324Z -- western%20digital -- wd%20discovery</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22169</link>
      <description>WD Discovery
versions prior to 5.0.589 contain a misconfiguration in the Node.js environment
settings that could allow code execution by utilizing the 'ELECTRON_RUN_AS_NODE' environment variable.
Any malicious application operating with standard user permissions can exploit
this vulnerability, enabling code execution within WD Discovery application's
context. WD Discovery version 5.0.589 addresses this issue by disabling certain
features and fuses in Electron. The attack vector for this issue requires the victim to have the WD Discovery app installed on their device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22169|2024-08-02T18:31:11.324Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 18:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22817|2024-08-02T10:20:31.069Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud%20os%205</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22817</link>
      <description>Server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability that could allow a rogue server on the local network to modify its URL using another DNS address to point back to the loopback adapter. This could then allow the URL to exploit other vulnerabilities on the local server. This was addressed by fixing DNS addresses that refer to loopback. This issue affects My Cloud OS 5 devices before 5.27.161, My Cloud Home, My Cloud Home Duo and SanDisk ibi devices before 9.5.1-104.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22817|2024-08-02T10:20:31.069Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:26:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22819|2024-08-02T10:20:30.729Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud%20os%205</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22819</link>
      <description>An uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability issue that could arise by sending crafted requests to a service to consume a large amount of memory, eventually resulting in the service being stopped and restarted was discovered in Western Digital My Cloud Home, My Cloud Home Duo, SanDisk ibi and Western Digital My Cloud OS 5 devices. This issue requires the attacker to already have root privileges in order to exploit this vulnerability. This issue affects My Cloud Home and My Cloud Home Duo: before 9.5.1-104; ibi: before 9.5.1-104; My Cloud OS 5: before 5.27.161.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22819|2024-08-02T10:20:30.729Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:26:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22817|2024-07-05T17:21:32.355Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud%20os%205</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22817</link>
      <description>Server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability that could allow a rogue server on the local network to modify its URL using another DNS address to point back to the loopback adapter. This could then allow the URL to exploit other vulnerabilities on the local server. This was addressed by fixing DNS addresses that refer to loopback. This issue affects My Cloud OS 5 devices before 5.27.161, My Cloud Home, My Cloud Home Duo and SanDisk ibi devices before 9.5.1-104.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22817|2024-07-05T17:21:32.355Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:26:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22168|2024-06-24T22:54:16.903Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud%20home%20web%20app</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22168</link>
      <description>A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability on the My Cloud, My Cloud Home, SanDisk ibi, and WD Cloud web apps was found which could allow an attacker to redirect the user to a crafted domain and reset their credentials, or to execute arbitrary client-side code in the user’s browser session to carry out malicious activities.The web apps for these devices have been automatically updated to resolve this vulnerability and improve the security of your devices and data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22168|2024-06-24T22:54:16.903Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 22:54:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22817|2024-02-05T21:26:42.020Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud%20os%205</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-22817</link>
      <description>Server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability that could allow a rogue server on the local network to modify its URL using another DNS address to point back to the loopback adapter. This could then allow the URL to exploit other vulnerabilities on the local server. This was addressed by fixing DNS addresses that refer to loopback. This issue affects My Cloud OS 5 devices before 5.27.161, My Cloud Home, My Cloud Home Duo and SanDisk ibi devices before 9.5.1-104.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22817|2024-02-05T21:26:42.020Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:26:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22819|2024-06-07T16:00:24.870Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud%20os%205</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-22819</link>
      <description>An uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability issue that could arise by sending crafted requests to a service to consume a large amount of memory, eventually resulting in the service being stopped and restarted was discovered in Western Digital My Cloud Home, My Cloud Home Duo, SanDisk ibi and Western Digital My Cloud OS 5 devices. This issue requires the attacker to already have root privileges in order to exploit this vulnerability. This issue affects My Cloud Home and My Cloud Home Duo: before 9.5.1-104; ibi: before 9.5.1-104; My Cloud OS 5: before 5.27.161.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22819|2024-06-07T16:00:24.870Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:26:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22168|2024-06-25T14:51:55.016Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud%20home%20web%20app</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22168</link>
      <description>A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability on the My Cloud, My Cloud Home, SanDisk ibi, and WD Cloud web apps was found which could allow an attacker to redirect the user to a crafted domain and reset their credentials, or to execute arbitrary client-side code in the user’s browser session to carry out malicious activities.The web apps for these devices have been automatically updated to resolve this vulnerability and improve the security of your devices and data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22168|2024-06-25T14:51:55.016Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 22:54:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22168|2024-08-01T22:35:34.879Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud%20home%20web%20app</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22168</link>
      <description>A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability on the My Cloud, My Cloud Home, SanDisk ibi, and WD Cloud web apps was found which could allow an attacker to redirect the user to a crafted domain and reset their credentials, or to execute arbitrary client-side code in the user’s browser session to carry out malicious activities.The web apps for these devices have been automatically updated to resolve this vulnerability and improve the security of your devices and data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22168|2024-08-01T22:35:34.879Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 22:54:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
