<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Western Digital -- My Cloud Home and My Cloud Home Duo</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/western%20digital/my%20cloud%20home%20and%20my%20cloud%20home%20duo.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Western Digital -- My Cloud Home and My Cloud Home Duo</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 19:19:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36328|2024-08-03T10:00:04.308Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud%20home%20and%20my%20cloud%20home%20duo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36328</link>
      <description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability that could allow an attacker to create arbitrary shares on arbitrary directories and exfiltrate sensitive files, passwords, users and device configurations was discovered in Western Digital My Cloud Home, My Cloud Home Duo, SanDisk ibi and Western Digital My Cloud OS 5 devices. This can only be exploited once an attacker gains root privileges on the devices using an authentication bypass issue or another vulnerability.This issue affects My Cloud Home and My Cloud Home Duo: before 9.4.0-191; ibi: before 9.4.0-191; My Cloud OS 5: before 5.26.202.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36328|2024-08-03T10:00:04.308Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 17:55:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36330|2024-08-03T10:00:04.306Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud%20home%20and%20my%20cloud%20home%20duo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36330</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow vulnerability was discovered on firmware version validation that could lead to an unauthenticated remote code execution in Western Digital My Cloud Home, My Cloud Home Duo and SanDisk ibi devices. An attacker would require exploitation of another vulnerability to raise their privileges in order to exploit this buffer overflow vulnerability.

This issue affects My Cloud Home and My Cloud Home Duo: before 9.4.0-191; ibi: before 9.4.0-191. 



</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36330|2024-08-03T10:00:04.306Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 23:16:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36326|2024-08-03T10:00:04.241Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud%20home%20and%20my%20cloud%20home%20duo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36326</link>
      <description>An uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability issue that could arise by sending crafted requests to a service to consume a large amount of memory, eventually resulting in the service being stopped and restarted was discovered in Western Digital My Cloud Home, My Cloud Home Duo, SanDisk ibi and Western Digital My Cloud OS 5 devices. This issue requires the attacker to already have root privileges in order to exploit this vulnerability.This issue affects My Cloud Home and My Cloud Home Duo: before 9.4.0-191; ibi: before 9.4.0-191; My Cloud OS 5: before 5.26.202.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36326|2024-08-03T10:00:04.241Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 17:53:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36329|2024-08-03T10:00:04.370Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud%20home%20and%20my%20cloud%20home%20duo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36329</link>
      <description>An improper privilege management issue that could allow an attacker to cause a denial of service over the OTA mechanism was discovered in Western Digital My Cloud Home, My Cloud Home Duo and SanDisk ibi devices.This issue affects My Cloud Home and My Cloud Home Duo: before 9.4.0-191; ibi: before 9.4.0-191.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36329|2024-08-03T10:00:04.370Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 19:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36327|2024-08-03T10:00:04.219Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud%20home%20and%20my%20cloud%20home%20duo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36327</link>
      <description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability that could allow an attacker to write files to locations with certain critical filesystem types leading to remote code execution was discovered in Western Digital My Cloud Home, My Cloud Home Duo, SanDisk ibi and Western Digital My Cloud OS 5 devices. This issue requires an authentication bypass issue to be triggered before this can be exploited. 
This issue affects My Cloud Home and My Cloud Home Duo: before 9.4.0-191; ibi: before 9.4.0-191; My Cloud OS 5: before 5.26.202.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36327|2024-08-03T10:00:04.219Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 17:54:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
