<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Western Digital -- My Cloud</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/western%20digital/my%20cloud.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Western Digital -- My Cloud</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 18:24:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22999|2024-08-03T03:28:42.794Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22999</link>
      <description>Western Digital My Cloud devices are vulnerable to a cross side scripting vulnerability that can allow a malicious user with elevated privileges access to drives being backed up to construct and inject JavaScript payloads into an authenticated user's browser. As a result, it may be possible to gain control over the authenticated session, steal data, modify settings, or redirect the user to malicious websites. The scope of impact can extend to other components.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22999|2024-08-03T03:28:42.794Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 18:47:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22990|2024-08-03T03:28:42.745Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22990</link>
      <description>A limited authentication bypass vulnerability was discovered that could allow an attacker to achieve remote code execution and escalate privileges on the My Cloud devices. Addressed this vulnerability by changing access token validation logic and rewriting rule logic on PHP scripts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22990|2024-08-03T03:28:42.745Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 20:27:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29844|2024-08-03T06:33:42.870Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29844</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the FTP service of Western Digital My Cloud OS 5 devices running firmware versions prior to 5.26.119 allows an attacker to read and write arbitrary files. This could lead to a full NAS compromise and would give remote execution capabilities to the attacker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29844|2024-08-03T06:33:42.870Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29838|2024-08-03T06:33:42.806Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29838</link>
      <description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in the encrypted volumes and auto mount features of Western Digital My Cloud devices allows insecure direct access to the drive information in the case of a device reset. This issue affects: Western Digital My Cloud My Cloud versions prior to 5.25.124 on Linux.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29838|2024-08-03T06:33:42.806Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23000|2024-08-03T03:28:43.001Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23000</link>
      <description>The Western Digital My Cloud Web App [https://os5.mycloud.com/] uses a weak SSLContext when attempting to configure port forwarding rules. This was enabled to maintain compatibility with old or outdated home routers. By using an "SSL" context instead of "TLS" or specifying stronger validation, deprecated or insecure protocols are permitted. As a result, a local user with no privileges can exploit this vulnerability and jeopardize the integrity, confidentiality and authenticity of information transmitted. The scope of impact cannot extend to other components and no user input is required to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23000|2024-08-03T03:28:43.001Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 18:46:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29839|2024-08-03T06:33:42.792Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29839</link>
      <description>Insufficiently Protected Credentials vulnerability in the remote backups application on Western Digital My Cloud devices that could allow an attacker who has gained access to a relevant endpoint to use that information to access protected data. This issue affects: Western Digital My Cloud My Cloud versions prior to 5.25.124 on Linux.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29839|2024-08-03T06:33:42.792Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29843|2024-08-03T06:33:42.818Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29843</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability in the DDNS service configuration of Western Digital My Cloud OS 5 devices running firmware versions prior to 5.26.119 allows an attacker to execute code in the context of the root user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29843|2024-08-03T06:33:42.818Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22994|2024-08-03T03:28:42.734Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22994</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability was discovered on Western Digital My Cloud devices where an attacker could trick a NAS device into loading through an unsecured HTTP call. This was a result insufficient verification of calls to the device. The vulnerability was addressed by disabling checks for internet connectivity using HTTP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22994|2024-08-03T03:28:42.734Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 19:35:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22991|2024-08-03T03:28:42.988Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22991</link>
      <description>A malicious user on the same LAN could use DNS spoofing followed by a command injection attack to trick a NAS device into loading through an unsecured HTTP call. Addressed this vulnerability by disabling checks for internet connectivity using HTTP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22991|2024-08-03T03:28:42.988Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 20:27:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22993|2024-08-03T03:28:43.023Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22993</link>
      <description>A limited SSRF vulnerability was discovered on Western Digital My Cloud devices that could allow an attacker to impersonate a server and reach any page on the server by bypassing access controls. The vulnerability was addressed by creating a whitelist for valid parameters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22993|2024-08-03T03:28:43.023Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 19:09:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22989|2024-08-03T03:28:42.838Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22989</link>
      <description>My Cloud OS 5 was vulnerable to a pre-authenticated stack overflow vulnerability on the FTP service that could be exploited by unauthenticated attackers on the network. Addressed the vulnerability by adding defenses against stack overflow issues.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22989|2024-08-03T03:28:42.838Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 20:27:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22995|2024-08-03T03:28:42.925Z -- western%20digital -- my%20cloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22995</link>
      <description>The combination of primitives offered by SMB and AFP in their default configuration allows the arbitrary writing of files. By exploiting these combination of primitives, an attacker can execute arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22995|2024-08-03T03:28:42.925Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
