<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Western Digital -- Sweet B Library</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/western%20digital/sweet%20b%20library.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Western Digital -- Sweet B Library</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 17:21:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23003|2024-08-03T03:28:42.989Z -- western%20digital -- sweet%20b%20library
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23003</link>
      <description>When computing a shared secret or point multiplication on the NIST P-256 curve that results in an X coordinate of zero, the resulting output is not properly reduced modulo the P-256 field prime and is invalid. The resulting output may cause an error when used in other operations. This may be leveraged by an attacker to cause an error scenario or incorrect choice of session key in applications which use the library, resulting in a limited denial of service for an individual user. The scope of impact cannot extend to other components.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23003|2024-08-03T03:28:42.989Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 18:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23001|2024-08-03T03:28:42.996Z -- western%20digital -- sweet%20b%20library
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23001</link>
      <description>When compressing or decompressing elliptic curve points using the Sweet B library, an incorrect choice of sign bit is used. An attacker with user level privileges and no other user's assistance can exploit this vulnerability with only knowledge of the public key and the library. The resulting output may cause an error when used in other operations; for instance, verification of a valid signature under a decompressed public key may fail. This may be leveraged by an attacker to cause an error scenario in applications which use the library, resulting in a limited denial of service for an individual user. The scope of impact cannot extend to other components.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23001|2024-08-03T03:28:42.996Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 18:51:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23002|2024-08-03T03:28:42.735Z -- western%20digital -- sweet%20b%20library
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23002</link>
      <description>When compressing or decompressing a point on the NIST P-256 elliptic curve with an X coordinate of zero, the resulting output is not properly reduced modulo the P-256 field prime and is invalid. The resulting output will cause an error when used in other operations. This may be leveraged by an attacker to cause an error scenario in applications which use the library, resulting in a limited denial of service for an individual user. The scope of impact cannot extend to other components.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23002|2024-08-03T03:28:42.735Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 18:52:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23004|2024-08-03T03:28:42.836Z -- western%20digital -- sweet%20b%20library
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23004</link>
      <description>When computing a shared secret or point multiplication on the NIST P-256 curve using a public key with an X coordinate of zero, an error is returned from the library, and an invalid unreduced value is written to the output buffer. This may be leveraged by an attacker to cause an error scenario, resulting in a limited denial of service for an individual user. The scope of impact cannot extend to other components.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23004|2024-08-03T03:28:42.836Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 18:55:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
