<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Western Digital -- WD Discovery</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/western%20digital/wd%20discovery.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Western Digital -- WD Discovery</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 19:19:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29835|2024-08-03T06:33:42.851Z -- western%20digital -- wd%20discovery
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29835</link>
      <description>WD Discovery software executable files were signed with an unsafe SHA-1 hashing algorithm. An attacker could use this weakness to create forged certificate signatures due to the use of a hashing algorithm that is not collision-free. This could thereby impact the confidentiality of user content. This issue affects: Western Digital WD Discovery WD Discovery Desktop App versions prior to 4.4.396 on Mac; WD Discovery Desktop App versions prior to 4.4.396 on Windows.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29835|2024-08-03T06:33:42.851Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 19:43:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22169|2024-08-02T18:31:11.324Z -- western%20digital -- wd%20discovery</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22169</link>
      <description>WD Discovery
versions prior to 5.0.589 contain a misconfiguration in the Node.js environment
settings that could allow code execution by utilizing the 'ELECTRON_RUN_AS_NODE' environment variable.
Any malicious application operating with standard user permissions can exploit
this vulnerability, enabling code execution within WD Discovery application's
context. WD Discovery version 5.0.589 addresses this issue by disabling certain
features and fuses in Electron. The attack vector for this issue requires the victim to have the WD Discovery app installed on their device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22169|2024-08-02T18:31:11.324Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 18:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
