<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for wpcalc -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/wpcalc/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for wpcalc -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 19:19:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0703|2024-08-01T18:11:35.679Z -- wpcalc -- sticky%20buttons%20%E2%80%93%20floating%20buttons%20builder
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0703</link>
      <description>The Sticky Buttons – floating buttons builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via sticky URLs in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0703|2024-08-01T18:11:35.679Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 11:01:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2457|2024-06-04T17:29:01.167Z -- wpcalc -- modal%20window%20%E2%80%93%20create%20popup%20modal%20window</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2457</link>
      <description>The Modal Window – create popup modal window plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2457|2024-06-04T17:29:01.167Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
