<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Beckhoff -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/beckhoff/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Beckhoff -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:23:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5636|2024-08-04T20:01:52.163Z -- beckhoff -- twincat%202
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5636</link>
      <description>When a Beckhoff TwinCAT Runtime receives a malformed UDP packet, the ADS Discovery Service shuts down. Note that the TwinCAT devices are still performing as normal. This issue affects TwinCAT 2 version 2304 (and prior) and TwinCAT 3.1 version 4204.0 (and prior).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5636|2024-08-04T20:01:52.163Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5637|2024-08-04T20:01:52.050Z -- beckhoff -- twincat%202
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5637</link>
      <description>When Beckhoff TwinCAT is configured to use the Profinet driver, a denial of service of the controller could be reached by sending a malformed UDP packet to the device. This issue affects TwinCAT 2 version 2304 (and prior) and TwinCAT 3.1 version 4204.0 (and prior).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5637|2024-08-04T20:01:52.050Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-12510|2024-08-04T11:56:52.097Z -- beckhoff -- twincat%20xar%203.1
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12510</link>
      <description>The default installation path of the TwinCAT XAR 3.1 software in all versions is underneath C:\TwinCAT. If the directory does not exist it and further subdirectories are created with permissions which allow every local user to modify the content. The default installation registers TcSysUI.exe for automatic execution upon log in of a user. If a less privileged user has a local account he or she can replace TcSysUI.exe. It will be executed automatically by another user during login. This is also true for users with administrative access. Consequently, a less privileged user can trick a higher privileged user into executing code he or she modified this way. By default Beckhoff’s IPCs are shipped with TwinCAT software installed this way and with just a single local user configured. Thus the vulnerability exists if further less privileged users have been added.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-12510|2024-08-04T11:56:52.097Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-12526|2024-08-04T11:56:52.054Z -- beckhoff -- twincat%20opc%20ua%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12526</link>
      <description>TwinCAT OPC UA Server in versions up to 2.3.0.12 and IPC Diagnostics UA Server in versions up to 3.1.0.1 from Beckhoff Automation GmbH &amp; Co. KG are vulnerable to denial of service attacks. The attacker needs to send several specifically crafted requests to the running OPC UA server. After some of these requests the OPC UA server is no longer responsive to any client. This is without effect to the real-time functionality of IPCs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-12526|2024-08-04T11:56:52.054Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-12494|2024-08-04T11:56:52.090Z -- beckhoff -- twincat%20driver%20for%20intel%208254x%20%28tcl8254x.sys%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12494</link>
      <description>Beckhoff's TwinCAT RT network driver for Intel 8254x and 8255x is providing EtherCAT functionality. The driver implements real-time features. Except for Ethernet frames sent from real-time functionality, all other Ethernet frames sent through the driver are not padded if their payload is less than the minimum Ethernet frame size. Instead, arbitrary memory content is transmitted within in the padding bytes of the frame. Most likely this memory contains slices from previously transmitted or received frames. By this method, memory content is disclosed, however, an attacker can hardly control which memory content is affected. For example, the disclosure can be provoked with small sized ICMP echo requests sent to the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-12494|2024-08-04T11:56:52.090Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 13:28:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
