<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Chengdu -- VEC40G</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/chengdu/vec40g.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Chengdu -- VEC40G</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 13:23:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2522|2024-08-02T06:26:09.671Z -- chengdu -- vec40g
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2522</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Chengdu VEC40G 3.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /send_order.cgi?parameter=access_detect of the component Network Detection. The manipulation of the argument COUNT with the input 3 | netstat -an leads to os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-228013 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Chengdu VEC40G 3.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei /send_order.cgi?parameter=access_detect der Komponente Network Detection. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments COUNT mit der Eingabe 3 | netstat -an mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2522|2024-08-02T06:26:09.671Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 17:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3206|2024-08-02T06:48:07.821Z -- chengdu -- vec40g
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3206</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Chengdu VEC40G 3.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /send_order.cgi?parameter=restart. The manipulation of the argument restart with the input reboot leads to denial of service. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-231229 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Chengdu VEC40G 3.0 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei /send_order.cgi?parameter=restart. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments restart mit der Eingabe reboot mit unbekannten Daten kann eine denial of service-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3206|2024-08-02T06:48:07.821Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 15:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
