<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle -- FLEXCUBE Investor Servicing</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle/flexcube%20investor%20servicing.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle -- FLEXCUBE Investor Servicing</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 21:22:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-8316|2024-10-09T19:59:44.744Z -- oracle -- flexcube%20investor%20servicing
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-8316</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Investor Servicing component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are 12.0.1, 12.0.2,12.0.4,12.1.0 and 12.3.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Investor Servicing. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle FLEXCUBE Investor Servicing, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle FLEXCUBE Investor Servicing accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle FLEXCUBE Investor Servicing accessible data. CVSS v3.0 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-8316|2024-10-09T19:59:44.744Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-8306|2024-10-09T20:01:25.232Z -- oracle -- flexcube%20investor%20servicing
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-8306</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Investor Servicing component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are 12.0.1, 12.0.2,12.0.4,12.1.0 and 12.3.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Investor Servicing. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle FLEXCUBE Investor Servicing accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle FLEXCUBE Investor Servicing accessible data. CVSS v3.0 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-8306|2024-10-09T20:01:25.232Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-8315|2024-10-09T19:59:54.517Z -- oracle -- flexcube%20investor%20servicing
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-8315</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Investor Servicing component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Infrastructure Code). Supported versions that are affected are 12.0.1, 12.0.2,12.0.4,12.1.0 and 12.3.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Investor Servicing. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle FLEXCUBE Investor Servicing accessible data as well as unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle FLEXCUBE Investor Servicing accessible data. CVSS v3.0 Base Score 8.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-8315|2024-10-09T19:59:54.517Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-8309|2024-10-09T20:00:55.090Z -- oracle -- flexcube%20investor%20servicing
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-8309</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Investor Servicing component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are 12.0.1, 12.0.2,12.0.4,12.1.0 and 12.3.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Investor Servicing. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle FLEXCUBE Investor Servicing accessible data. CVSS v3.0 Base Score 4.3 (Confidentiality impacts).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-8309|2024-10-09T20:00:55.090Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-8319|2024-10-09T19:59:13.933Z -- oracle -- flexcube%20investor%20servicing
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-8319</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Investor Servicing component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are 12.0.1, 12.0.2,12.0.4,12.1.0 and 12.3.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Investor Servicing. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle FLEXCUBE Investor Servicing, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle FLEXCUBE Investor Servicing accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle FLEXCUBE Investor Servicing accessible data. CVSS v3.0 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-8319|2024-10-09T19:59:13.933Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-5509|2024-10-09T20:05:00.577Z -- oracle -- flexcube%20investor%20servicing
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-5509</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Investor Servicing component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are 12.0.1, 12.0.2,12.0.4,12.1.0 and 12.3.0. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Investor Servicing. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle FLEXCUBE Investor Servicing accessible data. CVSS v3.0 Base Score 3.1 (Confidentiality impacts).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-5509|2024-10-09T20:05:00.577Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-8317|2024-10-09T19:59:33.455Z -- oracle -- flexcube%20investor%20servicing
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-8317</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Investor Servicing component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Unit Trust). Supported versions that are affected are 12.0.1, 12.0.2,12.0.4,12.1.0 and 12.3.0. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Investor Servicing. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle FLEXCUBE Investor Servicing accessible data. CVSS v3.0 Base Score 5.3 (Integrity impacts).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-8317|2024-10-09T19:59:33.455Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
