<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle -- MySQL Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle/mysql%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle -- MySQL Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 20:23:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3257|2024-10-09T19:40:40.335Z -- oracle -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3257</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server component of Oracle MySQL (subcomponent: Server: InnoDB). Supported versions that are affected are 5.6.34 and earlier5.7.16 and earlier. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS v3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3257|2024-10-09T19:40:40.335Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3256|2024-10-09T19:40:55.196Z -- oracle -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3256</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server component of Oracle MySQL (subcomponent: Server: Replication). Supported versions that are affected are 5.7.16 and earlier. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS v3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3256|2024-10-09T19:40:55.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3258|2024-10-09T19:40:31.532Z -- oracle -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3258</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server component of Oracle MySQL (subcomponent: Server: DDL). Supported versions that are affected are 5.5.53 and earlier, 5.6.34 and earlier and 5.7.16 and earlier. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS v3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3258|2024-10-09T19:40:31.532Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3273|2024-10-09T19:36:25.726Z -- oracle -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3273</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server component of Oracle MySQL (subcomponent: Server: DDL). Supported versions that are affected are 5.6.34 and earlier and 5.7.16 and earlier. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS v3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3273|2024-10-09T19:36:25.726Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3251|2024-10-09T19:44:55.694Z -- oracle -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3251</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server component of Oracle MySQL (subcomponent: Server: Optimizer). Supported versions that are affected are 5.7.16 and earlier. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS v3.0 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3251|2024-10-09T19:44:55.694Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-8327|2024-10-09T19:55:41.512Z -- oracle -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-8327</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server component of Oracle MySQL (subcomponent: Server: Replication). Supported versions that are affected are 5.6.34 and earlier and 5.7.16 and earlier. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS v3.0 Base Score 4.4 (Availability impacts).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-8327|2024-10-09T19:55:41.512Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3238|2024-10-09T19:51:59.764Z -- oracle -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3238</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server component of Oracle MySQL (subcomponent: Server: Optimizer). Supported versions that are affected are 5.5.53 and earlier, 5.6.34 and earlier and 5.7.16 and earlier. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS v3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3238|2024-10-09T19:51:59.764Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3243|2024-10-09T19:50:26.152Z -- oracle -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3243</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server component of Oracle MySQL (subcomponent: Server: Charsets). Supported versions that are affected are 5.5.53 and earlier. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS v3.0 Base Score 4.4 (Availability impacts).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3243|2024-10-09T19:50:26.152Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-8318|2024-10-09T19:59:23.390Z -- oracle -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-8318</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server component of Oracle MySQL (subcomponent: Server: Security: Encryption). Supported versions that are affected are 5.6.34 and earlier and 5.7.16 and earlier. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in MySQL Server, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS v3.0 Base Score 6.8 (Availability impacts).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-8318|2024-10-09T19:59:23.390Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3265|2024-10-09T19:38:08.370Z -- oracle -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3265</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server component of Oracle MySQL (subcomponent: Server: Packaging). Supported versions that are affected are 5.5.53 and earlier, 5.6.34 and earlier and 5.7.16 and earlier. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where MySQL Server executes to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all MySQL Server accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS v3.0 Base Score 5.6 (Confidentiality and Availability impacts).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3265|2024-10-09T19:38:08.370Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3244|2024-10-09T19:50:06.509Z -- oracle -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3244</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server component of Oracle MySQL (subcomponent: Server: DML). Supported versions that are affected are 5.5.53 and earlier, 5.6.34 and earlier and 5.7.16 and earlier. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS v3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3244|2024-10-09T19:50:06.509Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
