<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle -- VM VirtualBox</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle/vm%20virtualbox.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle -- VM VirtualBox</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 20:23:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3332|2024-08-05T14:23:33.880Z -- oracle -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3332</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: VirtualBox SVGA Emulation). Supported versions that are affected are VirtualBox prior to 5.0.32 and prior to 5.1.14. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS v3.0 Base Score 8.4 (Integrity and Availability impacts).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3332|2024-08-05T14:23:33.880Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3316|2024-08-05T14:23:34.077Z -- oracle -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3316</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: GUI). Supported versions that are affected are VirtualBox prior to 5.0.32 and prior to 5.1.14. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS v3.0 Base Score 8.4 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3316|2024-08-05T14:23:34.077Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3290|2024-08-05T14:23:33.252Z -- oracle -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3290</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Shared Folder). Supported versions that are affected are VirtualBox prior to 5.0.32 and prior to 5.1.14. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS v3.0 Base Score 7.9 (Integrity and Availability impacts).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3290|2024-08-05T14:23:33.252Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
