<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SimpleMachines -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/simplemachines/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SimpleMachines -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:23:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7437|2024-08-06T14:24:08.526Z -- simplemachines -- smf
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7437</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SimpleMachines SMF 2.1.4. Affected is an unknown function of the file /index.php?action=profile;u=2;area=showalerts;do=remove of the component Delete User Handler. The manipulation of the argument aid leads to improper control of resource identifiers. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273522 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in SimpleMachines SMF 2.1.4 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei /index.php?action=profile;u=2;area=showalerts;do=remove der Komponente Delete User Handler. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments aid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine improper control of resource identifiers-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7437|2024-08-06T14:24:08.526Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 14:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7437|2024-08-03T14:31:04.930Z -- simplemachines -- smf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7437</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SimpleMachines SMF 2.1.4. Affected is an unknown function of the file /index.php?action=profile;u=2;area=showalerts;do=remove of the component Delete User Handler. The manipulation of the argument aid leads to improper control of resource identifiers. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273522 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in SimpleMachines SMF 2.1.4 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei /index.php?action=profile;u=2;area=showalerts;do=remove der Komponente Delete User Handler. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments aid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine improper control of resource identifiers-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7437|2024-08-03T14:31:04.930Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 14:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7438|2024-08-03T15:31:03.669Z -- simplemachines -- smf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7438</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in SimpleMachines SMF 2.1.4 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /index.php?action=profile;u=2;area=showalerts;do=read of the component User Alert Read Status Handler. The manipulation of the argument aid leads to improper control of resource identifiers. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273523. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In SimpleMachines SMF 2.1.4 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei /index.php?action=profile;u=2;area=showalerts;do=read der Komponente User Alert Read Status Handler. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments aid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine improper control of resource identifiers-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7438|2024-08-03T15:31:03.669Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 15:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
