<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for OpenSSL -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/openssl/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for OpenSSL -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 17:21:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-4160|2024-06-24T15:29:25.029Z -- openssl -- openssl
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4160</link>
      <description>There is a carry propagation bug in the MIPS32 and MIPS64 squaring procedure. Many EC algorithms are affected, including some of the TLS 1.3 default curves. Impact was not analyzed in detail, because the pre-requisites for attack are considered unlikely and include reusing private keys. Analysis suggests that attacks against RSA and DSA as a result of this defect would be very difficult to perform and are not believed likely. Attacks against DH are considered just feasible (although very difficult) because most of the work necessary to deduce information about a private key may be performed offline. The amount of resources required for such an attack would be significant. However, for an attack on TLS to be meaningful, the server would have to share the DH private key among multiple clients, which is no longer an option since CVE-2016-0701. This issue affects OpenSSL versions 1.0.2, 1.1.1 and 3.0.0. It was addressed in the releases of 1.1.1m and 3.0.1 on the 15th of December 2021. For the 1.0.2 release it is addressed in git commit 6fc1aaaf3 that is available to premium support customers only. It will be made available in 1.0.2zc when it is released. The issue only affects OpenSSL on MIPS platforms. Fixed in OpenSSL 3.0.1 (Affected 3.0.0). Fixed in OpenSSL 1.1.1m (Affected 1.1.1-1.1.1l). Fixed in OpenSSL 1.0.2zc-dev (Affected 1.0.2-1.0.2zb).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-4160|2024-06-24T15:29:25.029Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6129|2024-01-15T11:13:29.926Z -- openssl -- openssl</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6129</link>
      <description>Issue summary: The POLY1305 MAC (message authentication code) implementation
contains a bug that might corrupt the internal state of applications running
on PowerPC CPU based platforms if the CPU provides vector instructions.

Impact summary: If an attacker can influence whether the POLY1305 MAC
algorithm is used, the application state might be corrupted with various
application dependent consequences.

The POLY1305 MAC (message authentication code) implementation in OpenSSL for
PowerPC CPUs restores the contents of vector registers in a different order
than they are saved. Thus the contents of some of these vector registers
are corrupted when returning to the caller. The vulnerable code is used only
on newer PowerPC processors supporting the PowerISA 2.07 instructions.

The consequences of this kind of internal application state corruption can
be various - from no consequences, if the calling application does not
depend on the contents of non-volatile XMM registers at all, to the worst
consequences, where the attacker could get complete control of the application
process. However unless the compiler uses the vector registers for storing
pointers, the most likely consequence, if any, would be an incorrect result
of some application dependent calculations or a crash leading to a denial of
service.

The POLY1305 MAC algorithm is most frequently used as part of the
CHACHA20-POLY1305 AEAD (authenticated encryption with associated data)
algorithm. The most common usage of this AEAD cipher is with TLS protocol
versions 1.2 and 1.3. If this cipher is enabled on the server a malicious
client can influence whether this AEAD cipher is used. This implies that
TLS server applications using OpenSSL can be potentially impacted. However
we are currently not aware of any concrete application that would be affected
by this issue therefore we consider this a Low severity security issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6129|2024-01-15T11:13:29.926Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 16:36:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6237|2024-04-25T06:27:26.990Z -- openssl -- openssl</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6237</link>
      <description>Issue summary: Checking excessively long invalid RSA public keys may take
a long time.

Impact summary: Applications that use the function EVP_PKEY_public_check()
to check RSA public keys may experience long delays. Where the key that
is being checked has been obtained from an untrusted source this may lead
to a Denial of Service.

When function EVP_PKEY_public_check() is called on RSA public keys,
a computation is done to confirm that the RSA modulus, n, is composite.
For valid RSA keys, n is a product of two or more large primes and this
computation completes quickly. However, if n is an overly large prime,
then this computation would take a long time.

An application that calls EVP_PKEY_public_check() and supplies an RSA key
obtained from an untrusted source could be vulnerable to a Denial of Service
attack.

The function EVP_PKEY_public_check() is not called from other OpenSSL
functions however it is called from the OpenSSL pkey command line
application. For that reason that application is also vulnerable if used
with the '-pubin' and '-check' options on untrusted data.

The OpenSSL SSL/TLS implementation is not affected by this issue.

The OpenSSL 3.0 and 3.1 FIPS providers are affected by this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6237|2024-04-25T06:27:26.990Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 06:27:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0727|2024-01-26T08:57:19.579Z -- openssl -- openssl</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0727</link>
      <description>Issue summary: Processing a maliciously formatted PKCS12 file may lead OpenSSL
to crash leading to a potential Denial of Service attack

Impact summary: Applications loading files in the PKCS12 format from untrusted
sources might terminate abruptly.

A file in PKCS12 format can contain certificates and keys and may come from an
untrusted source. The PKCS12 specification allows certain fields to be NULL, but
OpenSSL does not correctly check for this case. This can lead to a NULL pointer
dereference that results in OpenSSL crashing. If an application processes PKCS12
files from an untrusted source using the OpenSSL APIs then that application will
be vulnerable to this issue.

OpenSSL APIs that are vulnerable to this are: PKCS12_parse(),
PKCS12_unpack_p7data(), PKCS12_unpack_p7encdata(), PKCS12_unpack_authsafes()
and PKCS12_newpass().

We have also fixed a similar issue in SMIME_write_PKCS7(). However since this
function is related to writing data we do not consider it security significant.

The FIPS modules in 3.2, 3.1 and 3.0 are not affected by this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0727|2024-01-26T08:57:19.579Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 08:57:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4603|2024-05-16T15:21:20.050Z -- openssl -- openssl</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4603</link>
      <description>Issue summary: Checking excessively long DSA keys or parameters may be very
slow.

Impact summary: Applications that use the functions EVP_PKEY_param_check()
or EVP_PKEY_public_check() to check a DSA public key or DSA parameters may
experience long delays. Where the key or parameters that are being checked
have been obtained from an untrusted source this may lead to a Denial of
Service.

The functions EVP_PKEY_param_check() or EVP_PKEY_public_check() perform
various checks on DSA parameters. Some of those computations take a long time
if the modulus (`p` parameter) is too large.

Trying to use a very large modulus is slow and OpenSSL will not allow using
public keys with a modulus which is over 10,000 bits in length for signature
verification. However the key and parameter check functions do not limit
the modulus size when performing the checks.

An application that calls EVP_PKEY_param_check() or EVP_PKEY_public_check()
and supplies a key or parameters obtained from an untrusted source could be
vulnerable to a Denial of Service attack.

These functions are not called by OpenSSL itself on untrusted DSA keys so
only applications that directly call these functions may be vulnerable.

Also vulnerable are the OpenSSL pkey and pkeyparam command line applications
when using the `-check` option.

The OpenSSL SSL/TLS implementation is not affected by this issue.

The OpenSSL 3.0 and 3.1 FIPS providers are affected by this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4603|2024-05-16T15:21:20.050Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 15:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2511|2024-06-04T17:30:50.015Z -- openssl -- openssl</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2511</link>
      <description>Issue summary: Some non-default TLS server configurations can cause unbounded
memory growth when processing TLSv1.3 sessions

Impact summary: An attacker may exploit certain server configurations to trigger
unbounded memory growth that would lead to a Denial of Service

This problem can occur in TLSv1.3 if the non-default SSL_OP_NO_TICKET option is
being used (but not if early_data support is also configured and the default
anti-replay protection is in use). In this case, under certain conditions, the
session cache can get into an incorrect state and it will fail to flush properly
as it fills. The session cache will continue to grow in an unbounded manner. A
malicious client could deliberately create the scenario for this failure to
force a Denial of Service. It may also happen by accident in normal operation.

This issue only affects TLS servers supporting TLSv1.3. It does not affect TLS
clients.

The FIPS modules in 3.2, 3.1 and 3.0 are not affected by this issue. OpenSSL
1.0.2 is also not affected by this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2511|2024-06-04T17:30:50.015Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 13:51:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
