<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for NixOS -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/nixos/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for NixOS -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 21:24:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-32657|2024-04-22T22:24:06.762Z -- NixOS -- hydra
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-32657</link><description>Hydra is a Continuous Integration service for Nix based projects. Attackers can execute arbitrary code in the browser context of Hydra and execute authenticated HTTP requests. The abused feature allows Nix builds to specify files that Hydra serves to clients. One use of this functionality is serving NixOS `.iso` files. The issue is only with html files served by Hydra. The issue has been patched on https://hydra.nixos.org around 2024-04-21 14:30 UTC. The nixpkgs package were fixed in unstable and 23.11. Users with custom Hydra packages can apply the fix commit to their local installations. The vulnerability is only triggered when opening HTML build artifacts, so not opening them until the vulnerability is fixed works around the issue.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32657|2024-04-22T22:24:06.762Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 22:24:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27297|2024-03-11T21:25:51.065Z -- NixOS -- nix
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27297</link><description>Nix is a package manager for Linux and other Unix systems. A fixed-output derivations on Linux can send file descriptors to files in the Nix store to another program running on the host (or another fixed-output derivation) via Unix domain sockets in the abstract namespace. This allows to modify the output of the derivation, after Nix has registered the path as "valid" and immutable in the Nix database. In particular, this allows the output of fixed-output derivations to be modified from their expected content. This issue has been addressed in versions 2.3.18 2.18.2 2.19.4 and 2.20.5. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27297|2024-03-11T21:25:51.065Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 21:24:43 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>