<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for TrackR -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/trackr/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for TrackR -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 08:23:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6541|2024-08-06T01:36:27.330Z -- trackr -- bravo%20mobile%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6541</link>
      <description>TrackR Bravo device allows unauthenticated pairing, which enables unauthenticated connected applications to write to various device attributes. Updated apps, version 5.1.6 for iOS and 2.2.5 for Android, have been released by the vendor to address the vulnerabilities in CVE-2016-6538, CVE-2016-6539, CVE-2016-6540 and CVE-2016-6541.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6541|2024-08-06T01:36:27.330Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6539|2024-08-06T01:36:27.350Z -- trackr -- bravo%20mobile%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6539</link>
      <description>The Trackr device ID is constructed of a manufacturer identifier of four zeroes followed by the BLE MAC address in reverse. The MAC address can be obtained by being in close proximity to the Bluetooth device, effectively exposing the device ID. The ID can be used to track devices. Updated apps, version 5.1.6 for iOS and 2.2.5 for Android, have been released by the vendor to address the vulnerabilities in CVE-2016-6538, CVE-2016-6539, CVE-2016-6540 and CVE-2016-6541.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6539|2024-08-06T01:36:27.350Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6538|2024-08-06T01:36:27.362Z -- trackr -- bravo%20mobile%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6538</link>
      <description>The TrackR Bravo mobile app stores the account password used to authenticate to the cloud API in cleartext in the cache.db file. Updated apps, version 5.1.6 for iOS and 2.2.5 for Android, have been released by the vendor to address the vulnerabilities in CVE-2016-6538, CVE-2016-6539, CVE-2016-6540 and CVE-2016-6541.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6538|2024-08-06T01:36:27.362Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6540|2024-08-06T01:36:27.351Z -- trackr -- bravo%20mobile%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6540</link>
      <description>Unauthenticated access to the cloud-based service maintained by TrackR Bravo is allowed for querying or sending GPS data for any Trackr device by using the tracker ID number which can be discovered as described in CVE-2016-6539. Updated apps, version 5.1.6 for iOS and 2.2.5 for Android, have been released by the vendor to address the vulnerabilities in CVE-2016-6538, CVE-2016-6539, CVE-2016-6540 and CVE-2016-6541.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6540|2024-08-06T01:36:27.351Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
