<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for hedgedoc -- hedgedoc</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/hedgedoc/hedgedoc.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for hedgedoc -- hedgedoc</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 19:19:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21259|2024-08-03T18:09:14.988Z -- hedgedoc -- hedgedoc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21259</link>
      <description>HedgeDoc is open source software which lets you create real-time collaborative markdown notes. In HedgeDoc before version 1.7.2, an attacker can inject arbitrary JavaScript into a HedgeDoc note, which is executed when the note is viewed in slide mode. Depending on the configuration of the instance, the attacker may not need authentication to create or edit notes. The problem is patched in HedgeDoc 1.7.2. As a workaround, disallow loading JavaScript from 3rd party sites using the `Content-Security-Policy` header. Note that this will break some embedded content.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21259|2024-08-03T18:09:14.988Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 17:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24837|2024-08-03T04:20:50.602Z -- hedgedoc -- hedgedoc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24837</link>
      <description>HedgeDoc is an open-source, web-based, self-hosted, collaborative markdown editor. Images uploaded with HedgeDoc version 1.9.1 and later have an enumerable filename after the upload, resulting in potential information leakage of uploaded documents. This is especially relevant for private notes and affects all upload backends, except Lutim and imgur. This issue is patched in version 1.9.3 by replacing the filename generation with UUIDv4. If you cannot upgrade to HedgeDoc 1.9.3, it is possible to block POST requests to `/uploadimage`, which will disable future uploads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24837|2024-08-03T04:20:50.602Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 20:20:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
