<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Elastic -- Beats</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/elastic/beats.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Elastic -- Beats</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-49922|2023-12-12T18:23:32.489Z -- elastic -- beats
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-49922</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered by Elastic whereby Beats and Elastic Agent would log a raw event in its own logs at the WARN or ERROR level if ingesting that event to Elasticsearch failed with any 4xx HTTP status code except 409 or 429. Depending on the nature of the event that Beats or Elastic Agent attempted to ingest, this could lead to the insertion of sensitive or private information in the Beats or Elastic Agent logs. Elastic has released 8.11.3 and 7.17.16 that prevents this issue by limiting these types of logs to DEBUG level logging, which is disabled by default.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-49922|2023-12-12T18:23:32.489Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 18:23:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31421|2023-10-26T03:10:52.684Z -- elastic -- beats
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-31421</link>
      <description>It was discovered that when acting as TLS clients, Beats, Elastic Agent, APM Server, and Fleet Server did not verify whether the server certificate is valid for the target IP address; however, certificate signature validation is still performed. More specifically, when the client is configured to connect to an IP address (instead of a hostname) it does not validate the server certificate's IP SAN values against that IP address and certificate validation fails, and therefore the connection is not blocked as expected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31421|2023-10-26T03:10:52.684Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 03:10:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
