<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Elastic -- Elasticsearch</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/elastic/elasticsearch.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Elastic -- Elasticsearch</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-46673|2023-11-22T09:27:10.454Z -- elastic -- elasticsearch
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-46673</link>
      <description>It was identified that malformed scripts used in the script processor of an Ingest Pipeline could cause an Elasticsearch node to crash when calling the Simulate Pipeline API.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-46673|2023-11-22T09:27:10.454Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 09:27:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31418|2023-10-26T17:36:42.723Z -- elastic -- elasticsearch
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-31418</link>
      <description>An issue has been identified with how Elasticsearch handled incoming requests on the HTTP layer. An unauthenticated user could force an Elasticsearch node to exit with an OutOfMemory error by sending a moderate number of malformed HTTP requests. The issue was identified by Elastic Engineering and we have no indication that the issue is known or that it is being exploited in the wild.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31418|2023-10-26T17:36:42.723Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 17:36:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31419|2023-10-26T18:49:20.424Z -- elastic -- elasticsearch
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-31419</link>
      <description>A flaw was discovered in Elasticsearch, affecting the _search API that allowed a specially crafted query string to cause a Stack Overflow and ultimately a Denial of Service.




</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31419|2023-10-26T18:49:20.424Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 17:06:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31417|2023-10-26T17:47:37.065Z -- elastic -- elasticsearch
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-31417</link>
      <description>Elasticsearch generally filters out sensitive information and credentials before logging to the audit log. It was found that this filtering was not applied when requests to Elasticsearch use certain deprecated URIs for APIs. The impact of this flaw is that sensitive information such as passwords and tokens might be printed in cleartext in Elasticsearch audit logs. Note that audit logging is disabled by default and needs to be explicitly enabled and even when audit logging is enabled, request bodies that could contain sensitive information are not printed to the audit log unless explicitly configured.




</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31417|2023-10-26T17:47:37.065Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 17:47:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23449|2024-03-29T11:12:49.067Z -- elastic -- elasticsearch
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23449</link>
      <description>An uncaught exception in Elasticsearch &gt;= 8.4.0 and &lt; 8.11.1 occurs when an encrypted PDF is passed to an attachment processor through the REST API. The Elasticsearch ingest node that attempts to parse the PDF file will crash. This does not happen with password-protected PDF files or with unencrypted PDF files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23449|2024-03-29T11:12:49.067Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 11:12:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23451|2024-03-27T18:03:54.735Z -- elastic -- elasticsearch
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23451</link>
      <description>Incorrect Authorization issue exists in the API key based security model for Remote Cluster Security, which is currently in Beta, in Elasticsearch 8.10.0 and before 8.13.0. This allows a malicious user with a valid API key for a remote cluster configured to use the new Remote Cluster Security to read arbitrary documents from any index on the remote cluster, and only if they use the Elasticsearch custom transport protocol to issue requests with the target index ID, the shard ID and the document ID. None of Elasticsearch REST API endpoints are affected by this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23451|2024-03-27T18:03:54.735Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 18:03:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23450|2024-03-27T17:03:48.290Z -- elastic -- elasticsearch
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23450</link>
      <description>A flaw was discovered in Elasticsearch, where processing a document in a deeply nested pipeline on an ingest node could cause the Elasticsearch node to crash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23450|2024-03-27T17:03:48.290Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:03:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
