<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Elastic -- Kibana</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/elastic/kibana.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Elastic -- Kibana</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-46671|2023-12-13T06:57:59.826Z -- elastic -- kibana
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-46671</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered by Elastic whereby sensitive information may be recorded in Kibana logs in the event of an error. Elastic has released Kibana 8.11.1 which resolves this issue. The error message recorded in the log may contain account credentials for the kibana_system user, API Keys, and credentials of Kibana end-users. The issue occurs infrequently, only if an error is returned from an Elasticsearch cluster, in cases where there is user interaction and an unhealthy cluster (for example, when returning circuit breaker or no shard exceptions).
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-46671|2023-12-13T06:57:59.826Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 06:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-46675|2023-12-13T07:02:07.706Z -- elastic -- kibana
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-46675</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered by Elastic whereby sensitive information may be recorded in Kibana logs in the event of an error or in the event where debug level logging is enabled in Kibana. Elastic has released Kibana 8.11.2 which resolves this issue. The messages recorded in the log may contain Account credentials for the kibana_system user, API Keys, and credentials of Kibana end-users, Elastic Security package policy objects which can contain private keys, bearer token, and sessions of 3rd-party integrations and finally Authorization headers, client secrets, local file paths, and stack traces. The issue may occur in any Kibana instance running an affected version that could potentially receive an unexpected error when communicating to Elasticsearch causing it to include sensitive data into Kibana error logs. It could also occur under specific circumstances when debug level logging is enabled in Kibana. Note: It was found that the fix for ESA-2023-25 in Kibana 8.11.1 for a similar issue was incomplete.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-46675|2023-12-13T07:02:07.706Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 07:02:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31422|2023-10-26T01:43:54.868Z -- elastic -- kibana
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-31422</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered by Elastic whereby sensitive information is recorded in Kibana logs in the event of an error. The issue impacts only Kibana version 8.10.0 when logging in the JSON layout or when the pattern layout is configured to log the %meta pattern. Elastic has released Kibana 8.10.1 which resolves this issue. The error object recorded in the log contains request information, which can include sensitive data, such as authentication credentials, cookies, authorization headers, query params, request paths, and other metadata. Some examples of sensitive data which can be included in the logs are account credentials for kibana_system, kibana-metricbeat, or Kibana end-users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31422|2023-10-26T01:43:54.868Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 01:43:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31414|2023-05-04T00:00:00 -- elastic -- kibana
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-31414</link>
      <description>Kibana versions 8.0.0 through 8.7.0 contain an arbitrary code execution flaw. An attacker with write access to Kibana yaml or env configuration could add a specific payload that will attempt to execute JavaScript code. This could lead to the attacker executing arbitrary commands on the host system with permissions of the Kibana process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31414|2023-05-04T00:00:00</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31415|2023-05-04T00:00:00 -- elastic -- kibana
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-31415</link>
      <description>Kibana version 8.7.0 contains an arbitrary code execution flaw. An attacker with All privileges to the Uptime/Synthetics feature could send a request that will attempt to execute JavaScript code. This could lead to the attacker executing arbitrary commands on the host system with permissions of the Kibana process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31415|2023-05-04T00:00:00</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23446|2024-02-07T03:16:39.182Z -- elastic -- kibana
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23446</link>
      <description>An issue was discovered by Elastic, whereby the Detection Engine Search API does not respect Document-level security (DLS) or Field-level security (FLS) when querying the .alerts-security.alerts-{space_id} indices. Users who are authorized to call this API may obtain unauthorized access to documents if their roles are configured with DLS or FLS against the aforementioned index.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23446|2024-02-07T03:16:39.182Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 03:16:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
