<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Elastic -- X-Pack Security</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/elastic/x-pack%20security.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Elastic -- X-Pack Security</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 17:22:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8438|2024-08-05T16:34:22.961Z -- elastic -- x-pack%20security
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8438</link>
      <description>Elastic X-Pack Security versions 5.0.0 to 5.4.0 contain a privilege escalation bug in the run_as functionality. This bug prevents transitioning into the specified user specified in a run_as request. If a role has been created using a template that contains the _user properties, the behavior of run_as will be incorrect. Additionally if the run_as user specified does not exist, the transition will not happen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8438|2024-08-05T16:34:22.961Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8441|2024-08-05T16:34:22.945Z -- elastic -- x-pack%20security
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8441</link>
      <description>Elastic X-Pack Security versions prior to 5.4.1 and 5.3.3 did not always correctly apply Document Level Security to index aliases. This bug could allow a user with restricted permissions to view data they should not have access to when performing certain operations against an index alias.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8441|2024-08-05T16:34:22.945Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3822|2024-08-05T04:57:23.752Z -- elastic -- x-pack%20security
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3822</link>
      <description>X-Pack Security versions 6.2.0, 6.2.1, and 6.2.2 are vulnerable to a user impersonation attack via incorrect XML canonicalization and DOM traversal. An attacker might have been able to impersonate a legitimate user if the SAML Identity Provider allows for self registration with arbitrary identifiers and the attacker can register an account which an identifier that shares a suffix with a legitimate account. Both of those conditions must be true in order to exploit this flaw.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3822|2024-08-05T04:57:23.752Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
