<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for OpenText -- Visual COBOL, COBOL Server, Enterprise Developer, Enterprise Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/opentext/visual%20cobol%2C%20cobol%20server%2C%20enterprise%20developer%2C%20enterprise%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for OpenText -- Visual COBOL, COBOL Server, Enterprise Developer, Enterprise Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 19:20:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4501|2024-09-26T14:08:41.901Z -- opentext -- visual%20cobol%2C%20cobol%20server%2C%20enterprise%20developer%2C%20enterprise%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4501</link>
      <description>User authentication with username and password credentials is ineffective in OpenText (Micro Focus) Visual COBOL, COBOL Server, Enterprise Developer, and Enterprise Server (including product variants such as Enterprise Test Server), versions 7.0 patch updates 19 and 20, 8.0 patch updates 8 and 9, and 9.0 patch update 1, when LDAP-based authentication is used with certain configurations. When the vulnerability is active, authentication succeeds with any valid username, regardless of whether the password is correct; it may also succeed with an invalid username (and any password). This allows an attacker with access to the product to impersonate any user.

Mitigations: The issue is corrected in the upcoming patch update for each affected product. Product overlays and workaround instructions are available through OpenText Support. The vulnerable configurations are believed to be uncommon.

Administrators can test for the vulnerability in their installations by attempting to sign on to a Visual COBOL or Enterprise Server component such as ESCWA using a valid username and incorrect password.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4501|2024-09-26T14:08:41.901Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 18:05:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
