<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for rmountjoy92 -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/rmountjoy92/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for rmountjoy92 -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6899|2023-12-17T12:31:04.408Z -- rmountjoy92 -- dashmachine
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6899</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in rmountjoy92 DashMachine 0.5-4. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /settings/save_config of the component Config Handler. The manipulation of the argument value_template leads to code injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-248257 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In rmountjoy92 DashMachine 0.5-4 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei /settings/save_config der Komponente Config Handler. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments value_template mit unbekannten Daten kann eine code injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6899|2023-12-17T12:31:04.408Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 12:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6900|2023-12-17T13:31:04.489Z -- rmountjoy92 -- dashmachine
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6900</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in rmountjoy92 DashMachine 0.5-4. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /settings/delete_file. The manipulation of the argument file leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-248258 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in rmountjoy92 DashMachine 0.5-4 entdeckt. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei /settings/delete_file. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments file mit unbekannten Daten kann eine path traversal: '../filedir'-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6900|2023-12-17T13:31:04.489Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 13:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
