<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Xiamen Four-Faith -- Video Surveillance Management System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/xiamen%20four-faith/video%20surveillance%20management%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Xiamen Four-Faith -- Video Surveillance Management System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 19:20:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6308|2024-08-02T08:28:21.827Z -- xiamen%20four-faith -- video%20surveillance%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6308</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Xiamen Four-Faith Video Surveillance Management System 2016/2017. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Apache Struts. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-246134 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Xiamen Four-Faith Video Surveillance Management System 2016/2017 entdeckt. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Komponente Apache Struts. Durch das Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6308|2024-08-02T08:28:21.827Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 01:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
