<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for kalcaddle -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/kalcaddle/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for kalcaddle -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 17:22:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6850|2024-08-02T08:42:08.339Z -- kalcaddle -- kodexplorer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6850</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in kalcaddle KodExplorer up to 4.51.03. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /index.php?pluginApp/to/yzOffice/getFile of the component API Endpoint Handler. The manipulation of the argument path/file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 4.52.01 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as 5cf233f7556b442100cf67b5e92d57ceabb126c6. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-248218 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In kalcaddle KodExplorer bis 4.51.03 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei /index.php?pluginApp/to/yzOffice/getFile der Komponente API Endpoint Handler. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments path/file mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 4.52.01 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als 5cf233f7556b442100cf67b5e92d57ceabb126c6 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6850|2024-08-02T08:42:08.339Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 08:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6848|2024-08-02T08:42:07.684Z -- kalcaddle -- kodbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6848</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in kalcaddle kodbox up to 1.48. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function check of the file plugins/officeViewer/controller/libreOffice/index.class.php. The manipulation of the argument soffice leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 1.48.04 is able to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is 63a4d5708d210f119c24afd941d01a943e25334c. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-248209 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In kalcaddle kodbox bis 1.48 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Hierbei betrifft es die Funktion check der Datei plugins/officeViewer/controller/libreOffice/index.class.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments soffice mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 1.48.04 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als 63a4d5708d210f119c24afd941d01a943e25334c bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6848|2024-08-02T08:42:07.684Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 06:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6851|2024-08-02T08:42:07.941Z -- kalcaddle -- kodexplorer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6851</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in kalcaddle KodExplorer up to 4.51.03. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function unzipList of the file plugins/zipView/app.php of the component ZIP Archive Handler. The manipulation leads to code injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 4.52.01 is able to address this issue. The patch is named 5cf233f7556b442100cf67b5e92d57ceabb126c6. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248219.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in kalcaddle KodExplorer bis 4.51.03 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei geht es um die Funktion unzipList der Datei plugins/zipView/app.php der Komponente ZIP Archive Handler. Durch Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine code injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 4.52.01 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als 5cf233f7556b442100cf67b5e92d57ceabb126c6 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6851|2024-08-02T08:42:07.941Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6852|2024-08-02T08:42:07.824Z -- kalcaddle -- kodexplorer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6852</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in kalcaddle KodExplorer up to 4.51.03. Affected is an unknown function of the file plugins/webodf/app.php. The manipulation leads to server-side request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 4.52.01 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is 5cf233f7556b442100cf67b5e92d57ceabb126c6. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248220.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in kalcaddle KodExplorer bis 4.51.03 entdeckt. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei plugins/webodf/app.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine server-side request forgery-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 4.52.01 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als 5cf233f7556b442100cf67b5e92d57ceabb126c6 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6852|2024-08-02T08:42:07.824Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 11:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6849|2024-08-02T08:42:07.932Z -- kalcaddle -- kodbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6849</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in kalcaddle kodbox up to 1.48. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function cover of the file plugins/fileThumb/app.php. The manipulation of the argument path leads to server-side request forgery. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 1.48.04 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as 63a4d5708d210f119c24afd941d01a943e25334c. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-248210 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in kalcaddle kodbox bis 1.48 ausgemacht. Davon betroffen ist die Funktion cover der Datei plugins/fileThumb/app.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments path mit unbekannten Daten kann eine server-side request forgery-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 1.48.04 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als 63a4d5708d210f119c24afd941d01a943e25334c bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6849|2024-08-02T08:42:07.932Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 08:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6853|2024-08-02T08:42:07.690Z -- kalcaddle -- kodexplorer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6853</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in kalcaddle KodExplorer up to 4.51.03. Affected by this vulnerability is the function index of the file plugins/officeLive/app.php. The manipulation of the argument path leads to server-side request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 4.52.01 is able to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is 5cf233f7556b442100cf67b5e92d57ceabb126c6. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-248221 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In kalcaddle KodExplorer bis 4.51.03 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Das betrifft die Funktion index der Datei plugins/officeLive/app.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments path mit unbekannten Daten kann eine server-side request forgery-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 4.52.01 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als 5cf233f7556b442100cf67b5e92d57ceabb126c6 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6853|2024-08-02T08:42:07.690Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 12:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
