<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Facebook -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/facebook/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Facebook -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 19:19:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28081|2024-08-02T12:30:23.821Z -- facebook -- hermes
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28081</link>
      <description>A bytecode optimization bug in Hermes prior to commit e6ed9c1a4b02dc219de1648f44cd808a56171b81 could be used to cause an use-after-free and obtain arbitrary code execution via a carefully crafted payload. Note that this is only exploitable in cases where Hermes is used to execute untrusted JavaScript. Hence, most React Native applications are not affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28081|2024-08-02T12:30:23.821Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 21:26:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25933|2024-08-02T11:39:05.316Z -- facebook -- hermes
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25933</link>
      <description>A type confusion bug in TypedArray prior to commit e6ed9c1a4b02dc219de1648f44cd808a56171b81 could have been used by a malicious attacker to execute arbitrary code via untrusted JavaScript. Note that this is only exploitable in cases where Hermes is used to execute untrusted JavaScript. Hence, most React Native applications are not affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25933|2024-08-02T11:39:05.316Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 21:24:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38538|2024-08-02T17:46:56.586Z -- facebook -- whatsapp%20desktop%20for%20mac
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38538</link>
      <description>A race condition in an event subsystem led to a heap use-after-free issue in established audio/video calls that could have resulted in app termination or unexpected control flow with very low probability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38538|2024-08-02T17:46:56.586Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 19:10:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-23556|2024-08-02T10:35:32.836Z -- facebook -- hermes
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23556</link>
      <description>An error in BigInt conversion to Number in Hermes prior to commit a6dcafe6ded8e61658b40f5699878cd19a481f80 could have been used by a malicious attacker to execute arbitrary code due to an out-of-bound write. Note that this bug is only exploitable in cases where Hermes is used to execute untrusted JavaScript. Hence, most React Native applications are not affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-23556|2024-08-02T10:35:32.836Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 21:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-23759|2024-08-02T10:42:25.872Z -- facebook -- fizz
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23759</link>
      <description>There is a vulnerability in the fizz library prior to v2023.01.30.00 where a CHECK failure can be triggered remotely. This behavior requires the client supported cipher advertisement changing between the original ClientHello and the second ClientHello, crashing the process (impact is limited to denial of service).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-23759|2024-08-02T10:42:25.872Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 21:21:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-30470|2024-08-02T14:28:50.599Z -- facebook -- hermes
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30470</link>
      <description>A use-after-free related to unsound inference in the bytecode generation when optimizations are enabled for Hermes prior to commit da8990f737ebb9d9810633502f65ed462b819c09 could have been used by an attacker to achieve remote code execution. Note that this is only exploitable in cases where Hermes is used to execute untrusted JavaScript. Hence, most React Native applications are not affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-30470|2024-08-02T14:28:50.599Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 21:27:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28753|2024-08-02T13:51:37.299Z -- facebook -- netconsd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28753</link>
      <description>netconsd prior to v0.2 was vulnerable to an integer overflow in its parse_packet function. A malicious individual could leverage this overflow to create heap memory corruption with attacker controlled data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28753|2024-08-02T13:51:37.299Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 21:27:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-24832|2024-08-02T11:03:19.354Z -- facebook -- hermes
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24832</link>
      <description>A null pointer dereference bug in Hermes prior to commit 5cae9f72975cf0e5a62b27fdd8b01f103e198708 could have been used by an attacker to crash an Hermes runtime where the EnableHermesInternal config option was set to true. Note that this is only exploitable in cases where Hermes is used to execute untrusted JavaScript. Hence, most React Native applications are not affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-24832|2024-08-02T11:03:19.354Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 21:24:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-24833|2024-08-02T11:03:19.301Z -- facebook -- hermes
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24833</link>
      <description>A use-after-free in BigIntPrimitive addition in Hermes prior to commit a6dcafe6ded8e61658b40f5699878cd19a481f80 could have been used by an attacker to leak raw data from Hermes VM’s heap. Note that this is only exploitable in cases where Hermes is used to execute untrusted JavaScript. Hence, most React Native applications are not affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-24833|2024-08-02T11:03:19.301Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 21:24:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-23557|2024-08-02T10:35:33.573Z -- facebook -- hermes
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23557</link>
      <description>An error in Hermes' algorithm for copying objects properties prior to commit a00d237346894c6067a594983be6634f4168c9ad could be used by a malicious attacker to execute arbitrary code via type confusion. Note that this is only exploitable in cases where Hermes is used to execute untrusted JavaScript. Hence, most React Native applications are not affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-23557|2024-08-02T10:35:33.573Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 21:19:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38537|2024-08-02T17:46:56.022Z -- facebook -- whatsapp%20desktop%20for%20mac
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38537</link>
      <description>A race condition in a network transport subsystem led to a heap use-after-free issue in established or unsilenced incoming audio/video calls that could have resulted in app termination or unexpected control flow with very low probability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38537|2024-08-02T17:46:56.022Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 19:09:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
