<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Facebook -- Facebook Thrift</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/facebook/facebook%20thrift.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Facebook -- Facebook Thrift</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 20:22:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3565|2024-08-04T19:12:09.598Z -- facebook -- facebook%20thrift
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3565</link>
      <description>Legacy C++ Facebook Thrift servers (using cpp instead of cpp2) would not error upon receiving messages with containers of fields of unknown type. As a result, malicious clients could send short messages which would take a long time for the server to parse, potentially leading to denial of service. This issue affects Facebook Thrift prior to v2019.05.06.00.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3565|2024-08-04T19:12:09.598Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 15:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3564|2024-08-04T19:12:09.508Z -- facebook -- facebook%20thrift
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3564</link>
      <description>Go Facebook Thrift servers would not error upon receiving messages with containers of fields of unknown type. As a result, malicious clients could send short messages which would take a long time for the server to parse, potentially leading to denial of service. This issue affects Facebook Thrift prior to v2019.03.04.00.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3564|2024-08-04T19:12:09.508Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 15:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3559|2024-08-04T19:12:09.476Z -- facebook -- facebook%20thrift
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3559</link>
      <description>Java Facebook Thrift servers would not error upon receiving messages with containers of fields of unknown type. As a result, malicious clients could send short messages which would take a long time for the server to parse, potentially leading to denial of service. This issue affects Facebook Thrift prior to v2019.02.18.00.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3559|2024-08-04T19:12:09.476Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 15:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3553|2024-08-04T19:12:09.503Z -- facebook -- facebook%20thrift
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3553</link>
      <description>C++ Facebook Thrift servers would not error upon receiving messages declaring containers of sizes larger than the payload. As a result, malicious clients could send short messages which would result in a large memory allocation, potentially leading to denial of service. This issue affects Facebook Thrift prior to v2020.02.03.00.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3553|2024-08-04T19:12:09.503Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 20:30:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3552|2024-08-04T19:12:09.356Z -- facebook -- facebook%20thrift
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3552</link>
      <description>C++ Facebook Thrift servers (using cpp2) would not error upon receiving messages with containers of fields of unknown type. As a result, malicious clients could send short messages which would take a long time for the server to parse, potentially leading to denial of service. This issue affects Facebook Thrift prior to v2019.02.18.00.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3552|2024-08-04T19:12:09.356Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 15:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3558|2024-08-04T19:12:09.557Z -- facebook -- facebook%20thrift
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3558</link>
      <description>Python Facebook Thrift servers would not error upon receiving messages with containers of fields of unknown type. As a result, malicious clients could send short messages which would take a long time for the server to parse, potentially leading to denial of service. This issue affects Facebook Thrift prior to v2019.02.18.00.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3558|2024-08-04T19:12:09.557Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 15:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
