<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for swagger-api -- swagger-codegen</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/swagger-api/swagger-codegen.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for swagger-api -- swagger-codegen</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 23:23:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21363|2024-08-03T18:09:16.080Z -- swagger-api -- swagger-codegen
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21363</link>
      <description>swagger-codegen is an open-source project which contains a template-driven engine to generate documentation, API clients and server stubs in different languages by parsing your OpenAPI / Swagger definition. In swagger-codegen before version 2.4.19, on Unix like systems, the system's temporary directory is shared between all users on that system. A collocated user can observe the process of creating a temporary sub directory in the shared temporary directory and race to complete the creation of the temporary subdirectory. This vulnerability is local privilege escalation because the contents of the `outputFolder` can be appended to by an attacker. As such, code written to this directory, when executed can be attacker controlled. For more details refer to the referenced GitHub Security Advisory. This vulnerability is fixed in version 2.4.19. Note this is a distinct vulnerability from CVE-2021-21364.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21363|2024-08-03T18:09:16.080Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 03:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21364|2024-08-03T18:09:15.938Z -- swagger-api -- swagger-codegen
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21364</link>
      <description>swagger-codegen is an open-source project which contains a template-driven engine to generate documentation, API clients and server stubs in different languages by parsing your OpenAPI / Swagger definition. In swagger-codegen before version 2.4.19, on Unix-Like systems, the system temporary directory is shared between all local users. When files/directories are created, the default `umask` settings for the process are respected. As a result, by default, most processes/apis will create files/directories with the permissions `-rw-r--r--` and `drwxr-xr-x` respectively, unless an API that explicitly sets safe file permissions is used. Because this vulnerability impacts generated code, the generated code will remain vulnerable until fixed manually! This vulnerability is fixed in version 2.4.19. Note this is a distinct vulnerability from CVE-2021-21363.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21364|2024-08-03T18:09:15.938Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 03:05:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
