<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for OpenCV -- wechat_qrcode Module</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/opencv/wechat_qrcode%20module.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for OpenCV -- wechat_qrcode Module</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 09:23:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2617|2024-08-02T06:26:09.731Z -- opencv -- wechat_qrcode%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2617</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in OpenCV wechat_qrcode Module up to 4.7.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function DecodedBitStreamParser::decodeByteSegment of the file qrcode/decoder/decoded_bit_stream_parser.cpp. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-228547.
In OpenCV wechat_qrcode Module bis 4.7.0 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Betroffen ist die Funktion DecodedBitStreamParser::decodeByteSegment der Datei qrcode/decoder/decoded_bit_stream_parser.cpp. Dank der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine null pointer dereference-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2617|2024-08-02T06:26:09.731Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 05:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2618|2024-08-02T06:26:10.033Z -- opencv -- wechat_qrcode%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2618</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in OpenCV wechat_qrcode Module up to 4.7.0. Affected by this issue is the function DecodedBitStreamParser::decodeHanziSegment of the file qrcode/decoder/decoded_bit_stream_parser.cpp. The manipulation leads to memory leak. The attack may be launched remotely. The name of the patch is 2b62ff6181163eea029ed1cab11363b4996e9cd6. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-228548.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in OpenCV wechat_qrcode Module bis 4.7.0 entdeckt. Betroffen davon ist die Funktion DecodedBitStreamParser::decodeHanziSegment der Datei qrcode/decoder/decoded_bit_stream_parser.cpp. Dank Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine memory leak-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Patch wird als 2b62ff6181163eea029ed1cab11363b4996e9cd6 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2618|2024-08-02T06:26:10.033Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 05:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
