<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for oferwald -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oferwald/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for oferwald -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 14:22:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2462|2024-08-03T00:39:07.647Z -- oferwald -- transposh%20wordpress%20translation
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2462</link>
      <description>The Transposh WordPress Translation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to sensitive information disclosure to unauthenticated users in versions up to, and including, 1.0.8.1. This is due to insufficient permissions checking on the 'tp_history' AJAX action and insufficient restriction on the data returned in the response. This makes it possible for unauthenticated users to exfiltrate usernames of individuals who have translated text.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2462|2024-08-03T00:39:07.647Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 17:18:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2536|2024-08-03T00:39:08.222Z -- oferwald -- transposh%20wordpress%20translation
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2536</link>
      <description>The Transposh WordPress Translation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized setting changes by unauthenticated users in versions up to, and including, 1.0.8.1. This is due to insufficient validation of settings on the 'tp_translation' AJAX action which makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass any restrictions and influence the data shown on the site. Please note this is a separate issue from CVE-2022-2461. &#13;
&#13;
Notes from the researcher: When installed Transposh comes with a set of pre-configured options, one of these is the "Who can translate" setting under the "Settings" tab. However, this option is largely ignored, if Transposh has enabled its "autotranslate" feature (it's enabled by default) and the HTTP POST parameter "sr0" is larger than 0. This is caused by a faulty validation in "wp/transposh_db.php."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2536|2024-08-03T00:39:08.222Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 04:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2461|2024-08-03T00:39:07.801Z -- oferwald -- transposh%20wordpress%20translation
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2461</link>
      <description>The Transposh WordPress Translation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized setting changes by unauthenticated users in versions up to, and including, 1.0.8.1. This is due to insufficient permissions checking on the 'tp_translation' AJAX action and default settings which makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to influence the data shown on the site.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2461|2024-08-03T00:39:07.801Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 17:18:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
