<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for ISS -- BlackICE PC Protection</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/iss/blackice%20pc%20protection.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for ISS -- BlackICE PC Protection</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 04:24:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2003-5003|2024-08-08T02:35:17.306Z -- iss -- blackice%20pc%20protection
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2003-5003</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in ISS BlackICE PC Protection. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is the Update Handler. The manipulation with an unknown input leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2003-5003|2024-08-08T02:35:17.306Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 20:45:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2003-5002|2024-08-08T02:35:16.644Z -- iss -- blackice%20pc%20protection
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2003-5002</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in ISS BlackICE PC Protection. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the component Update Handler which allows cleartext transmission of data. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2003-5002|2024-08-08T02:35:16.644Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 20:45:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2003-5001|2024-08-08T02:35:17.270Z -- iss -- blackice%20pc%20protection
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2003-5001</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in ISS BlackICE PC Protection and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the component Cross Site Scripting Detection. The manipulation as part of POST/PUT/DELETE/OPTIONS Request leads to privilege escalation. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2003-5001|2024-08-08T02:35:17.270Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 20:45:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
