<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for capnsquarepants -- wordcraft</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/capnsquarepants/wordcraft.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for capnsquarepants -- wordcraft</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:23:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2009-10003|2024-08-07T07:32:23.777Z -- capnsquarepants -- wordcraft
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2009-10003</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in capnsquarepants wordcraft up to 0.6. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file tag.php. The manipulation of the argument tag leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 0.7 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as be23028633e8105de92f387036871c03f34d3124. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-219714 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in capnsquarepants wordcraft bis 0.6 ausgemacht. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei tag.php. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments tag mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 0.7 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als be23028633e8105de92f387036871c03f34d3124 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2009-10003|2024-08-07T07:32:23.777Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 18:58:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
