<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Netgear -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/netgear/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Netgear -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 22:22:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2396|2024-08-02T06:19:15.188Z -- netgear -- srx5308
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2396</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Netgear SRX5308 up to 4.3.5-3. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument USERDBUsers.Password leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-227674 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Netgear SRX5308 bis 4.3.5-3 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Komponente Web Management Interface. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments USERDBUsers.Password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2396|2024-08-02T06:19:15.188Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 22:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2393|2024-08-02T06:19:15.080Z -- netgear -- srx5308
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2393</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear SRX5308 up to 4.3.5-3. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=dmz_setup.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument ConfigPort.LogicalIfName leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-227671. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Netgear SRX5308 bis 4.3.5-3 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=dmz_setup.htm der Komponente Web Management Interface. Durch Manipulation des Arguments ConfigPort.LogicalIfName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2393|2024-08-02T06:19:15.080Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 21:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0849|2024-08-02T05:24:34.450Z -- netgear -- wndr3700v2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0849</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Netgear WNDR3700v2 1.0.1.14 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Web Interface. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-221152.
In Netgear WNDR3700v2 1.0.1.14 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle gefunden. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Komponente Web Interface. Durch Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0849|2024-08-02T05:24:34.450Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 21:43:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2384|2024-08-02T06:19:15.152Z -- netgear -- srx5308
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2384</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear SRX5308 up to 4.3.5-3. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=dmz_setup.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument dhcp.SecDnsIPByte2 leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-227662 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Netgear SRX5308 bis 4.3.5-3 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=dmz_setup.htm der Komponente Web Management Interface. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments dhcp.SecDnsIPByte2 mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2384|2024-08-02T06:19:15.152Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 17:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2392|2024-08-02T06:19:15.007Z -- netgear -- srx5308
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2392</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear SRX5308 up to 4.3.5-3. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=time_zone.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument ManualDate.minutes leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-227670 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in Netgear SRX5308 bis 4.3.5-3 ausgemacht. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=time_zone.htm der Komponente Web Management Interface. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments ManualDate.minutes mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2392|2024-08-02T06:19:15.007Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 20:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2381|2024-08-02T06:19:15.088Z -- netgear -- srx5308
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2381</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Netgear SRX5308 up to 4.3.5-3 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=bandwidth_profile.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument BandWidthProfile.ProfileName leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-227659. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Netgear SRX5308 bis 4.3.5-3 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=bandwidth_profile.htm der Komponente Web Management Interface. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments BandWidthProfile.ProfileName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2381|2024-08-02T06:19:15.088Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 17:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2388|2024-08-02T06:19:14.993Z -- netgear -- srx5308
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2388</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Netgear SRX5308 up to 4.3.5-3. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=firewall_logs_email.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument smtpServer.fromAddr leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-227666 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in Netgear SRX5308 bis 4.3.5-3 entdeckt. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=firewall_logs_email.htm der Komponente Web Management Interface. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments smtpServer.fromAddr mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2388|2024-08-02T06:19:14.993Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 19:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2390|2024-08-02T06:19:15.119Z -- netgear -- srx5308
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2390</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Netgear SRX5308 up to 4.3.5-3 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=time_zone.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument ntp.server1 leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-227668. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Netgear SRX5308 bis 4.3.5-3 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle gefunden. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=time_zone.htm der Komponente Web Management Interface. Dank Manipulation des Arguments ntp.server1 mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2390|2024-08-02T06:19:15.119Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 20:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2380|2024-08-02T06:19:15.222Z -- netgear -- srx5308
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2380</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Netgear SRX5308 up to 4.3.5-3. Affected is an unknown function. The manipulation leads to denial of service. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-227658 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Netgear SRX5308 bis 4.3.5-3 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil. Mit der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine denial of service-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2380|2024-08-02T06:19:15.222Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 16:54:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2391|2024-08-02T06:19:14.998Z -- netgear -- srx5308
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2391</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear SRX5308 up to 4.3.5-3 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=time_zone.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument ntp.server2 leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-227669 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in Netgear SRX5308 bis 4.3.5-3 gefunden. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=time_zone.htm der Komponente Web Management Interface. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments ntp.server2 mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2391|2024-08-02T06:19:14.998Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 20:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2383|2024-08-02T06:19:15.242Z -- netgear -- srx5308
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2383</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear SRX5308 up to 4.3.5-3. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=firewall_logs_email.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument smtpServer.fromAddr leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-227661 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Netgear SRX5308 bis 4.3.5-3 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=firewall_logs_email.htm der Komponente Web Management Interface. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments smtpServer.fromAddr mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2383|2024-08-02T06:19:15.242Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 17:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0848|2024-08-02T05:24:34.524Z -- netgear -- wndr3700v2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0848</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear WNDR3700v2 1.0.1.14. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-221147.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Netgear WNDR3700v2 1.0.1.14 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Komponente Web Management Interface. Durch die Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine denial of service-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0848|2024-08-02T05:24:34.524Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 21:31:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2382|2024-08-02T06:19:14.984Z -- netgear -- srx5308
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2382</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear SRX5308 up to 4.3.5-3 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=firewall_logs_email.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument sysLogInfo.serverName leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-227660. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Netgear SRX5308 bis 4.3.5-3 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=firewall_logs_email.htm der Komponente Web Management Interface. Durch Manipulation des Arguments sysLogInfo.serverName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2382|2024-08-02T06:19:14.984Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 17:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-49694|2024-08-02T22:01:25.766Z -- netgear -- netgear%20prosafe%20network%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49694</link>
      <description>


A low-privileged OS user with access to a Windows host where NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System is installed can create arbitrary JSP files in a Tomcat web application directory. The user can then execute the JSP files under the security context of SYSTEM.



</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-49694|2024-08-02T22:01:25.766Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 22:47:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2386|2024-08-02T06:19:15.216Z -- netgear -- srx5308
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2386</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Netgear SRX5308 up to 4.3.5-3. Affected is an unknown function of the file scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=firewall_logs_email.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument smtpServer.toAddr leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-227664. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in Netgear SRX5308 bis 4.3.5-3 entdeckt. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=firewall_logs_email.htm der Komponente Web Management Interface. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments smtpServer.toAddr mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2386|2024-08-02T06:19:15.216Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 18:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-49693|2024-08-02T22:01:25.966Z -- netgear -- netgear%20prosafe%20network%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49693</link>
      <description>
NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System has Java Debug Wire Protocol (JDWP) listening on port 11611 and it is remotely accessible by unauthenticated users, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary code.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-49693|2024-08-02T22:01:25.966Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 22:41:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2387|2024-08-02T06:19:14.996Z -- netgear -- srx5308
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2387</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Netgear SRX5308 up to 4.3.5-3. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=dmz_setup.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument winsServer1 leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-227665 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Netgear SRX5308 bis 4.3.5-3 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=dmz_setup.htm der Komponente Web Management Interface. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments winsServer1 mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2387|2024-08-02T06:19:14.996Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 19:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2394|2024-08-02T06:19:15.108Z -- netgear -- srx5308
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2394</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear SRX5308 up to 4.3.5-3. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument wanName leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-227672. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in Netgear SRX5308 bis 4.3.5-3 ausgemacht. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Komponente Web Management Interface. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments wanName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2394|2024-08-02T06:19:15.108Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 21:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2395|2024-08-02T06:19:15.140Z -- netgear -- srx5308
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2395</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Netgear SRX5308 up to 4.3.5-3. This affects an unknown part of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument Login.userAgent leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-227673 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Netgear SRX5308 bis 4.3.5-3 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Komponente Web Management Interface. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments Login.userAgent mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2395|2024-08-02T06:19:15.140Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 21:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-48725|2024-08-02T21:37:54.638Z -- netgear -- rax30
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48725</link>
      <description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the JSON Parsing getblockschedule() functionality of Netgear RAX30 1.0.11.96 and 1.0.7.78. A specially crafted HTTP request can lead to code execution. An attacker can make an authenticated HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-48725|2024-08-02T21:37:54.638Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 14:59:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0850|2024-08-02T05:24:34.449Z -- netgear -- wndr3700v2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0850</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear WNDR3700v2 1.0.1.14 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Web Interface. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-221153 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in Netgear WNDR3700v2 1.0.1.14 gefunden. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Komponente Web Interface. Durch das Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine denial of service-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0850|2024-08-02T05:24:34.449Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 21:45:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-24498|2024-08-02T10:56:04.232Z -- netgear -- prosafe%2024%20port%2010%2F100%20fs726tp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24498</link>
      <description>An uspecified endpoint in the web server of the switch does not properly authenticate the user identity, and may allow downloading a config page with the password to the switch in clear text.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-24498|2024-08-02T10:56:04.232Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2385|2024-08-02T06:19:14.996Z -- netgear -- srx5308
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2385</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear SRX5308 up to 4.3.5-3. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=ike_policies.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument IpsecIKEPolicy.IKEPolicyName leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-227663. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Netgear SRX5308 bis 4.3.5-3 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=ike_policies.htm der Komponente Web Management Interface. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments IpsecIKEPolicy.IKEPolicyName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2385|2024-08-02T06:19:14.996Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 18:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2389|2024-08-02T06:19:15.007Z -- netgear -- srx5308
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2389</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Netgear SRX5308 up to 4.3.5-3. This affects an unknown part of the file scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=firewall_logs_email.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument smtpServer.emailServer leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-227667. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in Netgear SRX5308 bis 4.3.5-3 gefunden. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=firewall_logs_email.htm der Komponente Web Management Interface. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments smtpServer.emailServer mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2389|2024-08-02T06:19:15.007Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 20:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38096|2024-08-02T17:30:13.691Z -- netgear -- prosafe%20network%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38096</link>
      <description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System MyHandlerInterceptor Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the MyHandlerInterceptor class. The issue results from improper implementation of the authentication mechanism. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-19718.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38096|2024-08-02T17:30:13.691Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38097|2024-08-02T17:30:14.123Z -- netgear -- prosafe%20network%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38097</link>
      <description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System BkreProcessThread Exposed Dangerous Function Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the BkreProcessThread class. The issue results from an exposed dangerous function. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM.
. Was ZDI-CAN-19719.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38097|2024-08-02T17:30:14.123Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38098|2024-08-02T17:30:14.353Z -- netgear -- prosafe%20network%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38098</link>
      <description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System UpLoadServlet Unrestricted File Upload Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the UpLoadServlet class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can allow the upload of arbitrary files. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-19720.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38098|2024-08-02T17:30:14.353Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38095|2024-08-02T17:30:13.933Z -- netgear -- prosafe%20network%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38095</link>
      <description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System MFileUploadController Unrestricted File Upload Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the MFileUploadController class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can allow the upload of arbitrary files. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-19717.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38095|2024-08-02T17:30:13.933Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38099|2024-08-02T17:30:14.026Z -- netgear -- prosafe%20network%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38099</link>
      <description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System getNodesByTopologyMapSearch SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the getNodesByTopologyMapSearch function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-19723.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38099|2024-08-02T17:30:14.026Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38101|2024-08-02T17:30:13.527Z -- netgear -- prosafe%20network%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38101</link>
      <description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System SettingConfigController Exposed Dangerous Function Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the SettingConfigController class. The issue results from an exposed dangerous function. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-19725.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38101|2024-08-02T17:30:13.527Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38102|2024-08-02T17:30:14.071Z -- netgear -- prosafe%20network%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38102</link>
      <description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System createUser Missing Authorization Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the createUser function. The issue results from the lack of authorization prior to allowing access to functionality. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges to resources normally protected from the user. Was ZDI-CAN-19726.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38102|2024-08-02T17:30:14.071Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38100|2024-08-02T17:30:14.049Z -- netgear -- prosafe%20network%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38100</link>
      <description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System clearAlertByIds SQL Injection Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the clearAlertByIds function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges to resources normally protected from the user. Was ZDI-CAN-19724.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38100|2024-08-02T17:30:14.049Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5505|2024-08-01T21:18:05.352Z -- netgear -- prosafe%20network%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5505</link>
      <description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System UpLoadServlet Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the UpLoadServlet class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-22724.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5505|2024-08-01T21:18:05.352Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:49:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7153|2024-08-01T21:52:30.308Z -- netgear -- wn604</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7153</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Netgear WN604 up to 20240719. Affected is an unknown function of the file siteSurvey.php. The manipulation leads to direct request. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272556. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in Netgear WN604 bis 20240719 entdeckt. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei siteSurvey.php. Durch das Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine direct request-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7153|2024-08-01T21:52:30.308Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 22:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5246|2024-08-01T21:03:11.154Z -- netgear -- prosafe%20network%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5246</link>
      <description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System Tomcat Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the product installer. The issue results from the use of a vulnerable version of Apache Tomcat. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-22868.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5246|2024-08-01T21:03:11.154Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 22:07:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5245|2024-08-01T21:03:11.107Z -- netgear -- prosafe%20network%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5245</link>
      <description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System Default Credentials Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the product installer. The issue results from the use of default MySQL credentials. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-22755.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5245|2024-08-01T21:03:11.107Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 22:07:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5247|2024-08-01T21:03:11.074Z -- netgear -- prosafe%20network%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5247</link>
      <description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System UpLoadServlet Unrestricted File Upload Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the UpLoadServlet class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can allow the upload of arbitrary files. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-22923.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5247|2024-08-01T21:03:11.074Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 22:07:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6646|2024-08-01T21:41:04.277Z -- netgear -- wn604</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6646</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear WN604 up to 20240710. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /downloadFile.php of the component Web Interface. The manipulation of the argument file with the input config leads to information disclosure. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-271052. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in Netgear WN604 bis 20240710 ausgemacht. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei /downloadFile.php der Komponente Web Interface. Dank Manipulation des Arguments file mit der Eingabe config mit unbekannten Daten kann eine information disclosure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6646|2024-08-01T21:41:04.277Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 17:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7153|2024-07-29T18:23:59.496Z -- netgear -- wn604</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7153</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Netgear WN604 up to 20240719. Affected is an unknown function of the file siteSurvey.php. The manipulation leads to direct request. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272556. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in Netgear WN604 bis 20240719 entdeckt. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei siteSurvey.php. Durch das Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine direct request-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7153|2024-07-29T18:23:59.496Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 22:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27361|2024-07-25T16:59:04.662Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27361</link>
      <description>NETGEAR RAX30 rex_cgi JSON Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR RAX30 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of JSON data. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-19355.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27361|2024-07-25T16:59:04.662Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6646|2024-07-10T20:01:16.816Z -- netgear -- wn604</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6646</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear WN604 up to 20240710. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /downloadFile.php of the component Web Interface. The manipulation of the argument file with the input config leads to information disclosure. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-271052. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in Netgear WN604 bis 20240710 ausgemacht. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei /downloadFile.php der Komponente Web Interface. Dank Manipulation des Arguments file mit der Eingabe config mit unbekannten Daten kann eine information disclosure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6646|2024-07-10T20:01:16.816Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 17:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27356|2024-07-10T15:55:30.728Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27356</link>
      <description>NETGEAR RAX30 logCtrl Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR RAX30 routers. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the logCtrl action. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-19825.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27356|2024-07-10T15:55:30.728Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1431|2024-07-05T17:20:50.569Z -- netgear -- r7000</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1431</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear R7000 1.0.11.136_10.2.120 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /debuginfo.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-253382 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Netgear R7000 1.0.11.136_10.2.120 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei /debuginfo.htm der Komponente Web Management Interface. Durch Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine information disclosure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1431|2024-07-05T17:20:50.569Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 02:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27360|2024-06-17T19:07:46.711Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27360</link>
      <description>NETGEAR RAX30 lighttpd Misconfiguration Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR RAX30. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the configuration of the lighttpd HTTP server. The issue results from allowing execution of files from untrusted sources. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-19398.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27360|2024-06-17T19:07:46.711Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38097|2024-06-05T20:21:28.426Z -- netgear -- prosafe%20network%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38097</link>
      <description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System BkreProcessThread Exposed Dangerous Function Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the BkreProcessThread class. The issue results from an exposed dangerous function. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM.
. Was ZDI-CAN-19719.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38097|2024-06-05T20:21:28.426Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38096|2024-06-05T20:21:09.458Z -- netgear -- prosafe%20network%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38096</link>
      <description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System MyHandlerInterceptor Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the MyHandlerInterceptor class. The issue results from improper implementation of the authentication mechanism. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-19718.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38096|2024-06-05T20:21:09.458Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38101|2024-06-05T20:23:04.229Z -- netgear -- prosafe%20network%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38101</link>
      <description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System SettingConfigController Exposed Dangerous Function Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the SettingConfigController class. The issue results from an exposed dangerous function. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-19725.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38101|2024-06-05T20:23:04.229Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38100|2024-06-05T20:22:51.633Z -- netgear -- prosafe%20network%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38100</link>
      <description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System clearAlertByIds SQL Injection Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the clearAlertByIds function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges to resources normally protected from the user. Was ZDI-CAN-19724.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38100|2024-06-05T20:22:51.633Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38102|2024-06-04T17:28:07.596Z -- netgear -- prosafe%20network%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38102</link>
      <description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System createUser Missing Authorization Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the createUser function. The issue results from the lack of authorization prior to allowing access to functionality. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges to resources normally protected from the user. Was ZDI-CAN-19726.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38102|2024-06-04T17:28:07.596Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38099|2024-06-05T20:22:21.671Z -- netgear -- prosafe%20network%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38099</link>
      <description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System getNodesByTopologyMapSearch SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the getNodesByTopologyMapSearch function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-19723.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38099|2024-06-05T20:22:21.671Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38095|2024-06-05T20:20:55.866Z -- netgear -- prosafe%20network%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38095</link>
      <description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System MFileUploadController Unrestricted File Upload Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the MFileUploadController class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can allow the upload of arbitrary files. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-19717.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38095|2024-06-05T20:20:55.866Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38098|2024-06-05T20:22:04.157Z -- netgear -- prosafe%20network%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38098</link>
      <description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System UpLoadServlet Unrestricted File Upload Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the UpLoadServlet class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can allow the upload of arbitrary files. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-19720.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38098|2024-06-05T20:22:04.157Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-48725|2024-03-07T18:00:06.823Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-48725</link>
      <description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the JSON Parsing getblockschedule() functionality of Netgear RAX30 1.0.11.96 and 1.0.7.78. A specially crafted HTTP request can lead to code execution. An attacker can make an authenticated HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-48725|2024-03-07T18:00:06.823Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 14:59:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27358|2024-06-06T15:50:11.494Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27358</link>
      <description>NETGEAR RAX30 SOAP Request SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR RAX30 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of specific SOAP requests. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-19754.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27358|2024-06-06T15:50:11.494Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27368|2024-06-04T17:24:52.825Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27368</link>
      <description>NETGEAR RAX30 soap_serverd Stack-based Buffer Overflow Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR RAX30 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the soap_serverd binary. When parsing SOAP message headers, the process does not properly validate the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-19839.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27368|2024-06-04T17:24:52.825Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27369|2024-06-04T17:24:50.810Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27369</link>
      <description>NETGEAR RAX30 soap_serverd  Stack-based Buffer Overflow Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR RAX30. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the soap_serverd binary. When parsing the request headers, the process does not properly validate the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-19840.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27369|2024-06-04T17:24:50.810Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27370|2024-06-05T19:33:25.989Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27370</link>
      <description>NETGEAR RAX30 Device Configuration Cleartext Storage Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of NETGEAR RAX30 routers. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of device configuration. The issue results from the storage of configuration secrets in plaintext. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose stored credentials, leading to further compromise. Was ZDI-CAN-19841.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27370|2024-06-05T19:33:25.989Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27367|2024-06-05T19:33:03.347Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27367</link>
      <description>NETGEAR RAX30 libcms_cli Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR RAX30 routers. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the libcms_cli module. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied command before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-19838.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27367|2024-06-05T19:33:03.347Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27356|2024-05-03T01:56:09.001Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27356</link>
      <description>NETGEAR RAX30 logCtrl Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR RAX30 routers. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the logCtrl action. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-19825.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27356|2024-05-03T01:56:09.001Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27360|2024-05-03T01:56:12.177Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27360</link>
      <description>NETGEAR RAX30 lighttpd Misconfiguration Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR RAX30. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the configuration of the lighttpd HTTP server. The issue results from allowing execution of files from untrusted sources. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-19398.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27360|2024-05-03T01:56:12.177Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27361|2024-05-03T01:56:12.897Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27361</link>
      <description>NETGEAR RAX30 rex_cgi JSON Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR RAX30 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of JSON data. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-19355.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27361|2024-05-03T01:56:12.897Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27357|2024-06-06T15:57:00.916Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27357</link>
      <description>NETGEAR RAX30 GetInfo Missing Authentication Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of NETGEAR RAX30 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of SOAP requests. The issue results from the lack of authentication prior to allowing access to functionality. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose sensitive information, leading to further compromise. Was ZDI-CAN-19608.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27357|2024-06-06T15:57:00.916Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41182|2024-06-04T17:22:01.267Z -- netgear -- prosafe%20network%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41182</link>
      <description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System ZipUtils Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the ZipUtils class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-19716.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41182|2024-06-04T17:22:01.267Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41183|2024-06-05T20:44:45.991Z -- netgear -- orbi%20760</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41183</link>
      <description>NETGEAR Orbi 760 SOAP API Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of NETGEAR Orbi 760 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the SOAP API. The issue results from the lack of authentication prior to allowing access to functionality. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-20524.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41183|2024-06-05T20:44:45.991Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34283|2024-06-04T17:21:20.948Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34283</link>
      <description>NETGEAR RAX30 USB Share Link Following Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of NETGEAR RAX30 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of symbolic links on removable USB media. By creating a symbolic link, an attacker can abuse the router's web server to access arbitrary local files. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-19498.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34283|2024-06-04T17:21:20.948Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34285|2024-06-04T17:21:15.056Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34285</link>
      <description>NETGEAR RAX30 cmsCli_authenticate Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR RAX30 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within a shared library used by the telnetd service, which listens on TCP port 23 by default. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-19918.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34285|2024-06-04T17:21:15.056Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34284|2024-06-05T20:57:09.030Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34284</link>
      <description>NETGEAR RAX30 Use of Hard-coded Credentials Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of NETGEAR RAX30 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the system configuration. The system contains a hardcoded user account which can be used to access the CLI service as a low-privileged user. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-19660.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34284|2024-06-05T20:57:09.030Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44450|2024-06-04T17:19:33.285Z -- netgear -- prosafe%20network%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-44450</link>
      <description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System getNodesByTopologyMapSearch SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the getNodesByTopologyMapSearch function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-21858.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44450|2024-06-04T17:19:33.285Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44449|2024-05-03T02:14:11.010Z -- netgear -- prosafe%20network%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-44449</link>
      <description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System clearAlertByIds SQL Injection Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the clearAlertByIds function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges to resources normally protected from the user. Was ZDI-CAN-21875.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44449|2024-05-03T02:14:11.010Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44445|2024-06-04T17:19:28.139Z -- netgear -- cax30</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-44445</link>
      <description>NETGEAR CAX30 SSO Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR CAX30 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the sso binary. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-19058.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44445|2024-06-04T17:19:28.139Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40480|2024-06-05T15:28:03.130Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40480</link>
      <description>NETGEAR RAX30 DHCP Server Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR RAX30 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DHCP server. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-19705.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40480|2024-06-05T15:28:03.130Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40479|2024-06-04T17:19:12.301Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40479</link>
      <description>NETGEAR RAX30 UPnP Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR RAX30 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the UPnP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-19704.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40479|2024-06-04T17:19:12.301Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40478|2024-06-05T20:38:48.907Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40478</link>
      <description>NETGEAR RAX30 Telnet CLI passwd Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR RAX30 routers. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the telnet CLI service, which listens on TCP port 23. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20009.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40478|2024-06-05T20:38:48.907Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35722|2024-05-03T01:57:42.315Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35722</link>
      <description>NETGEAR RAX30 UPnP Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR RAX30 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of UPnP port mapping requests. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20429.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35722|2024-05-03T01:57:42.315Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35721|2024-06-05T20:12:31.015Z -- netgear -- multiple%20routers</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35721</link>
      <description>NETGEAR Multiple Routers curl_post Improper Certificate Validation Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to compromise the integrity of downloaded information on affected installations of multiple NETGEAR routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the update functionality, which operates over HTTPS. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the certificate presented by the server. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-19981.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35721|2024-06-05T20:12:31.015Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50231|2024-06-04T17:17:40.847Z -- netgear -- prosafe%20network%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50231</link>
      <description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System saveNodeLabel Cross-Site Scripting Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. Minimal user interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability. 

The specific flaw exists within the saveNodeLabel method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can lead to the injection of an arbitrary script. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges to resources normally protected from the user. Was ZDI-CAN-21838.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50231|2024-06-04T17:17:40.847Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5246|2024-06-04T18:02:38.927Z -- netgear -- prosafe%20network%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5246</link>
      <description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System Tomcat Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the product installer. The issue results from the use of a vulnerable version of Apache Tomcat. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-22868.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5246|2024-06-04T18:02:38.927Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 22:07:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5505|2024-06-06T18:53:15.491Z -- netgear -- prosafe%20network%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5505</link>
      <description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System UpLoadServlet Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the UpLoadServlet class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-22724.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5505|2024-06-06T18:53:15.491Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:49:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5247|2024-06-04T18:02:29.045Z -- netgear -- prosafe%20network%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5247</link>
      <description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System UpLoadServlet Unrestricted File Upload Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the UpLoadServlet class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can allow the upload of arbitrary files. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-22923.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5247|2024-06-04T18:02:29.045Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 22:07:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5245|2024-06-04T18:02:10.251Z -- netgear -- prosafe%20network%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5245</link>
      <description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System Default Credentials Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the product installer. The issue results from the use of default MySQL credentials. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-22755.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5245|2024-06-04T18:02:10.251Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 22:07:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1431|2024-02-11T02:31:04.685Z -- netgear -- r7000</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1431</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear R7000 1.0.11.136_10.2.120 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /debuginfo.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-253382 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Netgear R7000 1.0.11.136_10.2.120 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei /debuginfo.htm der Komponente Web Management Interface. Durch Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine information disclosure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1431|2024-02-11T02:31:04.685Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 02:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1430|2024-02-11T00:31:04.302Z -- netgear -- r7000</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1430</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Netgear R7000 1.0.11.136_10.2.120 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /currentsetting.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-253381 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Netgear R7000 1.0.11.136_10.2.120 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei /currentsetting.htm der Komponente Web Management Interface. Durch das Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine information disclosure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1430|2024-02-11T00:31:04.302Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 00:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4235|2024-06-04T17:53:21.542Z -- netgear -- dg834gv5</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4235</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Netgear DG834Gv5 1.6.01.34. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to cleartext storage of sensitive information. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-262126 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Netgear DG834Gv5 1.6.01.34 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Komponente Web Management Interface. Durch das Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cleartext storage of sensitive information-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4235|2024-06-04T17:53:21.542Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 17:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34983|2024-06-13T18:58:27.059Z -- netgear -- multiple%20routers</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34983</link>
      <description>NETGEAR Multiple Routers httpd Missing Authentication for Critical Function Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of multiple NETGEAR routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the httpd service, which listens on TCP port 80 by default. The issue results from the lack of authentication prior to allowing access to system configuration information. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose stored credentials, leading to further compromise. Was ZDI-CAN-13708.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34983|2024-06-13T18:58:27.059Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34983|2024-06-18T18:38:20.962Z -- netgear -- multiple%20routers</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34983</link>
      <description>NETGEAR Multiple Routers httpd Missing Authentication for Critical Function Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of multiple NETGEAR routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the httpd service, which listens on TCP port 80 by default. The issue results from the lack of authentication prior to allowing access to system configuration information. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose stored credentials, leading to further compromise. Was ZDI-CAN-13708.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34983|2024-06-18T18:38:20.962Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35722|2024-07-05T21:01:40.570Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35722</link>
      <description>NETGEAR RAX30 UPnP Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR RAX30 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of UPnP port mapping requests. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20429.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35722|2024-07-05T21:01:40.570Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44449|2024-07-05T20:57:57.804Z -- netgear -- prosafe%20network%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44449</link>
      <description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System clearAlertByIds SQL Injection Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the clearAlertByIds function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges to resources normally protected from the user. Was ZDI-CAN-21875.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44449|2024-07-05T20:57:57.804Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6646|2024-07-10T17:31:04.041Z -- netgear -- wn604</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6646</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear WN604 up to 20240710. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /downloadFile.php of the component Web Interface. The manipulation of the argument file with the input config leads to information disclosure. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-271052. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in Netgear WN604 bis 20240710 ausgemacht. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei /downloadFile.php der Komponente Web Interface. Dank Manipulation des Arguments file mit der Eingabe config mit unbekannten Daten kann eine information disclosure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6646|2024-07-10T17:31:04.041Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 17:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1430|2024-07-15T20:33:07.639Z -- netgear -- r7000</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1430</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Netgear R7000 1.0.11.136_10.2.120 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /currentsetting.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-253381 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Netgear R7000 1.0.11.136_10.2.120 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei /currentsetting.htm der Komponente Web Management Interface. Durch das Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine information disclosure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1430|2024-07-15T20:33:07.639Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 00:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7153|2024-07-27T22:00:08.933Z -- netgear -- wn604</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7153</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Netgear WN604 up to 20240719. Affected is an unknown function of the file siteSurvey.php. The manipulation leads to direct request. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272556. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in Netgear WN604 bis 20240719 entdeckt. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei siteSurvey.php. Durch das Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine direct request-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7153|2024-07-27T22:00:08.933Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 22:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1430|2024-08-01T18:40:21.040Z -- netgear -- r7000</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1430</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Netgear R7000 1.0.11.136_10.2.120 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /currentsetting.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-253381 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Netgear R7000 1.0.11.136_10.2.120 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei /currentsetting.htm der Komponente Web Management Interface. Durch das Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine information disclosure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1430|2024-08-01T18:40:21.040Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 00:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1431|2024-08-01T18:40:21.093Z -- netgear -- r7000</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1431</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear R7000 1.0.11.136_10.2.120 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /debuginfo.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-253382 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Netgear R7000 1.0.11.136_10.2.120 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei /debuginfo.htm der Komponente Web Management Interface. Durch Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine information disclosure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1431|2024-08-01T18:40:21.093Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 02:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4235|2024-08-01T20:33:52.931Z -- netgear -- dg834gv5</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4235</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Netgear DG834Gv5 1.6.01.34. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to cleartext storage of sensitive information. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-262126 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Netgear DG834Gv5 1.6.01.34 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Komponente Web Management Interface. Durch das Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cleartext storage of sensitive information-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4235|2024-08-01T20:33:52.931Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 17:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27368|2024-08-02T12:09:43.325Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27368</link>
      <description>NETGEAR RAX30 soap_serverd Stack-based Buffer Overflow Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR RAX30 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the soap_serverd binary. When parsing SOAP message headers, the process does not properly validate the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-19839.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27368|2024-08-02T12:09:43.325Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27369|2024-08-02T12:09:43.407Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27369</link>
      <description>NETGEAR RAX30 soap_serverd  Stack-based Buffer Overflow Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR RAX30. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the soap_serverd binary. When parsing the request headers, the process does not properly validate the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-19840.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27369|2024-08-02T12:09:43.407Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27361|2024-08-02T12:09:43.400Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27361</link>
      <description>NETGEAR RAX30 rex_cgi JSON Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR RAX30 routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of JSON data. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-19355.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27361|2024-08-02T12:09:43.400Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27356|2024-08-02T12:09:43.353Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27356</link>
      <description>NETGEAR RAX30 logCtrl Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR RAX30 routers. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the logCtrl action. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-19825.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27356|2024-08-02T12:09:43.353Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27357|2024-08-02T12:09:43.388Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27357</link>
      <description>NETGEAR RAX30 GetInfo Missing Authentication Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of NETGEAR RAX30 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of SOAP requests. The issue results from the lack of authentication prior to allowing access to functionality. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose sensitive information, leading to further compromise. Was ZDI-CAN-19608.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27357|2024-08-02T12:09:43.388Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27360|2024-08-02T12:09:43.274Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27360</link>
      <description>NETGEAR RAX30 lighttpd Misconfiguration Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR RAX30. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the configuration of the lighttpd HTTP server. The issue results from allowing execution of files from untrusted sources. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-19398.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27360|2024-08-02T12:09:43.274Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27358|2024-08-02T12:09:43.431Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27358</link>
      <description>NETGEAR RAX30 SOAP Request SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR RAX30 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of specific SOAP requests. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-19754.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27358|2024-08-02T12:09:43.431Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27367|2024-08-02T12:09:43.430Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27367</link>
      <description>NETGEAR RAX30 libcms_cli Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR RAX30 routers. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the libcms_cli module. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied command before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-19838.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27367|2024-08-02T12:09:43.430Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27370|2024-08-02T12:09:43.336Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27370</link>
      <description>NETGEAR RAX30 Device Configuration Cleartext Storage Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of NETGEAR RAX30 routers. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of device configuration. The issue results from the storage of configuration secrets in plaintext. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose stored credentials, leading to further compromise. Was ZDI-CAN-19841.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27370|2024-08-02T12:09:43.336Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35722|2024-08-02T16:30:44.152Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35722</link>
      <description>NETGEAR RAX30 UPnP Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR RAX30 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of UPnP port mapping requests. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20429.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35722|2024-08-02T16:30:44.152Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34283|2024-08-02T16:10:05.478Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34283</link>
      <description>NETGEAR RAX30 USB Share Link Following Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of NETGEAR RAX30 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of symbolic links on removable USB media. By creating a symbolic link, an attacker can abuse the router's web server to access arbitrary local files. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-19498.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34283|2024-08-02T16:10:05.478Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34285|2024-08-02T16:10:05.507Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34285</link>
      <description>NETGEAR RAX30 cmsCli_authenticate Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR RAX30 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within a shared library used by the telnetd service, which listens on TCP port 23 by default. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-19918.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34285|2024-08-02T16:10:05.507Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34284|2024-08-02T16:10:05.610Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34284</link>
      <description>NETGEAR RAX30 Use of Hard-coded Credentials Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of NETGEAR RAX30 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the system configuration. The system contains a hardcoded user account which can be used to access the CLI service as a low-privileged user. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-19660.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34284|2024-08-02T16:10:05.610Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35721|2024-08-02T16:30:44.421Z -- netgear -- multiple%20routers</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35721</link>
      <description>NETGEAR Multiple Routers curl_post Improper Certificate Validation Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to compromise the integrity of downloaded information on affected installations of multiple NETGEAR routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the update functionality, which operates over HTTPS. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the certificate presented by the server. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-19981.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35721|2024-08-02T16:30:44.421Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:57:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41182|2024-08-02T18:54:04.857Z -- netgear -- prosafe%20network%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41182</link>
      <description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System ZipUtils Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the ZipUtils class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-19716.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41182|2024-08-02T18:54:04.857Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40480|2024-08-02T18:31:53.852Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40480</link>
      <description>NETGEAR RAX30 DHCP Server Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR RAX30 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DHCP server. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-19705.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40480|2024-08-02T18:31:53.852Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41183|2024-08-02T18:54:04.418Z -- netgear -- orbi%20760</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41183</link>
      <description>NETGEAR Orbi 760 SOAP API Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of NETGEAR Orbi 760 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the SOAP API. The issue results from the lack of authentication prior to allowing access to functionality. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-20524.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41183|2024-08-02T18:54:04.418Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40479|2024-08-02T18:31:53.963Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40479</link>
      <description>NETGEAR RAX30 UPnP Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR RAX30 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the UPnP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-19704.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40479|2024-08-02T18:31:53.963Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40478|2024-08-02T18:31:53.998Z -- netgear -- rax30</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40478</link>
      <description>NETGEAR RAX30 Telnet CLI passwd Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR RAX30 routers. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the telnet CLI service, which listens on TCP port 23. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20009.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40478|2024-08-02T18:31:53.998Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44449|2024-08-02T20:07:33.190Z -- netgear -- prosafe%20network%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44449</link>
      <description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System clearAlertByIds SQL Injection Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the clearAlertByIds function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges to resources normally protected from the user. Was ZDI-CAN-21875.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44449|2024-08-02T20:07:33.190Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44450|2024-08-02T20:07:33.369Z -- netgear -- prosafe%20network%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44450</link>
      <description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System getNodesByTopologyMapSearch SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the getNodesByTopologyMapSearch function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-21858.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44450|2024-08-02T20:07:33.369Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44445|2024-08-02T20:07:33.183Z -- netgear -- cax30</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44445</link>
      <description>NETGEAR CAX30 SSO Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR CAX30 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the sso binary. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-19058.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44445|2024-08-02T20:07:33.183Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
