<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for Netgear -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/netgear/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for Netgear -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 21:20:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-5246|2024-05-23T22:07:15.475Z -- NETGEAR -- ProSAFE Network Management System</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5246</link><description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System Tomcat Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the product installer. The issue results from the use of a vulnerable version of Apache Tomcat. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-22868.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5246|2024-05-23T22:07:15.475Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 22:07:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5247|2024-05-23T22:07:24.888Z -- NETGEAR -- ProSAFE Network Management System</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5247</link><description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System UpLoadServlet Unrestricted File Upload Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the UpLoadServlet class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can allow the upload of arbitrary files. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-22923.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5247|2024-05-23T22:07:24.888Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 22:07:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5245|2024-05-23T22:07:01.049Z -- NETGEAR -- ProSAFE Network Management System</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5245</link><description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System Default Credentials Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the product installer. The issue results from the use of default MySQL credentials. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-22755.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5245|2024-05-23T22:07:01.049Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 22:07:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1431|2024-02-11T02:31:04.685Z -- Netgear -- R7000</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1431</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear R7000 1.0.11.136_10.2.120 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /debuginfo.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-253382 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Netgear R7000 1.0.11.136_10.2.120 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei /debuginfo.htm der Komponente Web Management Interface. Durch Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine information disclosure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1431|2024-02-11T02:31:04.685Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 02:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1430|2024-02-11T00:31:04.302Z -- Netgear -- R7000</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1430</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Netgear R7000 1.0.11.136_10.2.120 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /currentsetting.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-253381 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Netgear R7000 1.0.11.136_10.2.120 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei /currentsetting.htm der Komponente Web Management Interface. Durch das Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine information disclosure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1430|2024-02-11T00:31:04.302Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 00:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4235|2024-04-26T17:31:07.743Z -- Netgear -- DG834Gv5</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4235</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Netgear DG834Gv5 1.6.01.34. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to cleartext storage of sensitive information. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-262126 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Netgear DG834Gv5 1.6.01.34 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Komponente Web Management Interface. Durch das Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cleartext storage of sensitive information-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4235|2024-04-26T17:31:07.743Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 17:31:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38097|2024-05-09T22:21:08.458Z -- NETGEAR -- ProSAFE Network Management System</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38097</link><description>NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System BkreProcessThread Exposed Dangerous Function Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR ProSAFE Network Management System. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the BkreProcessThread class. The issue results from an exposed dangerous function. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM.
. Was ZDI-CAN-19719.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38097|2024-05-09T22:21:08.458Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:59 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>