<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for NETGEAR -- R6700v3</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/netgear/r6700v3.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for NETGEAR -- R6700v3</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 18:24:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-27645|2024-08-03T05:32:59.899Z -- netgear -- r6700v3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27645</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of NETGEAR R6700v3 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within readycloud_control.cgi. The issue results from the lack of authentication prior to allowing access to functionality. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-15762.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-27645|2024-08-03T05:32:59.899Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-27646|2024-08-03T05:32:59.786Z -- netgear -- r6700v3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27646</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR R6700v3 1.0.4.120_10.0.91 routers. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed. The specific flaw exists within the circled daemon. A crafted circleinfo.txt file can trigger an overflow of a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-15879.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-27646|2024-08-03T05:32:59.786Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-27644|2024-08-03T05:32:59.965Z -- netgear -- r6700v3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27644</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to compromise the integrity of downloaded information on affected installations of NETGEAR R6700v3 1.0.4.120_10.0.91 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the downloading of files via HTTPS. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the certificate presented by the server. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-15797.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-27644|2024-08-03T05:32:59.965Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-27647|2024-08-03T05:32:59.969Z -- netgear -- r6700v3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27647</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR R6700v3 1.0.4.120_10.0.91 routers. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the name or email field provided to libreadycloud.so. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-15874.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-27647|2024-08-03T05:32:59.969Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-27643|2024-08-03T05:32:59.967Z -- netgear -- r6700v3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27643</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR R6700v3 1.0.4.120_10.0.91 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of SOAP requests. When parsing the SOAPAction header, the process does not properly validate the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-15692.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-27643|2024-08-03T05:32:59.967Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-27642|2024-08-03T05:32:59.905Z -- netgear -- r6700v3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27642</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of NETGEAR R6700v3 1.0.4.120_10.0.91 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the httpd service. The issue results from incorrect string matching logic when accessing protected pages. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-15854.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-27642|2024-08-03T05:32:59.905Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-27641|2024-08-03T05:32:59.983Z -- netgear -- r6700v3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27641</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR R6700v3 1.0.4.120_10.0.91 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the NetUSB module. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in an integer overflow before allocating a buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-15806.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-27641|2024-08-03T05:32:59.983Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
