<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Netgear -- SRX5308</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/netgear/srx5308.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Netgear -- SRX5308</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 18:24:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2396|2024-08-02T06:19:15.188Z -- netgear -- srx5308
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2396</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Netgear SRX5308 up to 4.3.5-3. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument USERDBUsers.Password leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-227674 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Netgear SRX5308 bis 4.3.5-3 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Komponente Web Management Interface. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments USERDBUsers.Password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2396|2024-08-02T06:19:15.188Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 22:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2393|2024-08-02T06:19:15.080Z -- netgear -- srx5308
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2393</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear SRX5308 up to 4.3.5-3. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=dmz_setup.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument ConfigPort.LogicalIfName leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-227671. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Netgear SRX5308 bis 4.3.5-3 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=dmz_setup.htm der Komponente Web Management Interface. Durch Manipulation des Arguments ConfigPort.LogicalIfName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2393|2024-08-02T06:19:15.080Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 21:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2384|2024-08-02T06:19:15.152Z -- netgear -- srx5308
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2384</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear SRX5308 up to 4.3.5-3. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=dmz_setup.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument dhcp.SecDnsIPByte2 leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-227662 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Netgear SRX5308 bis 4.3.5-3 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=dmz_setup.htm der Komponente Web Management Interface. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments dhcp.SecDnsIPByte2 mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2384|2024-08-02T06:19:15.152Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 17:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2392|2024-08-02T06:19:15.007Z -- netgear -- srx5308
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2392</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear SRX5308 up to 4.3.5-3. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=time_zone.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument ManualDate.minutes leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-227670 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in Netgear SRX5308 bis 4.3.5-3 ausgemacht. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=time_zone.htm der Komponente Web Management Interface. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments ManualDate.minutes mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2392|2024-08-02T06:19:15.007Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 20:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2381|2024-08-02T06:19:15.088Z -- netgear -- srx5308
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2381</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Netgear SRX5308 up to 4.3.5-3 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=bandwidth_profile.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument BandWidthProfile.ProfileName leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-227659. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Netgear SRX5308 bis 4.3.5-3 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=bandwidth_profile.htm der Komponente Web Management Interface. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments BandWidthProfile.ProfileName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2381|2024-08-02T06:19:15.088Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 17:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2388|2024-08-02T06:19:14.993Z -- netgear -- srx5308
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2388</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Netgear SRX5308 up to 4.3.5-3. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=firewall_logs_email.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument smtpServer.fromAddr leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-227666 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in Netgear SRX5308 bis 4.3.5-3 entdeckt. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=firewall_logs_email.htm der Komponente Web Management Interface. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments smtpServer.fromAddr mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2388|2024-08-02T06:19:14.993Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 19:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2390|2024-08-02T06:19:15.119Z -- netgear -- srx5308
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2390</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Netgear SRX5308 up to 4.3.5-3 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=time_zone.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument ntp.server1 leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-227668. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Netgear SRX5308 bis 4.3.5-3 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle gefunden. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=time_zone.htm der Komponente Web Management Interface. Dank Manipulation des Arguments ntp.server1 mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2390|2024-08-02T06:19:15.119Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 20:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2380|2024-08-02T06:19:15.222Z -- netgear -- srx5308
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2380</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Netgear SRX5308 up to 4.3.5-3. Affected is an unknown function. The manipulation leads to denial of service. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-227658 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Netgear SRX5308 bis 4.3.5-3 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil. Mit der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine denial of service-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2380|2024-08-02T06:19:15.222Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 16:54:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2391|2024-08-02T06:19:14.998Z -- netgear -- srx5308
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2391</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear SRX5308 up to 4.3.5-3 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=time_zone.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument ntp.server2 leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-227669 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in Netgear SRX5308 bis 4.3.5-3 gefunden. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=time_zone.htm der Komponente Web Management Interface. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments ntp.server2 mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2391|2024-08-02T06:19:14.998Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 20:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2383|2024-08-02T06:19:15.242Z -- netgear -- srx5308
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2383</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear SRX5308 up to 4.3.5-3. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=firewall_logs_email.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument smtpServer.fromAddr leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-227661 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Netgear SRX5308 bis 4.3.5-3 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=firewall_logs_email.htm der Komponente Web Management Interface. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments smtpServer.fromAddr mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2383|2024-08-02T06:19:15.242Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 17:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2382|2024-08-02T06:19:14.984Z -- netgear -- srx5308
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2382</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear SRX5308 up to 4.3.5-3 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=firewall_logs_email.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument sysLogInfo.serverName leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-227660. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Netgear SRX5308 bis 4.3.5-3 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=firewall_logs_email.htm der Komponente Web Management Interface. Durch Manipulation des Arguments sysLogInfo.serverName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2382|2024-08-02T06:19:14.984Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 17:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2386|2024-08-02T06:19:15.216Z -- netgear -- srx5308
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2386</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Netgear SRX5308 up to 4.3.5-3. Affected is an unknown function of the file scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=firewall_logs_email.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument smtpServer.toAddr leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-227664. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in Netgear SRX5308 bis 4.3.5-3 entdeckt. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=firewall_logs_email.htm der Komponente Web Management Interface. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments smtpServer.toAddr mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2386|2024-08-02T06:19:15.216Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 18:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2387|2024-08-02T06:19:14.996Z -- netgear -- srx5308
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2387</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Netgear SRX5308 up to 4.3.5-3. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=dmz_setup.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument winsServer1 leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-227665 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Netgear SRX5308 bis 4.3.5-3 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=dmz_setup.htm der Komponente Web Management Interface. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments winsServer1 mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2387|2024-08-02T06:19:14.996Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 19:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2394|2024-08-02T06:19:15.108Z -- netgear -- srx5308
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2394</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear SRX5308 up to 4.3.5-3. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument wanName leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-227672. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in Netgear SRX5308 bis 4.3.5-3 ausgemacht. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Komponente Web Management Interface. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments wanName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2394|2024-08-02T06:19:15.108Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 21:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2395|2024-08-02T06:19:15.140Z -- netgear -- srx5308
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2395</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Netgear SRX5308 up to 4.3.5-3. This affects an unknown part of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument Login.userAgent leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-227673 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Netgear SRX5308 bis 4.3.5-3 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Komponente Web Management Interface. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments Login.userAgent mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2395|2024-08-02T06:19:15.140Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 21:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2385|2024-08-02T06:19:14.996Z -- netgear -- srx5308
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2385</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear SRX5308 up to 4.3.5-3. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=ike_policies.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument IpsecIKEPolicy.IKEPolicyName leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-227663. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Netgear SRX5308 bis 4.3.5-3 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=ike_policies.htm der Komponente Web Management Interface. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments IpsecIKEPolicy.IKEPolicyName mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2385|2024-08-02T06:19:14.996Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 18:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2389|2024-08-02T06:19:15.007Z -- netgear -- srx5308
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2389</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Netgear SRX5308 up to 4.3.5-3. This affects an unknown part of the file scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=firewall_logs_email.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument smtpServer.emailServer leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-227667. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in Netgear SRX5308 bis 4.3.5-3 gefunden. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei scgi-bin/platform.cgi?page=firewall_logs_email.htm der Komponente Web Management Interface. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments smtpServer.emailServer mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2389|2024-08-02T06:19:15.007Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 20:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
