<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for britner -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/britner/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for britner -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 21:24:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-1999|2024-04-09T18:59:15.564Z -- britner -- Gutenberg Blocks by Kadence Blocks – Page Builder Features
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1999</link><description>The Gutenberg Blocks by Kadence Blocks – Page Builder Features plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Testimonial Widget's anchor style parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.25 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1999|2024-04-09T18:59:15.564Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:59:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1541|2024-03-13T15:27:15.628Z -- britner -- Gutenberg Blocks by Kadence Blocks – Page Builder Features
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1541</link><description>The Gutenberg Blocks by Kadence Blocks – Page Builder Features plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the htmlTag attribute in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.23 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1541|2024-03-13T15:27:15.628Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:27:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0598|2024-04-09T18:59:07.479Z -- britner -- Gutenberg Blocks by Kadence Blocks – Page Builder Features
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0598</link><description>The Gutenberg Blocks by Kadence Blocks – Page Builder Features plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the contact form message settings in all versions up to and including 3.2.17 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with editor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This primarily affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0598|2024-04-09T18:59:07.479Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:59:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4208|2024-05-15T02:32:44.089Z -- britner -- Gutenberg Blocks with AI by Kadence WP – Page Builder Features
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4208</link><description>The Gutenberg Blocks with AI by Kadence WP – Page Builder Features plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the typer effect in the advanced heading widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.37 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4208|2024-05-15T02:32:44.089Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 02:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4481|2024-05-10T06:44:57.771Z -- britner -- Gutenberg Blocks with AI by Kadence WP – Page Builder Features
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4481</link><description>The Gutenberg Blocks with AI by Kadence WP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'link' attribute of the plugin's blocks in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.36 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4481|2024-05-10T06:44:57.771Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 06:44:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4209|2024-05-11T01:56:00.078Z -- britner -- Gutenberg Blocks with AI by Kadence WP – Page Builder Features
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4209</link><description>The Gutenberg Blocks with AI by Kadence WP – Page Builder Features plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the countdown timer in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.36 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4209|2024-05-11T01:56:00.078Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 01:56:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4034|2024-05-02T16:52:43.574Z -- britner -- Virtue
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4034</link><description>The Virtue theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via a Post Author's name in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping when the latest posts feature is enabled on the homepage. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4034|2024-05-02T16:52:43.574Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3189|2024-05-15T02:32:43.451Z -- britner -- Gutenberg Blocks with AI by Kadence WP – Page Builder Features
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3189</link><description>The Gutenberg Blocks by Kadence Blocks – Page Builder Features plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'Testimonial', 'Progress Bar', 'Lottie Animations', 'Row Layout', 'Google Maps', and 'Advanced Gallery' blocks in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.37 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3189|2024-05-15T02:32:43.451Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 02:32:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2273|2024-05-02T16:52:49.167Z -- britner -- Gutenberg Blocks with AI by Kadence WP – Page Builder Features
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2273</link><description>The Gutenberg Blocks by Kadence Blocks – Page Builder Features plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via several parameters in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.34 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2273|2024-05-02T16:52:49.167Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2919|2024-04-23T20:52:05.587Z -- britner -- Gutenberg Blocks with AI by Kadence WP – Page Builder Features
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2919</link><description>The Gutenberg Blocks by Kadence Blocks – Page Builder Features plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the CountUp Widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.31 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2919|2024-04-23T20:52:05.587Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 02:32:40 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>