<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Flexera Software LLC -- FlexNet Publisher</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/flexera%20software%20llc/flexnet%20publisher.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Flexera Software LLC -- FlexNet Publisher</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 17:23:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-20032|2024-08-05T11:51:18.821Z -- flexera%20software%20llc -- flexnet%20publisher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-20032</link>
      <description>A Denial of Service vulnerability related to message decoding in lmgrd and vendor daemon components of FlexNet Publisher version 11.16.1.0 and earlier allows a remote attacker to send a combination of messages to lmgrd or the vendor daemon, causing the heartbeat between lmgrd and the vendor daemon to stop, and the vendor daemon to shut down.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-20032|2024-08-05T11:51:18.821Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 20:52:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-20034|2024-08-05T11:51:18.806Z -- flexera%20software%20llc -- flexnet%20publisher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-20034</link>
      <description>A Denial of Service vulnerability related to adding an item to a list in lmgrd and vendor daemon components of FlexNet Publisher version 11.16.1.0 and earlier allows a remote attacker to send a combination of messages to lmgrd or the vendor daemon, causing the heartbeat between lmgrd and the vendor daemon to stop, and the vendor daemon to shut down.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-20034|2024-08-05T11:51:18.806Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 20:54:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-20031|2024-08-05T11:51:18.328Z -- flexera%20software%20llc -- flexnet%20publisher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-20031</link>
      <description>A Denial of Service vulnerability related to preemptive item deletion in lmgrd and vendor daemon components of FlexNet Publisher version 11.16.1.0 and earlier allows a remote attacker to send a combination of messages to lmgrd or the vendor daemon, causing the heartbeat between lmgrd and the vendor daemon to stop, and the vendor daemon to shut down.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-20031|2024-08-05T11:51:18.328Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 20:47:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-20033|2024-08-05T11:51:18.821Z -- flexera%20software%20llc -- flexnet%20publisher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-20033</link>
      <description>A Remote Code Execution vulnerability in lmgrd and vendor daemon components of FlexNet Publisher version 11.16.1.0 and earlier could allow a remote attacker to corrupt the memory by allocating / deallocating memory, loading lmgrd or the vendor daemon and causing the heartbeat between lmgrd and the vendor daemon to stop. This would force the vendor daemon to shut down. No exploit of this vulnerability has been demonstrated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-20033|2024-08-05T11:51:18.821Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
