<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for biplob018 -- Image Hover Effects Ultimate (Image Gallery, Effects, Lightbox, Comparison or Magnifier)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/biplob018/image%20hover%20effects%20ultimate%20%28image%20gallery%2C%20effects%2C%20lightbox%2C%20comparison%20or%20magnifier%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for biplob018 -- Image Hover Effects Ultimate (Image Gallery, Effects, Lightbox, Comparison or Magnifier)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 16:24:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4207|2024-08-03T01:34:49.766Z -- biplob018 -- image%20hover%20effects%20ultimate%20%28image%20gallery%2C%20effects%2C%20lightbox%2C%20comparison%20or%20magnifier%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4207</link>
      <description>The Image Hover Effects Ultimate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via several values that can be added to an Image Hover in versions 9.8.1 to 9.8.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. By default, the plugin only allows administrators access to edit Image Hovers, however, if a site admin makes the plugin's features available to lower privileged users through the 'Who Can Edit?' setting then this can be exploited by those users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4207|2024-08-03T01:34:49.766Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 20:18:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2936|2024-08-03T00:52:59.812Z -- biplob018 -- image%20hover%20effects%20ultimate%20%28image%20gallery%2C%20effects%2C%20lightbox%2C%20comparison%20or%20magnifier%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2936</link>
      <description>The Image Hover Effects Ultimate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Video Link values that can be added to an Image Hover in versions up to, and including, 9.7.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. By default, the plugin only allows administrators access to edit Image Hovers, however, if a site admin makes the plugin's features available to lower privileged users through the 'Who Can Edit?' setting then this can be exploited by those users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2936|2024-08-03T00:52:59.812Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 17:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2935|2024-08-03T00:52:59.936Z -- biplob018 -- image%20hover%20effects%20ultimate%20%28image%20gallery%2C%20effects%2C%20lightbox%2C%20comparison%20or%20magnifier%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2935</link>
      <description>The Image Hover Effects Ultimate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Media Image URL value that can be added to an Image Hover in versions up to, and including, 9.7.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. By default, the plugin only allows administrators access to edit Image Hovers, however, if a site admin makes the plugin's features available to lower privileged users through the 'Who Can Edit?' setting then this can be exploited by those users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2935|2024-08-03T00:52:59.936Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 17:19:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
