<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Chunghwa Telecom -- NOKIA G-040W-Q</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/chunghwa%20telecom/nokia%20g-040w-q.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Chunghwa Telecom -- NOKIA G-040W-Q</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 21:22:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41355|2024-09-06T19:53:11.148Z -- chunghwa%20telecom -- nokia%20g-040w-q
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41355</link>
      <description>Chunghwa Telecom NOKIA G-040W-Q Firewall function has a vulnerability of input validation for ICMP redirect messages. An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted package to modify the network routing table, resulting in a denial of service or sensitive information leaking.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41355|2024-09-06T19:53:11.148Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 05:55:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41352|2024-09-06T19:55:40.699Z -- chunghwa%20telecom -- nokia%20g-040w-q
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41352</link>
      <description>Chunghwa Telecom NOKIA G-040W-Q has a vulnerability of insufficient filtering for user input. A remote attacker with administrator privilege can exploit this vulnerability to perform a Command Injection attack to execute arbitrary commands, disrupt the system or terminate services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41352|2024-09-06T19:55:40.699Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 05:44:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41353|2024-09-06T19:54:18.201Z -- chunghwa%20telecom -- nokia%20g-040w-q
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41353</link>
      <description>Chunghwa Telecom NOKIA G-040W-Q has a vulnerability of weak password requirements. A remote attacker with regular user privilege can easily infer the administrator password from system information after logging system, resulting in admin access and performing arbitrary system operations or disrupt service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41353|2024-09-06T19:54:18.201Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 05:48:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41350|2024-09-06T19:56:30.968Z -- chunghwa%20telecom -- nokia%20g-040w-q
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41350</link>
      <description>Chunghwa Telecom NOKIA G-040W-Q has a vulnerability of insufficient measures to prevent multiple failed authentication attempts. An unauthenticated remote attacker can execute a crafted Javascript to expose captcha in page, making it very easy for bots to bypass the captcha check and more susceptible to brute force attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41350|2024-09-06T19:56:30.968Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 04:44:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
