<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for IceWhaleTech -- ZimaOS</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/icewhaletech/zimaos.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for IceWhaleTech -- ZimaOS</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 22:23:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-48932|2024-10-24T21:00:27.791Z -- icewhaletech -- zimaos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48932</link>
      <description>ZimaOS is a fork of CasaOS, an operating system for Zima devices and x86-64 systems with UEFI. In version 1.2.4 and all prior versions, the API endpoint `http://&lt;Server-ip&gt;/v1/users/name` allows unauthenticated users to access sensitive information, such as usernames, without any authorization. This vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker to enumerate usernames and leverage them for further attacks, such as brute-force or phishing campaigns. As of time of publication, no known patched versions are available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-48932|2024-10-24T21:00:27.791Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 21:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-49357|2024-10-24T21:21:45.700Z -- icewhaletech -- zimaos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49357</link>
      <description>ZimaOS is a fork of CasaOS, an operating system for Zima devices and x86-64 systems with UEFI. In version 1.2.4 and all prior versions, the API endpoints in ZimaOS, such as `http://&lt;Server-IP&gt;/v1/users/image?path=/var/lib/casaos/1/app_order.json` and `http://&lt;Server-IP&gt;/v1/users/image?path=/var/lib/casaos/1/system.json`, expose sensitive data like installed applications and system information without requiring any authentication or authorization. This sensitive data leak can be exploited by attackers to gain detailed knowledge about the system setup, installed applications, and other critical information. As of time of publication, no known patched versions are available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-49357|2024-10-24T21:21:45.700Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 21:21:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-49359|2024-10-24T21:33:07.687Z -- icewhaletech -- zimaos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49359</link>
      <description>ZimaOS is a fork of CasaOS, an operating system for Zima devices and x86-64 systems with UEFI. In version 1.2.4 and all prior versions, the API endpoint `http://&lt;Zima_Server_IP:PORT&gt;/v2_1/file` in ZimaOS is vulnerable to a directory traversal attack, allowing authenticated users to list the contents of any directory on the server. By manipulating the path parameter, attackers can access sensitive system directories such as `/etc`, potentially exposing critical configuration files and increasing the risk of further attacks. As of time of publication, no known patched versions are available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-49359|2024-10-24T21:33:07.687Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 21:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-49358|2024-10-24T21:25:57.320Z -- icewhaletech -- zimaos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49358</link>
      <description>ZimaOS is a fork of CasaOS, an operating system for Zima devices and x86-64 systems with UEFI. In version 1.2.4 and all prior versions, the API endpoint `http://&lt;Server-IP&gt;/v1/users/login` in ZimaOS returns distinct responses based on whether a username exists or the password is incorrect. This behavior can be exploited for username enumeration, allowing attackers to determine whether a user exists in the system or not. Attackers can leverage this information in further attacks, such as credential stuffing or targeted password brute-forcing. As of time of publication, no known patched versions are available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-49358|2024-10-24T21:25:57.320Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 21:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-48931|2024-10-24T20:49:44.077Z -- icewhaletech -- zimaos</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48931</link>
      <description>ZimaOS is a fork of CasaOS, an operating system for Zima devices and x86-64 systems with UEFI. In version 1.2.4 and all prior versions, the ZimaOS API endpoint `http:///v3/file?token=&amp;amp;files=` is vulnerable to arbitrary file reading due to improper input validation. By manipulating the `files` parameter, authenticated users can read sensitive system files, including `/etc/shadow`, which contains password hashes for all users. This vulnerability exposes critical system data and poses a high risk for privilege escalation or system compromise. The vulnerability occurs because the API endpoint does not validate or restrict file paths provided via the `files` parameter. An attacker can exploit this by manipulating the file path to access sensitive files outside the intended directory. As of time of publication, no known patched versions are available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-48931|2024-10-24T20:49:44.077Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:49:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
