<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Trellix -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/trellix/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Trellix -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5607|2023-11-27T10:46:46.626Z -- trellix -- trellix%20application%20and%20change%20control%20%28tacc%29
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5607</link>
      <description>
An improper limitation of a path name to a restricted directory (path traversal) vulnerability in the TACC ePO extension, for on-premises ePO servers, prior to version 8.4.0 could lead to an authorised administrator attacker executing arbitrary code through uploading a specially crafted GTI reputation file. The attacker would need the appropriate privileges to access the relevant section of the User Interface. The import logic has been updated to restrict file types and content. 

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5607|2023-11-27T10:46:46.626Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 10:36:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5445|2023-11-17T10:01:36.927Z -- trellix -- epolicy%20orchestrator
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5445</link>
      <description>
An open redirect vulnerability in ePolicy Orchestrator prior to 5.10.0 CP1 Update 2, allows a remote low privileged user to modify the URL parameter for the purpose of redirecting URL request(s) to a malicious site. This impacts the dashboard area of the user interface. A user would need to be logged into ePO to trigger this vulnerability. To exploit this the attacker must change the HTTP payload post submission, prior to it reaching the ePO server.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5445|2023-11-17T10:01:36.927Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 10:01:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5444|2023-11-17T09:59:39.706Z -- trellix -- epolicy%20orchestrator
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5444</link>
      <description>
A Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in ePolicy Orchestrator prior to 5.10.0 CP1 Update 2 allows a remote low privilege user to successfully add a new user with administrator privileges to the ePO server. This impacts the dashboard area of the user interface. To exploit this the attacker must change the HTTP payload post submission, prior to it reaching the ePO server.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5444|2023-11-17T09:59:39.706Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 09:47:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1388|2023-06-07T07:32:52.231Z -- trellix -- trellix%20agent
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1388</link>
      <description>
A heap-based overflow vulnerability in TA prior to version 5.7.9 allows a remote user to alter the page heap in the macmnsvc process memory block, resulting in the service becoming unavailable.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1388|2023-06-07T07:32:52.231Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 07:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0976|2023-06-08T04:48:22.104Z -- trellix -- trellix%20agent
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0976</link>
      <description>
A command Injection Vulnerability in TA for mac-OS prior to version 5.7.9 allows local users to place an arbitrary file into the /Library/Trellix/Agent/bin/ folder. The malicious file is executed by running the TA deployment feature located in the System Tree. 

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0976|2023-06-08T04:48:22.104Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 07:35:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0977|2023-04-03T15:39:43.527Z -- trellix -- trellix%20agent
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0977</link>
      <description>
A heap-based overflow vulnerability in Trellix Agent (Windows and Linux) version 5.7.8 and earlier, allows a remote user to alter the page heap in the macmnsvc process memory block resulting in the service becoming unavailable.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0977|2023-04-03T15:39:43.527Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 15:39:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0221|2023-01-13T15:19:03.662Z -- trellix -- application%20and%20change%20control
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0221</link>
      <description>Product security bypass vulnerability in ACC prior to version 8.3.4 allows a locally logged-in attacker with administrator privileges to bypass the execution controls provided by ACC using the utilman program.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0221|2023-01-13T15:19:03.662Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 15:19:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0978|2023-04-03T15:34:38.217Z -- trellix -- trellix%20intelligent%20sandbox
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0978</link>
      <description>
A command injection vulnerability in Trellix Intelligent Sandbox CLI for version 5.2 and earlier, allows a local user to inject and execute arbitrary operating system commands using specially crafted strings. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of arguments that are passed to specific CLI command. The vulnerability allows the attack

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0978|2023-04-03T15:34:38.217Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 13:29:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0975|2023-04-03T15:27:34.022Z -- trellix -- trellix%20agent
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0975</link>
      <description>
A vulnerability exists in Trellix Agent for Windows version 5.7.8 and earlier, that allows local users, during install/upgrade workflow, to replace one of the Agent’s executables before it can be executed. This allows the user to elevate their permissions.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0975|2023-04-03T15:27:34.022Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 15:27:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0400|2023-02-02T08:17:29.178Z -- trellix -- data%20loss%20prevention%20%28dlp%29
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0400</link>
      <description>
The protection bypass vulnerability in DLP for Windows 11.9.x is addressed in version 11.10.0. This allowed a local user to bypass DLP controls when uploading sensitive data from a mapped drive into a web email client. Loading from a local driver was correctly prevented. Versions prior to 11.9 correctly detected and blocked the attempted upload of sensitive data.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0400|2023-02-02T08:17:29.178Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 16:34:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4814|2023-09-14T06:43:07.463Z -- trellix -- data%20loss%20prevention%20endpoint%20for%20windows
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4814</link>
      <description>
A Privilege escalation vulnerability exists in Trellix Windows DLP endpoint for windows which can be abused to delete any file/folder for which the user does not have permission to.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4814|2023-09-14T06:43:07.463Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 06:43:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3665|2023-10-04T14:32:52.925Z -- trellix -- trellix%20endpoint%20security
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3665</link>
      <description>
A code injection vulnerability in Trellix ENS 10.7.0 April 2023 release and earlier, allowed a local user to disable the ENS AMSI component via environment variables,
leading to denial of service and or the execution of arbitrary code.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3665|2023-10-04T14:32:52.925Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 14:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3946|2023-07-26T05:10:44.967Z -- trellix -- trellix%20epo
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3946</link>
      <description>
A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in ePO prior to 5.10 SP1 Update 1allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to potentially obtain access to an ePO administrator's session by convincing the authenticated ePO administrator to click on a carefully crafted link. This would lead to limited access to sensitive information and limited ability to alter some information in ePO.


</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3946|2023-07-26T05:10:44.967Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 05:10:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3438|2023-07-03T07:35:24.255Z -- trellix -- trellix%20move
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3438</link>
      <description>
An unquoted Windows search path vulnerability existed in the install the MOVE 4.10.x and earlier Windows install service (mvagtsce.exe). 
The misconfiguration allowed an unauthorized local user to insert arbitrary code into the unquoted service path to obtain privilege escalation and stop antimalware services.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3438|2023-07-03T07:35:24.255Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 07:35:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3314|2023-07-03T08:02:29.010Z -- trellix -- enterprise%20security%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3314</link>
      <description>
A vulnerability arises out of a failure to comprehensively sanitize the processing of a zip file(s). Incomplete neutralization of external commands used to control the process execution of the .zip application allows an authorized user to obtain control of the .zip application to execute arbitrary commands or obtain elevation of system privileges.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3314|2023-07-03T08:02:29.010Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 08:02:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3313|2023-07-03T07:53:15.697Z -- trellix -- enterprise%20security%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3313</link>
      <description>
An OS common injection vulnerability exists in the ESM certificate API, whereby incorrectly neutralized special elements may have allowed an unauthorized user to execute system command injection for the purpose of privilege escalation or to execute arbitrary commands.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3313|2023-07-03T07:53:15.697Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 07:53:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6070|2023-11-29T08:53:57.903Z -- trellix -- trellix%20enterprise%20security%20manager%20%28esm%29
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6070</link>
      <description>
A server-side request forgery vulnerability in ESM prior to version 11.6.8 allows a low privileged authenticated user to upload arbitrary content, potentially altering configuration. This is possible through the certificate validation functionality where the API accepts uploaded content and doesn't parse for invalid data

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6070|2023-11-29T08:53:57.903Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 08:53:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6119|2023-11-16T09:39:30.357Z -- trellix -- getsusp
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6119</link>
      <description>
An Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in Trellix GetSusp prior to version 5.0.0.27 allows a local, low privilege attacker to gain access to files that usually require a higher privilege level.  This is caused by GetSusp not correctly protecting a directory that it creates during execution, allowing an attacker to take over file handles used by GetSusp. As this runs with high privileges, the attacker gains elevated permissions. The file handles are opened as read-only. 

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6119|2023-11-16T09:39:30.357Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 09:39:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6071|2023-11-30T12:48:51.618Z -- trellix -- esm
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6071</link>
      <description>
An Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a command vulnerability in ESM prior to version 11.6.9 allows a remote administrator to execute arbitrary code as root on the ESM. This is possible as the input isn't correctly sanitized when adding a new data source.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6071|2023-11-30T12:48:51.618Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 12:48:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6072|2024-06-04T17:17:06.498Z -- trellix -- trellix%20central%20management%20%28cm%29
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6072</link>
      <description>
A cross-site scripting vulnerability in Trellix Central Management (CM) prior to 9.1.3.97129 allows a remote authenticated attacker to craft CM dashboard internal requests causing arbitrary content to be injected into the response when accessing the CM dashboard.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6072|2024-06-04T17:17:06.498Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:39:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0310|2024-01-10T10:43:46.006Z -- trellix -- trellix%20endpoint%20security%20%28ens%29%20web%20control
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0310</link>
      <description>
A content-security-policy vulnerability in ENS Control browser extension prior to 10.7.0 Update 15 allows a remote attacker to alter the response header parameter setting to switch the content security policy into report-only mode, allowing an attacker to bypass the content-security-policy configuration. 

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0310|2024-01-10T10:43:46.006Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 10:43:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0213|2024-01-09T13:01:13.209Z -- trellix -- trellix%20agent%20%28ta%29
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0213</link>
      <description>
A buffer overflow vulnerability in TA for Linux and TA for MacOS prior to 5.8.1 allows a local user to gain elevated permissions, or cause a Denial of Service (DoS), through exploiting a memory corruption issue in the TA service, which runs as root. This may also result in the disabling of event reporting to ePO, caused by failure to validate input from the file correctly. 

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0213|2024-01-09T13:01:13.209Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 13:01:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0206|2024-01-09T12:56:46.957Z -- trellix -- anti-malware%20engine
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0206</link>
      <description>
A symbolic link manipulation vulnerability in Trellix Anti-Malware Engine prior to the January 2024 release allows an authenticated local user to potentially gain an escalation of privileges. This was achieved by adding an entry to the registry under the Trellix ENS registry folder with a symbolic link to files that the user wouldn't normally have permission to. After a scan, the Engine would follow the links and remove the files

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0206|2024-01-09T12:56:46.957Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 12:56:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4843|2024-06-04T17:54:26.124Z -- trellix -- epolicy%20orchestrator
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4843</link>
      <description>ePO doesn't allow a regular privileged user to delete tasks or assignments. Insecure direct object references that allow a least privileged user to manipulate the client task and client task assignments, hence escalating his/her privilege.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4843|2024-06-04T17:54:26.124Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 06:04:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4844|2024-06-04T17:53:07.708Z -- trellix -- epolicy%20orchestrator
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4844</link>
      <description>Hardcoded credentials vulnerability in Trellix ePolicy Orchestrator (ePO) on Premise prior to 5.10 Service Pack 1 Update 2 allows an attacker with admin privileges on the ePO server to read the contents of the orion.keystore file, allowing them to access the ePO database encryption key.  This was possible through using a hard coded password for the keystore.  Access Control restrictions on the file mean this would not be exploitable unless the user is the system admin for the server that ePO is running on.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4844|2024-06-04T17:53:07.708Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 06:19:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
