<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for MediaTek, Inc. -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/mediatek%2C%20inc./all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for MediaTek, Inc. -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 23:21:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-20025|2024-03-04T02:43:35.600Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6739, MT6757, MT6761, MT6763, MT6765, MT6768, MT6771, MT6779, MT6785, MT6833, MT6853, MT6873, MT6877, MT6885, MT6893, MT8167, MT8168, MT8173, MT8175, MT8185, MT8195, MT8321, MT8362A, MT8365, MT8385, MT8395, MT8666, MT8673, MT8678, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8781, MT8786, MT8788, MT8789, MT8791, MT8791T, MT8796, MT8797, MT8798</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20025</link><description>In da, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541686; Issue ID: ALPS08541686.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20025|2024-03-04T02:43:35.600Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 02:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20064|2024-05-06T02:51:58.538Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6580, MT6761, MT6762, MT6768, MT6781, MT6789, MT6833, MT6853, MT6853T, MT6855, MT6873, MT6875, MT6877, MT6879, MT6883, MT6885, MT6886, MT6889, MT6891, MT6893, MT6895, MT6983, MT6985, MT6989, MT8678, MT8755, MT8775, MT8792, MT8796</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20064</link><description>In wlan service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08572601; Issue ID: MSV-1229.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20064|2024-05-06T02:51:58.538Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 02:51:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20033|2024-03-04T02:43:48.493Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT2713, MT6739, MT6761, MT6765, MT6768, MT6771, MT6779, MT6785, MT6789, MT6835, MT6855, MT6879, MT6883, MT6885, MT6886, MT6893, MT6895, MT6983, MT6985, MT8167, MT8167S, MT8168, MT8173, MT8175, MT8185, MT8188, MT8195, MT8321, MT8362A, MT8365, MT8370, MT8385, MT8390, MT8395, MT8666, MT8667, MT8673, MT8675, MT8676, MT8678, MT8755, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8775, MT8781, MT8786, MT8788, MT8789, MT8791, MT8792, MT8796, MT8797, MT8798</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20033</link><description>In nvram, there is a possible information disclosure due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08499945; Issue ID: ALPS08499945.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20033|2024-03-04T02:43:48.493Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 02:43:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20048|2024-04-01T02:35:09.283Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT2713, MT6781, MT6789, MT6835, MT6855, MT6879, MT6886, MT6895, MT6983, MT6985, MT6989, MT8167, MT8168, MT8173, MT8175, MT8188, MT8195, MT8321, MT8362A, MT8365, MT8385, MT8390, MT8395, MT8666, MT8667, MT8673, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8781, MT8786, MT8788, MT8789, MT8791, MT8791T, MT8796, MT8797, MT8798</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20048</link><description>In flashc, there is a possible information disclosure due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541769; Issue ID: ALPS08541769.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20048|2024-04-01T02:35:09.283Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:35:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20009|2024-02-05T05:59:29.526Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6580, MT6739, MT6761, MT6762, MT6765, MT6779, MT6785, MT6789, MT6833, MT6835, MT6853, MT6853T, MT6855, MT6873, MT6877, MT6879, MT6883, MT6885, MT6886, MT6889, MT6895, MT6983, MT6985, MT8163, MT8167, MT8167S, MT8168, MT8173, MT8175, MT8176, MT8185, MT8188, MT8188T</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20009</link><description>In alac decoder, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08441150; Issue ID: ALPS08441150.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20009|2024-02-05T05:59:29.526Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 05:59:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20029|2024-03-04T02:43:45.099Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6985, MT6989, MT8678, MT8796</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20029</link><description>In wlan firmware, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08477406; Issue ID: MSV-1010.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20029|2024-03-04T02:43:45.099Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 02:43:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20044|2024-04-01T02:35:02.526Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6739, MT6757, MT6761, MT6763, MT6765, MT6768, MT6771, MT6779, MT6781, MT6785, MT6833, MT6853, MT6873, MT6877, MT6885, MT6893, MT8167, MT8168, MT8173, MT8175, MT8185, MT8195, MT8321, MT8362A, MT8365, MT8385, MT8395, MT8666, MT8673, MT8678, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8781, MT8786, MT8788, MT8789, MT8791, MT8791T, MT8796, MT8797, MT8798</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20044</link><description>In da, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541784; Issue ID: ALPS08541784.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20044|2024-04-01T02:35:02.526Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20013|2024-02-05T05:59:36.678Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6580, MT6731, MT6735, MT6737, MT6739, MT6753, MT6757, MT6757C, MT6757CD, MT6757CH, MT6761, MT6762, MT6763, MT6765, MT6768, MT6769, MT6771, MT6779, MT6781, MT6785, MT6789, MT6833, MT6835, MT6853, MT6853T, MT6855, MT6873, MT6875, MT6877, MT6879, MT6883, MT6885, MT6886, MT6889, MT6891, MT6893, MT6895, MT6983, MT6985, MT8185, MT8321, MT8385, MT8666, MT8667, MT8673, MT8675, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8781, MT8786, MT8788, MT8789, MT8791, MT8791T, MT8797, MT8798</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20013</link><description>In keyInstall, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08471742; Issue ID: ALPS08308608.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20013|2024-02-05T05:59:36.678Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 05:59:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20005|2024-03-04T02:43:29.245Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6761, MT6762, MT6763, MT6765, MT6768, MT6769, MT6771, MT6779, MT6781, MT6785, MT6789, MT6833, MT6835, MT6853, MT6853T, MT6855, MT6873, MT6875, MT6877, MT6879, MT6883, MT6885, MT6886, MT6889, MT6891, MT6893, MT6895, MT6983, MT6985, MT8666, MT8666A, MT8666B, MT8667, MT8673, MT8675, MT8676, MT8678</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20005</link><description>In da, there is a possible permission bypass due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08355599; Issue ID: ALPS08355599.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20005|2024-03-04T02:43:29.245Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 02:43:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20052|2024-04-01T02:35:16.365Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT2713, MT2737, MT6781, MT6789, MT6835, MT6855, MT6879, MT6880, MT6886, MT6890, MT6895, MT6980, MT6983, MT6985, MT6989, MT6990, MT8167, MT8168, MT8173, MT8175, MT8188, MT8195, MT8321, MT8362A, MT8365, MT8385, MT8390, MT8395, MT8666, MT8667, MT8673, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8781, MT8786, MT8788, MT8789, MT8791, MT8791T, MT8796, MT8797, MT8798</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20052</link><description>In flashc, there is a possible information disclosure due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541757; Issue ID: ALPS08541761.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20052|2024-04-01T02:35:16.365Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:35:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20053|2024-04-01T02:35:18.101Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT2713, MT2737, MT6781, MT6789, MT6835, MT6855, MT6879, MT6880, MT6886, MT6890, MT6895, MT6980, MT6983, MT6985, MT6989, MT6990, MT8167, MT8168, MT8173, MT8175, MT8188, MT8195, MT8321, MT8362A, MT8365, MT8385, MT8390, MT8395, MT8666, MT8667, MT8673, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8781, MT8786, MT8788, MT8789, MT8791, MT8791T, MT8796, MT8797, MT8798</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20053</link><description>In flashc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541757; Issue ID: ALPS08541764.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20053|2024-04-01T02:35:18.101Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:35:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20004|2024-02-05T05:59:44.132Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT2735, MT6297, MT6833, MT6853, MT6855, MT6873, MT6875, MT6875T, MT6877, MT6880, MT6883, MT6885, MT6889, MT6890, MT6891, MT6893, MT8675, MT8791, MT8791T, MT8797</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20004</link><description>In Modem NL1, there is a possible system crash due to an improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service, if NW sent invalid NR RRC Connection Setup message, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01191612; Issue ID: MOLY01195812 (MSV-985).</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20004|2024-02-05T05:59:44.132Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 05:59:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20012|2024-02-05T05:59:35.241Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6580, MT6731, MT6735, MT6737, MT6739, MT6753, MT6757, MT6757C, MT6757CD, MT6757CH, MT6761, MT6762, MT6763, MT6765, MT6768, MT6769, MT6771, MT6779, MT6781, MT6785, MT6789, MT6833, MT6835, MT6853, MT6853T, MT6855, MT6873, MT6875, MT6877, MT6879, MT6883, MT6885, MT6886, MT6889, MT6891, MT6895, MT6983, MT6985, MT8321, MT8385, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8781, MT8786, MT8788, MT8789, MT8791T, MT8797, MT8798</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20012</link><description>In keyInstall, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to type confusion. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08358566; Issue ID: ALPS08358566.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20012|2024-02-05T05:59:35.241Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 05:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20045|2024-04-01T02:35:04.246Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6833, MT6835, MT6853, MT6853T, MT6855, MT6873, MT6875, MT6877, MT6879, MT6883, MT6885, MT6886, MT6889, MT6983, MT6985, MT6989, MT8167, MT8167S, MT8168, MT8188, MT8195, MT8321, MT8385, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8781, MT8786, MT8788, MT8789, MT8791, MT8797, MT8798</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20045</link><description>In audio, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect calculation of buffer size. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08024748; Issue ID: ALPS08029526.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20045|2024-04-01T02:35:04.246Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:35:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20028|2024-03-04T02:43:40.370Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6739, MT6757, MT6761, MT6763, MT6765, MT6768, MT6771, MT6779, MT6785, MT6833, MT6853, MT6873, MT6877, MT6885, MT6893, MT8163, MT8167, MT8168, MT8512</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20028</link><description>In da, there is a possible out of bounds write due to lack of valudation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541632; Issue ID: ALPS08541687.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20028|2024-03-04T02:43:40.370Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 02:43:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20049|2024-04-01T02:35:11.038Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT2713, MT2737, MT6781, MT6789, MT6835, MT6855, MT6879, MT6880, MT6886, MT6890, MT6895, MT6980, MT6983, MT6985, MT6989, MT6990, MT8167, MT8168, MT8173, MT8175, MT8188, MT8195, MT8321, MT8362A, MT8365, MT8385, MT8390, MT8395, MT8666, MT8667, MT8673, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8781, MT8786, MT8788, MT8789, MT8791, MT8791T, MT8796, MT8797, MT8798</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20049</link><description>In flashc, there is a possible information disclosure due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541765; Issue ID: ALPS08541765.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20049|2024-04-01T02:35:11.038Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:35:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20032|2024-03-04T02:43:46.798Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6580, MT6739, MT6761, MT6765, MT6768, MT6779, MT6781, MT6785, MT6789, MT6833, MT6835, MT6853, MT6855, MT6873, MT6877, MT6879, MT6883, MT6885, MT6886, MT6889, MT6893, MT6895, MT6983, MT6985, MT6989, MT8321, MT8673, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8781, MT8789, MT8791, MT8792, MT8796</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20032</link><description>In aee, there is a possible permission bypass due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08487630; Issue ID: MSV-1020.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20032|2024-03-04T02:43:46.798Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 02:43:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20024|2024-03-04T02:43:34.025Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6781, MT6789, MT6833, MT6835, MT6879, MT6886, MT6895, MT6983, MT6985, MT6989, MT8666, MT8666A, MT8666B, MT8667, MT8673, MT8676, MT8678</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20024</link><description>In flashc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to lack of valudation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541635; Issue ID: ALPS08541635.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20024|2024-03-04T02:43:34.025Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 02:43:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20039|2024-04-01T02:34:49.330Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT2731, MT2735, MT2737, MT3967, MT6297, MT6298, MT6739, MT6761, MT6762, MT6762D, MT6762M, MT6763, MT6765, MT6765T, MT6767, MT6768, MT6769, MT6769T, MT6769Z, MT6771, MT6779, MT6781, MT6783, MT6785, MT6785T, MT6785U, MT6789, MT6813, MT6815, MT6833, MT6835, MT6853, MT6855, MT6873, MT6875, MT6875T, MT6877, MT6879, MT6880, MT6883, MT6885, MT6886, MT6889, MT6890, MT6891, MT6893, MT6895, MT6895T, MT6896, MT6897, MT6980, MT6980D, MT6983, MT6985, MT6986, MT6986D, MT6989, MT6990, MT8666, MT8667, MT8673, MT8675, MT8676, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8781, MT8786, MT8788, MT8791, MT8791T, MT8792, MT8796, MT8797, MT8798</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20039</link><description>In modem protocol, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01240012; Issue ID: MSV-1215.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20039|2024-04-01T02:34:49.330Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20042|2024-04-01T02:34:59.065Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6739, MT6757, MT6761, MT6763, MT6765, MT6768, MT6771, MT6779, MT6781, MT6785, MT6833, MT6853, MT6873, MT6877, MT6885, MT6893, MT8167, MT8168, MT8173, MT8175, MT8183, MT8195, MT8321, MT8362A, MT8365, MT8385, MT8395, MT8666, MT8673, MT8678, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8781, MT8786, MT8788, MT8789, MT8791, MT8791T, MT8796, MT8797, MT8798</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20042</link><description>In da, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541780; Issue ID: ALPS08541780.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20042|2024-04-01T02:34:59.065Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:34:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20015|2024-02-05T05:59:38.166Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6739, MT6753, MT6757, MT6761, MT6762, MT6763, MT6765, MT6768, MT6769, MT6781, MT6833, MT6835, MT6853, MT6855, MT6873, MT6875, MT6877, MT6879, MT6883, MT6885, MT6886, MT6889, MT6893, MT6895, MT6983, MT6985, MT8321, MT8667, MT8673, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8781, MT8786, MT8788, MT8789, MT8791T, MT8797, MT8798</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20015</link><description>In telephony, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to a permissions bypass. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08441419; Issue ID: ALPS08441419.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20015|2024-02-05T05:59:38.166Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 05:59:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20003|2024-02-05T05:59:33.841Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT2735, MT6297, MT6833, MT6853, MT6855, MT6873, MT6875, MT6875T, MT6877, MT6880, MT6883, MT6885, MT6889, MT6890, MT6891, MT6893, MT8675, MT8791, MT8791T, MT8797</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20003</link><description>In Modem NL1, there is a possible system crash due to an improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service, if NW sent invalid NR RRC Connection Setup message, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01191612; Issue ID: MOLY01191612 (MSV-981).</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20003|2024-02-05T05:59:33.841Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 05:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20054|2024-04-01T02:35:19.821Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT2735, MT2737, MT6762, MT6765, MT6769, MT6833, MT6835, MT6853, MT6855, MT6873, MT6875, MT6877, MT6879, MT6883, MT6885, MT6889, MT6890, MT6891, MT6893, MT6895, MT6983, MT6985, MT6989, MT6990, MT8168, MT8173, MT8195, MT8321, MT8385, MT8390, MT8666, MT8667, MT8673, MT8676, MT8678, MT8755, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8775, MT8781, MT8786, MT8788, MT8791T, MT8792, MT8796, MT8893</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20054</link><description>In gnss, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08580200; Issue ID: ALPS08580200.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20054|2024-04-01T02:35:19.821Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:35:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20023|2024-03-04T02:43:32.414Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT2713, MT2737, MT6781, MT6789, MT6835, MT6855, MT6879, MT6880, MT6886, MT6890, MT6895, MT6980, MT6983, MT6985, MT6989, MT6990, MT8188, MT8188T, MT8370, MT8390, MT8673, MT8676, MT8678</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20023</link><description>In flashc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to lack of valudation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541638; Issue ID: ALPS08541638.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20023|2024-03-04T02:43:32.414Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 02:43:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20019|2024-03-04T02:43:27.661Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT7925, MT7927</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20019</link><description>In wlan driver, there is a possible memory leak due to improper input handling. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00351241; Issue ID: MSV-1173.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20019|2024-03-04T02:43:27.661Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 02:43:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20058|2024-05-06T02:51:53.743Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6765, MT6768, MT6785, MT6833, MT6853, MT6855, MT6893, MT6983, MT8321, MT8385, MT8755, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8771, MT8781, MT8786, MT8788, MT8789, MT8791T, MT8792, MT8795T, MT8796, MT8797, MT8798</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20058</link><description>In keyInstall, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08580204; Issue ID: ALPS08580204.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20058|2024-05-06T02:51:53.743Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 02:51:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20059|2024-05-06T02:51:55.410Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6580, MT6739, MT6761, MT6765, MT6768, MT6781, MT6789, MT6833, MT6835, MT6853, MT6855, MT6877, MT6879, MT6883, MT6885, MT6886, MT6889, MT6893, MT6895, MT6983, MT6985, MT6989, MT8188, MT8370, MT8390</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20059</link><description>In da, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to an incorrect status check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541749; Issue ID: ALPS08541749.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20059|2024-05-06T02:51:55.410Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 02:51:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20018|2024-03-04T02:43:26.082Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT7615</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20018</link><description>In wlan driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00348479; Issue ID: MSV-1019.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20018|2024-03-04T02:43:26.082Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 02:43:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20034|2024-03-04T02:43:50.219Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6761, MT6765, MT6768, MT6855, MT6895, MT8167, MT8168, MT8188, MT8321, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8781, MT8786, MT8788, MT8789, MT8791T, MT8797, MT8798</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20034</link><description>In battery, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08488849; Issue ID: ALPS08488849.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20034|2024-03-04T02:43:50.219Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 02:43:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20022|2024-03-04T02:43:30.832Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT2737, MT6789, MT6835, MT6855, MT6879, MT6880, MT6886, MT6890, MT6895, MT6980, MT6983, MT6985, MT6989, MT6990, MT8321, MT8385, MT8666, MT8667, MT8673, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8781, MT8786, MT8788, MT8789, MT8791, MT8796, MT8797, MT8798</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20022</link><description>In lk, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08528255; Issue ID: ALPS08528255.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20022|2024-03-04T02:43:30.832Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 02:43:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20055|2024-04-01T02:35:21.521Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT2713, MT8168, MT8173, MT8175, MT8188, MT8195, MT8365, MT8370, MT8390, MT8395, MT8673, MT8696, MT8781, MT8795T, MT8798, MT8871</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20055</link><description>In imgsys, there is a possible information disclosure due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation Patch ID: ALPS08518692; Issue ID: MSV-1012.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20055|2024-04-01T02:35:21.521Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:35:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20002|2024-02-05T05:59:42.613Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT5583, MT5586, MT5691, MT5695, MT5696, MT9010, MT9011, MT9012, MT9015, MT9016, MT9020, MT9021, MT9022, MT9025, MT9026, MT9216, MT9218, MT9220, MT9221, MT9222, MT9255, MT9256, MT9266, MT9269, MT9286, MT9288, MT9602, MT9603, MT9610, MT9611, MT9612, MT9613, MT9615, MT9617, MT9618, MT9629, MT9630, MT9631, MT9632, MT9633, MT9636, MT9638, MT9639, MT9649, MT9650, MT9652, MT9653, MT9660, MT9666, MT9667, MT9669, MT9671, MT9675, MT9679, MT9685, MT9686, MT9688, MT9689</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20002</link><description>In TVAPI, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: DTV03961715; Issue ID: DTV03961715.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20002|2024-02-05T05:59:42.613Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 05:59:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20043|2024-04-01T02:35:00.812Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6739, MT6757, MT6761, MT6763, MT6765, MT6768, MT6771, MT6779, MT6781, MT6785, MT6833, MT6853, MT6873, MT6877, MT6885, MT6893, MT8167, MT8168, MT8173, MT8175, MT8185, MT8195, MT8321, MT8362A, MT8365, MT8385, MT8395, MT8666, MT8673, MT8678, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8781, MT8786, MT8788, MT8789, MT8791, MT8791T, MT8796, MT8797, MT8798</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20043</link><description>In da, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541781; Issue ID: ALPS08541781.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20043|2024-04-01T02:35:00.812Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20038|2024-03-04T02:43:54.898Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6739, MT6761, MT6765, MT6768, MT6779, MT6781, MT6785, MT6789, MT6833, MT6835, MT6853, MT6855, MT6873, MT6877, MT6879, MT6883, MT6885, MT6886, MT6889, MT6893, MT6895, MT6897, MT6983, MT6985, MT6989, MT8168, MT8188, MT8195, MT8673, MT8675</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20038</link><description>In pq, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08495932; Issue ID: ALPS08495932.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20038|2024-03-04T02:43:54.898Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 02:43:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20056|2024-05-06T02:51:47.286Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6739, MT6761, MT6765, MT6768, MT6781, MT6785, MT6789, MT6833, MT6835, MT6853, MT6855, MT6873, MT6880, MT6885, MT6886, MT6890, MT6893, MT6895, MT6897, MT6983, MT6985, MT6989, MT8666, MT8667, MT8673, MT8676, MT8678</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20056</link><description>In preloader, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to an insecure default value. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08528185; Issue ID: ALPS08528185.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20056|2024-05-06T02:51:47.286Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 02:51:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20001|2024-02-05T05:59:41.091Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT5583, MT5586, MT5691, MT5695, MT5696, MT9010, MT9011, MT9012, MT9015, MT9016, MT9020, MT9021, MT9022, MT9025, MT9026, MT9216, MT9218, MT9220, MT9221, MT9222, MT9255, MT9256, MT9266, MT9269, MT9286, MT9288, MT9602, MT9603, MT9610, MT9611, MT9612, MT9613, MT9615, MT9617, MT9618, MT9629, MT9630, MT9631, MT9632, MT9633, MT9636, MT9638, MT9639, MT9649, MT9650, MT9652, MT9653, MT9660, MT9666, MT9667, MT9669, MT9671, MT9675, MT9679, MT9685, MT9686, MT9688, MT9689</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20001</link><description>In TVAPI, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: DTV03961601; Issue ID: DTV03961601.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20001|2024-02-05T05:59:41.091Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 05:59:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20017|2024-03-07T02:16:46.885Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6890, MT7915, MT7916, MT7981, MT7986</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20017</link><description>In wlan service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation Patch ID: WCNCR00350938; Issue ID: MSV-1132.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20017|2024-03-07T02:16:46.885Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 02:43:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20040|2024-04-01T02:34:53.921Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT2713, MT6580, MT6761, MT6762, MT6768, MT6781, MT6789, MT6833, MT6853, MT6853T, MT6855, MT6873, MT6875, MT6877, MT6879, MT6883, MT6885, MT6886, MT6889, MT6890, MT6891, MT6893, MT6895, MT6983, MT6985, MT6989, MT6990, MT7902, MT7915, MT7916, MT7920, MT7921, MT7922, MT7925, MT7927, MT7981, MT7986, MT8188, MT8195, MT8370, MT8390, MT8395, MT8518S, MT8532, MT8673, MT8678, MT8781, MT8791T, MT8792, MT8796, MT8797, MT8798</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20040</link><description>In wlan firmware, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08360153 (for MT6XXX chipsets) / WCNCR00363530 (for MT79XX chipsets); Issue ID: MSV-979.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20040|2024-04-01T02:34:53.921Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:34:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20037|2024-03-04T02:43:53.317Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6739, MT6761, MT6765, MT6768, MT6779, MT6781, MT6785, MT6789, MT6833, MT6835, MT6853, MT6855, MT6873, MT6877, MT6879, MT6883, MT6885, MT6886, MT6889, MT6893, MT6895, MT6897, MT6983, MT6985, MT6989, MT8168, MT8188, MT8195, MT8673, MT8675</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20037</link><description>In pq, there is a possible write-what-where condition due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08495937; Issue ID: ALPS08495937.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20037|2024-03-04T02:43:53.317Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 02:43:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20060|2024-05-06T02:51:57.024Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6580, MT6739, MT6761, MT6765, MT6768, MT6781, MT6789, MT6833, MT6835, MT6853, MT6855, MT6877, MT6879, MT6883, MT6885, MT6886, MT6889, MT6893, MT6895, MT6983, MT6985, MT6989, MT8188, MT8370, MT8390</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20060</link><description>In da, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to an incorrect status check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541749; Issue ID: ALPS08541754.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20060|2024-05-06T02:51:57.024Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 02:51:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20021|2024-05-06T02:52:01.865Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6768, MT6781, MT6785, MT6833, MT6853, MT6873, MT6877, MT6885, MT6893, MT8168, MT8183, MT8188, MT8188T, MT8195, MT8195Z, MT8321, MT8362A, MT8365, MT8385, MT8666, MT8666A, MT8666B, MT8667, MT8673, MT8675, MT8675, MT8676, MT8678, MT8765, MT8766, MT8766Z, MT8768, MT8768A, MT8768B, MT8768T, MT8768Z, MT8781, MT8781, MT8786, MT8788, MT8788T, MT8788, MT8788X, MT8788Z, MT8792, MT8795T, MT8796, MT8798</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20021</link><description>In atf spm, there is a possible way to remap physical memory to virtual memory due to a logic error. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08584568; Issue ID: MSV-1249.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20021|2024-05-06T02:52:01.865Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 02:52:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20020|2024-03-04T02:43:24.572Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT2713, MT2715, MT8173, MT8188, MT8195, MT8390, MT8395</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20020</link><description>In OPTEE, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08522504; Issue ID: ALPS08522504.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20020|2024-03-04T02:43:24.572Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 02:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20036|2024-03-04T02:43:51.821Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6835, MT6855, MT6879, MT6886, MT6895, MT6983, MT6985, MT8792, MT8796, MT8798</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20036</link><description>In vdec, there is a possible permission bypass due to a permissions bypass. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08509508; Issue ID: ALPS08509508.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20036|2024-03-04T02:43:51.821Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 02:43:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20041|2024-04-01T02:34:57.329Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT2713, MT6781, MT6789, MT6835, MT6855, MT6879, MT6886, MT6895, MT6983, MT6985, MT6989, MT8188, MT8673, MT8676, MT8781</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20041</link><description>In da, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541746; Issue ID: ALPS08541746.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20041|2024-04-01T02:34:57.329Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20016|2024-02-05T05:59:39.607Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6735, MT6737, MT6739, MT6753, MT6757, MT6761, MT6763, MT6765, MT6768, MT6771, MT6779, MT6781, MT6785, MT6833, MT6853, MT6855, MT6873, MT6877, MT6879, MT6885, MT6889, MT6893, MT6895, MT6983, MT8168, MT8183, MT8188, MT8195, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8791, MT8797, MT8798</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20016</link><description>In ged, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation Patch ID: ALPS07835901; Issue ID: ALPS07835901.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20016|2024-02-05T05:59:39.607Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 05:59:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20057|2024-05-06T02:51:48.972Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6761, MT6765, MT6768, MT6779, MT6781, MT6785, MT6789, MT6833, MT6835, MT6853, MT6855, MT6873, MT6877, MT6879, MT6883, MT6885, MT6886, MT6889, MT6893, MT6895, MT6897, MT6983, MT8321, MT8385, MT8755, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8771, MT8781, MT8786, MT8788, MT8789, MT8791T, MT8792, MT8795T, MT8796</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20057</link><description>In keyInstall, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08587881; Issue ID: ALPS08587881.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20057|2024-05-06T02:51:48.972Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 02:51:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20031|2024-03-04T02:43:43.509Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6739, MT6757, MT6761, MT6763, MT6765, MT6768, MT6771, MT6779, MT6785, MT6833, MT6853, MT6873, MT6877, MT6885, MT6893, MT8163, MT8167, MT8168, MT8512</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20031</link><description>In da, there is a possible out of bounds write due to lack of valudation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541632; Issue ID: ALPS08541742.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20031|2024-03-04T02:43:43.509Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 02:43:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20027|2024-03-04T02:43:38.785Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6739, MT6757, MT6761, MT6763, MT6765, MT6768, MT6771, MT6779, MT6785, MT6833, MT6853, MT6873, MT6877, MT6885, MT6893, MT8163, MT8167, MT8168, MT8512</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20027</link><description>In da, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541632; Issue ID: ALPS08541633.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20027|2024-03-04T02:43:38.785Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 02:43:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20050|2024-04-01T02:35:12.789Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT2713, MT2737, MT6781, MT6789, MT6835, MT6855, MT6879, MT6880, MT6886, MT6890, MT6895, MT6980, MT6983, MT6985, MT6989, MT6990, MT8167, MT8168, MT8173, MT8175, MT8188, MT8195, MT8321, MT8362A, MT8365, MT8385, MT8390, MT8395, MT8666, MT8667, MT8673, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8781, MT8786, MT8788, MT8789, MT8791, MT8791T, MT8796, MT8797, MT8798</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20050</link><description>In flashc, there is a possible information disclosure due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541757; Issue ID: ALPS08541757.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20050|2024-04-01T02:35:12.789Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:35:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20007|2024-02-05T05:59:28.064Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6580, MT6739, MT6761, MT6762, MT6765, MT6779, MT6785, MT6789, MT6833, MT6835, MT6853, MT6853T, MT6855, MT6873, MT6877, MT6879, MT6883, MT6885, MT6886, MT6889, MT6895, MT6983, MT6985, MT8321, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8786, MT8788, MT8789, MT8791, MT8797, MT8798</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20007</link><description>In mp3 decoder, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a race condition. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08441369; Issue ID: ALPS08441369.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20007|2024-02-05T05:59:28.064Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 05:59:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20011|2024-02-05T05:59:32.380Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6985, MT8127, MT8135, MT8167, MT8167S, MT8168, MT8173, MT8175, MT8176, MT8183, MT8185, MT8188, MT8188T, MT8195, MT8195Z, MT8312C, MT8312D</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20011</link><description>In alac decoder, there is a possible information disclosure due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to remote code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08441146; Issue ID: ALPS08441146.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20011|2024-02-05T05:59:32.380Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 05:59:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20046|2024-04-01T02:35:05.911Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6761, MT6765, MT6768, MT6789, MT6833, MT6855, MT6895, MT8167, MT8168, MT8188, MT8321, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8781, MT8786, MT8788, MT8789, MT8791T, MT8797, MT8798</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20046</link><description>In battery, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08485622; Issue ID: ALPS08485622.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20046|2024-04-01T02:35:05.911Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:35:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20047|2024-04-01T02:35:07.599Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6739, MT6768, MT6781, MT6833, MT6853, MT6877, MT6883, MT6885, MT6893, MT8183, MT8188, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8786, MT8788, MT8791, MT8797</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20047</link><description>In battery, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08587865; Issue ID: ALPS08486807.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20047|2024-04-01T02:35:07.599Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:35:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20010|2024-02-05T05:59:30.948Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6580, MT6731, MT6735, MT6737, MT6739, MT6753, MT6757, MT6757C, MT6757CD, MT6757CH, MT6761, MT6762, MT6763, MT6765, MT6768, MT6769, MT6771, MT6779, MT6781, MT6785, MT6789, MT6833, MT6835, MT6853, MT6853T, MT6855, MT6873, MT6875, MT6877, MT6879, MT6883, MT6885, MT6886, MT6889, MT6891, MT6893, MT6895, MT6983, MT6985, MT8185, MT8321, MT8385, MT8666, MT8667, MT8673, MT8675, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8781, MT8786, MT8788, MT8789, MT8791, MT8791T, MT8797, MT8798</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20010</link><description>In keyInstall, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to type confusion. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08358560; Issue ID: ALPS08358560.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20010|2024-02-05T05:59:30.948Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 05:59:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20006|2024-02-05T05:59:26.595Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT2713, MT6781, MT6880, MT6890, MT8188T</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20006</link><description>In da, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08477148; Issue ID: ALPS08477148.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20006|2024-02-05T05:59:26.595Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 05:59:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20051|2024-04-01T02:35:14.528Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT2713, MT2737, MT6781, MT6789, MT6835, MT6855, MT6879, MT6880, MT6886, MT6890, MT6895, MT6980, MT6983, MT6985, MT6989, MT6990, MT8167, MT8168, MT8173, MT8175, MT8188, MT8195, MT8321, MT8362A, MT8365, MT8385, MT8390, MT8395, MT8666, MT8667, MT8673, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8781, MT8786, MT8788, MT8789, MT8791, MT8791T, MT8796, MT8797, MT8798</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20051</link><description>In flashc, there is a possible system crash due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541757; Issue ID: ALPS08541758.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20051|2024-04-01T02:35:14.528Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:35:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20026|2024-03-04T02:43:37.173Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6739, MT6757, MT6761, MT6763, MT6765, MT6768, MT6771, MT6779, MT6785, MT6833, MT6853, MT6873, MT6877, MT6885, MT6893, MT8163, MT8167, MT8168, MT8512</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20026</link><description>In da, there is a possible information disclosure due to improper input validation. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541632; Issue ID: ALPS08541632.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20026|2024-03-04T02:43:37.173Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 02:43:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20030|2024-03-04T02:43:41.943Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6739, MT6757, MT6761, MT6763, MT6765, MT6768, MT6771, MT6779, MT6785, MT6833, MT6853, MT6873, MT6877, MT6885, MT6893, MT8167, MT8168, MT8195, MT8512</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20030</link><description>In da, there is a possible information disclosure due to improper input validation. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541632; Issue ID: ALPS08541741.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20030|2024-03-04T02:43:41.943Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 02:43:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20065|2024-06-03T02:04:42.174Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6768, MT6781, MT6835, MT6853, MT6855, MT6877, MT6879, MT6885, MT6886, MT6893, MT6983, MT6985, MT6989</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20065</link><description>In telephony, there is a possible information disclosure due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08698617; Issue ID: MSV-1394.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20065|2024-06-03T02:04:42.174Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 02:04:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20067|2024-06-03T02:04:45.365Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6813, MT6815, MT6835, MT6878, MT6897, MT6899, MT6986, MT6986D, MT6991, MT8792</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20067</link><description>In modem, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input invalidation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01267285; Issue ID: MSV-1462.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20067|2024-06-03T02:04:45.365Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 02:04:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20071|2024-06-03T02:04:51.932Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6890, MT6990, MT7622</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20071</link><description>In wlan driver, there is a possible out of bounds read due to improper input validation. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00364733; Issue ID: MSV-1331.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20071|2024-06-03T02:04:51.932Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 02:04:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20070|2024-06-03T02:04:50.274Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6298, MT6813, MT6815, MT6833, MT6835, MT6853, MT6855, MT6873, MT6875, MT6875T, MT6877, MT6878, MT6879, MT6883, MT6885, MT6889, MT6891, MT6893, MT6895, MT6895T, MT6896, MT6897, MT6980, MT6980D, MT6983, MT6990, MT8673, MT8675, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8771, MT8786, MT8791T, MT8792, MT8797, MT8798</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20070</link><description>In modem, there is a possible information disclosure due to using risky cryptographic algorithm during connection establishment negotiation. This could lead to remote information disclosure, when weak encryption algorithm is used, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY00942482; Issue ID: MSV-1469.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20070|2024-06-03T02:04:50.274Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 02:04:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20068|2024-06-03T02:04:47.010Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6298, MT6813, MT6815, MT6835, MT6878, MT6879, MT6895, MT6895T, MT6896, MT6897, MT6899, MT6980, MT6980D, MT6983, MT6986, MT6986D, MT6990, MT6991, MT8673, MT8675, MT8771, MT8791T, MT8792, MT8797, MT8798</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20068</link><description>In modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is no needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01270721; Issue ID: MSV-1479.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20068|2024-06-03T02:04:47.010Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 02:04:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20075|2024-06-03T02:04:58.359Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6833, MT6853, MT6873, MT6877, MT6885, MT6893, MT8185, MT8675, MT8786, MT8789</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20075</link><description>In eemgpu, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08713302; Issue ID: MSV-1393.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20075|2024-06-03T02:04:58.359Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 02:04:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20073|2024-06-03T02:04:55.154Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6890, MT7622</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20073</link><description>In wlan service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00367704; Issue ID: MSV-1411.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20073|2024-06-03T02:04:55.154Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 02:04:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20072|2024-06-03T02:04:53.505Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6890, MT6990, MT7622</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20072</link><description>In wlan driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00364732; Issue ID: MSV-1332.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20072|2024-06-03T02:04:53.505Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 02:04:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20066|2024-06-03T02:04:43.910Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6298, MT6813, MT6815, MT6835, MT6878, MT6879, MT6895, MT6895T, MT6896, MT6897, MT6899, MT6980, MT6980D, MT6983, MT6986, MT6986D, MT6990, MT6991, MT8673, MT8792, MT8798</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20066</link><description>In modem, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is no needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01267281; Issue ID: MSV-1477.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20066|2024-06-03T02:04:43.910Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 02:04:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20074|2024-06-03T02:04:56.653Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6580, MT6739, MT6761, MT6765, MT6768, MT6779, MT6781, MT6785, MT6789, MT6833, MT6835, MT6853, MT6855, MT6873, MT6877, MT6879, MT6883, MT6885, MT6886, MT6889, MT6893, MT6895, MT6897, MT6983, MT6985, MT6989, MT8666, MT8667, MT8673, MT8676</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20074</link><description>In dmc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08668110; Issue ID: MSV-1333.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20074|2024-06-03T02:04:56.653Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 02:04:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20069|2024-06-03T02:04:48.667Z -- MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6833, MT6853, MT6855, MT6873, MT6875, MT6875T, MT6877, MT6883, MT6885, MT6889, MT6891, MT6893, MT8675, MT8771, MT8791T, MT8797</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20069</link><description>In modem, there is a possible selection of less-secure algorithm during the VoWiFi IKE due to a missing DH downgrade check. This could lead to remote information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01286330; Issue ID: MSV-1430.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20069|2024-06-03T02:04:48.667Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 02:04:48 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>