<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for MediaTek, Inc. -- MT2731, MT6570, MT6580, MT6595, MT6732, MT6735, MT6737, MT6737M, MT6738, MT6739, MT6750, MT6750S, MT6752, MT6753, MT6755, MT6757, MT6758, MT6761, MT6762, MT6762D, MT6762M, MT6763, MT6765, MT6765T, MT6767, MT6768, MT6769, MT6769T, MT6769Z, MT6771, MT6775, MT6779, MT6781, MT6783, MT6785, MT6785T, MT6789, MT6795, MT6797, MT6799, MT6813, MT6815, MT6833, MT6835, MT6853, MT6855, MT6873, MT6875, MT6875T, MT6877, MT6878, MT6879, MT6883, MT6885, MT6886, MT6889, MT6891, MT6893, MT6895, MT6895T, MT6896, MT6897, MT6983, MT6985, MT6989, MT8666, MT8666A, MT8667, MT8673, MT8675, MT8765, MT8766, MT8766Z, MT8768, MT8768A, MT8768B, MT8768T, MT8768Z, MT8781, MT8786, MT8788, MT8788T, MT8788X, MT8788Z, MT8791, MT8791T, MT8797, MT8798</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/mediatek%2C%20inc./mt2731%2C%20mt6570%2C%20mt6580%2C%20mt6595%2C%20mt6732%2C%20mt6735%2C%20mt6737%2C%20mt6737m%2C%20mt6738%2C%20mt6739%2C%20mt6750%2C%20mt6750s%2C%20mt6752%2C%20mt6753%2C%20mt6755%2C%20mt6757%2C%20mt6758%2C%20mt6761%2C%20mt6762%2C%20mt6762d%2C%20mt6762m.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for MediaTek, Inc. -- MT2731, MT6570, MT6580, MT6595, MT6732, MT6735, MT6737, MT6737M, MT6738, MT6739, MT6750, MT6750S, MT6752, MT6753, MT6755, MT6757, MT6758, MT6761, MT6762, MT6762D, MT6762M, MT6763, MT6765, MT6765T, MT6767, MT6768, MT6769, MT6769T, MT6769Z, MT6771, MT6775, MT6779, MT6781, MT6783, MT6785, MT6785T, MT6789, MT6795, MT6797, MT6799, MT6813, MT6815, MT6833, MT6835, MT6853, MT6855, MT6873, MT6875, MT6875T, MT6877, MT6878, MT6879, MT6883, MT6885, MT6886, MT6889, MT6891, MT6893, MT6895, MT6895T, MT6896, MT6897, MT6983, MT6985, MT6989, MT8666, MT8666A, MT8667, MT8673, MT8675, MT8765, MT8766, MT8766Z, MT8768, MT8768A, MT8768B, MT8768T, MT8768Z, MT8781, MT8786, MT8788, MT8788T, MT8788X, MT8788Z, MT8791, MT8791T, MT8797, MT8798</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 15:23:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20819|2024-08-02T09:14:40.994Z -- mediatek%2C%20inc. -- mt2731%2C%20mt6570%2C%20mt6580%2C%20mt6595%2C%20mt6732%2C%20mt6735%2C%20mt6737%2C%20mt6737m%2C%20mt6738%2C%20mt6739%2C%20mt6750%2C%20mt6750s%2C%20mt6752%2C%20mt6753%2C%20mt6755%2C%20mt6757%2C%20mt6758%2C%20mt6761%2C%20mt6762%2C%20mt6762d%2C%20mt6762m
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20819</link>
      <description>In CDMA PPP protocol, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege with no additional execution privilege needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01068234; Issue ID: ALPS08010003.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20819|2024-08-02T09:14:40.994Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 02:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
