<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for MediaTek, Inc. -- MT2731, MT2735, MT6297, MT6725, MT6739, MT6761, MT6762, MT6762D, MT6762M, MT6763, MT6765, MT6765T, MT6767, MT6768, MT6769, MT6769T, MT6769Z, MT6771, MT6779, MT6781, MT6783, MT6785, MT6785T, MT6789, MT6833, MT6853, MT6855, MT6873, MT6875, MT6877, MT6879, MT6880, MT6883, MT6885, MT6889, MT6890, MT6891, MT6893, MT6895, MT6983, MT8385, MT8666, MT8667, MT8675, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8786, MT8788, MT8789, MT8791, MT8797</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/mediatek%2C%20inc./mt2731%2C%20mt2735%2C%20mt6297%2C%20mt6725%2C%20mt6739%2C%20mt6761%2C%20mt6762%2C%20mt6762d%2C%20mt6762m%2C%20mt6763%2C%20mt6765%2C%20mt6765t%2C%20mt6767%2C%20mt6768%2C%20mt6769%2C%20mt6769t%2C%20mt6769z%2C%20mt6771%2C%20mt6779%2C%20mt6781%2C%20mt678.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for MediaTek, Inc. -- MT2731, MT2735, MT6297, MT6725, MT6739, MT6761, MT6762, MT6762D, MT6762M, MT6763, MT6765, MT6765T, MT6767, MT6768, MT6769, MT6769T, MT6769Z, MT6771, MT6779, MT6781, MT6783, MT6785, MT6785T, MT6789, MT6833, MT6853, MT6855, MT6873, MT6875, MT6877, MT6879, MT6880, MT6883, MT6885, MT6889, MT6890, MT6891, MT6893, MT6895, MT6983, MT8385, MT8666, MT8667, MT8675, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8786, MT8788, MT8789, MT8791, MT8797</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 11:20:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26446|2024-08-03T05:03:32.927Z -- mediatek%2C%20inc. -- mt2731%2C%20mt2735%2C%20mt6297%2C%20mt6725%2C%20mt6739%2C%20mt6761%2C%20mt6762%2C%20mt6762d%2C%20mt6762m%2C%20mt6763%2C%20mt6765%2C%20mt6765t%2C%20mt6767%2C%20mt6768%2C%20mt6769%2C%20mt6769t%2C%20mt6769z%2C%20mt6771%2C%20mt6779%2C%20mt6781%2C%20mt678
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26446</link>
      <description>In Modem 4G RRC, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service, when concatenating improper SIB12 (CMAS message), with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY00867883; Issue ID: ALPS07274118.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26446|2024-08-03T05:03:32.927Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
