<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for MediaTek, Inc. -- MT2713, MT2735, MT2737, MT6739, MT6761, MT6762, MT6763, MT6765, MT6768, MT6769, MT6771, MT6779, MT6781, MT6785, MT6789, MT6833, MT6835, MT6853, MT6853T, MT6855, MT6873, MT6875, MT6877, MT6879, MT6880, MT6883, MT6885, MT6886, MT6889, MT6890, MT6891, MT6893, MT6895, MT6980, MT6983, MT6985, MT6990, MT8167, MT8167S, MT8168, MT8173, MT8175, MT8185, MT8188, MT8195, MT8321, MT8362A, MT8365, MT8385, MT8395, MT8666, MT8667, MT8673, MT8675, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8781, MT8786, MT8788, MT8789, MT8791, MT8791T, MT8797</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/mediatek%2C%20inc./mt2713%2C%20mt2735%2C%20mt2737%2C%20mt6739%2C%20mt6761%2C%20mt6762%2C%20mt6763%2C%20mt6765%2C%20mt6768%2C%20mt6769%2C%20mt6771%2C%20mt6779%2C%20mt6781%2C%20mt6785%2C%20mt6789%2C%20mt6833%2C%20mt6835%2C%20mt6853%2C%20mt6853t%2C%20mt6855%2C%20mt6873%2C.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for MediaTek, Inc. -- MT2713, MT2735, MT2737, MT6739, MT6761, MT6762, MT6763, MT6765, MT6768, MT6769, MT6771, MT6779, MT6781, MT6785, MT6789, MT6833, MT6835, MT6853, MT6853T, MT6855, MT6873, MT6875, MT6877, MT6879, MT6880, MT6883, MT6885, MT6886, MT6889, MT6890, MT6891, MT6893, MT6895, MT6980, MT6983, MT6985, MT6990, MT8167, MT8167S, MT8168, MT8173, MT8175, MT8185, MT8188, MT8195, MT8321, MT8362A, MT8365, MT8385, MT8395, MT8666, MT8667, MT8673, MT8675, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8781, MT8786, MT8788, MT8789, MT8791, MT8791T, MT8797</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 19:20:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20790|2024-08-02T09:14:40.989Z -- mediatek%2C%20inc. -- mt2713%2C%20mt2735%2C%20mt2737%2C%20mt6739%2C%20mt6761%2C%20mt6762%2C%20mt6763%2C%20mt6765%2C%20mt6768%2C%20mt6769%2C%20mt6771%2C%20mt6779%2C%20mt6781%2C%20mt6785%2C%20mt6789%2C%20mt6833%2C%20mt6835%2C%20mt6853%2C%20mt6853t%2C%20mt6855%2C%20mt6873%2C
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20790</link>
      <description>In nvram, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS07740194; Issue ID: ALPS07740194.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20790|2024-08-02T09:14:40.989Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 03:21:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
