<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for MediaTek, Inc. -- MT2735, MT6779, MT6781, MT6783, MT6785, MT6785T, MT6789, MT6813, MT6833, MT6833P, MT6835, MT6853, MT6853T, MT6855, MT6873, MT6875, MT6877, MT6877T, MT6878, MT6879, MT6880, MT6883, MT6885, MT6886, MT6889, MT6890, MT6891, MT6893, MT6895, MT6895T, MT6896, MT6897, MT6980, MT6980D, MT6983T, MT6983W, MT6983Z, MT6985, MT6985T, MT6989, MT6990</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/mediatek%2C%20inc./mt2735%2C%20mt6779%2C%20mt6781%2C%20mt6783%2C%20mt6785%2C%20mt6785t%2C%20mt6789%2C%20mt6813%2C%20mt6833%2C%20mt6833p%2C%20mt6835%2C%20mt6853%2C%20mt6853t%2C%20mt6855%2C%20mt6873%2C%20mt6875%2C%20mt6877%2C%20mt6877t%2C%20mt6878%2C%20mt6879%2C%20mt6880.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for MediaTek, Inc. -- MT2735, MT6779, MT6781, MT6783, MT6785, MT6785T, MT6789, MT6813, MT6833, MT6833P, MT6835, MT6853, MT6853T, MT6855, MT6873, MT6875, MT6877, MT6877T, MT6878, MT6879, MT6880, MT6883, MT6885, MT6886, MT6889, MT6890, MT6891, MT6893, MT6895, MT6895T, MT6896, MT6897, MT6980, MT6980D, MT6983T, MT6983W, MT6983Z, MT6985, MT6985T, MT6989, MT6990</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32874|2024-01-02T02:49:38.153Z -- mediatek%2C%20inc. -- mt2735%2C%20mt6779%2C%20mt6781%2C%20mt6783%2C%20mt6785%2C%20mt6785t%2C%20mt6789%2C%20mt6813%2C%20mt6833%2C%20mt6833p%2C%20mt6835%2C%20mt6853%2C%20mt6853t%2C%20mt6855%2C%20mt6873%2C%20mt6875%2C%20mt6877%2C%20mt6877t%2C%20mt6878%2C%20mt6879%2C%20mt6880
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32874</link>
      <description>In Modem IMS Stack, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01161803; Issue ID: MOLY01161803 (MSV-893).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32874|2024-01-02T02:49:38.153Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 02:49:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
