<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for MediaTek, Inc. -- MT2731, MT2735, MT6297, MT6725, MT6735, MT6737, MT6739, MT6750, MT6750S, MT6755, MT6757, MT6757P, MT6758, MT6761, MT6762, MT6762D, MT6762M, MT6763, MT6765, MT6765T, MT6767, MT6768, MT6769, MT6769T, MT6769Z, MT6771, MT6775, MT6779, MT6781, MT6783, MT6785, MT6785T, MT6789, MT6797, MT6799, MT6833, MT6853, MT6855, MT6873, MT6875, MT6877, MT6879, MT6880, MT6883, MT6885, MT6889, MT6890, MT6891, MT6893, MT6895, MT6983, MT8666, MT8667, MT8675, MT8735A, MT8735B, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8771, MT8781, MT8786, MT8788, MT8789, MT8791, MT8797</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/mediatek%2C%20inc./mt2731%2C%20mt2735%2C%20mt6297%2C%20mt6725%2C%20mt6735%2C%20mt6737%2C%20mt6739%2C%20mt6750%2C%20mt6750s%2C%20mt6755%2C%20mt6757%2C%20mt6757p%2C%20mt6758%2C%20mt6761%2C%20mt6762%2C%20mt6762d%2C%20mt6762m%2C%20mt6763%2C%20mt6765%2C%20mt6765t%2C%20mt676.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for MediaTek, Inc. -- MT2731, MT2735, MT6297, MT6725, MT6735, MT6737, MT6739, MT6750, MT6750S, MT6755, MT6757, MT6757P, MT6758, MT6761, MT6762, MT6762D, MT6762M, MT6763, MT6765, MT6765T, MT6767, MT6768, MT6769, MT6769T, MT6769Z, MT6771, MT6775, MT6779, MT6781, MT6783, MT6785, MT6785T, MT6789, MT6797, MT6799, MT6833, MT6853, MT6855, MT6873, MT6875, MT6877, MT6879, MT6880, MT6883, MT6885, MT6889, MT6890, MT6891, MT6893, MT6895, MT6983, MT8666, MT8667, MT8675, MT8735A, MT8735B, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8771, MT8781, MT8786, MT8788, MT8789, MT8791, MT8797</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 12:25:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21744|2024-08-03T02:53:35.802Z -- mediatek%2C%20inc. -- mt2731%2C%20mt2735%2C%20mt6297%2C%20mt6725%2C%20mt6735%2C%20mt6737%2C%20mt6739%2C%20mt6750%2C%20mt6750s%2C%20mt6755%2C%20mt6757%2C%20mt6757p%2C%20mt6758%2C%20mt6761%2C%20mt6762%2C%20mt6762d%2C%20mt6762m%2C%20mt6763%2C%20mt6765%2C%20mt6765t%2C%20mt676
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21744</link>
      <description>In Modem 2G RR, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote code execution when decoding GPRS Packet Neighbour Cell Data (PNCD) improper neighbouring cell size with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY00810064; Issue ID: ALPS06641626.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21744|2024-08-03T02:53:35.802Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 13:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20083|2024-08-03T02:02:30.449Z -- mediatek%2C%20inc. -- mt2731%2C%20mt2735%2C%20mt6297%2C%20mt6725%2C%20mt6735%2C%20mt6737%2C%20mt6739%2C%20mt6750%2C%20mt6750s%2C%20mt6755%2C%20mt6757%2C%20mt6757p%2C%20mt6758%2C%20mt6761%2C%20mt6762%2C%20mt6762d%2C%20mt6762m%2C%20mt6763%2C%20mt6765%2C%20mt6765t%2C%20mt676
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20083</link>
      <description>In Modem 2G/3G CC, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote code execution when decoding combined FACILITY with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY00803883; Issue ID: MOLY00803883.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20083|2024-08-03T02:02:30.449Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 13:05:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
