<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for MediaTek, Inc. -- MT2713, MT6580, MT6761, MT6765, MT6768, MT6779, MT6781, MT6785, MT6789, MT6833, MT6835, MT6853, MT6855, MT6873, MT6877, MT6879, MT6883, MT6885, MT6886, MT6889, MT6893, MT6895, MT6983, MT6985, MT7921, MT8168, MT8175, MT8188, MT8195, MT8321, MT8365, MT8390, MT8666, MT8667, MT8673, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8781, MT8786, MT8788, MT8791T, MT8797, MT8798</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/mediatek%2C%20inc./mt2713%2C%20mt6580%2C%20mt6761%2C%20mt6765%2C%20mt6768%2C%20mt6779%2C%20mt6781%2C%20mt6785%2C%20mt6789%2C%20mt6833%2C%20mt6835%2C%20mt6853%2C%20mt6855%2C%20mt6873%2C%20mt6877%2C%20mt6879%2C%20mt6883%2C%20mt6885%2C%20mt6886%2C%20mt6889%2C%20mt6893%2C%.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for MediaTek, Inc. -- MT2713, MT6580, MT6761, MT6765, MT6768, MT6779, MT6781, MT6785, MT6789, MT6833, MT6835, MT6853, MT6855, MT6873, MT6877, MT6879, MT6883, MT6885, MT6886, MT6889, MT6893, MT6895, MT6983, MT6985, MT7921, MT8168, MT8175, MT8188, MT8195, MT8321, MT8365, MT8390, MT8666, MT8667, MT8673, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8781, MT8786, MT8788, MT8791T, MT8797, MT8798</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 22:23:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32825|2024-08-02T15:25:37.016Z -- mediatek%2C%20inc. -- mt2713%2C%20mt6580%2C%20mt6761%2C%20mt6765%2C%20mt6768%2C%20mt6779%2C%20mt6781%2C%20mt6785%2C%20mt6789%2C%20mt6833%2C%20mt6835%2C%20mt6853%2C%20mt6855%2C%20mt6873%2C%20mt6877%2C%20mt6879%2C%20mt6883%2C%20mt6885%2C%20mt6886%2C%20mt6889%2C%20mt6893%2C%
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32825</link>
      <description>In bluethooth service, there is a possible out of bounds reads due to improper input validation. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS07884130; Issue ID: ALPS07884130.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32825|2024-08-02T15:25:37.016Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 03:50:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
