<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for MediaTek, Inc. -- MT2713, MT6779, MT6781, MT6785, MT6789, MT6833, MT6835, MT6853, MT6855, MT6873, MT6877, MT6879, MT6885, MT6886, MT6889, MT6891, MT6893, MT6895, MT6983, MT8168, MT8175, MT8188, MT8195, MT8365, MT8666, MT8667, MT8673, MT8781, MT8781WIFI, MT8791, MT8791T, MT8791WIFI, MT8797, MT8797WIFI</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/mediatek%2C%20inc./mt2713%2C%20mt6779%2C%20mt6781%2C%20mt6785%2C%20mt6789%2C%20mt6833%2C%20mt6835%2C%20mt6853%2C%20mt6855%2C%20mt6873%2C%20mt6877%2C%20mt6879%2C%20mt6885%2C%20mt6886%2C%20mt6889%2C%20mt6891%2C%20mt6893%2C%20mt6895%2C%20mt6983%2C%20mt8168%2C%20mt8175%2C%.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for MediaTek, Inc. -- MT2713, MT6779, MT6781, MT6785, MT6789, MT6833, MT6835, MT6853, MT6855, MT6873, MT6877, MT6879, MT6885, MT6886, MT6889, MT6891, MT6893, MT6895, MT6983, MT8168, MT8175, MT8188, MT8195, MT8365, MT8666, MT8667, MT8673, MT8781, MT8781WIFI, MT8791, MT8791T, MT8791WIFI, MT8797, MT8797WIFI</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 18:24:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32808|2024-08-02T15:25:37.140Z -- mediatek%2C%20inc. -- mt2713%2C%20mt6779%2C%20mt6781%2C%20mt6785%2C%20mt6789%2C%20mt6833%2C%20mt6835%2C%20mt6853%2C%20mt6855%2C%20mt6873%2C%20mt6877%2C%20mt6879%2C%20mt6885%2C%20mt6886%2C%20mt6889%2C%20mt6891%2C%20mt6893%2C%20mt6895%2C%20mt6983%2C%20mt8168%2C%20mt8175%2C%
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32808</link>
      <description>In bluetooth driver, there is a possible read and write access to registers due to improper access control of register interface. This could lead to local leak of sensitive information with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS07849751; Issue ID: ALPS07849751.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32808|2024-08-02T15:25:37.140Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 02:28:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32809|2024-08-02T15:25:37.098Z -- mediatek%2C%20inc. -- mt2713%2C%20mt6779%2C%20mt6781%2C%20mt6785%2C%20mt6789%2C%20mt6833%2C%20mt6835%2C%20mt6853%2C%20mt6855%2C%20mt6873%2C%20mt6877%2C%20mt6879%2C%20mt6885%2C%20mt6886%2C%20mt6889%2C%20mt6891%2C%20mt6893%2C%20mt6895%2C%20mt6983%2C%20mt8168%2C%20mt8175%2C%
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32809</link>
      <description>In bluetooth driver, there is a possible read and write access to registers due to improper access control of register interface. This could lead to local leak of sensitive information with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS07849753; Issue ID: ALPS07849753.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32809|2024-08-02T15:25:37.098Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 02:28:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
