<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6580, MT6735, MT6737, MT6739, MT6750, MT6753, MT6755, MT6762, MT6763, MT6765, MT6768, MT6769, MT6771, MT6779, MT6781, MT6785, MT6833, MT6853, MT6853T, MT6873, MT6877, MT6885, MT6890, MT6891, MT6893, MT8163, MT8167, MT8167S, MT8168, MT8173, MT8175, MT8183, MT8321, MT8362A, MT8365, MT8385, MT8666, MT8667, MT8735A, MT8735B, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8786, MT8788</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/mediatek%2C%20inc./mt6580%2C%20mt6735%2C%20mt6737%2C%20mt6739%2C%20mt6750%2C%20mt6753%2C%20mt6755%2C%20mt6762%2C%20mt6763%2C%20mt6765%2C%20mt6768%2C%20mt6769%2C%20mt6771%2C%20mt6779%2C%20mt6781%2C%20mt6785%2C%20mt6833%2C%20mt6853%2C%20mt6853t%2C%20mt6873%2C%20mt6877%2C.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6580, MT6735, MT6737, MT6739, MT6750, MT6753, MT6755, MT6762, MT6763, MT6765, MT6768, MT6769, MT6771, MT6779, MT6781, MT6785, MT6833, MT6853, MT6853T, MT6873, MT6877, MT6885, MT6890, MT6891, MT6893, MT8163, MT8167, MT8167S, MT8168, MT8173, MT8175, MT8183, MT8321, MT8362A, MT8365, MT8385, MT8666, MT8667, MT8735A, MT8735B, MT8765, MT8766, MT8768, MT8786, MT8788</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 21:21:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-20052|2024-08-03T01:55:46.379Z -- mediatek%2C%20inc. -- mt6580%2C%20mt6735%2C%20mt6737%2C%20mt6739%2C%20mt6750%2C%20mt6753%2C%20mt6755%2C%20mt6762%2C%20mt6763%2C%20mt6765%2C%20mt6768%2C%20mt6769%2C%20mt6771%2C%20mt6779%2C%20mt6781%2C%20mt6785%2C%20mt6833%2C%20mt6853%2C%20mt6853t%2C%20mt6873%2C%20mt6877%2C
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-20052</link>
      <description>In mdp, there is a possible memory corruption due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS05836642; Issue ID: ALPS05836642.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-20052|2024-08-03T01:55:46.379Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 19:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
