<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6761, MT6762, MT6763, MT6765, MT6768, MT6769, MT6771, MT6779, MT6781, MT6785, MT6789, MT6795, MT6797, MT6799, MT6833, MT6853, MT6853T, MT6873, MT6875, MT6877, MT6879, MT6883, MT6885, MT6889, MT6891, MT6893, MT6895, MT8167, MT8167S, MT8168, MT8173, MT8185, MT8321, MT8362A, MT8365, MT8385, MT8666, MT8675, MT8768, MT8786, MT8788, MT8789, MT8791, MT8797</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/mediatek%2C%20inc./mt6761%2C%20mt6762%2C%20mt6763%2C%20mt6765%2C%20mt6768%2C%20mt6769%2C%20mt6771%2C%20mt6779%2C%20mt6781%2C%20mt6785%2C%20mt6789%2C%20mt6795%2C%20mt6797%2C%20mt6799%2C%20mt6833%2C%20mt6853%2C%20mt6853t%2C%20mt6873%2C%20mt6875%2C%20mt6877%2C%20mt6879%2C.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6761, MT6762, MT6763, MT6765, MT6768, MT6769, MT6771, MT6779, MT6781, MT6785, MT6789, MT6795, MT6797, MT6799, MT6833, MT6853, MT6853T, MT6873, MT6875, MT6877, MT6879, MT6883, MT6885, MT6889, MT6891, MT6893, MT6895, MT8167, MT8167S, MT8168, MT8173, MT8185, MT8321, MT8362A, MT8365, MT8385, MT8666, MT8675, MT8768, MT8786, MT8788, MT8789, MT8791, MT8797</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 20:22:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21775|2024-08-03T02:53:35.958Z -- mediatek%2C%20inc. -- mt6761%2C%20mt6762%2C%20mt6763%2C%20mt6765%2C%20mt6768%2C%20mt6769%2C%20mt6771%2C%20mt6779%2C%20mt6781%2C%20mt6785%2C%20mt6789%2C%20mt6795%2C%20mt6797%2C%20mt6799%2C%20mt6833%2C%20mt6853%2C%20mt6853t%2C%20mt6873%2C%20mt6875%2C%20mt6877%2C%20mt6879%2C
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21775</link>
      <description>In sched driver, there is a possible use after free due to improper locking. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS06479032; Issue ID: ALPS06479032.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21775|2024-08-03T02:53:35.958Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 13:07:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
