<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6761, MT6762, MT6765, MT6768, MT6769, MT6779, MT6781, MT6785, MT6789, MT6833, MT6835, MT6853, MT6855, MT6873, MT6875, MT6877, MT6879, MT6883, MT6885, MT6886, MT6889, MT6891, MT6893, MT6895, MT6983, MT6985, MT7663, MT7668, MT7902, MT7921, MT8167, MT8167S, MT8173, MT8175, MT8195, MT8362A, MT8365, MT8385, MT8518, MT8532, MT8666, MT8695, MT8781, MT8788</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/mediatek%2C%20inc./mt6761%2C%20mt6762%2C%20mt6765%2C%20mt6768%2C%20mt6769%2C%20mt6779%2C%20mt6781%2C%20mt6785%2C%20mt6789%2C%20mt6833%2C%20mt6835%2C%20mt6853%2C%20mt6855%2C%20mt6873%2C%20mt6875%2C%20mt6877%2C%20mt6879%2C%20mt6883%2C%20mt6885%2C%20mt6886%2C%20mt6889%2C%.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for MediaTek, Inc. -- MT6761, MT6762, MT6765, MT6768, MT6769, MT6779, MT6781, MT6785, MT6789, MT6833, MT6835, MT6853, MT6855, MT6873, MT6875, MT6877, MT6879, MT6883, MT6885, MT6886, MT6889, MT6891, MT6893, MT6895, MT6983, MT6985, MT7663, MT7668, MT7902, MT7921, MT8167, MT8167S, MT8173, MT8175, MT8195, MT8362A, MT8365, MT8385, MT8518, MT8532, MT8666, MT8695, MT8781, MT8788</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 11:20:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20731|2024-08-02T09:14:40.963Z -- mediatek%2C%20inc. -- mt6761%2C%20mt6762%2C%20mt6765%2C%20mt6768%2C%20mt6769%2C%20mt6779%2C%20mt6781%2C%20mt6785%2C%20mt6789%2C%20mt6833%2C%20mt6835%2C%20mt6853%2C%20mt6855%2C%20mt6873%2C%20mt6875%2C%20mt6877%2C%20mt6879%2C%20mt6883%2C%20mt6885%2C%20mt6886%2C%20mt6889%2C%
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20731</link>
      <description>In wlan, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS07573495; Issue ID: ALPS07573495.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20731|2024-08-02T09:14:40.963Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 12:11:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-20732|2024-08-02T09:14:40.943Z -- mediatek%2C%20inc. -- mt6761%2C%20mt6762%2C%20mt6765%2C%20mt6768%2C%20mt6769%2C%20mt6779%2C%20mt6781%2C%20mt6785%2C%20mt6789%2C%20mt6833%2C%20mt6835%2C%20mt6853%2C%20mt6855%2C%20mt6873%2C%20mt6875%2C%20mt6877%2C%20mt6879%2C%20mt6883%2C%20mt6885%2C%20mt6886%2C%20mt6889%2C%
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20732</link>
      <description>In wlan, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS07573480; Issue ID: ALPS07573480.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-20732|2024-08-02T09:14:40.943Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 12:11:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
