<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for alejandropascual -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/alejandropascual/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for alejandropascual -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 23:21:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0550|2024-08-02T05:17:49.653Z -- alejandropascual -- quick%20restaurant%20menu
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0550</link>
      <description>The Quick Restaurant Menu plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in versions up to, and including, 2.0.2. This is due to the fact that during menu item deletion/modification, the plugin does not verify that the post ID provided to the AJAX action is indeed a menu item. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access or higher, to modify or delete arbitrary posts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0550|2024-08-02T05:17:49.653Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 20:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0555|2024-08-02T05:17:49.766Z -- alejandropascual -- quick%20restaurant%20menu
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0555</link>
      <description>The Quick Restaurant Menu plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass due to a missing capability check on its AJAX actions in versions up to, and including, 2.0.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level permissions and above, to invoke those actions intended for administrator use. Actions include menu item creation, update and deletion and other menu management functions. Since the plugin does not verify that a post ID passed to one of its AJAX actions belongs to a menu item, this can lead to arbitrary post deletion/alteration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0555|2024-08-02T05:17:49.766Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 20:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0553|2024-08-02T05:17:49.819Z -- alejandropascual -- quick%20restaurant%20menu
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0553</link>
      <description>The Quick Restaurant Menu plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via its settings parameters in versions up to, and including, 2.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0553|2024-08-02T05:17:49.819Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 20:27:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0554|2024-08-02T05:17:49.833Z -- alejandropascual -- quick%20restaurant%20menu
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0554</link>
      <description>The Quick Restaurant Menu plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 2.0.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on its AJAX actions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update menu items, via forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0554|2024-08-02T05:17:49.833Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 20:28:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
