<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for zzdevelop -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/zzdevelop/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for zzdevelop -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 23:20:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2023-7259|2024-05-24T07:00:10.006Z -- zzdevelop -- lenosp</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-7259</link><description>** DISPUTED ** A vulnerability was found in zzdevelop lenosp up to 20230831. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the component Adduser Page. The manipulation of the argument username with the input  leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266127. NOTE: The vendor rejected the issue because he claims that XSS which require administrative privileges are not of any use for attackers.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in zzdevelop lenosp bis 20230831 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Komponente Adduser Page. Durch Manipulation des Arguments username mit der Eingabe  mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Die wahre Existenz der vermeintlichen Schwachstelle wird zur Zeit in Frage gestellt.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7259|2024-05-24T07:00:10.006Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 07:00:10 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>