<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for cbeust -- testng</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cbeust/testng.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for cbeust -- testng</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 16:24:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4065|2024-08-03T01:27:54.473Z -- cbeust -- testng
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4065</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in cbeust testng 7.5.0/7.6.0/7.6.1/7.7.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function testngXmlExistsInJar of the file testng-core/src/main/java/org/testng/JarFileUtils.java of the component XML File Parser. The manipulation leads to path traversal. The attack can be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 7.5.1 and 7.7.1 is able to address this issue. The patch is named 9150736cd2c123a6a3b60e6193630859f9f0422b. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-214027.
In cbeust testng 7.5.0/7.6.0/7.6.1/7.7.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Betroffen ist die Funktion testngXmlExistsInJar der Datei testng-core/src/main/java/org/testng/JarFileUtils.java der Komponente XML File Parser. Dank der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine path traversal-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 7.5.1 and 7.7.1 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als 9150736cd2c123a6a3b60e6193630859f9f0422b bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4065|2024-08-03T01:27:54.473Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
