<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for shaonsina -- Sina Extension for Elementor (Slider, Gallery, Form, Modal, Data Table, Tab, Particle, Free Elementor Widgets &amp; Elementor Templates)</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/shaonsina/sina%20extension%20for%20elementor%20%28slider%2C%20gallery%2C%20form%2C%20modal%2C%20data%20table%2C%20tab%2C%20particle%2C%20free%20elementor%20widgets%20%26%20elementor%20templates%29.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for shaonsina -- Sina Extension for Elementor (Slider, Gallery, Form, Modal, Data Table, Tab, Particle, Free Elementor Widgets &amp; Elementor Templates)</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 21:54:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-4373|2024-05-15T01:56:55.723Z -- shaonsina -- Sina Extension for Elementor (Slider, Gallery, Form, Modal, Data Table, Tab, Particle, Free Elementor Widgets &amp; Elementor Templates)
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4373</link><description>The Sina Extension for Elementor (Slider, Gallery, Form, Modal, Data Table, Tab, Particle, Free Elementor Widgets &amp; Elementor Templates) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Sina Particle Layer widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4373|2024-05-15T01:56:55.723Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 01:56:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4333|2024-05-14T12:50:02.482Z -- shaonsina -- Sina Extension for Elementor (Slider, Gallery, Form, Modal, Data Table, Tab, Particle, Free Elementor Widgets &amp; Elementor Templates)
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4333</link><description>The Sina Extension for Elementor (Slider, Gallery, Form, Modal, Data Table, Tab, Particle, Free Elementor Widgets &amp; Elementor Templates) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to DOM-Based Cross-Site Scripting via several parameters in versions up to, and including, 3.5.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4333|2024-05-14T12:50:02.482Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 12:50:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3988|2024-04-25T07:33:59.403Z -- shaonsina -- Sina Extension for Elementor (Slider, Gallery, Form, Modal, Data Table, Tab, Particle, Free Elementor Widgets &amp; Elementor Templates)
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3988</link><description>The Sina Extension for Elementor (Slider, Gallery, Form, Modal, Data Table, Tab, Particle, Free Elementor Widgets &amp; Elementor Templates) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Sina Fancy Text Widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3988|2024-04-25T07:33:59.403Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 07:33:59 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>