<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for ukrsolution -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ukrsolution/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for ukrsolution -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 16:28:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-1679|2024-05-02T16:52:35.334Z -- ukrsolution -- Print Labels with Barcodes. Create price tags, product labels, order labels for WooCommerce
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1679</link><description>The Print Labels with Barcodes. Create price tags, product labels, order labels for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the template and javascript label fields in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1679|2024-05-02T16:52:35.334Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1677|2024-05-02T16:52:13.585Z -- ukrsolution -- Print Labels with Barcodes. Create price tags, product labels, order labels for WooCommerce
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1677</link><description>The Print Labels with Barcodes. Create price tags, product labels, order labels for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data, modification of data, and loss of data due to an improper capability check on 42 separate AJAX functions in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber access and above, to fully control the plugin which includes the ability to modify plugin settings and profiles, and create, edit, retrieve, and delete templates and barcodes.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1677|2024-05-02T16:52:13.585Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27998|2024-03-19T16:46:43.176Z -- UkrSolution -- Barcode Scanner with Inventory &amp; Order Manager
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27998</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in UkrSolution Barcode Scanner with Inventory &amp; Order Manager allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Barcode Scanner with Inventory &amp; Order Manager: from n/a through 1.5.3.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27998|2024-03-19T16:46:43.176Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 16:46:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33567|2024-05-17T08:17:10.452Z -- UkrSolution -- Barcode Scanner with Inventory &amp; Order Manager
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-33567</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in UkrSolution Barcode Scanner with Inventory &amp; Order Manager allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Barcode Scanner with Inventory &amp; Order Manager: from n/a through 1.5.3.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33567|2024-05-17T08:17:10.452Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 08:17:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34557|2024-05-09T11:40:40.149Z -- UkrSolution -- Barcode Scanner with Inventory &amp; Order Manager
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-34557</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in UkrSolution Barcode Scanner with Inventory &amp; Order Manager.This issue affects Barcode Scanner with Inventory &amp; Order Manager: from n/a through 1.5.4.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34557|2024-05-09T11:40:40.149Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:40:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34556|2024-05-09T12:09:15.251Z -- UkrSolution -- Barcode Scanner with Inventory &amp; Order Manager
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-34556</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in UkrSolution Barcode Scanner with Inventory &amp; Order Manager.This issue affects Barcode Scanner with Inventory &amp; Order Manager: from n/a through 1.5.4.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34556|2024-05-09T12:09:15.251Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 12:09:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2661|2024-05-02T16:52:00.115Z -- ukrsolution -- Barcode Scanner and Inventory manager. POS (Point of Sale) – scan barcodes &amp; create orders with barcode reader.
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2661</link><description>The Barcode Scanner and Inventory manager. POS (Point of Sale) – scan barcodes &amp; create orders with barcode reader. plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to blind SQL Injection via the ‘currentIds’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.4 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber access or higher, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2661|2024-05-02T16:52:00.115Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>