<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Newcomer1989 -- TSN-Ranksystem</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/newcomer1989/tsn-ranksystem.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Newcomer1989 -- TSN-Ranksystem</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 22:22:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-25073|2024-08-05T12:33:47.851Z -- newcomer1989 -- tsn-ranksystem
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25073</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Newcomer1989 TSN-Ranksystem up to 1.2.6 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function getlog of the file webinterface/bot.php. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 1.2.7 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as b3a3cd8efe2cd3bd3c5b3b7abf2fe80dbee51b77. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-218002 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In Newcomer1989 TSN-Ranksystem bis 1.2.6 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle gefunden. Betroffen ist die Funktion getlog der Datei webinterface/bot.php. Durch Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 1.2.7 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als b3a3cd8efe2cd3bd3c5b3b7abf2fe80dbee51b77 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-25073|2024-08-05T12:33:47.851Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 13:54:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
