<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for GamerZ -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/gamerz/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for GamerZ -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 18:24:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2473|2024-08-03T00:39:07.851Z -- gamerz -- wp-useronline
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2473</link>
      <description>The WP-UserOnline plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘templates[browsingpage][text]' parameter in versions up to, and including, 2.87.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with administrative capabilities and above to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. The only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html is disabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2473|2024-08-03T00:39:07.851Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 17:18:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2941|2024-08-03T00:53:00.461Z -- gamerz -- wp-useronline
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2941</link>
      <description>The WP-UserOnline plugin for WordPress has multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerabilities in versions up to, and including 2.88.0. This is due to the fact that all fields in the "Naming Conventions" section do not properly sanitize user input, nor escape it on output. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrative privileges, to inject JavaScript code into the setting that will execute whenever a user accesses the injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2941|2024-08-03T00:53:00.461Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 17:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2011-10006|2024-07-05T17:22:37.804Z -- gamerz -- wp-postratings</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2011-10006</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in GamerZ WP-PostRatings up to 1.64. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file wp-postratings.php. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 1.65 is able to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is 6182a5682b12369ced0becd3b505439ce2eb8132. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-259629 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in GamerZ WP-PostRatings bis 1.64 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei wp-postratings.php. Durch das Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 1.65 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als 6182a5682b12369ced0becd3b505439ce2eb8132 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2011-10006|2024-07-05T17:22:37.804Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 13:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
