<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for GNU Project -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/gnu%20project/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for GNU Project -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 14:22:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28734|2024-08-03T06:03:52.014Z -- gnu%20project -- gnu%20grub
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28734</link>
      <description>Out-of-bounds write when handling split HTTP headers; When handling split HTTP headers, GRUB2 HTTP code accidentally moves its internal data buffer point by one position. This can lead to a out-of-bound write further when parsing the HTTP request, writing a NULL byte past the buffer. It's conceivable that an attacker controlled set of packets can lead to corruption of the GRUB2's internal memory metadata.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28734|2024-08-03T06:03:52.014Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:22:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28736|2024-08-03T06:03:52.084Z -- gnu%20project -- gnu%20grub
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28736</link>
      <description>There's a use-after-free vulnerability in grub_cmd_chainloader() function; The chainloader command is used to boot up operating systems that doesn't support multiboot and do not have direct support from GRUB2. When executing chainloader more than once a use-after-free vulnerability is triggered. If an attacker can control the GRUB2's memory allocation pattern sensitive data may be exposed and arbitrary code execution can be achieved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28736|2024-08-03T06:03:52.084Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:23:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28735|2024-08-03T06:03:52.586Z -- gnu%20project -- gnu%20grub
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28735</link>
      <description>The GRUB2's shim_lock verifier allows non-kernel files to be loaded on shim-powered secure boot systems. Allowing such files to be loaded may lead to unverified code and modules to be loaded in GRUB2 breaking the secure boot trust-chain.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28735|2024-08-03T06:03:52.586Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:22:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28733|2024-08-03T06:03:52.571Z -- gnu%20project -- gnu%20grub
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28733</link>
      <description>Integer underflow in grub_net_recv_ip4_packets; A malicious crafted IP packet can lead to an integer underflow in grub_net_recv_ip4_packets() function on rsm-&gt;total_len value. Under certain circumstances the total_len value may end up wrapping around to a small integer number which will be used in memory allocation. If the attack succeeds in such way, subsequent operations can write past the end of the buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28733|2024-08-03T06:03:52.571Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:20:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
