<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for phpscriptpoint -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/phpscriptpoint/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for phpscriptpoint -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 20:23:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3858|2024-08-02T07:08:50.341Z -- phpscriptpoint -- car%20listing
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3858</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in phpscriptpoint Car Listing 1.6 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /search.php. The manipulation of the argument country/state/city leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. VDB-235210 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In phpscriptpoint Car Listing 1.6 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle gefunden. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei /search.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments country/state/city mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3858|2024-08-02T07:08:50.341Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 01:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3861|2024-08-02T07:08:50.602Z -- phpscriptpoint -- insurance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3861</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in phpscriptpoint Insurance 1.2. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /search.php. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The identifier VDB-235213 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In phpscriptpoint Insurance 1.2 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei /search.php. Dank der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3861|2024-08-02T07:08:50.602Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 03:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3945|2024-08-02T07:08:50.668Z -- phpscriptpoint -- lawyer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3945</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in phpscriptpoint Lawyer 1.6. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file search.php. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The identifier VDB-235401 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in phpscriptpoint Lawyer 1.6 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei search.php. Dank Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3945|2024-08-02T07:08:50.668Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 21:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3859|2024-08-02T07:08:50.552Z -- phpscriptpoint -- car%20listing
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3859</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in phpscriptpoint Car Listing 1.6 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /search.php of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument brand_id/model_id/car_condition/car_category_id/body_type_id/fuel_type_id/transmission_type_id/year/mileage_start/mileage_end/country/state/city leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-235211. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in phpscriptpoint Car Listing 1.6 gefunden. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei /search.php der Komponente GET Parameter Handler. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments brand_id/model_id/car_condition/car_category_id/body_type_id/fuel_type_id/transmission_type_id/year/mileage_start/mileage_end/country/state/city mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3859|2024-08-02T07:08:50.552Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 02:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3856|2024-08-02T07:08:50.203Z -- phpscriptpoint -- ecommerce
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3856</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in phpscriptpoint Ecommerce 1.15. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /blog-single.php. The manipulation of the argument slug leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-235208. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in phpscriptpoint Ecommerce 1.15 entdeckt. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei /blog-single.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments slug mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3856|2024-08-02T07:08:50.203Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3944|2024-08-02T07:08:50.672Z -- phpscriptpoint -- lawyer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3944</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in phpscriptpoint Lawyer 1.6 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file page.php. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-235400. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in phpscriptpoint Lawyer 1.6 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei page.php. Dank der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3944|2024-08-02T07:08:50.672Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 19:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3855|2024-08-02T07:08:50.512Z -- phpscriptpoint -- jobseeker
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3855</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in phpscriptpoint JobSeeker 1.5. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /search-result.php. The manipulation of the argument kw/lc/ct/cp/p leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-235207. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In phpscriptpoint JobSeeker 1.5 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei /search-result.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments kw/lc/ct/cp/p mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3855|2024-08-02T07:08:50.512Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 23:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3854|2024-08-02T07:08:50.528Z -- phpscriptpoint -- bloodbank
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3854</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in phpscriptpoint BloodBank 1.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /search of the component POST Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument country/city/blood_group_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. VDB-235206 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in phpscriptpoint BloodBank 1.1 entdeckt. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei /search der Komponente POST Parameter Handler. Durch Manipulation des Arguments country/city/blood_group_id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3854|2024-08-02T07:08:50.528Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 23:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3857|2024-08-02T07:08:50.500Z -- phpscriptpoint -- ecommerce
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3857</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in phpscriptpoint Ecommerce 1.15. This affects an unknown part of the file /product.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The identifier VDB-235209 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in phpscriptpoint Ecommerce 1.15 gefunden. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei /product.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3857|2024-08-02T07:08:50.500Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 01:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3853|2024-08-02T07:08:50.466Z -- phpscriptpoint -- bloodbank
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3853</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in phpscriptpoint BloodBank 1.1. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file page.php. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The identifier VDB-235205 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in phpscriptpoint BloodBank 1.1 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei page.php. Durch die Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3853|2024-08-02T07:08:50.466Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 22:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3860|2024-08-02T07:08:50.536Z -- phpscriptpoint -- insurance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3860</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in phpscriptpoint Insurance 1.2. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /page.php. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-235212. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in phpscriptpoint Insurance 1.2 ausgemacht. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei /page.php. Durch Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3860|2024-08-02T07:08:50.536Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 02:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3984|2024-08-02T07:08:50.731Z -- phpscriptpoint -- recipepoint
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3984</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in phpscriptpoint RecipePoint 1.9. This affects an unknown part of the file /recipe-result. The manipulation of the argument text/category/type/difficulty/cuisine/cooking_method leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The identifier VDB-235605 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in phpscriptpoint RecipePoint 1.9 gefunden. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei /recipe-result. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments text/category/type/difficulty/cuisine/cooking_method mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3984|2024-08-02T07:08:50.731Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 03:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
