<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Hancom -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/hancom/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Hancom -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 16:24:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50235|2024-05-03T02:14:51.048Z -- hancom -- office</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50235</link>
      <description>Hancom Office Show PPT File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Hancom Office Show. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PPT files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20387.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50235|2024-05-03T02:14:51.048Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51598|2024-06-05T14:25:08.665Z -- hancom -- office</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51598</link>
      <description>Hancom Office Word DOC File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Hancom Office Word. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DOC files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20384.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51598|2024-06-05T14:25:08.665Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
