<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for navidrome -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/navidrome/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for navidrome -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 23:22:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51442|2024-08-02T22:32:10.031Z -- navidrome -- navidrome
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51442</link>
      <description>Navidrome is an open source web-based music collection server and streamer. A security vulnerability has been identified in navidrome's subsonic endpoint, allowing for authentication bypass. This exploit enables unauthorized access to any known account by utilizing a JSON Web Token (JWT) signed with the key "not so secret". The vulnerability can only be exploited on instances that have never been restarted. Navidrome supports an extension to the subsonic authentication scheme, where a JWT can be provided using a `jwt` query parameter instead of the traditional password or token and salt (corresponding to resp. the `p` or `t` and `s` query parameters). This authentication bypass vulnerability potentially affects all instances that don't protect the subsonic endpoint `/rest/`, which is expected to be most instances in a standard deployment, and most instances in the reverse proxy setup too (as the documentation mentions to leave that endpoint unprotected). This issue has been patched in version 0.50.2.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51442|2024-08-02T22:32:10.031Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 14:54:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32963|2024-06-04T17:49:41.638Z -- navidrome -- navidrome</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-32963</link>
      <description>Navidrome is an open source web-based music collection server and streamer. In affected versions of Navidrome are subject to a parameter tampering vulnerability where an attacker has the ability to manipulate parameter values in the HTTP requests. The attacker is able to change the parameter values in the body and successfully impersonate another user. In this case, the attacker created a playlist, added song, posted arbitrary comment, set the playlist to be public, and put the admin as the owner of the playlist. The attacker must be able to intercept http traffic for this attack. Each known user is impacted. An attacker can obtain the ownerId from shared playlist information, meaning every user who has shared a playlist is also impacted, as they can be impersonated. This issue has been addressed in version 0.52.0 and users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32963|2024-06-04T17:49:41.638Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 06:39:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32963|2024-08-02T02:27:52.376Z -- navidrome -- navidrome</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32963</link>
      <description>Navidrome is an open source web-based music collection server and streamer. In affected versions of Navidrome are subject to a parameter tampering vulnerability where an attacker has the ability to manipulate parameter values in the HTTP requests. The attacker is able to change the parameter values in the body and successfully impersonate another user. In this case, the attacker created a playlist, added song, posted arbitrary comment, set the playlist to be public, and put the admin as the owner of the playlist. The attacker must be able to intercept http traffic for this attack. Each known user is impacted. An attacker can obtain the ownerId from shared playlist information, meaning every user who has shared a playlist is also impacted, as they can be impersonated. This issue has been addressed in version 0.52.0 and users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32963|2024-08-02T02:27:52.376Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 06:39:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
