<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for IET-OU -- Open Media Player</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/iet-ou/open%20media%20player.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for IET-OU -- Open Media Player</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 09:23:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-25086|2024-08-05T03:00:19.103Z -- iet-ou -- open%20media%20player
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25086</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in IET-OU Open Media Player up to 1.5.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function webvtt of the file application/controllers/timedtext.php. The manipulation of the argument ttml_url leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 1.5.1 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is 3f39f2d68d11895929c04f7b49b97a734ae7cd1f. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-216862 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In IET-OU Open Media Player bis 1.5.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist die Funktion webvtt der Datei application/controllers/timedtext.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments ttml_url mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 1.5.1 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als 3f39f2d68d11895929c04f7b49b97a734ae7cd1f bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-25086|2024-08-05T03:00:19.103Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 08:38:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
