<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Dell -- Avamar</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/dell/avamar.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Dell -- Avamar</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 18:24:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5329|2024-08-04T08:22:09.263Z -- dell -- avamar
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5329</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Avamar Server contains an open redirect vulnerability. A remote unauthenticated attacker may exploit this vulnerability to redirect application users to arbitrary web URLs by tricking the victim users to click on maliciously crafted links.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5329|2024-08-04T08:22:09.263Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-36316|2024-08-04T00:54:51.391Z -- dell -- avamar
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-36316</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Avamar Server versions 18.2, 19.1, 19.2, 19.3, and 19.4 contain an improper privilege management vulnerability in AUI. A malicious user with high privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the disclosure of the AUI info and performing some unauthorized operation on the AUI.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-36316|2024-08-04T00:54:51.391Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-36318|2024-08-04T00:54:51.414Z -- dell -- avamar
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-36318</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Avamar versions 18.2,19.1,19.2,19.3,19.4 contain a plain-text password storage vulnerability. A high privileged user could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to a complete outage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-36318|2024-08-04T00:54:51.414Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-29493|2024-08-04T16:55:09.764Z -- dell -- avamar
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-29493</link>
      <description>DELL EMC Avamar Server, versions 19.1, 19.2, 19.3, contain a SQL Injection Vulnerability in Fitness Analyzer. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the execution of certain SQL commands on the application's backend database, causing unauthorized read and write access to application data. Exploitation may lead to leakage or deletion of sensitive backup data; hence the severity is Critical. Dell EMC recommends customers to upgrade at the earliest opportunity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-29493|2024-08-04T16:55:09.764Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-36317|2024-08-04T00:54:51.453Z -- dell -- avamar
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-36317</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Avamar Server version 19.4 contains a plain-text password storage vulnerability in AvInstaller. A local attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the disclosure of certain user credentials. The attacker may be able to use the exposed credentials to access the vulnerable application with privileges of the compromised account.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-36317|2024-08-04T00:54:51.453Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-29495|2024-08-04T16:55:09.897Z -- dell -- avamar
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-29495</link>
      <description>DELL EMC Avamar Server, versions 19.1, 19.2, 19.3, contain an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in Fitness Analyzer. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the execution of arbitrary OS commands on the application's underlying OS with high privileges. This vulnerability is considered critical as it can be leveraged to completely compromise the vulnerable application as well as the underlying operating system. Dell recommends customers to upgrade at the earliest opportunity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-29495|2024-08-04T16:55:09.897Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-29494|2024-08-04T16:55:10.652Z -- dell -- avamar
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-29494</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Avamar Server, versions 19.1, 19.2, 19.3, contain a Path Traversal Vulnerability in PDM. A remote user could potentially exploit this vulnerability, to gain unauthorized write access to the arbitrary files stored on the server filesystem, causing deletion of arbitrary files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-29494|2024-08-04T16:55:10.652Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
