<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Dell -- Dell Encryption Enterprise</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/dell/dell%20encryption%20enterprise.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Dell -- Dell Encryption Enterprise</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 19:19:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5327|2024-08-04T08:22:09.235Z -- dell -- dell%20encryption%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5327</link>
      <description>Dell Security Management Server versions prior to 10.2.10 contain a Java RMI Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability. When the server is exposed to the internet and Windows Firewall is disabled, a remote unauthenticated attacker may exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted RMI request to execute arbitrary code on the target host.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5327|2024-08-04T08:22:09.235Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5358|2024-08-04T08:30:23.442Z -- dell -- dell%20encryption%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5358</link>
      <description>Dell Encryption versions prior to 10.7 and Dell Endpoint Security Suite versions prior to 2.7 contain a privilege escalation vulnerability due to incorrect permissions. A local malicious user with low privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability to gain elevated privilege on the affected system with the help of a symbolic link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5358|2024-08-04T08:30:23.442Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5385|2024-08-04T08:30:23.923Z -- dell -- dell%20encryption%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5385</link>
      <description>Dell Encryption versions prior to 10.8 and Dell Endpoint Security Suite versions prior to 2.8 contain a privilege escalation vulnerability because of an incomplete fix for CVE-2020-5358. A local malicious user with low privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability to gain elevated privilege on the affected system with the help of a symbolic link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5385|2024-08-04T08:30:23.923Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
