<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Dell -- Dell Client Consumer and Commercial Platforms</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/dell/dell%20client%20consumer%20and%20commercial%20platforms.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Dell -- Dell Client Consumer and Commercial Platforms</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 13:23:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5363|2024-08-04T08:30:23.893Z -- dell -- dell%20client%20consumer%20and%20commercial%20platforms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5363</link>
      <description>Select Dell Client Consumer and Commercial platforms include an issue that allows the BIOS Admin password to be changed through Dell's manageability interface without knowledge of the current BIOS Admin password. This could potentially allow an unauthorized actor, with physical access and/or OS administrator privileges to the device, to gain privileged access to the platform and the hard drive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5363|2024-08-04T08:30:23.893Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5324|2024-08-04T08:22:09.224Z -- dell -- dell%20client%20consumer%20and%20commercial%20platforms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5324</link>
      <description>Dell Client Consumer and Commercial Platforms contain an Arbitrary File Overwrite Vulnerability. The vulnerability is limited to the Dell Firmware Update Utility during the time window while being executed by an administrator. During this time window, a locally authenticated low-privileged malicious user could exploit this vulnerability by tricking an administrator into overwriting arbitrary files via a symlink attack. The vulnerability does not affect the actual binary payload that the update utility delivers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5324|2024-08-04T08:22:09.224Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5362|2024-08-04T08:30:24.088Z -- dell -- dell%20client%20consumer%20and%20commercial%20platforms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5362</link>
      <description>Dell Client Consumer and Commercial platforms include an improper authorization vulnerability in the Dell Manageability interface for which an unauthorized actor, with local system access with OS administrator privileges, could bypass the BIOS Administrator authentication to restore BIOS Setup configuration to default values.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5362|2024-08-04T08:30:24.088Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5326|2024-08-04T08:22:09.254Z -- dell -- dell%20client%20consumer%20and%20commercial%20platforms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5326</link>
      <description>Affected Dell Client platforms contain a BIOS Setup configuration authentication bypass vulnerability in the pre-boot Intel Rapid Storage Response Technology (iRST) Manager menu. An attacker with physical access to the system could perform unauthorized changes to the BIOS Setup configuration settings without requiring the BIOS Admin password by selecting the Optimized Defaults option in the pre-boot iRST Manager.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5326|2024-08-04T08:22:09.254Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
