<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Dell -- Dell PowerProtect Data Manager DM5500 Appliance</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/dell/dell%20powerprotect%20data%20manager%20dm5500%20appliance.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Dell -- Dell PowerProtect Data Manager DM5500 Appliance</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 23:22:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44291|2024-08-02T19:59:51.989Z -- dell -- dell%20powerprotect%20data%20manager%20dm5500%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44291</link>
      <description>


Dell DM5500 5.14.0.0 contains an OS command injection vulnerability in the appliance. A remote attacker with high privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the execution of arbitrary OS commands on the underlying OS, with the privileges of the vulnerable application. Exploitation may lead to a system take over by an attacker.



</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44291|2024-08-02T19:59:51.989Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 08:13:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44302|2024-08-02T19:59:51.984Z -- dell -- dell%20powerprotect%20data%20manager%20dm5500%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44302</link>
      <description>
Dell DM5500 5.14.0.0 and prior contain an improper authentication vulnerability. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability to gain access of resources or functionality that could possibly lead to execute arbitrary code.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44302|2024-08-02T19:59:51.984Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 08:44:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44305|2024-08-02T19:59:51.975Z -- dell -- dell%20powerprotect%20data%20manager%20dm5500%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44305</link>
      <description>


Dell DM5500 5.14.0.0, contains a Stack-based Buffer Overflow Vulnerability in the appliance. An unauthenticated remote attacker may exploit this vulnerability to crash the affected process or execute arbitrary code on the system by sending specially crafted input data.



</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44305|2024-08-02T19:59:51.975Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 08:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44300|2024-08-02T19:59:51.938Z -- dell -- dell%20powerprotect%20data%20manager%20dm5500%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44300</link>
      <description>


Dell DM5500 5.14.0.0, contain a Plain-text Password Storage Vulnerability in the appliance. A local attacker with privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the disclosure of certain service credentials. The attacker may be able to use the exposed credentials to access the vulnerable application with privileges of the compromised account.



</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44300|2024-08-02T19:59:51.938Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 08:36:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44304|2024-08-02T19:59:52.017Z -- dell -- dell%20powerprotect%20data%20manager%20dm5500%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44304</link>
      <description>


Dell DM5500 contains a privilege escalation vulnerability in the appliance. A remote attacker with low privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability to escape the restricted shell and gain root access to the appliance.



</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44304|2024-08-02T19:59:52.017Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 08:19:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44306|2024-08-02T19:59:52.025Z -- dell -- dell%20powerprotect%20data%20manager%20dm5500%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44306</link>
      <description>


Dell DM5500 contains a path traversal vulnerability in the appliance. A remote attacker with high privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability to overwrite configuration files stored on the server filesystem.



</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44306|2024-08-02T19:59:52.025Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 08:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44301|2024-08-02T19:59:52.140Z -- dell -- dell%20powerprotect%20data%20manager%20dm5500%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44301</link>
      <description>


Dell DM5500 5.14.0.0 and prior contain a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability. A network attacker with low privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the execution of malicious HTML or JavaScript code in a victim user's web browser in the context of the vulnerable web application. Exploitation may lead to information disclosure, session theft, or client-side request forgery.



</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44301|2024-08-02T19:59:52.140Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 08:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
