<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Dell -- Integrated Dell Remote Access Controller (iDRAC)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/dell/integrated%20dell%20remote%20access%20controller%20%28idrac%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Dell -- Integrated Dell Remote Access Controller (iDRAC)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 16:24:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26198|2024-08-04T15:49:07.162Z -- dell -- integrated%20dell%20remote%20access%20controller%20%28idrac%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26198</link>
      <description>Dell EMC iDRAC9 versions prior to 4.32.10.00 and 4.40.00.00 contain a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability in the iDRAC9 web application. A remote attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability to run malicious HTML or JavaScript in a victim’s browser by tricking a victim in to following a specially crafted link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26198|2024-08-04T15:49:07.162Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-36299|2024-08-04T00:54:51.382Z -- dell -- integrated%20dell%20remote%20access%20controller%20%28idrac%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-36299</link>
      <description>Dell iDRAC9 versions 4.40.00.00 and later, but prior to 4.40.29.00 and 5.00.00.00 contain an SQL injection vulnerability. A remote authenticated malicious user with low privileges may potentially exploit this vulnerability to cause information disclosure or denial of service by supplying specially crafted input data to the affected application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-36299|2024-08-04T00:54:51.382Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-36347|2024-08-04T00:54:51.541Z -- dell -- integrated%20dell%20remote%20access%20controller%20%28idrac%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-36347</link>
      <description>iDRAC9 versions prior to 5.00.20.00 and iDRAC8 versions prior to 2.82.82.82 contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability. An authenticated remote attacker with high privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability to control process execution and gain access to the iDRAC operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-36347|2024-08-04T00:54:51.541Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-36348|2024-08-04T00:54:51.394Z -- dell -- integrated%20dell%20remote%20access%20controller%20%28idrac%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-36348</link>
      <description>iDRAC9 versions prior to 5.00.20.00 contain an input injection vulnerability. A remote authenticated malicious user with low privileges may potentially exploit this vulnerability to cause information disclosure or denial of service by supplying specially crafted input data to iDRAC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-36348|2024-08-04T00:54:51.394Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5366|2024-08-04T08:30:23.394Z -- dell -- integrated%20dell%20remote%20access%20controller%20%28idrac%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5366</link>
      <description>Dell EMC iDRAC9 versions prior to 4.20.20.20 contain a Path Traversal Vulnerability. A remote authenticated malicious user with low privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability by manipulating input parameters to gain unauthorized read access to the arbitrary files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5366|2024-08-04T08:30:23.394Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-36300|2024-08-04T00:54:51.447Z -- dell -- integrated%20dell%20remote%20access%20controller%20%28idrac%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-36300</link>
      <description>iDRAC9 versions prior to 5.00.00.00 contain an improper input validation vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker may potentially exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted malicious request to crash the webserver or cause information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-36300|2024-08-04T00:54:51.447Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-36346|2024-08-04T00:54:51.438Z -- dell -- integrated%20dell%20remote%20access%20controller%20%28idrac%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-36346</link>
      <description>Dell iDRAC 8 prior to version 2.82.82.82 contain a denial of service vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability to deny access to the iDRAC webserver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-36346|2024-08-04T00:54:51.438Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-36301|2024-08-04T00:54:51.400Z -- dell -- integrated%20dell%20remote%20access%20controller%20%28idrac%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-36301</link>
      <description>Dell iDRAC 9 prior to version 4.40.40.00 and iDRAC 8 prior to version 2.80.80.80 contain a Stack Buffer Overflow in Racadm. An authenticated remote attacker may potentially exploit this vulnerability to control process execution and gain access to the underlying operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-36301|2024-08-04T00:54:51.400Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5344|2024-08-04T08:30:23.389Z -- dell -- integrated%20dell%20remote%20access%20controller%20%28idrac%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5344</link>
      <description>Dell EMC iDRAC7, iDRAC8 and iDRAC9 versions prior to 2.65.65.65, 2.70.70.70, 4.00.00.00 contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker may exploit this vulnerability to crash the affected process or execute arbitrary code on the system by sending specially crafted input data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5344|2024-08-04T08:30:23.389Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
