<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Dell -- Integrated Dell Remote Access Controller (iDRAC)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/dell/integrated%20dell%20remote%20access%20controller%20%28idrac%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Dell -- Integrated Dell Remote Access Controller (iDRAC)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 18:25:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21580|2024-09-16T17:33:01.755Z -- dell -- integrated%20dell%20remote%20access%20controller%20%28idrac%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21580</link>
      <description>Dell EMC iDRAC8 versions prior to 2.80.80.80 &amp; Dell EMC iDRAC9 versions prior to 5.00.00.00 contain a Content spoofing / Text injection, where a malicious URL can inject text to present a customized message on the application that can phish users into believing that the message is legitimate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21580|2024-09-16T17:33:01.755Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 15:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5366|2024-09-16T17:29:00.784Z -- dell -- integrated%20dell%20remote%20access%20controller%20%28idrac%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5366</link>
      <description>Dell EMC iDRAC9 versions prior to 4.20.20.20 contain a Path Traversal Vulnerability. A remote authenticated malicious user with low privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability by manipulating input parameters to gain unauthorized read access to the arbitrary files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5366|2024-09-16T17:29:00.784Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 13:45:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21541|2024-09-16T17:38:25.537Z -- dell -- integrated%20dell%20remote%20access%20controller%20%28idrac%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21541</link>
      <description>Dell EMC iDRAC9 versions prior to 4.40.00.00 contain a DOM-based cross-site scripting vulnerability. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability by tricking a victim application user to supply malicious HTML or JavaScript code to DOM environment in the browser. The malicious code is then executed by the web browser in the context of the vulnerable web application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21541|2024-09-16T17:38:25.537Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 20:55:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21539|2024-09-16T16:58:47.474Z -- dell -- integrated%20dell%20remote%20access%20controller%20%28idrac%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21539</link>
      <description>Dell EMC iDRAC9 versions prior to 4.40.00.00 contain a Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) race condition vulnerability. A remote authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability to gain elevated privileges when a user with higher privileges is simultaneously accessing iDRAC through the web interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21539|2024-09-16T16:58:47.474Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 20:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
