<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Dell -- Isilon OneFS</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/dell/isilon%20onefs.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Dell -- Isilon OneFS</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 15:22:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5369|2024-08-04T08:30:23.806Z -- dell -- isilon%20onefs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5369</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Isilon OneFS versions 8.2.2 and earlier and Dell EMC PowerScale OneFS version 9.0.0 contain a privilege escalation vulnerability. An authenticated malicious user may exploit this vulnerability by using SyncIQ to gain unauthorized access to system management files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5369|2024-08-04T08:30:23.806Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5365|2024-08-04T08:30:23.432Z -- dell -- isilon%20onefs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5365</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Isilon versions 8.2.2 and earlier contain a remotesupport vulnerability. The pre-configured support account, remotesupport, is bundled in the Dell EMC Isilon OneFS installation. This account is used for diagnostics and other support functions. Although the default password is different for every cluster, it is predictable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5365|2024-08-04T08:30:23.432Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5318|2024-08-04T08:22:09.254Z -- dell -- isilon%20onefs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5318</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Isilon OneFS versions 8.1.2, 8.1.0.4, 8.1.0.3, and 8.0.0.7 contain a vulnerability in some configurations. An attacker may exploit this vulnerability to gain access to restricted files. The non-RAN HTTP and WebDAV file-serving components have a vulnerability wherein when either are enabled, and Basic Authentication is enabled for either or both components, files are accessible without authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5318|2024-08-04T08:22:09.254Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5347|2024-08-04T08:30:23.308Z -- dell -- isilon%20onefs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5347</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Isilon OneFS versions 8.2.2 and earlier contain a denial of service vulnerability. SmartConnect had an error condition that may be triggered to loop, using CPU and potentially preventing other SmartConnect DNS responses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5347|2024-08-04T08:30:23.308Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5371|2024-08-04T08:30:24.227Z -- dell -- isilon%20onefs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5371</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Isilon OneFS versions 8.2.2 and earlier and Dell EMC PowerScale version 9.0.0 contain a file permissions vulnerability. An attacker, with network or local file access, could take advantage of insufficiently applied file permissions or gain unauthorized access to files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5371|2024-08-04T08:30:24.227Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5353|2024-08-04T08:30:23.439Z -- dell -- isilon%20onefs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5353</link>
      <description>The Dell Isilon OneFS versions 8.2.2 and earlier and Dell EMC PowerScale OneFS version 9.0.0 default configuration for Network File System (NFS) allows access to an 'admin' home directory. An attacker may leverage a spoofed Unique Identifier (UID) over NFS to rewrite sensitive files to gain administrative access to the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5353|2024-08-04T08:30:23.439Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5355|2024-08-04T08:30:23.446Z -- dell -- isilon%20onefs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5355</link>
      <description>The Dell Isilon OneFS versions 8.2.2 and earlier SSHD process improperly allows Transmission Control Protocol (TCP) and stream forwarding. This provides the remotesupport user and users with restricted shells more access than is intended.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5355|2024-08-04T08:30:23.446Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5383|2024-08-04T08:30:23.957Z -- dell -- isilon%20onefs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5383</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Isilon OneFS version 8.2.2 and Dell EMC PowerScale OneFS version 9.0.0 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability in the Likewise component. A remote unauthenticated malicious attacker may potentially exploit this vulnerability to cause a process restart.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5383|2024-08-04T08:30:23.957Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5328|2024-08-04T08:22:09.299Z -- dell -- isilon%20onefs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5328</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Isilon OneFS versions prior to 8.2.0 contain an unauthorized access vulnerability due to a lack of thorough authorization checks when SyncIQ is licensed, but encrypted syncs are not marked as required. When this happens, loss of control of the cluster can occur.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5328|2024-08-04T08:22:09.299Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5364|2024-08-04T08:30:23.683Z -- dell -- isilon%20onefs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5364</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Isilon OneFS versions 8.2.2 and earlier contain an SNMPv2 vulnerability. The SNMPv2 services is enabled, by default, with a pre-configured community string. This community string allows read-only access to many aspects of the Isilon cluster, some of which are considered sensitive and can foster additional access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5364|2024-08-04T08:30:23.683Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
