<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Dell -- PowerEdge BIOS Intel 15G</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/dell/poweredge%20bios%20intel%2015g.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Dell -- PowerEdge BIOS Intel 15G</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:22:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21557|2024-08-03T18:16:23.041Z -- dell -- poweredge%20bios%20intel%2015g
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21557</link>
      <description>Dell PowerEdge Server BIOS and select Dell Precision Rack BIOS contain an out-of-bounds array access vulnerability. A local malicious user with high privileges may potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to a denial of service, arbitrary code execution, or information disclosure in System Management Mode.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21557|2024-08-03T18:16:23.041Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21556|2024-08-03T18:16:23.115Z -- dell -- poweredge%20bios%20intel%2015g
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21556</link>
      <description>Dell PowerEdge R640, R740, R740XD, R840, R940, R940xa, MX740c, MX840c, and T640 Server BIOS contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in systems with NVDIMM-N installed. A local malicious user with high privileges may potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to a denial of Service, arbitrary code execution, or information disclosure in UEFI or BIOS Preboot Environment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21556|2024-08-03T18:16:23.115Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21555|2024-08-03T18:16:22.970Z -- dell -- poweredge%20bios%20intel%2015g
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21555</link>
      <description>Dell PowerEdge R640, R740, R740XD, R840, R940, R940xa, MX740c, MX840c, and T640 Server BIOS contain a heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability in systems with NVDIMM-N installed. A local malicious user with high privileges may potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to a denial of Service, arbitrary code execution, or information disclosure in UEFI or BIOS Preboot Environment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21555|2024-08-03T18:16:22.970Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21554|2024-08-03T18:16:23.043Z -- dell -- poweredge%20bios%20intel%2015g
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21554</link>
      <description>Dell PowerEdge R640, R740, R740XD, R840, R940, R940xa, MX740c, MX840c, and, Dell Precision 7920 Rack Workstation BIOS contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in systems with Intel Optane DC Persistent Memory installed. A local malicious user with high privileges may potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to a denial of Service, arbitrary code execution, or information disclosure in UEFI or BIOS Preboot Environment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21554|2024-08-03T18:16:23.043Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
