<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Dell -- PowerStore</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/dell/powerstore.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Dell -- PowerStore</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 14:22:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26866|2024-08-03T05:18:37.981Z -- dell -- powerstore
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26866</link>
      <description>Dell PowerStore Versions before v2.1.1.0. contains a Stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability. A high privileged network attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the storage of malicious HTML or JavaScript codes in a trusted application data store. When a victim user accesses the data store through their browsers, the malicious code gets executed by the web browser in the context of the vulnerable web application. Exploitation may lead to information disclosure, session theft, or client-side request forgery.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26866|2024-08-03T05:18:37.981Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22555|2024-08-03T03:14:55.708Z -- dell -- powerstore
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22555</link>
      <description>Dell EMC PowerStore, contains an OS command injection Vulnerability. A locally authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the execution of arbitrary OS commands on the PowerStore underlying OS, with the privileges of the vulnerable application. Exploitation may lead to an elevation of privilege.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22555|2024-08-03T03:14:55.708Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26870|2024-08-03T05:18:38.025Z -- dell -- powerstore
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26870</link>
      <description>Dell PowerStore versions 2.1.0.x contain an Authentication bypass vulnerability. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability under specific configuration. An attacker would gain unauthorized access upon successful exploit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26870|2024-08-03T05:18:38.025Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22557|2024-08-03T03:14:55.739Z -- dell -- powerstore
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22557</link>
      <description>PowerStore contains Plain-Text Password Storage Vulnerability in PowerStore X &amp; T environments running versions 2.0.0.x and 2.0.1.x A locally authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the disclosure of certain user credentials. The attacker may be able to use the exposed credentials to access the vulnerable application with privileges of the compromised account.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22557|2024-08-03T03:14:55.739Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-32498|2024-08-03T07:46:43.374Z -- dell -- powerstore
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32498</link>
      <description>Dell EMC PowerStore, Versions prior to v3.0.0.0 contain a DLL Hijacking vulnerability in PSTCLI. A local attacker can potentially exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code, escalate privileges, and bypass software allow list solutions, leading to system takeover or IP exposure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-32498|2024-08-03T07:46:43.374Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22556|2024-08-03T03:14:55.674Z -- dell -- powerstore
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22556</link>
      <description>Dell PowerStore contains an Uncontrolled Resource Consumption Vulnerability in PowerStore User Interface. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the Denial of Service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22556|2024-08-03T03:14:55.674Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-33923|2024-08-03T08:09:22.809Z -- dell -- powerstore
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-33923</link>
      <description>Dell PowerStore, versions prior to 3.0.0.0, contains an OS Command Injection vulnerability in PowerStore T environment. A locally authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the execution of arbitrary OS command on the PowerStore underlying OS. Exploiting may lead to a system take over by an attacker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-33923|2024-08-03T08:09:22.809Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26868|2024-08-03T05:18:38.050Z -- dell -- powerstore
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26868</link>
      <description>Dell EMC PowerStore versions 2.0.0.x, 2.0.1.x, and 2.1.0.x are vulnerable to a command injection flaw. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the execution of arbitrary OS commands on the application's underlying OS, with the privileges of the vulnerable application. Exploitation may lead to a system takeover by an attacker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26868|2024-08-03T05:18:38.050Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26867|2024-08-03T05:18:38.118Z -- dell -- powerstore
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26867</link>
      <description>PowerStore SW v2.1.1.0 supports the option to export data to either a CSV or an XLSX file. The data is taken as is, without any validation or sanitization. It allows a malicious, authenticated user to inject payloads that might get interpreted as formulas by the corresponding spreadsheet application that is being used to open the CSV/XLSX file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26867|2024-08-03T05:18:38.118Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26869|2024-08-03T05:18:37.954Z -- dell -- powerstore
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26869</link>
      <description>Dell PowerStore versions 2.0.0.x, 2.0.1.x and 2.1.0.x contains an open port vulnerability. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to information disclosure and arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26869|2024-08-03T05:18:37.954Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31234|2024-08-03T07:11:39.878Z -- dell -- powerstore
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31234</link>
      <description>Dell EMC PowerStore, contain(s) an Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts Vulnerability in PowerStore Manager GUI. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to password brute-forcing. Account takeover is possible if weak passwords are used by users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31234|2024-08-03T07:11:39.878Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
