<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Dell -- RSA Identity Governance &amp; Lifecycle</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/dell/rsa%20identity%20governance%20%26%20lifecycle.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Dell -- RSA Identity Governance &amp; Lifecycle</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 06:24:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18571|2024-08-05T01:54:14.492Z -- dell -- rsa%20identity%20governance%20%26%20lifecycle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18571</link>
      <description>The RSA Identity Governance and Lifecycle and RSA Via Lifecycle and Governance products prior to 7.1.1 P03 contain a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability in the My Access Live module [MAL]. An authenticated malicious local user could potentially exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted URL with scripts. When victim users access the module through their browsers, the malicious code gets injected and executed by the web browser in the context of the vulnerable web application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18571|2024-08-05T01:54:14.492Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18572|2024-08-05T01:54:14.426Z -- dell -- rsa%20identity%20governance%20%26%20lifecycle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18572</link>
      <description>The RSA Identity Governance and Lifecycle and RSA Via Lifecycle and Governance products prior to 7.1.1 P03 contain an Improper Authentication vulnerability. A Java JMX agent running on the remote host is configured with plain text password authentication. An unauthenticated remote attacker can connect to the JMX agent and monitor and manage the Java application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18572|2024-08-05T01:54:14.426Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18573|2024-08-05T01:54:14.362Z -- dell -- rsa%20identity%20governance%20%26%20lifecycle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18573</link>
      <description>The RSA Identity Governance and Lifecycle and RSA Via Lifecycle and Governance products prior to 7.1.1 P03 contain a Session Fixation vulnerability. An authenticated malicious local user could potentially exploit this vulnerability as the session token is exposed as part of the URL. A remote attacker can gain access to victim’s session and perform arbitrary actions with privileges of the user within the compromised session.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18573|2024-08-05T01:54:14.362Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
