<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Dell -- RSA Authentication Manager</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/dell/rsa%20authentication%20manager.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Dell -- RSA Authentication Manager</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 19:19:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5340|2024-08-04T08:30:22.853Z -- dell -- rsa%20authentication%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5340</link>
      <description>RSA Authentication Manager versions prior to 8.4 P10 contain a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Security Console. A malicious RSA Authentication Manager Security Console administrator with advanced privileges could exploit this vulnerability to store arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code through the Security Console web interface. When other Security Console administrators attempt to change the default security domain mapping, the injected scripts could potentially be executed in their browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5340|2024-08-04T08:30:22.853Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5339|2024-08-04T08:30:23.357Z -- dell -- rsa%20authentication%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5339</link>
      <description>RSA Authentication Manager versions prior to 8.4 P10 contain a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Security Console. A malicious RSA Authentication Manager Security Console administrator with advanced privileges could exploit this vulnerability to store arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code through the Security Console web interface. When other Security Console administrators open the affected report page, the injected scripts could potentially be executed in their browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5339|2024-08-04T08:30:23.357Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5346|2024-08-04T08:30:23.436Z -- dell -- rsa%20authentication%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5346</link>
      <description>RSA Authentication Manager versions prior to 8.4 P11 contain a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Security Console. A malicious RSA Authentication Manager Security Console administrator with advanced privileges could exploit this vulnerability to store arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code through the Security Console web interface. When other Security Console administrators open the affected page, the injected scripts could potentially be executed in their browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5346|2024-08-04T08:30:23.436Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
