<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Dell -- SupportAssist Client Consumer</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/dell/supportassist%20client%20consumer.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Dell -- SupportAssist Client Consumer</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 21:42:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-36297|2024-09-16T20:38:07.749Z -- dell -- supportassist%20client%20consumer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-36297</link>
      <description>SupportAssist Client version 3.8 and 3.9 contains an Untrusted search path vulnerability that allows attackers to load an arbitrary .dll file via .dll planting/hijacking, only by a separate administrative action that is not a default part of the SOSInstallerTool.exe installation for executing arbitrary dll's,</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-36297|2024-09-16T20:38:07.749Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 19:20:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-36286|2024-09-16T19:25:15.640Z -- dell -- supportassist%20client%20consumer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-36286</link>
      <description>Dell SupportAssist Client Consumer versions 3.9.13.0 and any versions prior to 3.9.13.0 contain an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability that can be exploited by using the Windows feature of NTFS called Symbolic links. Symbolic links can be created by any(non-privileged) user under some object directories, but by themselves are not sufficient to successfully escalate privileges. However, combining them with a different object, such as the NTFS junction point allows for the exploitation. Support assist clean files functionality do not distinguish junction points from the physical folder and proceeds to clean the target of the junction that allows nonprivileged users to create junction points and delete arbitrary files on the system which can be accessed only by the admin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-36286|2024-09-16T19:25:15.640Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 19:20:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29094|2024-09-16T16:53:37.826Z -- dell -- supportassist%20client%20consumer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29094</link>
      <description>Dell SupportAssist Client Consumer versions (3.10.4 and versions prior) and Dell SupportAssist Client Commercial versions (3.1.1 and versions prior) contain an arbitrary file deletion/overwrite vulnerability. Authenticated non-admin user could exploit the issue and delete or overwrite arbitrary files on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29094|2024-09-16T16:53:37.826Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 20:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
