<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Dell -- Unity</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/dell/unity.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Dell -- Unity</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 21:43:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-29490|2024-09-16T19:19:39.044Z -- dell -- unity
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-29490</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Unity, Unity XT, and UnityVSA versions prior to 5.0.4.0.5.012 contain a Denial of Service vulnerability on NAS Servers with NFS exports. A remote authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability and cause Denial of Service (Storage Processor Panic) by sending specially crafted UDP requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-29490|2024-09-16T19:19:39.044Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 21:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26199|2024-09-16T20:17:54.764Z -- dell -- unity
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26199</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Unity, Unity XT, and UnityVSA versions prior to 5.0.4.0.5.012 contain a plain-text password storage vulnerability. A user credentials (including the Unisphere admin privilege user) password is stored in a plain text in multiple log files. A local authenticated attacker with access to the log files may use the exposed password to gain access with the privileges of the compromised user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26199|2024-09-16T20:17:54.764Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 21:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21547|2024-09-16T18:34:33.545Z -- dell -- unity
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21547</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Unity, UnityVSA, and Unity XT versions prior to 5.0.7.0.5.008 contain a plain-text password storage vulnerability when the Dell Upgrade Readiness Utility is run on the system. The credentials of the Unisphere Administrator are stored in plain text. A local malicious user with high privileges may use the exposed password to gain access with the privileges of the compromised user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21547|2024-09-16T18:34:33.545Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 21:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5319|2024-09-16T20:27:11.870Z -- dell -- unity
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5319</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Unity, Dell EMC Unity XT, and Dell EMC UnityVSA versions prior to 5.0.2.0.5.009 contain a Denial of Service vulnerability on NAS Server SSH implementation that is used to provide SFTP service on a NAS server. A remote unauthenticated attacker may potentially exploit this vulnerability and cause a Denial of Service (Storage Processor Panic) by sending an out of order SSH protocol sequence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5319|2024-09-16T20:27:11.870Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 17:45:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21590|2024-09-16T20:57:44.496Z -- dell -- unity
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21590</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Unity, Unity XT, and UnityVSA versions prior to 5.1.0.0.5.394 contain a plain-text password storage vulnerability. A local malicious user with high privileges may use the exposed password to gain access with the privileges of the compromised user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21590|2024-09-16T20:57:44.496Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
