<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Dell -- Unity</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/dell/unity.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Dell -- Unity</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 13:24:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29085|2024-09-17T03:23:38.857Z -- dell -- unity
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29085</link>
      <description>Dell Unity, Dell UnityVSA, and Dell Unity XT versions prior to 5.2.0.0.5.173 contain a plain-text password storage vulnerability when certain off-array tools are run on the system. The credentials of a user with high privileges are stored in plain text. A local malicious user with high privileges may use the exposed password to gain access with the privileges of the compromised user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29085|2024-09-17T03:23:38.857Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 21:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21589|2024-09-17T03:58:38.925Z -- dell -- unity
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21589</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Unity, Unity XT, and UnityVSA versions prior to 5.1.0.0.5.394 do not exit on failed Initialization. A local authenticated Service user could potentially exploit this vulnerability to escalate privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21589|2024-09-17T03:58:38.925Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 15:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21591|2024-09-17T03:48:49.687Z -- dell -- unity
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21591</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Unity, Unity XT, and UnityVSA versions prior to 5.1.0.0.5.394 contain a plain-text password storage vulnerability. A local malicious user with high privileges may use the exposed password to gain access with the privileges of the compromised user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21591|2024-09-17T03:48:49.687Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 15:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29084|2024-09-17T01:21:14.297Z -- dell -- unity
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29084</link>
      <description>Dell Unity, Dell UnityVSA, and Dell Unity XT versions before 5.2.0.0.5.173 do not restrict excessive authentication attempts in Unisphere GUI. A remote unauthenticated attacker may potentially exploit this vulnerability to brute-force passwords and gain access to the system as the victim. Account takeover is possible if weak passwords are used by users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29084|2024-09-17T01:21:14.297Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 21:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43589|2024-09-17T00:21:04.462Z -- dell -- unity
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43589</link>
      <description>Dell EMC Unity, Dell EMC UnityVSA and Dell EMC Unity XT versions prior to 5.1.2.0.5.007 contain an operating system (OS) command injection Vulnerability. A locally authenticated user with high privileges may potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the execution of arbitrary OS commands on the Unity underlying OS, with the privileges of the vulnerable application. Exploitation may lead to an elevation of privilege.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43589|2024-09-17T00:21:04.462Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 20:10:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
