<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Dell -- Wyse Management Suite</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/dell/wyse%20management%20suite.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Dell -- Wyse Management Suite</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 11:21:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-29496|2024-09-17T03:28:01.564Z -- dell -- wyse%20management%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-29496</link>
      <description>Dell Wyse Management Suite versions prior to 3.1 contain a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability. A remote authenticated malicious user with high privileges could exploit this vulnerability to store malicious HTML or JavaScript code while creating the Enduser. When victim users access the submitted data through their browsers, the malicious code gets executed by the web browser in the context of the vulnerable application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-29496|2024-09-17T03:28:01.564Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 21:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29090|2024-09-17T02:37:35.608Z -- dell -- wyse%20management%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29090</link>
      <description>Dell Wyse Management Suite 3.6.1 and below contains a Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability. A low privileged malicious user could potentially exploit this vulnerability in order to obtain credentials. The attacker may be able to use the exposed credentials to access the target device and perform unauthorized actions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29090|2024-09-17T02:37:35.608Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 16:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21533|2024-09-17T00:56:07.667Z -- dell -- wyse%20management%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21533</link>
      <description>Wyse Management Suite versions up to 3.2 contains a vulnerability wherein a malicious authenticated user can cause a denial of service in the job status retrieval page, also affecting other users that would have normally access to the same subset of job details</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21533|2024-09-17T00:56:07.667Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 21:20:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21586|2024-09-17T01:31:36.108Z -- dell -- wyse%20management%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21586</link>
      <description>Wyse Management Suite versions 3.2 and earlier contain an absolute path traversal vulnerability. A remote authenticated malicious user could exploit this vulnerability in order to read arbitrary files on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21586|2024-09-17T01:31:36.108Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 16:15:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-33925|2024-09-17T00:11:09.693Z -- dell -- wyse%20management%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-33925</link>
      <description>Dell Wyse Management Suite 3.6.1 and below contains an Improper Access control vulnerability in UI. An remote authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability by bypassing access controls in order to download reports containing sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-33925|2024-09-17T00:11:09.693Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 16:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-36337|2024-09-17T00:32:21.587Z -- dell -- wyse%20management%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-36337</link>
      <description>Dell Wyse Management Suite version 3.3.1 and prior support insecure Transport Security Protocols TLS 1.0 and TLS 1.1 which are susceptible to Man-In-The-Middle attacks thereby compromising Confidentiality and Integrity of data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-36337|2024-09-17T00:32:21.587Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 17:05:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-29498|2024-09-17T02:57:03.173Z -- dell -- wyse%20management%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-29498</link>
      <description>Dell Wyse Management Suite versions prior to 3.1 contain an open redirect vulnerability. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability to redirect application users to arbitrary web URLs by tricking the victim users to click on maliciously crafted links. The vulnerability could be used to conduct phishing attacks that cause users to unknowingly visit malicious sites.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-29498|2024-09-17T02:57:03.173Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 21:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23155|2024-09-17T01:05:34.074Z -- dell -- wyse%20management%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23155</link>
      <description>Dell Wyse Management Suite versions 2.0 through 3.5.2 contain an unrestricted file upload vulnerability. A malicious user with admin privileges can exploit this vulnerability in order to execute arbitrary code on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23155|2024-09-17T01:05:34.074Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 20:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-33926|2024-09-17T04:29:00.986Z -- dell -- wyse%20management%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-33926</link>
      <description>Dell Wyse Management Suite 3.6.1 and below contains an improper access control vulnerability. A remote malicious user could exploit this vulnerability in order to retain access to a file repository after it has been revoked.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-33926|2024-09-17T04:29:00.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 16:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3770|2024-09-17T02:02:12.080Z -- dell -- wyse%20management%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3770</link>
      <description>Dell Wyse Management Suite versions prior to 1.4.1 contain a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability when unregistering a device. A remote authenticated malicious user with low privileges could exploit this vulnerability to store malicious HTML or JavaScript code. When victim users access the submitted data through their browsers, the malicious code gets executed by the web browser in the context of the vulnerable application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3770|2024-09-17T02:02:12.080Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 20:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-33927|2024-09-17T00:46:28.916Z -- dell -- wyse%20management%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-33927</link>
      <description>Dell Wyse Management Suite 3.6.1 and below contains a Session Fixation vulnerability. A unauthenticated attacker could exploit this by taking advantage of a user with multiple active sessions in order to hijack a user's session.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-33927|2024-09-17T00:46:28.916Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 16:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-33928|2024-09-17T02:37:41.986Z -- dell -- wyse%20management%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-33928</link>
      <description>Dell Wyse Management Suite 3.6.1 and below contains an Plain-text Password Storage Vulnerability in UI. An attacker with low privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the disclosure of certain user credentials. The attacker may be able to use the exposed credentials to access the vulnerable application with privileges of the compromised account.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-33928|2024-09-17T02:37:41.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 16:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-33929|2024-09-17T04:09:04.781Z -- dell -- wyse%20management%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-33929</link>
      <description>Dell Wyse Management Suite 3.6.1 and below contains a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability in EndUserSummary page. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the execution of malicious HTML or JavaScript code in a victim user's web browser in the context of the vulnerable web application. Exploitation may lead to information disclosure, session theft, or client-side request forgery.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-33929|2024-09-17T04:09:04.781Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 16:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-29497|2024-09-17T03:48:05.520Z -- dell -- wyse%20management%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-29497</link>
      <description>Dell Wyse Management Suite versions prior to 3.1 contain a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability. A remote authenticated malicious user with low privileges could exploit this vulnerability to store malicious HTML or JavaScript code under the device tag. When victim users access the submitted data through their browsers, the malicious code gets executed by the web browser in the context of the vulnerable application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-29497|2024-09-17T03:48:05.520Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 21:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
