<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Dell -- Wyse Management Suite</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/dell/wyse%20management%20suite.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Dell -- Wyse Management Suite</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 11:20:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-34365|2024-08-03T09:07:16.285Z -- dell -- wyse%20management%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34365</link>
      <description>WMS 3.7 contains a Path Traversal Vulnerability in Device API. An attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, to gain unauthorized read access to the files stored on the server filesystem, with the privileges of the running web application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-34365|2024-08-03T09:07:16.285Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23155|2024-08-03T03:36:19.919Z -- dell -- wyse%20management%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23155</link>
      <description>Dell Wyse Management Suite versions 2.0 through 3.5.2 contain an unrestricted file upload vulnerability. A malicious user with admin privileges can exploit this vulnerability in order to execute arbitrary code on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23155|2024-08-03T03:36:19.919Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-33928|2024-08-03T08:09:22.812Z -- dell -- wyse%20management%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-33928</link>
      <description>Dell Wyse Management Suite 3.6.1 and below contains an Plain-text Password Storage Vulnerability in UI. An attacker with low privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the disclosure of certain user credentials. The attacker may be able to use the exposed credentials to access the vulnerable application with privileges of the compromised account.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-33928|2024-08-03T08:09:22.812Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-33926|2024-08-03T08:09:22.713Z -- dell -- wyse%20management%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-33926</link>
      <description>Dell Wyse Management Suite 3.6.1 and below contains an improper access control vulnerability. A remote malicious user could exploit this vulnerability in order to retain access to a file repository after it has been revoked.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-33926|2024-08-03T08:09:22.713Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-33925|2024-08-03T08:09:22.808Z -- dell -- wyse%20management%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-33925</link>
      <description>Dell Wyse Management Suite 3.6.1 and below contains an Improper Access control vulnerability in UI. An remote authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability by bypassing access controls in order to download reports containing sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-33925|2024-08-03T08:09:22.808Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-33931|2024-08-03T08:09:22.703Z -- dell -- wyse%20management%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-33931</link>
      <description>Dell Wyse Management Suite 3.6.1 and below contains an Improper Access control vulnerability in UI. An attacker with no access to Alert Classification page could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the change the alert categories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-33931|2024-08-03T08:09:22.703Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-33927|2024-08-03T08:09:22.803Z -- dell -- wyse%20management%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-33927</link>
      <description>Dell Wyse Management Suite 3.6.1 and below contains a Session Fixation vulnerability. A unauthenticated attacker could exploit this by taking advantage of a user with multiple active sessions in order to hijack a user's session.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-33927|2024-08-03T08:09:22.803Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-33929|2024-08-03T08:09:22.814Z -- dell -- wyse%20management%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-33929</link>
      <description>Dell Wyse Management Suite 3.6.1 and below contains a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability in EndUserSummary page. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the execution of malicious HTML or JavaScript code in a victim user's web browser in the context of the vulnerable web application. Exploitation may lead to information disclosure, session theft, or client-side request forgery.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-33929|2024-08-03T08:09:22.814Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29090|2024-08-03T06:10:59.294Z -- dell -- wyse%20management%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29090</link>
      <description>Dell Wyse Management Suite 3.6.1 and below contains a Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability. A low privileged malicious user could potentially exploit this vulnerability in order to obtain credentials. The attacker may be able to use the exposed credentials to access the target device and perform unauthorized actions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29090|2024-08-03T06:10:59.294Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-33930|2024-08-03T08:09:22.799Z -- dell -- wyse%20management%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-33930</link>
      <description>Dell Wyse Management Suite 3.6.1 and below contains Information Disclosure in Devices error pages. An attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the disclosure of certain sensitive information. The attacker may be able to use the exposed information to access and further vulnerability research.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-33930|2024-08-03T08:09:22.799Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29097|2024-08-03T06:10:59.266Z -- dell -- wyse%20management%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29097</link>
      <description>Dell WMS 3.6.1 and below contains a Path Traversal vulnerability in Device API. A remote attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, to gain unauthorized read access to the files stored on the server filesystem, with the privileges of the running web application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29097|2024-08-03T06:10:59.266Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-33924|2024-08-03T08:09:22.798Z -- dell -- wyse%20management%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-33924</link>
      <description>Dell Wyse Management Suite 3.6.1 and below contains an Improper Access control vulnerability with which an attacker with no access to create rules could potentially exploit this vulnerability and create rules.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-33924|2024-08-03T08:09:22.798Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29096|2024-08-03T06:10:58.966Z -- dell -- wyse%20management%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29096</link>
      <description>Dell Wyse Management Suite 3.6.1 and below contains a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability in saveGroupConfigurations page. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the execution of malicious HTML or JavaScript code in a victim user's web browser in the context of the vulnerable web application. Exploitation may lead to information disclosure, session theft, or client-side request forgery.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29096|2024-08-03T06:10:58.966Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
