<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Dell -- Wyse Management Suite</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/dell/wyse%20management%20suite.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Dell -- Wyse Management Suite</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 07:20:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23155|2024-08-03T03:36:19.919Z -- dell -- wyse%20management%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23155</link>
      <description>Dell Wyse Management Suite versions 2.0 through 3.5.2 contain an unrestricted file upload vulnerability. A malicious user with admin privileges can exploit this vulnerability in order to execute arbitrary code on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23155|2024-08-03T03:36:19.919Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29090|2024-08-03T06:10:59.294Z -- dell -- wyse%20management%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29090</link>
      <description>Dell Wyse Management Suite 3.6.1 and below contains a Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability. A low privileged malicious user could potentially exploit this vulnerability in order to obtain credentials. The attacker may be able to use the exposed credentials to access the target device and perform unauthorized actions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29090|2024-08-03T06:10:59.294Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29097|2024-08-03T06:10:59.266Z -- dell -- wyse%20management%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29097</link>
      <description>Dell WMS 3.6.1 and below contains a Path Traversal vulnerability in Device API. A remote attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, to gain unauthorized read access to the files stored on the server filesystem, with the privileges of the running web application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29097|2024-08-03T06:10:59.266Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29096|2024-08-03T06:10:58.966Z -- dell -- wyse%20management%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29096</link>
      <description>Dell Wyse Management Suite 3.6.1 and below contains a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability in saveGroupConfigurations page. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the execution of malicious HTML or JavaScript code in a victim user's web browser in the context of the vulnerable web application. Exploitation may lead to information disclosure, session theft, or client-side request forgery.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29096|2024-08-03T06:10:58.966Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
