<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Adobe -- Prelude</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/adobe/prelude.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Adobe -- Prelude</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 18:24:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43012|2024-09-17T00:16:06.157Z -- adobe -- prelude
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43012</link>
      <description>Adobe Prelude version 10.1 (and earlier) are affected by a memory corruption vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker could leverage this vulnerability to achieve arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious M4A file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43012|2024-09-17T00:16:06.157Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 21:18:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40774|2024-09-17T02:57:22.908Z -- adobe -- prelude
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40774</link>
      <description>Adobe Prelude version 10.1 (and earlier) is affected by a null pointer dereference vulnerability when parsing a specially crafted file. An unauthenticated attacker could leverage this vulnerability to achieve an application denial-of-service in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40774|2024-09-17T02:57:22.908Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 15:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40771|2024-09-17T03:43:23.716Z -- adobe -- prelude
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40771</link>
      <description>Adobe Prelude version 10.1 (and earlier) is affected by a memory corruption vulnerability due to insecure handling of a malicious WAV file, potentially resulting in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. User interaction is required in that the victim must open a specially crafted file to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40771|2024-09-17T03:43:23.716Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 15:18:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28594|2024-09-17T02:53:20.660Z -- adobe -- prelude
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28594</link>
      <description>Adobe Creative Cloud Desktop Application (installer) version 2.4 (and earlier) is affected by an Uncontrolled Search Path Element vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker could leverage this vulnerability to achieve arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28594|2024-09-17T02:53:20.660Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 18:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35999|2024-09-17T03:14:33.977Z -- adobe -- prelude
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35999</link>
      <description>Adobe Prelude version 10.0 (and earlier) is affected by a memory corruption vulnerability when parsing a specially crafted file. An unauthenticated attacker could leverage this vulnerability to achieve arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35999|2024-09-17T03:14:33.977Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 18:10:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
