<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for dgtlmoon -- changedetection.io</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/dgtlmoon/changedetection.io.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for dgtlmoon -- changedetection.io</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 22:02:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-32651|2024-04-25T23:49:28.540Z -- dgtlmoon -- changedetection.io
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-32651</link><description>changedetection.io is an open source web page change detection, website watcher, restock monitor and notification service. There is a Server Side Template Injection (SSTI) in Jinja2 that allows Remote Command Execution on the server host. Attackers can run any system command without any restriction and they could use a reverse shell. The impact is critical as the attacker can completely takeover the server machine. This can be reduced if changedetection is behind a login page, but this isn't required by the application (not by default and not enforced).</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32651|2024-04-25T23:49:28.540Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 23:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23329|2024-01-19T19:49:54.624Z -- dgtlmoon -- changedetection.io
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23329</link><description> changedetection.io is an open source tool designed to monitor websites for content changes. In affected versions the API endpoint `/api/v1/watch/&lt;uuid&gt;/history` can be accessed by any unauthorized user. As a result any unauthorized user can check one's watch history. However, because unauthorized party first needs to know a watch UUID, and the watch history endpoint itself returns only paths to the snapshot on the server, an impact on users' data privacy is minimal. This issue has been addressed in version 0.45.13. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23329|2024-01-19T19:49:54.624Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 19:49:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34061|2024-05-02T13:58:21.939Z -- dgtlmoon -- changedetection.io
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-34061</link><description>changedetection.io is a free open source web page change detection, website watcher, restock monitor and notification service. In affected versions Input in parameter notification_urls is not processed resulting in javascript execution in the application. A reflected XSS vulnerability happens when the user input from a URL or POST data is reflected on the page without being stored, thus allowing the attacker to inject malicious content. This issue has been addressed in version 0.45.22. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34061|2024-05-02T13:58:21.939Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 13:58:21 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>