<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Teltonika -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/teltonika/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Teltonika -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 20:23:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2588|2024-08-02T06:26:09.842Z -- teltonika -- remote%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2588</link>
      <description>
Teltonika’s Remote Management System versions prior to 4.10.0 have a feature allowing users to access managed devices’ local secure shell (SSH)/web management services over the cloud proxy. A user can request a web proxy and obtain a URL in the Remote Management System cloud subdomain. This URL could be shared with others without Remote Management System authentication . An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to create a malicious webpage that uses a trusted and certified domain. An attacker could initiate a reverse shell when a victim connects to the malicious webpage, achieving remote code execution on the victim device.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2588|2024-08-02T06:26:09.842Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 15:09:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32348|2024-08-02T15:10:25.003Z -- teltonika -- remote%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32348</link>
      <description>
Teltonika’s Remote Management System versions prior to 4.10.0 contain a virtual private network (VPN) hub feature for cross-device communication that uses OpenVPN. It connects new devices in a manner that allows the new device to communicate with all Teltonika devices connected to the VPN. The OpenVPN server also allows users to route through it. An attacker could route a connection to a remote server through the OpenVPN server, enabling them to scan and access data from other Teltonika devices connected to the VPN.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32348|2024-08-02T15:10:25.003Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 15:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32349|2024-08-02T15:10:24.909Z -- teltonika -- rut%20model%20routers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32349</link>
      <description>
Version 00.07.03.4 and prior of Teltonika’s RUT router firmware contain a packet dump utility that contains proper validation for filter parameters. However, variables for validation checks are stored in an external configuration file. An authenticated attacker could use an exposed UCI configuration utility to change these variables and enable malicious parameters in the dump utility, which could result in arbitrary code execution.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32349|2024-08-02T15:10:24.909Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 15:12:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2587|2024-08-02T06:26:09.758Z -- teltonika -- remote%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2587</link>
      <description>
Teltonika’s Remote Management System versions prior to 4.10.0 contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the main page of the web interface. An attacker with the MAC address and serial number of a connected device could send a maliciously crafted JSON file with an HTML object to trigger the vulnerability. This could allow the attacker to execute scripts in the account context and obtain remote code execution on managed devices.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2587|2024-08-02T06:26:09.758Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 15:06:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2586|2024-08-02T06:26:09.736Z -- teltonika -- remote%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2586</link>
      <description>
Teltonika’s Remote Management System versions 4.14.0 is vulnerable to an unauthorized attacker registering previously unregistered devices through the RMS platform. If the user has not disabled the "RMS management feature" enabled by default, then an attacker could register that device to themselves. This could enable the attacker to perform different operations on the user's devices, including remote code execution with 'root' privileges (using the 'Task Manager' feature on RMS).

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2586|2024-08-02T06:26:09.736Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 15:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32346|2024-08-02T15:10:24.890Z -- teltonika -- remote%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32346</link>
      <description>
Teltonika’s Remote Management System versions prior to 4.10.0 contain a function that allows users to claim their devices. This function returns information based on whether the serial number of a device has already been claimed, the MAC address of a device has already been claimed, or whether the attempt to claim a device was successful. An attacker could exploit this to create a list of the serial numbers and MAC addresses of all devices cloud-connected to the Remote Management System.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32346|2024-08-02T15:10:24.890Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 14:45:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32347|2024-08-02T15:10:24.907Z -- teltonika -- remote%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32347</link>
      <description>
Teltonika’s Remote Management System versions prior to 4.10.0 use device serial numbers and MAC addresses to identify devices from the user perspective for device claiming and from the device perspective for authentication. If an attacker obtained the serial number and MAC address of a device, they could authenticate as that device and steal communication credentials of the device. This could allow an attacker to enable arbitrary command execution as root by utilizing management options within the newly registered devices.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32347|2024-08-02T15:10:24.907Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 14:58:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32350|2024-08-02T15:10:24.899Z -- teltonika -- rut%20model%20routers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32350</link>
      <description>
Versions 00.07.00 through 00.07.03 of Teltonika’s RUT router firmware contain an operating system (OS) command injection vulnerability in a Lua service. An attacker could exploit a parameter in the vulnerable function that calls a user-provided package name by instead providing a package with a malicious name that contains an OS command injection payload.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32350|2024-08-02T15:10:24.899Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 15:14:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
