<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Teltonika -- Remote Management System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/teltonika/remote%20management%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Teltonika -- Remote Management System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 08:24:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2588|2024-08-02T06:26:09.842Z -- teltonika -- remote%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2588</link>
      <description>
Teltonika’s Remote Management System versions prior to 4.10.0 have a feature allowing users to access managed devices’ local secure shell (SSH)/web management services over the cloud proxy. A user can request a web proxy and obtain a URL in the Remote Management System cloud subdomain. This URL could be shared with others without Remote Management System authentication . An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to create a malicious webpage that uses a trusted and certified domain. An attacker could initiate a reverse shell when a victim connects to the malicious webpage, achieving remote code execution on the victim device.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2588|2024-08-02T06:26:09.842Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 15:09:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2587|2024-08-02T06:26:09.758Z -- teltonika -- remote%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2587</link>
      <description>
Teltonika’s Remote Management System versions prior to 4.10.0 contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the main page of the web interface. An attacker with the MAC address and serial number of a connected device could send a maliciously crafted JSON file with an HTML object to trigger the vulnerability. This could allow the attacker to execute scripts in the account context and obtain remote code execution on managed devices.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2587|2024-08-02T06:26:09.758Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 15:06:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2586|2024-08-02T06:26:09.736Z -- teltonika -- remote%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2586</link>
      <description>
Teltonika’s Remote Management System versions 4.14.0 is vulnerable to an unauthorized attacker registering previously unregistered devices through the RMS platform. If the user has not disabled the "RMS management feature" enabled by default, then an attacker could register that device to themselves. This could enable the attacker to perform different operations on the user's devices, including remote code execution with 'root' privileges (using the 'Task Manager' feature on RMS).

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2586|2024-08-02T06:26:09.736Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 15:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
