<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Maiwei -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/maiwei/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Maiwei -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 19:20:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6101|2024-08-02T08:21:17.270Z -- maiwei -- safety%20production%20control%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6101</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Maiwei Safety Production Control Platform 4.1. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /TC/V2.7/ha.html of the component Intelligent Monitoring. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-245063. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Maiwei Safety Production Control Platform 4.1 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei /TC/V2.7/ha.html der Komponente Intelligent Monitoring. Mittels dem Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine information disclosure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6101|2024-08-02T08:21:17.270Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 16:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6100|2024-08-02T08:21:17.418Z -- maiwei -- safety%20production%20control%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6100</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Maiwei Safety Production Control Platform 4.1. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /api/DataDictionary/GetItemList. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-245062 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Maiwei Safety Production Control Platform 4.1 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei /api/DataDictionary/GetItemList. Durch Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine information disclosure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6100|2024-08-02T08:21:17.418Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 15:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6102|2024-08-02T08:21:17.403Z -- maiwei -- safety%20production%20control%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6102</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Maiwei Safety Production Control Platform 4.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /Content/Plugins/uploader/FileChoose.html?fileUrl=/Upload/File/Pics/&amp;parent. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-245064. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Maiwei Safety Production Control Platform 4.1 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei /Content/Plugins/uploader/FileChoose.html?fileUrl=/Upload/File/Pics/&amp;parent. Mittels Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6102|2024-08-02T08:21:17.403Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 17:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
