<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for patriksimek -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/patriksimek/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for patriksimek -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29199|2023-04-14T18:37:03.847Z -- patriksimek -- vm2
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-29199</link>
      <description>There exists a vulnerability in source code transformer (exception sanitization logic) of vm2 for versions up to 3.9.15, allowing attackers to bypass `handleException()` and leak unsanitized host exceptions which can be used to escape the sandbox and run arbitrary code in host context. A threat actor can bypass the sandbox protections to gain remote code execution rights on the host running the sandbox. This vulnerability was patched in the release of version `3.9.16` of `vm2`.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29199|2023-04-14T18:37:03.847Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 18:37:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29017|2023-04-06T19:18:34.243Z -- patriksimek -- vm2
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-29017</link>
      <description>vm2 is a sandbox that can run untrusted code with whitelisted Node's built-in modules. Prior to version 3.9.15, vm2 was not properly handling host objects passed to `Error.prepareStackTrace` in case of unhandled async errors. A threat actor could bypass the sandbox protections to gain remote code execution rights on the host running the sandbox. This vulnerability was patched in the release of version 3.9.15 of vm2. There are no known workarounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29017|2023-04-06T19:18:34.243Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 19:18:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32313|2023-05-15T19:45:13.963Z -- patriksimek -- vm2
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32313</link>
      <description>vm2 is a sandbox that can run untrusted code with Node's built-in modules. In versions 3.9.17 and lower of vm2 it was possible to get a read-write reference to the node `inspect` method and edit options for `console.log`. As a result a threat actor can edit options for the `console.log` command. This vulnerability was patched in the release of version `3.9.18` of `vm2`. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade may make the `inspect` method readonly with `vm.readonly(inspect)` after creating a vm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32313|2023-05-15T19:45:13.963Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 19:45:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32314|2023-05-15T19:46:32.834Z -- patriksimek -- vm2
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32314</link>
      <description>vm2 is a sandbox that can run untrusted code with Node's built-in modules. A sandbox escape vulnerability exists in vm2 for versions up to and including 3.9.17. It abuses an unexpected creation of a host object based on the specification of `Proxy`. As a result a threat actor can bypass the sandbox protections to gain remote code execution rights on the host running the sandbox. This vulnerability was patched in the release of version `3.9.18` of `vm2`. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32314|2023-05-15T19:46:32.834Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 19:46:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37466|2023-09-15T17:16:58.315Z -- patriksimek -- vm2
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37466</link>
      <description>vm2 is an advanced vm/sandbox for Node.js. The library contains critical security issues and should not be used for production. The maintenance of the project has been discontinued. In vm2 for versions up to 3.9.19, `Promise` handler sanitization can be bypassed with the `@@species` accessor property allowing attackers to escape the sandbox and run arbitrary code, potentially allowing remote code execution inside the context of vm2 sandbox.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37466|2023-09-15T17:16:58.315Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 23:17:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37903|2023-07-21T19:42:09.346Z -- patriksimek -- vm2
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37903</link>
      <description>vm2 is an open source vm/sandbox for Node.js. In vm2 for versions up to and including 3.9.19, Node.js custom inspect function allows attackers to escape the sandbox and run arbitrary code. This may result in Remote Code Execution, assuming the attacker has arbitrary code execution primitive inside the context of vm2 sandbox. There are no patches and no known workarounds. Users are advised to find an alternative software.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37903|2023-07-21T19:42:09.346Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 19:42:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-30547|2023-04-17T21:42:10.514Z -- patriksimek -- vm2
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-30547</link>
      <description>vm2 is a sandbox that can run untrusted code with whitelisted Node's built-in modules. There exists a vulnerability in exception sanitization of vm2 for versions up to 3.9.16, allowing attackers to raise an unsanitized host exception inside `handleException()` which can be used to escape the sandbox and run arbitrary code in host context. This vulnerability was patched in the release of version `3.9.17` of `vm2`. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability. Users are advised to upgrade.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-30547|2023-04-17T21:42:10.514Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 21:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
