<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for rsyslog -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/rsyslog/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for rsyslog -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 23:22:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2011-1490|2024-08-06T22:28:41.394Z -- rsyslog -- rsyslog
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2011-1490</link>
      <description>A memory leak in rsyslog before 5.7.6 was found in the way deamon processed log messages are logged when multiple rulesets were used and some output batches contained messages belonging to more than one ruleset. A local attacker could cause denial of the rsyslogd daemon service via a log message belonging to more than one ruleset</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2011-1490|2024-08-06T22:28:41.394Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 01:37:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2011-1488|2024-08-06T22:28:41.761Z -- rsyslog -- rsyslog
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2011-1488</link>
      <description>A memory leak in rsyslog before 5.7.6 was found in the way deamon processed log messages are logged when $RepeatedMsgReduction was enabled. A local attacker could use this flaw to cause a denial of the rsyslogd daemon service by crashing the service via a sequence of repeated log messages sent within short periods of time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2011-1488|2024-08-06T22:28:41.761Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 01:15:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2011-1489|2024-08-06T22:28:41.423Z -- rsyslog -- rsyslog
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2011-1489</link>
      <description>A memory leak in rsyslog before 5.7.6 was found in the way deamon processed log messages were logged when multiple rulesets were used and some output batches contained messages belonging to more than one ruleset. A local attacker could cause denial of the rsyslogd daemon service via a log message belonging to more than one ruleset.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2011-1489|2024-08-06T22:28:41.423Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 01:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
