<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for McAfee,LLC -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/mcafee%2Cllc/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for McAfee,LLC -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 21:21:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23892|2024-08-03T19:14:09.649Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20endpoint%20security%20%28ens%29%20for%20linux
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23892</link>
      <description>By exploiting a time of check to time of use (TOCTOU) race condition during the Endpoint Security for Linux Threat Prevention and Firewall (ENSL TP/FW) installation process, a local user can perform a privilege escalation attack to obtain administrator privileges for the purpose of executing arbitrary code through insecure use of predictable temporary file locations.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23892|2024-08-03T19:14:09.649Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 09:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23889|2024-08-03T19:14:09.155Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20epolicy%20orchestrator%20%28epo%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23889</link>
      <description>Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability in McAfee ePolicy Orchestrator (ePO) prior to 5.10 Update 10 allows ePO administrators to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via multiple parameters where the administrator's entries were not correctly sanitized.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23889|2024-08-03T19:14:09.155Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 09:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23873|2024-08-03T19:14:09.882Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20total%20protection%20%28mtp%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23873</link>
      <description>Privilege Escalation vulnerability in McAfee Total Protection (MTP) prior to 16.0.30 allows a local user to gain elevated privileges and perform arbitrary file deletion as the SYSTEM user potentially causing Denial of Service via manipulating Junction link, after enumerating certain files, at a specific time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23873|2024-08-03T19:14:09.882Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 10:20:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23887|2024-08-03T19:14:09.191Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20data%20loss%20prevention%20%28dlp%29%20endpoint%20for%20windows
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23887</link>
      <description>Privilege Escalation vulnerability in McAfee Data Loss Prevention (DLP) Endpoint for Windows prior to 11.6.100 allows a local, low privileged, attacker to write to arbitrary controlled kernel addresses. This is achieved by launching applications, suspending them, modifying the memory and restarting them when they are monitored by McAfee DLP through the hdlphook driver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23887|2024-08-03T19:14:09.191Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 07:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23876|2024-08-03T19:14:09.349Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20total%20protection%20%28mtp%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23876</link>
      <description>Bypass Remote Procedure call in McAfee Total Protection (MTP) prior to 16.0.30 allows a local user to gain elevated privileges and perform arbitrary file modification as the SYSTEM user potentially causing Denial of Service via executing carefully constructed malware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23876|2024-08-03T19:14:09.349Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 10:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23893|2024-08-03T19:14:09.452Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20drive%20encryption%20%28mde%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23893</link>
      <description>Privilege Escalation vulnerability in a Windows system driver of McAfee Drive Encryption (DE) prior to 7.3.0 could allow a local non-admin user to gain elevated system privileges via exploiting an unutilized memory buffer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23893|2024-08-03T19:14:09.452Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 09:25:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-4038|2024-08-03T17:16:03.446Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20network%20security%20manager%20%28nsm%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4038</link>
      <description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in McAfee Network Security Manager (NSM) prior to 10.1 Minor 7 allows a remote authenticated administrator to embed a XSS in the administrator interface via specially crafted custom rules containing HTML. NSM did not correctly sanitize custom rule content in all scenarios.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-4038|2024-08-03T17:16:03.446Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 15:55:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23874|2024-08-03T19:14:09.385Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20total%20protection%20%28mtp%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23874</link>
      <description>Arbitrary Process Execution vulnerability in McAfee Total Protection (MTP) prior to 16.0.30 allows a local user to gain elevated privileges and execute arbitrary code bypassing MTP self-defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23874|2024-08-03T19:14:09.385Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 10:25:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23888|2024-08-03T19:14:09.497Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20epolicy%20orchestrator%20%28epo%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23888</link>
      <description>Unvalidated client-side URL redirect vulnerability in McAfee ePolicy Orchestrator (ePO) prior to 5.10 Update 10 could cause an authenticated ePO user to load an untrusted site in an ePO iframe which could steal information from the authenticated user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23888|2024-08-03T19:14:09.497Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 09:30:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23872|2024-08-03T19:14:09.378Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20total%20protection%20%28mtp%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23872</link>
      <description>Privilege Escalation vulnerability in the File Lock component of McAfee Total Protection (MTP) prior to 16.0.32 allows a local user to gain elevated privileges by manipulating a symbolic link in the IOCTL interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23872|2024-08-03T19:14:09.378Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 09:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-1823|2024-08-03T00:17:00.722Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20consumer%20product%20removal%20tool
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1823</link>
      <description>Improper privilege management vulnerability in McAfee Consumer Product Removal Tool prior to version 10.4.128 could allow a local user to modify a configuration file and perform a LOLBin (Living off the land) attack. This could result in the user gaining elevated permissions and being able to execute arbitrary code, through not correctly checking the integrity of the configuration file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-1823|2024-08-03T00:17:00.722Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 10:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23894|2024-08-03T19:14:09.394Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20database%20security%20%28dbsec%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23894</link>
      <description>Deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability in McAfee Database Security (DBSec) prior to 4.8.2 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to create a reverse shell with administrator privileges on the DBSec server via carefully constructed Java serialized object sent to the DBSec server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23894|2024-08-03T19:14:09.394Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 13:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23884|2024-08-03T19:14:09.417Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20content%20security%20reporter%20%28csr%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23884</link>
      <description>Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information vulnerability in the ePO Extension of McAfee Content Security Reporter (CSR) prior to 2.8.0 allows an ePO administrator to view the unencrypted password of the McAfee Web Gateway (MWG) or the password of the McAfee Web Gateway Cloud Server (MWGCS) read only user used to retrieve log files for analysis in CSR.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23884|2024-08-03T19:14:09.417Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 07:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-4088|2024-08-03T17:16:03.698Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20data%20loss%20prevention%20%28dlp%29%20epo%20extension
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4088</link>
      <description>SQL injection vulnerability in Data Loss Protection (DLP) ePO extension 11.8.x prior to 11.8.100, 11.7.x prior to 11.7.101, and 11.6.401 allows a remote authenticated attacker to inject unfiltered SQL into the DLP part of the ePO database. This could lead to remote code execution on the ePO server with privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-4088|2024-08-03T17:16:03.698Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 16:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23891|2024-08-03T19:14:09.739Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20total%20protection%20%28mtp%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23891</link>
      <description>Privilege Escalation vulnerability in McAfee Total Protection (MTP) prior to 16.0.32 allows a local user to gain elevated privileges by impersonating a client token which could lead to the bypassing of MTP self-defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23891|2024-08-03T19:14:09.739Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 09:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23885|2024-08-03T19:14:09.417Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20web%20gateway%20%28mwg%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23885</link>
      <description>Privilege escalation vulnerability in McAfee Web Gateway (MWG) prior to 9.2.8 allows an authenticated user to gain elevated privileges through the User Interface and execute commands on the appliance via incorrect improper neutralization of user input in the troubleshooting page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23885|2024-08-03T19:14:09.417Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 09:20:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23890|2024-08-03T19:14:09.188Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20epolicy%20orchestrator%20%28epo%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23890</link>
      <description>Information leak vulnerability in the Agent Handler of McAfee ePolicy Orchestrator (ePO) prior to 5.10 Update 10 allows an unauthenticated user to download McAfee product packages (specifically McAfee Agent) available in ePO repository and install them on their own machines to have it managed and then in turn get policy details from the ePO server. This can only happen when the ePO Agent Handler is installed in a Demilitarized Zone (DMZ) to service machines not connected to the network through a VPN.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23890|2024-08-03T19:14:09.188Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 09:35:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23896|2024-08-03T19:14:09.467Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20database%20security%20%28dbsec%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23896</link>
      <description>Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information vulnerability in the administrator interface of McAfee Database Security (DBSec) prior to 4.8.2 allows an administrator to view the unencrypted password of the McAfee Insights Server used to pass data to the Insights Server. This user is restricted to only have access to DBSec data in the Insights Server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23896|2024-08-03T19:14:09.467Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 13:10:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-1824|2024-08-03T00:17:00.711Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20consumer%20product%20removal%20tool
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1824</link>
      <description>An uncontrolled search path vulnerability in McAfee Consumer Product Removal Tool prior to version 10.4.128 could allow a local attacker to perform a sideloading attack by using a specific file name. This could result in the user gaining elevated permissions and being able to execute arbitrary code as there were insufficient checks on the executable being signed by McAfee.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-1824|2024-08-03T00:17:00.711Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 10:15:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23895|2024-08-03T19:14:09.408Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20database%20security%20%28dbsec%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23895</link>
      <description>Deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability in McAfee Database Security (DBSec) prior to 4.8.2 allows a remote authenticated attacker to create a reverse shell with administrator privileges on the DBSec server via carefully constructed Java serialized object sent to the DBSec server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23895|2024-08-03T19:14:09.408Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 13:05:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23886|2024-08-03T19:14:09.648Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20data%20loss%20prevention%20%28dlp%29%20endpoint%20for%20windows
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23886</link>
      <description>Denial of Service vulnerability in McAfee Data Loss Prevention (DLP) Endpoint for Windows prior to 11.6.100 allows a local, low privileged, attacker to cause a BSoD through suspending a process, modifying the processes memory and restarting it. This is triggered by the hdlphook driver reading invalid memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23886|2024-08-03T19:14:09.648Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 07:50:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
