<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for McAfee,LLC -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/mcafee%2Cllc/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for McAfee,LLC -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 19:19:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7282|2024-08-04T09:25:48.950Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20total%20protection%20%28mtp%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7282</link>
      <description>Privilege Escalation vulnerability in McAfee Total Protection (MTP) before 16.0.R26 allows local users to delete files the user would otherwise not have access to via manipulating symbolic links to redirect a McAfee delete action to an unintended file. This is achieved through running a malicious script or program on the target machine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7282|2024-08-04T09:25:48.950Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 13:25:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7289|2024-08-04T09:25:48.951Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20active%20response%20%28mar%29%20for%20windows
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7289</link>
      <description>Privilege Escalation vulnerability in McAfee Active Response (MAR) for Windows prior to 2.4.3 Hotfix 1 allows a malicious script or program to perform functions that the local executing user has not been granted access to.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7289|2024-08-04T09:25:48.951Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7346|2024-08-04T09:25:49.105Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20data%20loss%20prevention%20%28dlp%29%20endpoint%20for%20windows
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7346</link>
      <description>Privilege Escalation vulnerability in McAfee Data Loss Prevention (DLP) for Windows prior to 11.6.100 allows a local, low privileged, attacker through the use of junctions to cause the product to load DLLs of the attacker's choosing. This requires the creation and removal of junctions by the attacker along with sending a specific IOTL command at the correct time.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7346|2024-08-04T09:25:49.105Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 16:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7270|2024-08-04T09:25:48.671Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20advanced%20threat%20defense%20%28atd%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7270</link>
      <description>Exposure of Sensitive Information in the web interface in McAfee Advanced Threat Defense (ATD) prior to 4.12.2 allows remote authenticated users to view sensitive unencrypted information via a carefully crafted HTTP request parameter. The risk is partially mitigated if your ATD instances are deployed as recommended with no direct access from the Internet to them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7270|2024-08-04T09:25:48.671Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 08:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7335|2024-08-04T09:25:49.121Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20total%20protection%20%28mtp%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7335</link>
      <description>Privilege Escalation vulnerability in Microsoft Windows client McAfee Total Protection (MTP) prior to 16.0.29 allows local users to gain elevated privileges via careful manipulation of a folder by creating a junction link. This exploits a lack of protection through a timing issue and is only exploitable in a small time window.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7335|2024-08-04T09:25:49.121Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 08:50:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7269|2024-08-04T09:25:48.625Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20advanced%20threat%20defense%20%28atd%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7269</link>
      <description>Exposure of Sensitive Information in the web interface in McAfee Advanced Threat Defense (ATD) prior to 4.12.2 allows remote authenticated users to view sensitive unencrypted information via a carefully crafted HTTP request parameter. The risk is partially mitigated if your ATD instances are deployed as recommended with no direct access from the Internet to them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7269|2024-08-04T09:25:48.625Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 08:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7334|2024-08-04T09:25:48.982Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20application%20and%20change%20control%20%28macc%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7334</link>
      <description>Improper privilege assignment vulnerability in the installer McAfee Application and Change Control (MACC) prior to 8.3.2 allows local administrators to change or update the configuration settings via a carefully constructed MSI configured to mimic the genuine installer. This version adds further controls for installation/uninstallation of software.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7334|2024-08-04T09:25:48.982Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7326|2024-08-04T09:25:48.970Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20active%20response
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7326</link>
      <description>Improperly implemented security check in McAfee Active Response (MAR) prior to 2.4.4 may allow local administrators to execute malicious code via stopping a core Windows service leaving McAfee core trust component in an inconsistent state resulting in MAR failing open rather than closed</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7326|2024-08-04T09:25:48.970Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7266|2024-08-04T09:25:48.359Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20virusscan%20enterprise%20%28vse%29%20for%20windows
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7266</link>
      <description>Privilege Escalation vulnerability in McAfee VirusScan Enterprise (VSE) for Windows prior to 8.8 Patch 14 Hotfix 116778 allows local users to delete files the user would otherwise not have access to via manipulating symbolic links to redirect a McAfee delete action to an unintended file. This is achieved through running a malicious script or program on the target machine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7266|2024-08-04T09:25:48.359Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7267|2024-08-04T09:25:48.580Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20virusscan%20enterprise%20%28vse%29%20for%20linux
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7267</link>
      <description>Privilege Escalation vulnerability in McAfee VirusScan Enterprise (VSE) for Linux prior to 2.0.3 Hotfix 2635000 allows local users to delete files the user would otherwise not have access to via manipulating symbolic links to redirect a McAfee delete action to an unintended file. This is achieved through running a malicious script or program on the target machine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7267|2024-08-04T09:25:48.580Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7281|2024-08-04T09:25:48.689Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20total%20protection%20%28mtp%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7281</link>
      <description>Privilege Escalation vulnerability in McAfee Total Protection (MTP) prior to 16.0.R26 allows local users to delete files the user would otherwise not have access to via manipulating symbolic links to redirect a McAfee delete action to an unintended file. This is achieved through running a malicious script or program on the target machine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7281|2024-08-04T09:25:48.689Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 13:25:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7291|2024-08-04T09:25:48.817Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20active%20response%20%28mar%29%20for%20mac
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7291</link>
      <description>Privilege Escalation vulnerability in McAfee Active Response (MAR) for Mac prior to 2.4.3 Hotfix 1 allows a malicious script or program to perform functions that the local executing user has not been granted access to.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7291|2024-08-04T09:25:48.817Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7265|2024-08-04T09:25:48.917Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20endpoint%20security%20%28ens%29%20for%20mac
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7265</link>
      <description>Privilege Escalation vulnerability in McAfee Endpoint Security (ENS) for Mac prior to 10.6.9 allows local users to delete files the user would otherwise not have access to via manipulating symbolic links to redirect a McAfee delete action to an unintended file. This is achieved through running a malicious script or program on the target machine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7265|2024-08-04T09:25:48.917Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7288|2024-08-04T09:25:48.820Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20exploit%20detection%20and%20response%20%28edr%29%20for%20mac
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7288</link>
      <description>Privilege Escalation vulnerability in McAfee Exploit Detection and Response (EDR) for Mac prior to 3.1.0 Hotfix 1 allows a malicious script or program to perform functions that the local executing user has not been granted access to.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7288|2024-08-04T09:25:48.820Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7330|2024-08-04T09:25:49.094Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20total%20protection%20%28mtp%29%20trial
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7330</link>
      <description>Privilege Escalation vulnerability in McAfee Total Protection (MTP) trial prior to 4.0.176.1 allows local users to schedule tasks which call malicious software to execute with elevated privileges via editing of environment variables</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7330|2024-08-04T09:25:49.094Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 08:55:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7290|2024-08-04T09:25:48.624Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20active%20response%20%28mar%29%20for%20linux
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7290</link>
      <description>Privilege Escalation vulnerability in McAfee Active Response (MAR) for Linux prior to 2.4.3 Hotfix 1 allows a malicious script or program to perform functions that the local executing user has not been granted access to.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7290|2024-08-04T09:25:48.624Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7287|2024-08-04T09:25:48.845Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20exploit%20detection%20and%20response%20%28edr%29%20for%20linux
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7287</link>
      <description>Privilege Escalation vulnerability in McAfee Exploit Detection and Response (EDR) for Linux prior to 3.1.0 Hotfix 1 allows a malicious script or program to perform functions that the local executing user has not been granted access to.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7287|2024-08-04T09:25:48.845Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7310|2024-08-04T09:25:48.981Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20total%20protection%20%28mtp%29%20trial
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7310</link>
      <description>Privilege Escalation vulnerability in the installer in McAfee McAfee Total Protection (MTP) trial prior to 4.0.161.1 allows local users to change files that are part of write protection rules via manipulating symbolic links to redirect a McAfee file operations to an unintended file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7310|2024-08-04T09:25:48.981Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 08:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7299|2024-08-04T09:25:49.069Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20true%20key%20windows%20client
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7299</link>
      <description>Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information in Memory vulnerability in Microsoft Windows client in McAfee True Key (TK) prior to 6.2.109.2 allows a local user logged in with administrative privileges to access to another user’s passwords on the same machine via triggering a process dump in specific situations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7299|2024-08-04T09:25:49.069Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7308|2024-08-04T09:25:49.044Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20endpoint%20security%20%28ens%29%20for%20windows
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7308</link>
      <description>Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information between McAfee Endpoint Security (ENS) for Windows prior to 10.7.0 February 2021 Update and McAfee Global Threat Intelligence (GTI) servers using DNS allows a remote attacker to view the requests from ENS and responses from GTI over DNS. By gaining control of an intermediate DNS server or altering the network DNS configuration, it is possible for an attacker to intercept requests and send their own responses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7308|2024-08-04T09:25:49.044Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 07:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7327|2024-08-04T09:25:49.032Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20mvision%20endpoint%20detection%20and%20response
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7327</link>
      <description>Improperly implemented security check in McAfee MVISION Endpoint Detection and Response Client (MVEDR) prior to 3.2.0 may allow local administrators to execute malicious code via stopping a core Windows service leaving McAfee core trust component in an inconsistent state resulting in MVEDR failing open rather than closed</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7327|2024-08-04T09:25:49.032Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7264|2024-08-04T09:25:48.690Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20endpoint%20security%20%28ens%29%20for%20windows
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7264</link>
      <description>Privilege Escalation vulnerability in McAfee Endpoint Security (ENS) for Windows prior to 10.7.0 Hotfix 199847 allows local users to delete files the user would otherwise not have access to via manipulating symbolic links to redirect a McAfee delete action to an unintended file. This is achieved through running a malicious script or program on the target machine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7264|2024-08-04T09:25:48.690Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7286|2024-08-04T09:25:48.621Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20exploit%20detection%20and%20response%20%28edr%29%20for%20windows
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7286</link>
      <description>Privilege Escalation vulnerability in McAfee Exploit Detection and Response (EDR) for Windows prior to 3.1.0 Hotfix 1 allows a malicious script or program to perform functions that the local executing user has not been granted access to.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7286|2024-08-04T09:25:48.621Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7285|2024-08-04T09:25:48.715Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20mvision%20endpoint
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7285</link>
      <description>Privilege Escalation vulnerability in McAfee MVISION Endpoint prior to 20.5.0.94 allows a malicious script or program to perform functions that the local executing user has not been granted access to.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7285|2024-08-04T09:25:48.715Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7283|2024-08-04T09:25:48.525Z -- mcafee%2Cllc -- mcafee%20total%20protection%20%28mtp%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7283</link>
      <description>Privilege Escalation vulnerability in McAfee Total Protection (MTP) before 16.0.R26 allows local users to create and edit files via symbolic link manipulation in a location they would otherwise not have access to. This is achieved through running a malicious script or program on the target machine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7283|2024-08-04T09:25:48.525Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 13:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
