<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for realmag777 -- WPCS – WordPress Currency Switcher Professional</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/realmag777/wpcs%20%E2%80%93%20wordpress%20currency%20switcher%20professional.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for realmag777 -- WPCS – WordPress Currency Switcher Professional</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 23:21:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2555|2024-08-02T06:26:09.359Z -- realmag777 -- wpcs%20%E2%80%93%20wordpress%20currency%20switcher%20professional
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2555</link>
      <description>The WPCS – WordPress Currency Switcher Professional plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the create function in versions up to, and including, 1.1.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level permissions and above, to create a custom drop-down currency switcher.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2555|2024-08-02T06:26:09.359Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 05:33:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2557|2024-08-02T06:26:09.368Z -- realmag777 -- wpcs%20%E2%80%93%20wordpress%20currency%20switcher%20professional
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2557</link>
      <description>The WPCS – WordPress Currency Switcher Professional plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the save function in versions up to, and including, 1.1.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level permissions and above, to edit an arbitrary custom drop-down currency switcher.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2557|2024-08-02T06:26:09.368Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 05:33:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2558|2024-08-02T06:26:09.704Z -- realmag777 -- wpcs%20%E2%80%93%20wordpress%20currency%20switcher%20professional
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2558</link>
      <description>The WPCS – WordPress Currency Switcher Professional plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's wpcs_current_currency shortcode in versions up to, and including, 1.1.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2558|2024-08-02T06:26:09.704Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 05:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2556|2024-08-02T06:26:09.694Z -- realmag777 -- wpcs%20%E2%80%93%20wordpress%20currency%20switcher%20professional
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2556</link>
      <description>The WPCS – WordPress Currency Switcher Professional plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the anonymous function for the wpcs_sd_delete action in versions up to, and including, 1.1.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level permissions and above, to delete an arbitrary custom drop-down currency switcher.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2556|2024-08-02T06:26:09.694Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 05:33:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51506|2024-08-02T22:32:10.345Z -- realmag777 -- wpcs%20%E2%80%93%20wordpress%20currency%20switcher%20professional
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51506</link>
      <description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in realmag777 WPCS – WordPress Currency Switcher Professional allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WPCS – WordPress Currency Switcher Professional: from n/a through 1.2.0.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51506|2024-08-02T22:32:10.345Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 11:22:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
