<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Jenkins Project -- Jenkins</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/jenkins%20project/jenkins.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Jenkins Project -- Jenkins</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 18:24:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27899|2024-08-02T12:23:30.612Z -- jenkins%20project -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27899</link>
      <description>Jenkins 2.393 and earlier, LTS 2.375.3 and earlier creates a temporary file in the default temporary directory with the default permissions for newly created files when uploading a plugin for installation, potentially allowing attackers with access to the Jenkins controller file system to read and write the file before it is used, potentially resulting in arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27899|2024-08-02T12:23:30.612Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 17:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27903|2024-08-02T12:23:30.640Z -- jenkins%20project -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27903</link>
      <description>Jenkins 2.393 and earlier, LTS 2.375.3 and earlier creates a temporary file in the default temporary directory with the default permissions for newly created files when uploading a file parameter through the CLI, potentially allowing attackers with access to the Jenkins controller file system to read and write the file before it is used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27903|2024-08-02T12:23:30.640Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 17:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27901|2024-08-02T12:23:30.540Z -- jenkins%20project -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27901</link>
      <description>Jenkins 2.393 and earlier, LTS 2.375.3 and earlier uses the Apache Commons FileUpload library without specifying limits for the number of request parts introduced in version 1.5 for CVE-2023-24998 in org.kohsuke.stapler.RequestImpl, allowing attackers to trigger a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27901|2024-08-02T12:23:30.540Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 17:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27898|2024-08-02T12:23:30.482Z -- jenkins%20project -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27898</link>
      <description>Jenkins 2.270 through 2.393 (both inclusive), LTS 2.277.1 through 2.375.3 (both inclusive) does not escape the Jenkins version a plugin depends on when rendering the error message stating its incompatibility with the current version of Jenkins, resulting in a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exploitable by attackers able to provide plugins to the configured update sites and have this message shown by Jenkins instances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27898|2024-08-02T12:23:30.482Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 17:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35141|2024-08-02T16:23:59.560Z -- jenkins%20project -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35141</link>
      <description>In Jenkins 2.399 and earlier, LTS 2.387.3 and earlier, POST requests are sent in order to load the list of context actions. If part of the URL includes insufficiently escaped user-provided values, a victim may be tricked into sending a POST request to an unexpected endpoint by opening a context menu.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35141|2024-08-02T16:23:59.560Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 12:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27902|2024-08-02T12:23:30.635Z -- jenkins%20project -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27902</link>
      <description>Jenkins 2.393 and earlier, LTS 2.375.3 and earlier shows temporary directories related to job workspaces, which allows attackers with Item/Workspace permission to access their contents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27902|2024-08-02T12:23:30.635Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 17:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27904|2024-08-02T12:23:30.559Z -- jenkins%20project -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27904</link>
      <description>Jenkins 2.393 and earlier, LTS 2.375.3 and earlier prints an error stack trace on agent-related pages when agent connections are broken, potentially revealing information about Jenkins configuration that is otherwise inaccessible to attackers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27904|2024-08-02T12:23:30.559Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 17:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27900|2024-08-02T12:23:30.566Z -- jenkins%20project -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27900</link>
      <description>Jenkins 2.393 and earlier, LTS 2.375.3 and earlier uses the Apache Commons FileUpload library without specifying limits for the number of request parts introduced in version 1.5 for CVE-2023-24998 in hudson.util.MultipartFormDataParser, allowing attackers to trigger a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27900|2024-08-02T12:23:30.566Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 17:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39151|2024-08-02T18:02:06.055Z -- jenkins%20project -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39151</link>
      <description>Jenkins 2.415 and earlier, LTS 2.401.2 and earlier does not sanitize or properly encode URLs in build logs when transforming them into hyperlinks, resulting in a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exploitable by attackers able to control build log contents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39151|2024-08-02T18:02:06.055Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 13:54:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
