<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Jenkins Project -- Jenkins</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/jenkins%20project/jenkins.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Jenkins Project -- Jenkins</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39151|2023-10-24T12:51:12.389Z -- jenkins%20project -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39151</link>
      <description>Jenkins 2.415 and earlier, LTS 2.401.2 and earlier does not sanitize or properly encode URLs in build logs when transforming them into hyperlinks, resulting in a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exploitable by attackers able to control build log contents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39151|2023-10-24T12:51:12.389Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 13:54:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43496|2023-10-24T12:52:02.385Z -- jenkins%20project -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43496</link>
      <description>Jenkins 2.423 and earlier, LTS 2.414.1 and earlier creates a temporary file in the system temporary directory with the default permissions for newly created files when installing a plugin from a URL, potentially allowing attackers with access to the system temporary directory to replace the file before it is installed in Jenkins, potentially resulting in arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43496|2023-10-24T12:52:02.385Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 16:06:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43497|2023-10-24T12:52:03.617Z -- jenkins%20project -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43497</link>
      <description>In Jenkins 2.423 and earlier, LTS 2.414.1 and earlier, processing file uploads using the Stapler web framework creates temporary files in the default system temporary directory with the default permissions for newly created files, potentially allowing attackers with access to the Jenkins controller file system to read and write the files before they are used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43497|2023-10-24T12:52:03.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 16:06:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43498|2023-10-24T12:52:04.805Z -- jenkins%20project -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43498</link>
      <description>In Jenkins 2.423 and earlier, LTS 2.414.1 and earlier, processing file uploads using MultipartFormDataParser creates temporary files in the default system temporary directory with the default permissions for newly created files, potentially allowing attackers with access to the Jenkins controller file system to read and write the files before they are used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43498|2023-10-24T12:52:04.805Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 16:06:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43494|2023-10-24T12:51:59.931Z -- jenkins%20project -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43494</link>
      <description>Jenkins 2.50 through 2.423 (both inclusive), LTS 2.60.1 through 2.414.1 (both inclusive) does not exclude sensitive build variables (e.g., password parameter values) from the search in the build history widget, allowing attackers with Item/Read permission to obtain values of sensitive variables used in builds by iteratively testing different characters until the correct sequence is discovered.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43494|2023-10-24T12:51:59.931Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 16:06:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43495|2023-10-24T12:52:01.123Z -- jenkins%20project -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43495</link>
      <description>Jenkins 2.423 and earlier, LTS 2.414.1 and earlier does not escape the value of the 'caption' constructor parameter of 'ExpandableDetailsNote', resulting in a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exploitable by attackers able to control this parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43495|2023-10-24T12:52:01.123Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 16:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27899|2023-10-24T12:49:04.120Z -- jenkins%20project -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27899</link>
      <description>Jenkins 2.393 and earlier, LTS 2.375.3 and earlier creates a temporary file in the default temporary directory with the default permissions for newly created files when uploading a plugin for installation, potentially allowing attackers with access to the Jenkins controller file system to read and write the file before it is used, potentially resulting in arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27899|2023-10-24T12:49:04.120Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 17:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27898|2023-10-24T12:49:02.967Z -- jenkins%20project -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27898</link>
      <description>Jenkins 2.270 through 2.393 (both inclusive), LTS 2.277.1 through 2.375.3 (both inclusive) does not escape the Jenkins version a plugin depends on when rendering the error message stating its incompatibility with the current version of Jenkins, resulting in a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exploitable by attackers able to provide plugins to the configured update sites and have this message shown by Jenkins instances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27898|2023-10-24T12:49:02.967Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 17:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27904|2023-10-24T12:49:09.772Z -- jenkins%20project -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27904</link>
      <description>Jenkins 2.393 and earlier, LTS 2.375.3 and earlier prints an error stack trace on agent-related pages when agent connections are broken, potentially revealing information about Jenkins configuration that is otherwise inaccessible to attackers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27904|2023-10-24T12:49:09.772Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 17:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27903|2023-10-24T12:49:08.639Z -- jenkins%20project -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27903</link>
      <description>Jenkins 2.393 and earlier, LTS 2.375.3 and earlier creates a temporary file in the default temporary directory with the default permissions for newly created files when uploading a file parameter through the CLI, potentially allowing attackers with access to the Jenkins controller file system to read and write the file before it is used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27903|2023-10-24T12:49:08.639Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 17:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27902|2023-10-24T12:49:07.493Z -- jenkins%20project -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27902</link>
      <description>Jenkins 2.393 and earlier, LTS 2.375.3 and earlier shows temporary directories related to job workspaces, which allows attackers with Item/Workspace permission to access their contents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27902|2023-10-24T12:49:07.493Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 17:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27901|2023-10-24T12:49:06.381Z -- jenkins%20project -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27901</link>
      <description>Jenkins 2.393 and earlier, LTS 2.375.3 and earlier uses the Apache Commons FileUpload library without specifying limits for the number of request parts introduced in version 1.5 for CVE-2023-24998 in org.kohsuke.stapler.RequestImpl, allowing attackers to trigger a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27901|2023-10-24T12:49:06.381Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 17:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27900|2023-10-24T12:49:05.247Z -- jenkins%20project -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27900</link>
      <description>Jenkins 2.393 and earlier, LTS 2.375.3 and earlier uses the Apache Commons FileUpload library without specifying limits for the number of request parts introduced in version 1.5 for CVE-2023-24998 in hudson.util.MultipartFormDataParser, allowing attackers to trigger a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27900|2023-10-24T12:49:05.247Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 17:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35141|2023-10-24T12:50:34.086Z -- jenkins%20project -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35141</link>
      <description>In Jenkins 2.399 and earlier, LTS 2.387.3 and earlier, POST requests are sent in order to load the list of context actions. If part of the URL includes insufficiently escaped user-provided values, a victim may be tricked into sending a POST request to an unexpected endpoint by opening a context menu.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35141|2023-10-24T12:50:34.086Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 12:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23897|2024-04-15T15:06:41.647Z -- jenkins%20project -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23897</link>
      <description>Jenkins 2.441 and earlier, LTS 2.426.2 and earlier does not disable a feature of its CLI command parser that replaces an '@' character followed by a file path in an argument with the file's contents, allowing unauthenticated attackers to read arbitrary files on the Jenkins controller file system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23897|2024-04-15T15:06:41.647Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 17:52:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23898|2024-04-15T15:07:27.730Z -- jenkins%20project -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23898</link>
      <description>Jenkins 2.217 through 2.441 (both inclusive), LTS 2.222.1 through 2.426.2 (both inclusive) does not perform origin validation of requests made through the CLI WebSocket endpoint, resulting in a cross-site WebSocket hijacking (CSWSH) vulnerability, allowing attackers to execute CLI commands on the Jenkins controller.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23898|2024-04-15T15:07:27.730Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 17:52:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
