<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Zarthus -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/zarthus/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Zarthus -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:23:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2015-10096|2024-08-06T08:58:26.542Z -- zarthus -- irc%20twitter%20announcer%20bot
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-10096</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Zarthus IRC Twitter Announcer Bot up to 1.1.0. This affects the function get_tweets of the file lib/twitterbot/plugins/twitter_announcer.rb. The manipulation of the argument tweet leads to command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. Upgrading to version 1.1.1 is able to address this issue. The patch is named 6b1941b7fc2c70e1f40981b43c84a2c20cc12bd3. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-223383.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Zarthus IRC Twitter Announcer Bot bis 1.1.0 gefunden. Dabei betrifft es die Funktion get_tweets der Datei lib/twitterbot/plugins/twitter_announcer.rb. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments tweet mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Sie ist schwierig auszunutzen. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 1.1.1 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als 6b1941b7fc2c70e1f40981b43c84a2c20cc12bd3 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2015-10096|2024-08-06T08:58:26.542Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 04:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
