<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for man-group -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/man-group/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for man-group -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 19:19:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3408|2024-06-06T18:54:43.713Z -- man-group -- man-group%2Fdtale
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3408</link>
      <description>man-group/dtale version 3.10.0 is vulnerable to an authentication bypass and remote code execution (RCE) due to improper input validation. The vulnerability arises from a hardcoded `SECRET_KEY` in the flask configuration, allowing attackers to forge a session cookie if authentication is enabled. Additionally, the application fails to properly restrict custom filter queries, enabling attackers to execute arbitrary code on the server by bypassing the restriction on the `/update-settings` endpoint, even when `enable_custom_filters` is not enabled. This vulnerability allows attackers to bypass authentication mechanisms and execute remote code on the server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3408|2024-06-06T18:54:43.713Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:54:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21642|2024-01-05T21:11:41.528Z -- man-group -- dtale</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21642</link>
      <description>D-Tale is a visualizer for Pandas data structures. Users hosting versions D-Tale prior to 3.9.0 publicly can be vulnerable to server-side request forgery (SSRF), allowing attackers to access files on the server. Users should upgrade to version 3.9.0, where the `Load From the Web` input is turned off by default. The only workaround for versions earlier than 3.9.0 is to only host D-Tale to trusted users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21642|2024-01-05T21:11:41.528Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 21:11:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
