<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for CODESYS -- Runtime Toolkit</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/codesys/runtime%20toolkit.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for CODESYS -- Runtime Toolkit</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 15:22:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-32142|2024-08-03T07:32:55.956Z -- codesys -- runtime%20toolkit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32142</link>
      <description>Multiple CODESYS Products are prone to a out-of bounds read or write access. A low privileged remote attacker may craft a request with invalid offset, which can cause an out-of-bounds read or write access, resulting in denial-of-service condition or local memory overwrite, which can lead to a change of local files. User interaction is not required.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-32142|2024-08-03T07:32:55.956Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-32143|2024-08-03T07:32:55.974Z -- codesys -- runtime%20toolkit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32143</link>
      <description>In multiple CODESYS products, file download and upload function allows access to internal files in the working directory e.g. firmware files of the PLC. All requests are processed on the controller only if no level 1 password is configured on the controller or if remote attacker has previously successfully authenticated himself to the controller. A successful Attack may lead to a denial of service, change of local files, or drain of confidential Information. User interaction is not required</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-32143|2024-08-03T07:32:55.974Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-32141|2024-08-03T07:32:56.012Z -- codesys -- runtime%20toolkit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32141</link>
      <description>Multiple CODESYS Products are prone to a buffer over read. A low privileged remote attacker may craft a request with an invalid offset, which can cause an internal buffer over-read, resulting in a denial-of-service condition. User interaction is not required.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-32141|2024-08-03T07:32:56.012Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-32140|2024-08-03T07:32:55.985Z -- codesys -- runtime%20toolkit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32140</link>
      <description>Multiple CODESYS products are affected to a buffer overflow.A low privileged remote attacker may craft a request, which can cause a buffer copy without checking the size of the service, resulting in a denial-of-service condition. User Interaction is not required.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-32140|2024-08-03T07:32:55.985Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-32139|2024-08-03T07:32:56.024Z -- codesys -- runtime%20toolkit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32139</link>
      <description>In multiple CODESYS products, a low privileged remote attacker may craft a request, which cause an out-of-bounds read, resulting in a denial-of-service condition. User Interaction is not required.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-32139|2024-08-03T07:32:56.024Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-32138|2024-08-03T07:32:56.049Z -- codesys -- runtime%20toolkit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32138</link>
      <description>In multiple CODESYS products, a remote attacker may craft a request which may cause an unexpected sign extension, resulting in a denial-of-service condition or memory overwrite.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-32138|2024-08-03T07:32:56.049Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-32137|2024-08-03T07:32:56.007Z -- codesys -- runtime%20toolkit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32137</link>
      <description>In multiple CODESYS products, a low privileged remote attacker may craft a request, which may cause a heap-based buffer overflow, resulting in a denial-of-service condition or memory overwrite. User interaction is not required.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-32137|2024-08-03T07:32:56.007Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-1965|2024-08-03T00:24:43.779Z -- codesys -- runtime%20toolkit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1965</link>
      <description>Multiple products of CODESYS implement a improper error handling. A low privilege remote attacker may craft a request, which is not properly processed by the error handling. In consequence, the file referenced by the request could be deleted. User interaction is not required.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-1965|2024-08-03T00:24:43.779Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-32136|2024-08-03T07:32:56.014Z -- codesys -- runtime%20toolkit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32136</link>
      <description>In multiple CODESYS products, a low privileged remote attacker may craft a request that cause a read access to an uninitialized pointer, resulting in a denial-of-service. User interaction is not required.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-32136|2024-08-03T07:32:56.014Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
