<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for The Linux Foundation -- kernel</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/the%20linux%20foundation/kernel.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for The Linux Foundation -- kernel</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 13:24:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-14634|2024-08-05T09:38:13.057Z -- the%20linux%20foundation -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-14634</link>
      <description>An integer overflow flaw was found in the Linux kernel's create_elf_tables() function. An unprivileged local user with access to SUID (or otherwise privileged) binary could use this flaw to escalate their privileges on the system. Kernel versions 2.6.x, 3.10.x and 4.14.x are believed to be vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-14634|2024-08-05T09:38:13.057Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-16885|2024-08-05T10:32:54.243Z -- the%20linux%20foundation -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-16885</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel that allows the userspace to call memcpy_fromiovecend() and similar functions with a zero offset and buffer length which causes the read beyond the buffer boundaries, in certain cases causing a memory access fault and a system halt by accessing invalid memory address. This issue only affects kernel version 3.10.x as shipped with Red Hat Enterprise Linux 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-16885|2024-08-05T10:32:54.243Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-14633|2024-08-05T09:38:13.035Z -- the%20linux%20foundation -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-14633</link>
      <description>A security flaw was found in the chap_server_compute_md5() function in the ISCSI target code in the Linux kernel in a way an authentication request from an ISCSI initiator is processed. An unauthenticated remote attacker can cause a stack buffer overflow and smash up to 17 bytes of the stack. The attack requires the iSCSI target to be enabled on the victim host. Depending on how the target's code was built (i.e. depending on a compiler, compile flags and hardware architecture) an attack may lead to a system crash and thus to a denial-of-service or possibly to a non-authorized access to data exported by an iSCSI target. Due to the nature of the flaw, privilege escalation cannot be fully ruled out, although we believe it is highly unlikely. Kernel versions 4.18.x, 4.14.x and 3.10.x are believed to be vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-14633|2024-08-05T09:38:13.035Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-16880|2024-08-05T10:32:54.187Z -- the%20linux%20foundation -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-16880</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's handle_rx() function in the [vhost_net] driver. A malicious virtual guest, under specific conditions, can trigger an out-of-bounds write in a kmalloc-8 slab on a virtual host which may lead to a kernel memory corruption and a system panic. Due to the nature of the flaw, privilege escalation cannot be fully ruled out. Versions from v4.16 and newer are vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-16880|2024-08-05T10:32:54.187Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-14641|2024-08-05T09:38:12.826Z -- the%20linux%20foundation -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-14641</link>
      <description>A security flaw was found in the ip_frag_reasm() function in net/ipv4/ip_fragment.c in the Linux kernel from 4.19-rc1 to 4.19-rc3 inclusive, which can cause a later system crash in ip_do_fragment(). With certain non-default, but non-rare, configuration of a victim host, an attacker can trigger this crash remotely, thus leading to a remote denial-of-service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-14641|2024-08-05T09:38:12.826Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
