<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for The Linux Foundation -- kernel</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/the%20linux%20foundation/kernel.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for The Linux Foundation -- kernel</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 20:22:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3882|2024-08-04T19:19:18.633Z -- the%20linux%20foundation -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3882</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's vfio interface implementation that permits violation of the user's locked memory limit. If a device is bound to a vfio driver, such as vfio-pci, and the local attacker is administratively granted ownership of the device, it may cause a system memory exhaustion and thus a denial of service (DoS). Versions 3.10, 4.14 and 4.18 are vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3882|2024-08-04T19:19:18.633Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 15:23:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3896|2024-08-04T19:26:26.644Z -- the%20linux%20foundation -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3896</link>
      <description>A double-free can happen in idr_remove_all() in lib/idr.c in the Linux kernel 2.6 branch. An unprivileged local attacker can use this flaw for a privilege escalation or for a system crash and a denial of service (DoS).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3896|2024-08-04T19:26:26.644Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 23:40:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3874|2024-08-04T19:19:18.619Z -- the%20linux%20foundation -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3874</link>
      <description>The SCTP socket buffer used by a userspace application is not accounted by the cgroups subsystem. An attacker can use this flaw to cause a denial of service attack. Kernel 3.10.x and 4.18.x branches are believed to be vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3874|2024-08-04T19:19:18.619Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 18:30:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3901|2024-08-04T19:26:26.688Z -- the%20linux%20foundation -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3901</link>
      <description>A race condition in perf_event_open() allows local attackers to leak sensitive data from setuid programs. As no relevant locks (in particular the cred_guard_mutex) are held during the ptrace_may_access() call, it is possible for the specified target task to perform an execve() syscall with setuid execution before perf_event_alloc() actually attaches to it, allowing an attacker to bypass the ptrace_may_access() check and the perf_event_exit_task(current) call that is performed in install_exec_creds() during privileged execve() calls. This issue affects kernel versions before 4.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3901|2024-08-04T19:26:26.688Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 15:22:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3837|2024-08-04T19:19:18.565Z -- the%20linux%20foundation -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3837</link>
      <description>It was found that the net_dma code in tcp_recvmsg() in the 2.6.32 kernel as shipped in RHEL6 is thread-unsafe. So an unprivileged multi-threaded userspace application calling recvmsg() for the same network socket in parallel executed on ioatdma-enabled hardware with net_dma enabled can leak the memory, crash the host leading to a denial-of-service or cause a random memory corruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3837|2024-08-04T19:19:18.565Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 14:37:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10751|2024-08-04T11:14:15.560Z -- the%20linux%20foundation -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10751</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernels SELinux LSM hook implementation before version 5.7, where it incorrectly assumed that an skb would only contain a single netlink message. The hook would incorrectly only validate the first netlink message in the skb and allow or deny the rest of the messages within the skb with the granted permission without further processing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10751|2024-08-04T11:14:15.560Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 14:54:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3887|2024-08-04T19:19:18.713Z -- the%20linux%20foundation -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3887</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the way KVM hypervisor handled x2APIC Machine Specific Rregister (MSR) access with nested(=1) virtualization enabled. In that, L1 guest could access L0's APIC register values via L2 guest, when 'virtualize x2APIC mode' is enabled. A guest could use this flaw to potentially crash the host kernel resulting in DoS issue. Kernel versions from 4.16 and newer are vulnerable to this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3887|2024-08-04T19:19:18.713Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
