<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for GZ Scripts -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/gz%20scripts/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for GZ Scripts -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 22:23:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3555|2024-10-23T20:25:51.690Z -- gz%20scripts -- php%20vacation%20rental%20script
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3555</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in GZ Scripts PHP Vacation Rental Script 1.8. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /preview.php. The manipulation of the argument page/layout/sort_by/property_id leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The identifier VDB-233349 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in GZ Scripts PHP Vacation Rental Script 1.8 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei /preview.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments page/layout/sort_by/property_id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3555|2024-10-23T20:25:51.690Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 12:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3559|2024-10-23T20:02:47.889Z -- gz%20scripts -- php%20gz%20appointment%20scheduling%20script
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3559</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in GZ Scripts PHP GZ Appointment Scheduling Script 1.8. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /load.php. The manipulation of the argument first_name/second_name/phone/address_1/country leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The identifier VDB-233353 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In GZ Scripts PHP GZ Appointment Scheduling Script 1.8 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei /load.php. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments first_name/second_name/phone/address_1/country mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3559|2024-10-23T20:02:47.889Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 14:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
