<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for GZ Scripts -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/gz%20scripts/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for GZ Scripts -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 19:20:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3557|2024-08-02T07:01:55.953Z -- gz%20scripts -- property%20listing%20script
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3557</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in GZ Scripts Property Listing Script 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /preview.php. The manipulation of the argument page/layout/sort_by leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-233351. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in GZ Scripts Property Listing Script 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei /preview.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments page/layout/sort_by mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3557|2024-08-02T07:01:55.953Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 13:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3564|2024-08-02T07:01:55.930Z -- gz%20scripts -- gz%20multi%20hotel%20booking%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3564</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in GZ Scripts GZ Multi Hotel Booking System 1.8. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument adults/children/cal_id leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. VDB-233358 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in GZ Scripts GZ Multi Hotel Booking System 1.8 ausgemacht. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei /index.php. Durch Manipulation des Arguments adults/children/cal_id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3564|2024-08-02T07:01:55.930Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 17:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3555|2024-08-02T07:01:56.966Z -- gz%20scripts -- php%20vacation%20rental%20script
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3555</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in GZ Scripts PHP Vacation Rental Script 1.8. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /preview.php. The manipulation of the argument page/layout/sort_by/property_id leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The identifier VDB-233349 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in GZ Scripts PHP Vacation Rental Script 1.8 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei /preview.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments page/layout/sort_by/property_id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3555|2024-08-02T07:01:56.966Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 12:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3642|2024-08-02T07:01:57.266Z -- gz%20scripts -- vacation%20rental%20website
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3642</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in GZ Scripts Vacation Rental Website 1.8 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /VacationRentalWebsite/property/8/ad-has-principes/ of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument username/title/comment leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-233888.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in GZ Scripts Vacation Rental Website 1.8 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei /VacationRentalWebsite/property/8/ad-has-principes/ der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments username/title/comment mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3642|2024-08-02T07:01:57.266Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 17:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3556|2024-08-02T07:01:56.699Z -- gz%20scripts -- car%20listing%20script%20php
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3556</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in GZ Scripts Car Listing Script PHP 1.8. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /preview.php. The manipulation of the argument page/sort_by leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. VDB-233350 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In GZ Scripts Car Listing Script PHP 1.8 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei /preview.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments page/sort_by mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3556|2024-08-02T07:01:56.699Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 13:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3554|2024-08-02T07:01:56.879Z -- gz%20scripts -- gz%20forum%20script
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3554</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in GZ Scripts GZ Forum Script 1.8 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /preview.php. The manipulation of the argument catid/topicid/topic/topic_message/free_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-233348. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in GZ Scripts GZ Forum Script 1.8 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei /preview.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments catid/topicid/topic/topic_message/free_name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3554|2024-08-02T07:01:56.879Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 12:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3544|2024-08-02T07:01:56.039Z -- gz%20scripts -- time%20slot%20booking%20calendar%20php
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3544</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in GZ Scripts Time Slot Booking Calendar PHP 1.8. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /load.php. The manipulation of the argument first_name/second_name/phone/address_1/country leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-233296. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In GZ Scripts Time Slot Booking Calendar PHP 1.8 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei /load.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments first_name/second_name/phone/address_1/country mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3544|2024-08-02T07:01:56.039Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 17:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3559|2024-08-02T07:01:56.453Z -- gz%20scripts -- php%20gz%20appointment%20scheduling%20script
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3559</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in GZ Scripts PHP GZ Appointment Scheduling Script 1.8. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /load.php. The manipulation of the argument first_name/second_name/phone/address_1/country leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The identifier VDB-233353 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In GZ Scripts PHP GZ Appointment Scheduling Script 1.8 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei /load.php. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments first_name/second_name/phone/address_1/country mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3559|2024-08-02T07:01:56.453Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 14:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3562|2024-08-02T07:01:56.063Z -- gz%20scripts -- php%20crm%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3562</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in GZ Scripts PHP CRM Platform 1.8 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument action leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-233356. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In GZ Scripts PHP CRM Platform 1.8 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle gefunden. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei /index.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments action mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3562|2024-08-02T07:01:56.063Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 16:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3561|2024-08-02T07:01:55.910Z -- gz%20scripts -- php%20gz%20hotel%20booking%20script
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3561</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in GZ Scripts PHP GZ Hotel Booking Script 1.8. This affects an unknown part of the file /load.php. The manipulation of the argument first_name/second_name/phone/address_1/country leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-233355. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in GZ Scripts PHP GZ Hotel Booking Script 1.8 gefunden. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei /load.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments first_name/second_name/phone/address_1/country mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3561|2024-08-02T07:01:55.910Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 15:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3970|2024-08-02T07:08:50.824Z -- gz%20scripts -- availability%20booking%20calendar%20php
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3970</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in GZ Scripts Availability Booking Calendar PHP 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /index.php?controller=GzUser&amp;action=edit&amp;id=1 of the component Image Handler. The manipulation of the argument img leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-235569 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in GZ Scripts Availability Booking Calendar PHP 1.0 gefunden. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei /index.php?controller=GzUser&amp;action=edit&amp;id=1 der Komponente Image Handler. Durch Manipulation des Arguments img mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3970|2024-08-02T07:08:50.824Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 12:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3543|2024-08-02T07:01:57.514Z -- gz%20scripts -- availability%20booking%20calendar%20php
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3543</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in GZ Scripts Availability Booking Calendar PHP 1.8. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file load.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument cid/first_name/second_name/address_1/country leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-233295. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in GZ Scripts Availability Booking Calendar PHP 1.8 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei load.php der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments cid/first_name/second_name/address_1/country mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3543|2024-08-02T07:01:57.514Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 16:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3560|2024-08-02T07:01:55.960Z -- gz%20scripts -- ticket%20booking%20script
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3560</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in GZ Scripts Ticket Booking Script 1.8. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /load.php. The manipulation of the argument first_name/second_name/phone/address_1/country leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. VDB-233354 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in GZ Scripts Ticket Booking Script 1.8 entdeckt. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei /load.php. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments first_name/second_name/phone/address_1/country mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3560|2024-08-02T07:01:55.960Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 15:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3558|2024-08-02T07:01:56.648Z -- gz%20scripts -- event%20booking%20calendar
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3558</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in GZ Scripts Event Booking Calendar 1.8. Affected is an unknown function of the file /load.php. The manipulation of the argument first_name/second_name/phone/address_1/country leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-233352. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in GZ Scripts Event Booking Calendar 1.8 entdeckt. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei /load.php. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments first_name/second_name/phone/address_1/country mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3558|2024-08-02T07:01:56.648Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 14:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3757|2024-08-02T07:08:49.605Z -- gz%20scripts -- car%20rental%20script
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3757</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in GZ Scripts Car Rental Script 1.8. Affected is an unknown function of the file /EventBookingCalendar/load.php?controller=GzFront/action=checkout/cid=1/layout=calendar/show_header=T/local=3. The manipulation of the argument first_name/second_name/phone/address_1/country leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-234432. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in GZ Scripts Car Rental Script 1.8 entdeckt. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei /EventBookingCalendar/load.php?controller=GzFront/action=checkout/cid=1/layout=calendar/show_header=T/local=3. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments first_name/second_name/phone/address_1/country mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3757|2024-08-02T07:08:49.605Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 04:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3563|2024-08-02T07:01:56.047Z -- gz%20scripts -- gz%20e%20learning%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3563</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in GZ Scripts GZ E Learning Platform 1.8 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component URL Parameter Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The identifier VDB-233357 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in GZ Scripts GZ E Learning Platform 1.8 gefunden. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Komponente URL Parameter Handler. Durch die Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3563|2024-08-02T07:01:56.047Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 16:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3969|2024-08-02T07:08:50.715Z -- gz%20scripts -- availability%20booking%20calendar%20php
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3969</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in GZ Scripts Availability Booking Calendar PHP 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file index.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument promo_code leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-235568.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in GZ Scripts Availability Booking Calendar PHP 1.0 entdeckt. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei index.php der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments promo_code mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3969|2024-08-02T07:08:50.715Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 11:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
