<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for GZ Scripts -- Availability Booking Calendar PHP</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/gz%20scripts/availability%20booking%20calendar%20php.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for GZ Scripts -- Availability Booking Calendar PHP</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 07:22:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3543|2024-08-02T07:01:57.514Z -- gz%20scripts -- availability%20booking%20calendar%20php
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3543</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in GZ Scripts Availability Booking Calendar PHP 1.8. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file load.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument cid/first_name/second_name/address_1/country leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-233295. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in GZ Scripts Availability Booking Calendar PHP 1.8 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei load.php der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments cid/first_name/second_name/address_1/country mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3543|2024-08-02T07:01:57.514Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 16:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
