<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for opencontainers -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/opencontainers/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for opencontainers -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 20:23:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25809|2024-08-02T11:32:12.344Z -- opencontainers -- runc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25809</link>
      <description>runc is a CLI tool for spawning and running containers according to the OCI specification. In affected versions it was found that rootless runc makes `/sys/fs/cgroup` writable in following conditons: 1. when runc is executed inside the user namespace, and the `config.json` does not specify the cgroup namespace to be unshared (e.g.., `(docker|podman|nerdctl) run --cgroupns=host`, with Rootless Docker/Podman/nerdctl) or 2. when runc is executed outside the user namespace, and `/sys` is mounted with `rbind, ro` (e.g., `runc spec --rootless`; this condition is very rare). A container may gain the write access to user-owned cgroup hierarchy `/sys/fs/cgroup/user.slice/...` on the host . Other users's cgroup hierarchies are not affected. Users are advised to upgrade to version 1.1.5. Users unable to upgrade may unshare the cgroup namespace (`(docker|podman|nerdctl) run --cgroupns=private)`. This is the default behavior of Docker/Podman/nerdctl on cgroup v2 hosts. or add `/sys/fs/cgroup` to `maskedPaths`.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25809|2024-08-02T11:32:12.344Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 18:22:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28642|2024-08-02T13:43:23.241Z -- opencontainers -- runc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28642</link>
      <description>runc is a CLI tool for spawning and running containers according to the OCI specification. It was found that AppArmor can be bypassed when `/proc` inside the container is symlinked with a specific mount configuration. This issue has been fixed in runc version 1.1.5, by prohibiting symlinked `/proc`. See PR #3785 for details. users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should avoid using an untrusted container image.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28642|2024-08-02T13:43:23.241Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 18:15:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
