<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Vesystem -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/vesystem/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Vesystem -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3803|2024-04-15T18:31:05.145Z -- vesystem -- cloud%20desktop
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3803</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Vesystem Cloud Desktop up to 20240408. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /Public/webuploader/0.1.5/server/fileupload.php. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-260776. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Vesystem Cloud Desktop bis 20240408 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei /Public/webuploader/0.1.5/server/fileupload.php. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments file mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3803|2024-04-15T18:31:05.145Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 18:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3804|2024-06-04T17:32:40.490Z -- vesystem -- cloud%20desktop
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3804</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Vesystem Cloud Desktop up to 20240408. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /Public/webuploader/0.1.5/server/fileupload2.php. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-260777 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Vesystem Cloud Desktop bis 20240408 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei /Public/webuploader/0.1.5/server/fileupload2.php. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments file mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3804|2024-06-04T17:32:40.490Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 19:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
