<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Linux Kernel -- Kernel</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/linux%20kernel/kernel.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Linux Kernel -- Kernel</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 19:19:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14386|2024-08-04T12:46:34.367Z -- linux%20kernel -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14386</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel before 5.9-rc4. Memory corruption can be exploited to gain root privileges from unprivileged processes. The highest threat from this vulnerability is to data confidentiality and integrity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14386|2024-08-04T12:46:34.367Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 12:48:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14304|2024-08-04T12:39:36.607Z -- linux%20kernel -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14304</link>
      <description>A memory disclosure flaw was found in the Linux kernel's ethernet drivers, in the way it read data from the EEPROM of the device. This flaw allows a local user to read uninitialized values from the kernel memory. The highest threat from this vulnerability is to confidentiality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14304|2024-08-04T12:39:36.607Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 19:40:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10781|2024-08-04T11:14:15.582Z -- linux%20kernel -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10781</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux Kernel before 5.8-rc6 in the ZRAM kernel module, where a user with a local account and the ability to read the /sys/class/zram-control/hot_add file can create ZRAM device nodes in the /dev/ directory. This read allocates kernel memory and is not accounted for a user that triggers the creation of that ZRAM device. With this vulnerability, continually reading the device may consume a large amount of system memory and cause the Out-of-Memory (OOM) killer to activate and terminate random userspace processes, possibly making the system inoperable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10781|2024-08-04T11:14:15.582Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10767|2024-08-04T11:14:15.591Z -- linux%20kernel -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10767</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel before 5.8-rc1 in the implementation of the Enhanced IBPB (Indirect Branch Prediction Barrier). The IBPB mitigation will be disabled when STIBP is not available or when the Enhanced Indirect Branch Restricted Speculation (IBRS) is available. This flaw allows a local attacker to perform a Spectre V2 style attack when this configuration is active. The highest threat from this vulnerability is to confidentiality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10767|2024-08-04T11:14:15.591Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 22:14:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10766|2024-08-04T11:14:15.011Z -- linux%20kernel -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10766</link>
      <description>A logic bug flaw was found in Linux kernel before 5.8-rc1 in the implementation of SSBD. A bug in the logic handling allows an attacker with a local account to disable SSBD protection during a context switch when additional speculative execution mitigations are in place. This issue was introduced when the per task/process conditional STIPB switching was added on top of the existing SSBD switching. The highest threat from this vulnerability is to confidentiality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10766|2024-08-04T11:14:15.011Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 22:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1749|2024-08-04T06:46:30.814Z -- linux%20kernel -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1749</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's implementation of some networking protocols in IPsec, such as VXLAN and GENEVE tunnels over IPv6. When an encrypted tunnel is created between two hosts, the kernel isn't correctly routing tunneled data over the encrypted link; rather sending the data unencrypted. This would allow anyone in between the two endpoints to read the traffic unencrypted. The main threat from this vulnerability is to data confidentiality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1749|2024-08-04T06:46:30.814Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 14:35:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14385|2024-08-04T12:46:34.096Z -- linux%20kernel -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14385</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel before 5.9-rc4. A failure of the file system metadata validator in XFS can cause an inode with a valid, user-creatable extended attribute to be flagged as corrupt. This can lead to the filesystem being shutdown, or otherwise rendered inaccessible until it is remounted, leading to a denial of service. The highest threat from this vulnerability is to system availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14385|2024-08-04T12:46:34.096Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 21:14:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14314|2024-08-04T12:39:36.409Z -- linux%20kernel -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14314</link>
      <description>A memory out-of-bounds read flaw was found in the Linux kernel before 5.9-rc2 with the ext3/ext4 file system, in the way it accesses a directory with broken indexing. This flaw allows a local user to crash the system if the directory exists. The highest threat from this vulnerability is to system availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14314|2024-08-04T12:39:36.409Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10732|2024-08-04T11:14:14.998Z -- linux%20kernel -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10732</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's implementation of Userspace core dumps. This flaw allows an attacker with a local account to crash a trivial program and exfiltrate private kernel data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10732|2024-08-04T11:14:14.998Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10768|2024-08-04T11:14:15.299Z -- linux%20kernel -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10768</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux Kernel before 5.8-rc1 in the prctl() function, where it can be used to enable indirect branch speculation after it has been disabled. This call incorrectly reports it as being 'force disabled' when it is not and opens the system to Spectre v2 attacks. The highest threat from this vulnerability is to confidentiality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10768|2024-08-04T11:14:15.299Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 23:13:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
