<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for WordPress Foundation -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/wordpress%20foundation/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for WordPress Foundation -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5692|2024-04-05T12:52:32.816Z -- wordpress%20foundation -- wordpress
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5692</link>
      <description>WordPress Core is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in versions up to, and including,  6.4.3 via the redirect_guess_404_permalink function. This can allow unauthenticated attackers to expose the slug of a custom post whose 'publicly_queryable' post status has been set to 'false'.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5692|2024-04-05T12:52:32.816Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 12:52:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2745|2023-05-17T08:36:44.034Z -- wordpress%20foundation -- wordpress
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-2745</link>
      <description>WordPress Core is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in versions up to, and including, 6.2, via the ‘wp_lang’ parameter. This allows unauthenticated attackers to access and load arbitrary translation files. In cases where an attacker is able to upload a crafted translation file onto the site, such as via an upload form, this could be also used to perform a Cross-Site Scripting attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2745|2023-05-17T08:36:44.034Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 08:36:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4439|2024-06-04T17:54:08.655Z -- wordpress%20foundation -- wordpress
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4439</link>
      <description>WordPress Core is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via user display names in the Avatar block in various versions up to 6.5.2 due to insufficient output escaping on the display name. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. In addition, it also makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that have the comment block present and display the comment author's avatar.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4439|2024-06-04T17:54:08.655Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 05:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
