<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Schneider Electric SE -- 66074 MGE Network Management Card Transverse installed in MGE UPS and MGE STS</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/schneider%20electric%20se/66074%20mge%20network%20management%20card%20transverse%20installed%20in%20mge%20ups%20and%20mge%20sts.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Schneider Electric SE -- 66074 MGE Network Management Card Transverse installed in MGE UPS and MGE STS</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 22:22:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7246|2024-08-05T06:24:11.827Z -- schneider%20electric%20se -- 66074%20mge%20network%20management%20card%20transverse%20installed%20in%20mge%20ups%20and%20mge%20sts
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7246</link>
      <description>A cleartext transmission of sensitive information vulnerability exists in Schneider Electric's 66074 MGE Network Management Card Transverse installed in MGE UPS and MGE STS. he integrated web server (Port 80/443/TCP) of the affected devices could allow remote attackers to discover an administrative account. If default on device, it is not using a SSL in settings and if multiple request of the page "Access Control" (IP-address device/ups/pas_cont.htm) account data will be sent in cleartext</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7246|2024-08-05T06:24:11.827Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7245|2024-08-05T06:24:11.357Z -- schneider%20electric%20se -- 66074%20mge%20network%20management%20card%20transverse%20installed%20in%20mge%20ups%20and%20mge%20sts
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7245</link>
      <description>An improper authorization vulnerability exists In Schneider Electric's 66074 MGE Network Management Card Transverse installed in MGE UPS and MGE STS. The integrated web server (Port 80/443/TCP) of the affected devices could allow a remote attacker to change UPS control and shutdown parameters or other critical settings without authorization.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7245|2024-08-05T06:24:11.357Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7243|2024-08-05T06:24:11.636Z -- schneider%20electric%20se -- 66074%20mge%20network%20management%20card%20transverse%20installed%20in%20mge%20ups%20and%20mge%20sts
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7243</link>
      <description>An authorization bypass vulnerability exists In Schneider Electric's 66074 MGE Network Management Card Transverse installed in MGE UPS and MGE STS. The integrated web server (Port 80/443/TCP) of the affected devices could allow a remote attacker to get a full access to device, bypassing the authorization system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7243|2024-08-05T06:24:11.636Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7244|2024-08-05T06:24:11.508Z -- schneider%20electric%20se -- 66074%20mge%20network%20management%20card%20transverse%20installed%20in%20mge%20ups%20and%20mge%20sts
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7244</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability exists In Schneider Electric's 66074 MGE Network Management Card Transverse installed in MGE UPS and MGE STS. The integrated web server (Port 80/443/TCP) of the affected devices could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive device information if network access was obtained.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7244|2024-08-05T06:24:11.508Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
