<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Ubiquiti Inc -- UniFi Connect EV Station</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ubiquiti%20inc/unifi%20connect%20ev%20station.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Ubiquiti Inc -- UniFi Connect EV Station</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29206|2024-06-04T17:56:59.455Z -- ubiquiti%20inc -- unifi%20connect%20ev%20station
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-29206</link>
      <description>An Improper Access Control could allow a malicious actor authenticated in the API to enable Android Debug Bridge (ADB) and make unsupported changes to the system.

 

Affected Products:

UniFi Connect EV Station (Version 1.1.18 and earlier) 

UniFi Connect EV Station Pro (Version 1.1.18 and earlier)

UniFi Access G2 Reader Pro (Version 1.2.172 and earlier)

UniFi Access Reader Pro (Version 2.7.238 and earlier)

UniFi Access Intercom (Version 1.0.66 and earlier)

UniFi Access Intercom Viewer (Version 1.0.5 and earlier)

UniFi Connect Display (Version 1.9.324 and earlier)

UniFi Connect Display Cast (Version 1.6.225 and earlier)

 

Mitigation:

Update UniFi Connect Application to Version 3.10.7 or later.

Update UniFi Connect EV Station to Version 1.2.15 or later.   

Update UniFi Connect EV Station Pro to Version 1.2.15 or later.

Update UniFi Access G2 Reader Pro Version 1.3.37 or later.

Update UniFi Access Reader Pro Version 2.8.19 or later.

Update UniFi Access Intercom Version 1.1.32 or later.

Update UniFi Access Intercom Viewer Version 1.1.6 or later.

Update UniFi Connect Display to Version 1.11.348 or later. 

Update UniFi Connect Display Cast to Version 1.8.255 or later.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29206|2024-06-04T17:56:59.455Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
