<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Ubiquiti -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ubiquiti/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Ubiquiti -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 10:23:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1457|2024-08-02T05:49:11.641Z -- ubiquiti -- edgerouter%20x
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1457</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Ubiquiti EdgeRouter X 2.0.9-hotfix.6. Affected is an unknown function of the component Static Routing Configuration Handler. The manipulation of the argument next-hop-interface leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. VDB-223302 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor position is that post-authentication issues are not accepted as vulnerabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1457|2024-08-02T05:49:11.641Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1456|2024-08-02T05:49:11.556Z -- ubiquiti -- edgerouter%20x
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1456</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Ubiquiti EdgeRouter X 2.0.9-hotfix.6. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component NAT Configuration Handler. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. The identifier VDB-223301 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor position is that post-authentication issues are not accepted as vulnerabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1456|2024-08-02T05:49:11.556Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2377|2024-08-02T06:19:14.992Z -- ubiquiti -- edgerouter%20x
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2377</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Ubiquiti EdgeRouter X up to 2.0.9-hotfix.6. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument name leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-227653 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In Ubiquiti EdgeRouter X bis 2.0.9-hotfix.6 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Komponente Web Management Interface. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2377|2024-08-02T06:19:14.992Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 15:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2379|2024-08-02T06:19:14.991Z -- ubiquiti -- edgerouter%20x
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2379</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Ubiquiti EdgeRouter X up to 2.0.9-hotfix.6. This affects an unknown part of the component Web Service. The manipulation leads to denial of service. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-227655.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Ubiquiti EdgeRouter X bis 2.0.9-hotfix.6 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Komponente Web Service. Durch Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine denial of service-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2379|2024-08-02T06:19:14.991Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 16:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2373|2024-08-02T06:19:14.944Z -- ubiquiti -- edgerouter%20x
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2373</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Ubiquiti EdgeRouter X up to 2.0.9-hotfix.6. This affects an unknown part of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument ecn-up leads to command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-227649 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Ubiquiti EdgeRouter X bis 2.0.9-hotfix.6 gefunden. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Komponente Web Management Interface. Durch Manipulation des Arguments ecn-up mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2373|2024-08-02T06:19:14.944Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 14:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2378|2024-08-02T06:19:14.921Z -- ubiquiti -- edgerouter%20x
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2378</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Ubiquiti EdgeRouter X up to 2.0.9-hotfix.6. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument suffix-rate-up leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-227654 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Ubiquiti EdgeRouter X bis 2.0.9-hotfix.6 ausgemacht. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Komponente Web Management Interface. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments suffix-rate-up mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2378|2024-08-02T06:19:14.921Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 16:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2376|2024-08-02T06:19:15.146Z -- ubiquiti -- edgerouter%20x
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2376</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Ubiquiti EdgeRouter X up to 2.0.9-hotfix.6. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument dpi leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-227652.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Ubiquiti EdgeRouter X bis 2.0.9-hotfix.6 ausgemacht. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Komponente Web Management Interface. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments dpi mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2376|2024-08-02T06:19:15.146Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 15:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2375|2024-08-02T06:19:15.021Z -- ubiquiti -- edgerouter%20x
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2375</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Ubiquiti EdgeRouter X up to 2.0.9-hotfix.6 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument src leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-227651.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Ubiquiti EdgeRouter X bis 2.0.9-hotfix.6 gefunden. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Komponente Web Management Interface. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments src mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2375|2024-08-02T06:19:15.021Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 15:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2374|2024-08-02T06:19:14.979Z -- ubiquiti -- edgerouter%20x
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2374</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Ubiquiti EdgeRouter X up to 2.0.9-hotfix.6 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument ecn-down leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-227650 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In Ubiquiti EdgeRouter X bis 2.0.9-hotfix.6 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle gefunden. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Komponente Web Management Interface. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments ecn-down mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2374|2024-08-02T06:19:14.979Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 14:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1458|2024-08-02T05:49:11.425Z -- ubiquiti -- edgerouter%20x
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1458</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Ubiquiti EdgeRouter X 2.0.9-hotfix.6 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component OSPF Handler. The manipulation of the argument area leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-223303. NOTE: The vendor position is that post-authentication issues are not accepted as vulnerabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1458|2024-08-02T05:49:11.425Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34786|2024-08-02T02:59:22.620Z -- ubiquiti -- unifi%20ios%20app</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34786</link>
      <description>UniFi iOS app 10.15.0 introduces a misconfiguration on 2nd Generation UniFi Access Points configured as standalone (not using UniFi Network Application) that could cause the SSID name to change and/or the WiFi Password to be removed on the 5GHz Radio.

This vulnerability is fixed in UniFi iOS app 10.15.2 and later.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34786|2024-08-02T02:59:22.620Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 01:07:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37380|2024-07-22T18:38:00.606Z -- ubiquiti -- unifi%20u6%2B%20access%20point</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37380</link>
      <description>A misconfiguration on UniFi U6+ Access Point could cause an incorrect VLAN traffic forwarding to APs meshed to UniFi U6+ Access Point.


Affected Products:
UniFi U6+ Access Point (Version 6.6.65 and earlier) 

 
Mitigation:
Update your UniFi U6+ Access Point to Version 6.6.74 or later.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37380|2024-07-22T18:38:00.606Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 18:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34786|2024-07-09T01:07:28.069Z -- ubiquiti -- unifi%20ios%20app</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34786</link>
      <description>UniFi iOS app 10.15.0 introduces a misconfiguration on 2nd Generation UniFi Access Points configured as standalone (not using UniFi Network Application) that could cause the SSID name to change and/or the WiFi Password to be removed on the 5GHz Radio.

This vulnerability is fixed in UniFi iOS app 10.15.2 and later.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34786|2024-07-09T01:07:28.069Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 01:07:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34786|2024-07-10T21:10:29.883Z -- ubiquiti -- unifi%20ios%20app</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34786</link>
      <description>UniFi iOS app 10.15.0 introduces a misconfiguration on 2nd Generation UniFi Access Points configured as standalone (not using UniFi Network Application) that could cause the SSID name to change and/or the WiFi Password to be removed on the 5GHz Radio.

This vulnerability is fixed in UniFi iOS app 10.15.2 and later.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34786|2024-07-10T21:10:29.883Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 01:07:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37380|2024-07-23T13:34:22.252Z -- ubiquiti -- unifi%20u6%2B%20access%20point</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37380</link>
      <description>A misconfiguration on UniFi U6+ Access Point could cause an incorrect VLAN traffic forwarding to APs meshed to UniFi U6+ Access Point.


Affected Products:
UniFi U6+ Access Point (Version 6.6.65 and earlier) 

 
Mitigation:
Update your UniFi U6+ Access Point to Version 6.6.74 or later.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37380|2024-07-23T13:34:22.252Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 18:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37380|2024-08-02T03:50:56.070Z -- ubiquiti -- unifi%20u6%2B%20access%20point</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37380</link>
      <description>A misconfiguration on UniFi U6+ Access Point could cause an incorrect VLAN traffic forwarding to APs meshed to UniFi U6+ Access Point.


Affected Products:
UniFi U6+ Access Point (Version 6.6.65 and earlier) 

 
Mitigation:
Update your UniFi U6+ Access Point to Version 6.6.74 or later.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37380|2024-08-02T03:50:56.070Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 18:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
