<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Wago -- WAGO e!Cockpit</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/wago/wago%20e%21cockpit.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Wago -- WAGO e!Cockpit</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:23:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5107|2024-08-04T19:47:56.719Z -- wago -- wago%20e%21cockpit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5107</link>
      <description>A cleartext transmission vulnerability exists in the network communication functionality of WAGO e!Cockpit version 1.5.1.1. An attacker with access to network traffic can easily intercept, interpret, and manipulate data coming from, or destined for e!Cockpit. This includes passwords, configurations, and binaries being transferred to endpoints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5107|2024-08-04T19:47:56.719Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 23:41:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5158|2024-08-04T19:47:56.569Z -- wago -- wago%20e%21cockpit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5158</link>
      <description>An exploitable firmware downgrade vulnerability exists in the firmware update package functionality of the WAGO e!COCKPIT automation software v1.6.1.5. A specially crafted firmware update file can allow an attacker to install an older firmware version while the user thinks a newer firmware version is being installed. An attacker can create a custom firmware update package with invalid metadata in order to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5158|2024-08-04T19:47:56.569Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 23:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5159|2024-08-04T19:47:56.607Z -- wago -- wago%20e%21cockpit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5159</link>
      <description>An exploitable improper input validation vulnerability exists in the firmware update functionality of WAGO e!COCKPIT automation software v1.6.0.7. A specially crafted firmware update file can allow an attacker to write arbitrary files to arbitrary locations on WAGO controllers as a part of executing a firmware update, potentially resulting in code execution. An attacker can create a malicious firmware update package file using any zip utility. The user must initiate a firmware update through e!COCKPIT and choose the malicious wup file using the file browser to trigger the vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5159|2024-08-04T19:47:56.607Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 22:35:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5106|2024-08-04T19:47:55.965Z -- wago -- wago%20e%21cockpit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5106</link>
      <description>A hard-coded encryption key vulnerability exists in the authentication functionality of WAGO e!Cockpit version 1.5.1.1. An attacker with access to communications between e!Cockpit and CoDeSyS Gateway can trivially recover the password of any user attempting to log in, in plain text.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5106|2024-08-04T19:47:55.965Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 23:41:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
