<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for SAP_SE -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sap_se/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for SAP_SE -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 22:02:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-28167|2024-04-09T00:55:46.326Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP Group Reporting Data Collection (Enter Package Data)
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-28167</link><description>SAP Group Reporting Data Collection does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. On successful exploitation, specific data can be changed via the Enter Package Data app although the user does not have sufficient authorization causing high impact on Integrity of the appliction.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28167|2024-04-09T00:55:46.326Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:55:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28165|2024-05-14T03:51:20.267Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-28165</link><description>
SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform is vulnerable to stored XSS allowing an attacker to manipulate a parameter in the Opendocument URL which could lead to high impact on Confidentiality and Integrity of the application

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28165|2024-05-14T03:51:20.267Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 03:51:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28163|2024-03-12T00:45:42.419Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP NetWeaver Process Integration (Support Web Pages)
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-28163</link><description>Under certain conditions, Support Web Pages of SAP NetWeaver Process Integration (PI) - versions 7.50, allows an attacker to access information which would otherwise be restricted, causing low impact on Confidentiality with no impact on Integrity and Availability of the application.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28163|2024-03-12T00:45:42.419Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4139|2024-05-14T04:01:51.145Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP S/4 HANA (Manage Bank Statement Reprocessing Rules)
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4139</link><description>Manage Bank Statement ReProcessing Rules does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. By exploiting this vulnerability, an attacker can delete rules of other users affecting the integrity of the application. Confidentiality and Availability are not affected.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4139|2024-05-14T04:01:51.145Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 03:51:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4138|2024-05-14T04:01:25.521Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP S/4 HANA (Manage Bank Statement Reprocessing Rules)
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4138</link><description>Manage Bank Statement ReProcessing Rules does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. By exploiting this vulnerability, an attacker can enable/disable the sharing rule of other users affecting the integrity of the application. Confidentiality and Availability are not affected.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4138|2024-05-14T04:01:25.521Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 03:53:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22130|2024-02-13T02:29:51.706Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP CRM WebClient UI
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22130</link><description>Print preview option in SAP CRM WebClient UI - versions S4FND 102, S4FND 103, S4FND 104, S4FND 105, S4FND 106, S4FND 107, S4FND 108, WEBCUIF 700, WEBCUIF 701, WEBCUIF 730, WEBCUIF 731, WEBCUIF 746, WEBCUIF 747, WEBCUIF 748, WEBCUIF 800, WEBCUIF 801, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability. An attacker with low privileges can cause limited impact to confidentiality and integrity of the appliaction data after successful exploitation.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22130|2024-02-13T02:29:51.706Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:29:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22126|2024-02-13T01:58:27.745Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP NetWeaver AS Java (User Admin Application)
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22126</link><description>The User Admin application of SAP NetWeaver AS for Java - version 7.50, insufficiently validates and improperly encodes the incoming URL parameters before including them into the redirect URL. This results in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability, leading to a high impact on confidentiality and mild impact on integrity and availability.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22126|2024-02-13T01:58:27.745Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 01:58:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22127|2024-03-12T00:29:37.694Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP NetWeaver AS Java (Administrator Log Viewer plug-in)
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22127</link><description>SAP NetWeaver Administrator AS Java (Administrator Log Viewer plug-in) - version 7.50, allows an attacker with high privileges to upload potentially dangerous files which leads to command injection vulnerability. This would enable the attacker to run commands which can cause high impact on confidentiality, integrity and availability of the application.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22127|2024-03-12T00:29:37.694Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:29:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22131|2024-02-13T02:30:51.886Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP ABA (Application Basis)
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22131</link><description>In SAP ABA (Application Basis) - versions 700, 701, 702, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 75C, 75I, an attacker authenticated as a user with a remote execution authorization can use a vulnerable interface. This allows the attacker to use the interface to invoke an application function to perform actions which they would not normally be permitted to perform.  Depending on the function executed, the attack can read or modify any user/business data and can make the entire system unavailable.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22131|2024-02-13T02:30:51.886Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:30:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22124|2024-01-09T01:19:55.940Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP NetWeaver (Internet Communication Manager)
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22124</link><description>Under certain conditions, Internet Communication Manager (ICM) or SAP Web Dispatcher - versions KERNEL 7.22, KERNEL 7.53, KERNEL 7.54, KRNL64UC 7.22, KRNL64UC 7.22EXT, KRNL64UC 7.53, KRNL64NUC 7.22, KRNL64NUC 7.22_EXT, WEBDISP 7.22_EXT, WEBDISP 7.53, WEBDISP 7.54, could allow an attacker to access information which would otherwise be restricted causing high impact on confidentiality.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22124|2024-01-09T01:19:55.940Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 01:19:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22132|2024-02-13T02:33:01.622Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP IDES Systems
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22132</link><description>SAP IDES ECC-systems contain code that permits the execution of arbitrary program code of user's choice.An attacker can therefore control the behaviour of the system by executing malicious code which can potentially escalate privileges with low impact on confidentiality, integrity and availability of the system.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22132|2024-02-13T02:33:01.622Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:33:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22128|2024-02-13T02:02:14.281Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP NetWeaver Business Client for HTML
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22128</link><description>SAP NWBC for HTML - versions SAP_UI 754, SAP_UI 755, SAP_UI 756, SAP_UI 757, SAP_UI 758, SAP_BASIS 700, SAP_BASIS 701, SAP_BASIS 702, SAP_BASIS 731, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker can inject malicious javascript to cause limited impact to confidentiality and integrity of the application data after successful exploitation.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22128|2024-02-13T02:02:14.281Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:02:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22129|2024-02-13T03:40:54.670Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP Companion
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22129</link><description>SAP Companion - version &lt;3.1.38, has a URL with parameter that could be vulnerable to XSS attack. The attacker could send a malicious link to a user that would possibly allow an attacker to retrieve the sensitive information and cause minor impact on the integrity of the web application.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22129|2024-02-13T03:40:54.670Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 03:40:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22133|2024-03-12T00:32:50.856Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP Fiori Front End Server
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22133</link><description>SAP Fiori Front End Server - version 605, allows altering of approver details on the read-only field when sending leave request information. This could lead to creation of request with incorrect approver causing low impact on Confidentiality and Integrity with no impact on Availability of the application.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22133|2024-03-12T00:32:50.856Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:32:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22125|2024-01-09T01:20:19.403Z -- SAP_SE -- Microsoft Edge browser extension (SAP GUI connector for Microsoft Edge)
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22125</link><description>Under certain conditions the Microsoft Edge browser extension (SAP GUI connector for Microsoft Edge) - version 1.0, allows an attacker to access highly sensitive information which would otherwise be restricted causing high impact on confidentiality.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22125|2024-01-09T01:20:19.403Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 01:20:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32730|2024-04-26T16:06:39.373Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP Enable Now
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-32730</link><description>SAP Enable Now Manager does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. On successful exploitation, the attacker with the role 'Learner' could gain access to other user's data in manager which will lead to a high impact to the confidentiality of the application.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32730|2024-04-26T16:06:39.373Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 16:06:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32731|2024-05-14T03:38:59.839Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP My Travel Requests 
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-32731</link><description>
SAP My Travel Requests does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. On successful exploitation, the attacker can upload a malicious attachment to a business trip request which will lead to a low impact on the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the application. 

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32731|2024-05-14T03:38:59.839Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 03:07:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32733|2024-05-14T03:38:19.474Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP NetWeaver Application Server ABAP and ABAP Platform 
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-32733</link><description>
Due to missing input validation and output encoding of untrusted data, SAP NetWeaver Application Server ABAP and ABAP Platform allows an unauthenticated attacker to inject malicious JavaScript code into the dynamically crafted web page. On successful exploitation the attacker can access or modify sensitive information with no impact on availability of the application

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32733|2024-05-14T03:38:19.474Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 03:38:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27902|2024-03-12T00:45:08.794Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP NetWeaver AS ABAP applications based on SAPGUI for HTML (WebGUI)
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27902</link><description>Applications based on SAP GUI for HTML in SAP NetWeaver AS ABAP - versions 7.89, 7.93, do not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. A successful attack can allow a malicious attacker to access and modify data through their ability to execute code in a user’s browser. There is no impact on the availability of the system

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27902|2024-03-12T00:45:08.794Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:45:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27898|2024-04-09T00:52:54.390Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP NetWeaver
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27898</link><description>SAP NetWeaver application, due to insufficient input validation, allows an attacker to send a crafted request from a vulnerable web application targeting internal systems behind firewalls that are normally inaccessible to an attacker from the external network, resulting in a Server-Side Request Forgery vulnerability. Thus, having a low impact on confidentiality.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27898|2024-04-09T00:52:54.390Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:52:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27899|2024-04-09T00:54:17.167Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP NetWeaver AS Java User Management Engine
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27899</link><description>Self-Registration and Modify your own profile in User Admin Application of NetWeaver AS Java does not enforce proper security requirements for the content of the newly defined security answer. This can be leveraged by an attacker to cause profound impact on confidentiality and low impact on both integrity and availability.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27899|2024-04-09T00:54:17.167Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:54:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27900|2024-03-12T00:44:15.235Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP ABAP Platform
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27900</link><description>Due to missing authorization check, attacker with business user account in SAP ABAP Platform - version 758, 795, can change the privacy setting of job templates from shared to private. As a result, the selected template would only be accessible to the owner.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27900|2024-03-12T00:44:15.235Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:44:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27901|2024-04-09T00:55:03.642Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP Asset Accounting
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27901</link><description>SAP Asset Accounting could allow a high privileged attacker to exploit insufficient validation of path information provided by the users and pass it through to the file API's. Thus, causing a considerable impact on confidentiality, integrity and availability of the application.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27901|2024-04-09T00:55:03.642Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:55:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33002|2024-05-14T04:02:24.237Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP S/4HANA (Document Service Handler for DPS)
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-33002</link><description>Document Service handler (obsolete) in Data Provisioning Service does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability with low impact on Confidentiality and Integrity of the application.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33002|2024-05-14T04:02:24.237Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 03:49:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33009|2024-05-14T03:58:53.953Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP Global Label Management (GLM)
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-33009</link><description>SAP Global Label Management is vulnerable to SQL injection. On exploitation the attacker can use specially crafted inputs to modify database commands resulting in the retrieval of additional information persisted by the system. This could lead to low impact on Confidentiality and Integrity of the application.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33009|2024-05-14T03:58:53.953Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 03:58:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33008|2024-05-14T03:46:17.394Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP Replication Server 
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-33008</link><description>
SAP Replication Server allows an attacker to use gateway for executing some commands to RSSD. This could result in crashing the Replication Server due to memory corruption with high impact on Availability of the system.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33008|2024-05-14T03:46:17.394Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 03:46:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33004|2024-05-14T04:00:25.081Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Webservices)
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-33004</link><description>SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform is vulnerable to Insecure Storage as dynamic web pages are getting cached even after logging out. On successful exploitation, the attacker can see the sensitive information through cache and can open the pages causing limited impact on Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability of the application.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33004|2024-05-14T04:00:25.081Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 04:00:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33007|2024-05-14T04:03:03.929Z -- SAP_SE -- SAPUI5 (PDFViewer)
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-33007</link><description>PDFViewer is a control delivered as part of SAPUI5 product which shows the PDF content in an embedded mode by default. If a PDF document contains embedded JavaScript (or any harmful client-side script), the PDFViewer will execute the JavaScript embedded in the PDF which can cause a potential security threat.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33007|2024-05-14T04:03:03.929Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 03:44:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33006|2024-05-14T04:16:06.647Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP NetWeaver Application Server ABAP and ABAP Platform
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-33006</link><description>
An unauthenticated attacker can upload a malicious file to the server which when accessed by a victim can allow an attacker to completely compromise system. 

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33006|2024-05-14T04:16:06.647Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 04:16:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33000|2024-05-14T04:02:46.636Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP Bank Account Management
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-33000</link><description>SAP Bank Account Management does not perform necessary authorization check for an authorized user, resulting in escalation of privileges. As a result, it has a low impact to confidentiality to the system.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33000|2024-05-14T04:02:46.636Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 03:46:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24742|2024-02-13T02:42:56.483Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP CRM (WebClient UI)
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-24742</link><description>SAP CRM WebClient UI - version S4FND 102, S4FND 103, S4FND 104, S4FND 105, S4FND 106, WEBCUIF 701, WEBCUIF 731, WEBCUIF 746, WEBCUIF 747, WEBCUIF 748, WEBCUIF 800, WEBCUIF 801, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. An attacker with low privileges can cause limited impact to integrity of the application data after successful exploitation. There is no impact on confidentiality and availability.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24742|2024-02-13T02:42:56.483Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:42:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24739|2024-02-13T02:34:17.247Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP BAM (Bank Account Management)
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-24739</link><description>SAP Bank Account Management (BAM) allows an authenticated user with restricted access to use functions which can result in escalation of privileges with low impact on confidentiality, integrity and availability of the application.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24739|2024-02-13T02:34:17.247Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:34:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24743|2024-02-13T02:43:40.755Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP NetWeaver AS Java (Guided Procedures)
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-24743</link><description>SAP NetWeaver AS Java (CAF - Guided Procedures) - version 7.50, allows an unauthenticated attacker to submit a malicious request with a crafted XML file over the network, which when parsed will enable him to access sensitive files and data but not modify them. There are expansion limits in place so that availability is not affected.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24743|2024-02-13T02:43:40.755Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:43:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24740|2024-02-13T02:35:21.224Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP NetWeaver Application Server ABAP (SAP Kernel)
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-24740</link><description>SAP NetWeaver Application Server (ABAP) - versions KERNEL 7.53, KERNEL 7.54, KERNEL 7.77, KERNEL 7.85, KERNEL 7.89, KERNEL 7.93, KERNEL 7.94, KRNL64UC 7.53, under certain conditions, allows an attacker to access information which could otherwise be restricted with low impact on confidentiality of the application.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24740|2024-02-13T02:35:21.224Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:35:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24741|2024-02-13T03:43:14.238Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP Master Data Governance Material
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-24741</link><description>SAP Master Data Governance for Material Data - versions 618, 619, 620, 621, 622, 800, 801, 802, 803, 804, does not perform necessary authorization check for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. This could allow an attacker to read some sensitive information but no impact to integrity and availability.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24741|2024-02-13T03:43:14.238Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 03:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34687|2024-05-14T03:56:24.324Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP NetWeaver Application server for ABAP and ABAP Platform
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-34687</link><description>SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP and ABAP Platform do not sufficiently encode user controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.
An attacker can control code that is executed within a user’s browser, which could result in modification, deletion of data, including accessing or deleting files, or stealing session cookies which an attacker could use to hijack a user’s session. Hence, this could have impact on Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability of the system.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34687|2024-05-14T03:56:24.324Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 03:56:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30214|2024-04-09T00:56:29.336Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP Business Connector
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30214</link><description>The application allows a high privilege attacker to append a malicious GET query parameter to Service invocations, which are reflected in the server response. Under certain circumstances, if the parameter contains a JavaScript, the script could be processed on client side.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30214|2024-04-09T00:56:29.336Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:56:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30218|2024-04-09T01:04:40.206Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP NetWeaver AS ABAP and ABAP Platform
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30218</link><description>The ABAP Application Server of SAP NetWeaver as well as ABAP Platform allows an attacker to prevent legitimate users from accessing a service, either by crashing or flooding the service. This leads to a considerable impact on availability.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30218|2024-04-09T01:04:40.206Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 01:04:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30215|2024-04-09T00:56:59.180Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP Business Connector
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30215</link><description>The Resource Settings page allows a high privilege attacker to load exploitable payload to be stored and reflected whenever a User visits the page. In a successful attack, some information could be obtained and/or modified. However, the attacker does not have control over what information is obtained, or the amount or kind of loss is limited.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30215|2024-04-09T00:56:59.180Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:56:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30216|2024-04-09T01:02:41.597Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP S/4 HANA (Cash Management)
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30216</link><description>Cash Management in SAP S/4 HANA does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. By exploiting this vulnerability, attacker can add notes in the review request with 'completed' status affecting the integrity of the application. Confidentiality and Availability are not impacted.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30216|2024-04-09T01:02:41.597Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 01:02:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30217|2024-04-09T01:03:20.926Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP S/4 HANA (Cash Management)
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30217</link><description>Cash Management in SAP S/4 HANA does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. By exploiting this vulnerability, an attacker can approve or reject a bank account application affecting the integrity of the application. Confidentiality and Availability are not impacted.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30217|2024-04-09T01:03:20.926Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 01:03:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21736|2024-01-09T01:15:17.763Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP S/4HANA Finance (Advanced Payment Management)
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21736</link><description>SAP S/4HANA Finance for (Advanced Payment Management) - versions SAPSCORE 128, S4CORE 107, does not perform necessary authorization checks. A function import could be triggered allowing the attacker to create in-house bank accounts leading to low impact on the confidentiality of the application.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21736|2024-01-09T01:15:17.763Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 01:15:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21737|2024-01-09T01:18:19.305Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP Application Interface Framework (File Adapter)
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21737</link><description>In SAP Application Interface Framework File Adapter - version 702, a high privilege user can use a function module to traverse through various layers and execute OS commands directly. By this, such user can control the behaviour of the application. This leads to considerable impact on confidentiality, integrity and availability.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21737|2024-01-09T01:18:19.305Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 01:18:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21738|2024-01-09T01:19:29.437Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP NetWeaver ABAP Application Server and ABAP Platform
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21738</link><description>SAP NetWeaver ABAP Application Server and ABAP Platform do not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. An attacker with low privileges can cause limited impact to confidentiality of the application data after successful exploitation.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21738|2024-01-09T01:19:29.437Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 01:19:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21734|2024-01-09T00:54:47.844Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP Marketing (Contacts App)
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21734</link><description>SAP Marketing (Contacts App) - version 160, allows an attacker with low privileges to trick a user to open malicious page which could lead to a very convincing phishing attack with low impact on confidentiality and integrity of the application.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21734|2024-01-09T00:54:47.844Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 00:54:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21735|2024-01-30T21:23:44.935Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP LT Replication Server
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21735</link><description>SAP LT Replication Server - version S4CORE 103, S4CORE 104, S4CORE 105, S4CORE 106, S4CORE 107, S4CORE 108, does not perform necessary authorization checks. This could allow an attacker with high privileges to perform unintended actions, resulting in escalation of privileges, which has High impact on confidentiality, integrity and availability of the system.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21735|2024-01-30T21:23:44.935Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 00:57:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25646|2024-04-09T00:47:43.364Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP BusinessObjects Web Intelligence
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25646</link><description>Due to improper validation, SAP BusinessObject Business Intelligence Launch Pad allows an authenticated attacker to access operating system information using crafted document. On successful exploitation there could be a considerable impact on confidentiality of the application.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25646|2024-04-09T00:47:43.364Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:47:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25645|2024-03-12T00:53:58.649Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP NetWeaver (Enterprise Portal)
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25645</link><description>Under certain condition SAP NetWeaver (Enterprise Portal) - version 7.50 allows an attacker to access information which would otherwise be restricted causing low impact on confidentiality of the application and with no impact on Integrity and Availability of the application.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25645|2024-03-12T00:53:58.649Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:53:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25644|2024-03-12T00:33:44.473Z -- SAP_SE -- NetWeaver (WSRM)
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25644</link><description>Under certain conditions SAP NetWeaver WSRM - version 7.50, allows an attacker to access information which would otherwise be restricted, causing low impact on Confidentiality with no impact on Integrity and Availability of the application.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25644|2024-03-12T00:33:44.473Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:33:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25643|2024-02-13T03:37:14.954Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP Fiori app (My Overtime Requests)
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25643</link><description>The SAP Fiori app (My Overtime Request) - version 605, does not perform the necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user which may result in an escalation of privileges. It is possible to manipulate the URLs of data requests to access information that the user should not have access to. There is no impact on integrity and availability.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25643|2024-02-13T03:37:14.954Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 03:37:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25642|2024-02-13T03:19:07.733Z -- SAP_SE -- SAP Cloud Connector
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25642</link><description>Due to improper validation of certificate in SAP Cloud Connector - version 2.0, attacker can impersonate the genuine servers to interact with SCC breaking the mutual authentication. Hence, the attacker can intercept the request to view/modify sensitive information. There is no impact on the availability of the system.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25642|2024-02-13T03:19:07.733Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:44:20 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>