<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SAP_SE -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sap_se/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SAP_SE -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 18:24:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-36924|2024-08-02T17:01:10.031Z -- sap_se -- sap%20erp%20defense%20forces%20and%20public%20security
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36924</link>
      <description>While using a specific function, SAP ERP Defense Forces and Public Security - versions 600, 603, 604, 605, 616, 617, 618, 802, 803, 804, 805, 806, 807, allows an authenticated attacker with admin privileges to write arbitrary data to the syslog file. On successful exploitation, an attacker could modify all the syslog data causing a complete compromise of integrity of the application.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-36924|2024-08-02T17:01:10.031Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 02:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37484|2024-08-02T17:16:30.284Z -- sap_se -- sap%20powerdesigner
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37484</link>
      <description>SAP PowerDesigner - version 16.7, queries all password hashes in the backend database and compares it with the user provided one during login attempt, which might allow an attacker to access password hashes from the client's memory.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37484|2024-08-02T17:16:30.284Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-36925|2024-08-02T17:01:10.054Z -- sap_se -- sap%20solution%20manager%20%28diagnostics%20agent%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36925</link>
      <description>SAP Solution Manager (Diagnostics agent) - version 7.20, allows an unauthenticated attacker to blindly execute HTTP requests. On successful exploitation, the attacker can cause a limited impact on confidentiality and availability of the application and other applications the Diagnostics Agent can reach.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-36925|2024-08-02T17:01:10.054Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 02:57:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32111|2024-08-02T15:03:29.106Z -- sap_se -- sap%20powerdesigner%20%28proxy%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32111</link>
      <description>In SAP PowerDesigner (Proxy) - version 16.7, an attacker can send a crafted request from a remote host to the proxy machine and crash the proxy server, due to faulty implementation of memory management causing a memory corruption. This leads to a high impact on availability of the application.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32111|2024-08-02T15:03:29.106Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 01:38:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37489|2024-08-02T17:16:30.312Z -- sap_se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28version%20management%20system%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37489</link>
      <description>Due to the lack of validation, SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Version Management System) - version 403, permits an unauthenticated user to read the code snippet through the UI, which leads to low impact on confidentiality and no impact on the application's availability or integrity.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37489|2024-08-02T17:16:30.312Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 00:55:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28764|2024-08-02T13:51:37.075Z -- sap_se -- sap%20businessobjects%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28764</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Platform - versions 420, 430, Information design tool transmits sensitive information as cleartext in the binaries over the network. This could allow an unauthenticated attacker with deep knowledge to gain sensitive information such as user credentials and domain names, which may have a low impact on confidentiality and no impact on the integrity and availability of the system.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28764|2024-08-02T13:51:37.075Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 00:55:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0019|2024-08-02T04:54:32.570Z -- sap_se -- sap%20grc%20%28process%20control%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0019</link>
      <description>In SAP GRC (Process Control) - versions GRCFND_A V1200, GRCFND_A V8100, GRCPINW V1100_700, GRCPINW V1100_731, GRCPINW V1200_750, remote-enabled function module in the proprietary SAP solution enables an authenticated attacker with minimal privileges to access all the confidential data stored in the database. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability can expose user credentials from client-specific tables of the database, leading to high impact on confidentiality.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0019|2024-08-02T04:54:32.570Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:06:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-30741|2024-08-02T14:37:15.013Z -- sap_se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30741</link>
      <description>Due to insufficient input validation, SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform - versions 420, 430, allows an unauthenticated attacker to redirect users to untrusted site using a malicious link. On successful exploitation, an attacker can view or modify information causing a limited impact on confidentiality and integrity of the application.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-30741|2024-08-02T14:37:15.013Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 01:34:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31403|2024-08-02T14:53:30.887Z -- sap_se -- sap%20business%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31403</link>
      <description>SAP Business One installation - version 10.0, does not perform proper authentication and authorization checks for SMB shared folder. As a result, any malicious user can read and write to the SMB shared folder. Additionally, the files in the folder can be executed or be used by the installation process leading to considerable impact on confidentiality, integrity and availability.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31403|2024-08-02T14:53:30.887Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:59:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37491|2024-08-02T17:16:30.741Z -- sap_se -- sap%20message%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37491</link>
      <description>The ACL (Access Control List) of SAP Message Server - versions KERNEL 7.22, KERNEL 7.53, KERNEL 7.54, KERNEL 7.77, RNL64UC 7.22, RNL64UC 7.22EXT, RNL64UC 7.53, KRNL64NUC 7.22, KRNL64NUC 7.22EXT, can be bypassed in certain conditions, which may enable an authenticated malicious user to enter the network of the SAP systems served by the attacked SAP Message server. This may lead to unauthorized read and write of data as well as rendering the system unavailable.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37491|2024-08-02T17:16:30.741Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:46:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37488|2024-08-02T17:16:30.183Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20process%20integration
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37488</link>
      <description>In SAP NetWeaver Process Integration - versions SAP_XIESR 7.50, SAP_XITOOL 7.50, SAP_XIAF 7.50, user-controlled inputs, if not sufficiently encoded, could result in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attack. On successful exploitation the attacker can cause limited impact on confidentiality and integrity of the system.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37488|2024-08-02T17:16:30.183Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:43:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32112|2024-08-02T15:03:28.988Z -- sap_se -- vendor%20master%20hierarchy
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32112</link>
      <description>Vendor Master Hierarchy - versions SAP_APPL 500, SAP_APPL 600, SAP_APPL 602, SAP_APPL 603, SAP_APPL 604, SAP_APPL 605, SAP_APPL 606, SAP_APPL 616, SAP_APPL 617, SAP_APPL 618, S4CORE 100, does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user to access some of its function. This could lead to modification of data impacting the integrity of the system.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32112|2024-08-02T15:03:28.988Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 01:42:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-30743|2024-08-02T14:37:15.433Z -- sap_se -- sapui5
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30743</link>
      <description>Due to improper neutralization of input in SAPUI5 - versions SAP_UI 750, SAP_UI 754, SAP_UI 755, SAP_UI 756, SAP_UI 757, UI_700 200, sap.m.FormattedText SAPUI5 control allows injection of untrusted CSS. This blocks user’s interaction with the application. Further, in the absence of URL validation by the application, the vulnerability could lead to the attacker reading or modifying user’s information through phishing attack.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-30743|2024-08-02T14:37:15.433Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 01:35:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-36926|2024-08-02T17:01:10.044Z -- sap_se -- sap%20host%20agent
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36926</link>
      <description>Due to missing authentication check in SAP Host Agent - version 7.22, an unauthenticated attacker can set an undocumented parameter to a particular compatibility value and in turn call read functions. This allows the attacker to gather some non-sensitive information about the server.  There is no impact on integrity or availability.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-36926|2024-08-02T17:01:10.044Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:38:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35874|2024-08-02T16:30:45.380Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35874</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver Application Server ABAP and ABAP Platform - version KRNL64NUC, 7.22, KRNL64NUC 7.22EXT, KRNL64UC 7.22, KRNL64UC 7.22EXT, KRNL64UC 7.53, KERNEL 7.22, KERNEL, 7.53, KERNEL 7.77, KERNEL 7.81, KERNEL 7.85, KERNEL 7.89, KERNEL 7.54, KERNEL 7.92, KERNEL 7.93, under some conditions, performs improper authentication checks for functionalities that require user identity. An attacker can perform malicious actions over the network, extending the scope of impact, causing a limited impact on confidentiality, integrity and availability.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35874|2024-08-02T16:30:45.380Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 02:47:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29188|2024-08-02T14:00:15.860Z -- sap_se -- sap%20crm%20webclient%20ui
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29188</link>
      <description>SAP CRM WebClient UI - versions SAPSCORE 129, S4FND 102, S4FND 103, S4FND 104, S4FND 105, S4FND 106, S4FND 107, WEBCUIF 701, WEBCUIF 731, WEBCUIF 746, WEBCUIF 747, WEBCUIF 748, WEBCUIF 800, WEBCUIF 801, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. After successful exploitation, an attacker with user level access can read and modify some sensitive information but cannot delete the data.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29188|2024-08-02T14:00:15.860Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 00:57:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-23858|2024-08-02T10:42:27.147Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20for%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23858</link>
      <description>Due to insufficient input validation, SAP NetWeaver AS for ABAP and ABAP Platform - versions 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, 755, 756, 757, 789, 790, allows an unauthenticated attacker to send a crafted URL to a user, and by clicking the URL, the tricked user accesses SAP and might be directed with the response to somewhere out-side SAP and enter sensitive data. This could cause a limited impact on confidentiality and integrity of the application.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-23858|2024-08-02T10:42:27.147Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33992|2024-08-02T15:54:14.204Z -- sap_se -- sap%20business%20warehouse%20and%20sap%20bw%2F4hana
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33992</link>
      <description>The SAP BW BICS communication layer in SAP Business Warehouse and SAP BW/4HANA - version SAP_BW 730, SAP_BW 731, SAP_BW 740, SAP_BW 730, SAP_BW 750, DW4CORE 100, DW4CORE 200, DW4CORE 300, may expose unauthorized cell values to the data response. To be able to exploit this, the user still needs authorizations on the query as well as on the keyfigure/measure level. The missing check only affects the data level.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33992|2024-08-02T15:54:14.204Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 02:34:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37487|2024-08-02T17:16:29.971Z -- sap_se -- sap%20business%20one%20%28service%20layer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37487</link>
      <description>SAP Business One (Service Layer) - version 10.0, allows an authenticated attacker with deep knowledge perform certain operation to access unintended data over the network which could lead to high impact on confidentiality with no impact on integrity and availability of the application

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37487|2024-08-02T17:16:29.971Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:42:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-30740|2024-08-02T14:37:15.377Z -- sap_se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30740</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform - versions 420, 430, allows an authenticated attacker to access sensitive information which is otherwise restricted. On successful exploitation, there could be a high impact on confidentiality, limited impact on integrity and availability of the application.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-30740|2024-08-02T14:37:15.377Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 01:34:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32114|2024-08-02T15:03:29.114Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20%28change%20and%20transport%20system%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32114</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver (Change and Transport System) - versions 702, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 753, 754, 755, 756, 757, allows an authenticated user with admin privileges to maliciously run a benchmark program repeatedly in intent to slowdown or make the server unavailable which may lead to a limited impact on Availability with No impact on Confidentiality and Integrity of the application.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32114|2024-08-02T15:03:29.114Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 02:38:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33985|2024-08-02T15:54:14.116Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20enterprise%20portal
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33985</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver Enterprise Portal - version 7.50, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs over the network, resulting in reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability, therefore changing the scope of the attack. On successful exploitation, an attacker can view or modify information causing a limited impact on confidentiality and integrity of the application.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33985|2024-08-02T15:54:14.116Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 02:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0020|2024-08-02T04:54:32.627Z -- sap_se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0020</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence platform - versions 420, 430, allows an authenticated attacker to access sensitive information which is otherwise restricted. On successful exploitation, there could be a high impact on confidentiality and limited impact on integrity of the application.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0020|2024-08-02T04:54:32.627Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:08:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37490|2024-08-02T17:16:30.325Z -- sap_se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20%28installer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37490</link>
      <description>SAP Business Objects Installer - versions 420, 430, allows an authenticated attacker within the network to overwrite an executable file created in a temporary directory during the installation process. On replacing this executable with a malicious file, an attacker can completely compromise the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the system

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37490|2024-08-02T17:16:30.325Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:46:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37492|2024-08-02T17:16:30.352Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37492</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver Application Server ABAP and ABAP Platform - versions SAP_BASIS 700, SAP_BASIS 701, SAP_BASIS 702, SAP_BASIS 731, SAP_BASIS 740, SAP_BASIS 750, SAP_BASIS 752, SAP_BASIS 753, SAP_BASIS 754, SAP_BASIS 755, SAP_BASIS 756, SAP_BASIS 757, SAP_BASIS 758, SAP_BASIS 793, SAP_BASIS 804, does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. This could allow an attacker to read sensitive information which can be used in a subsequent serious attack.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37492|2024-08-02T17:16:30.352Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:47:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32115|2024-08-02T15:03:29.236Z -- sap_se -- master%20data%20synchronization%20%28mds%20compare%20tool%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32115</link>
      <description>An attacker can exploit MDS COMPARE TOOL and use specially crafted inputs to read and modify database commands, resulting in the retrieval of additional information persisted by the system.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32115|2024-08-02T15:03:29.236Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 02:42:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31406|2024-08-02T14:53:30.643Z -- sap_se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31406</link>
      <description>Due to insufficient input validation, SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform - versions 420, 430, allows an unauthenticated attacker to redirect users to untrusted site using a malicious link. On successful exploitation, an attacker can view or modify information causing a limited impact on confidentiality and integrity of the application.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31406|2024-08-02T14:53:30.643Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 01:37:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-36923|2024-08-02T17:01:10.143Z -- sap_se -- sap%20powerdesigner
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36923</link>
      <description>SAP SQLA for PowerDesigner 17 bundled with SAP PowerDesigner 16.7 SP06 PL03, allows an attacker with local access to the system, to place a malicious library, that can be executed by the application. An attacker could thereby control the behavior of the application.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-36923|2024-08-02T17:01:10.143Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:36:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0021|2024-08-02T04:54:32.586Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0021</link>
      <description>Due to insufficient encoding of user input, SAP NetWeaver - versions 700, 701, 702, 731, 740, 750, allows an unauthenticated attacker to inject code that may expose sensitive data like user ID and password, which could lead to reflected Cross-Site scripting. These endpoints are normally exposed over the network and successful exploitation can partially impact confidentiality of the application.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0021|2024-08-02T04:54:32.586Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 04:34:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27499|2024-08-02T12:16:35.477Z -- sap_se -- gui%20for%20html
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27499</link>
      <description>SAP GUI for HTML - versions KERNEL 7.22, 7.53, 7.54, 7.77, 7.81, 7.85, 7.89, 7.91, KRNL64UC, 7.22, 7.22EXT, KRNL64UC 7.22, 7.22EXT does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in a reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. An attacker could craft a malicious URL and lure the victim to click, the script supplied by the attacker will execute in the victim user's browser. The information from the victim's web browser can either be modified or read and sent to the attacker.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27499|2024-08-02T12:16:35.477Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 02:48:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-30742|2024-08-02T14:37:15.409Z -- sap_se -- sap%20crm%20%28webclient%20ui%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30742</link>
      <description>SAP CRM (WebClient UI) - versions S4FND 102, S4FND 103, S4FND 104, S4FND 105, S4FND 106, S4FND 107, WEBCUIF 700, WEBCUIF 701, WEBCUIF 731, WEBCUIF 746, WEBCUIF 747, WEBCUIF 748, WEBCUIF 800, WEBCUIF 801, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.An attacker could store a malicious URL and lure the victim to click, causing the script supplied by the attacker to execute in the victim user's session. The information from the victim's session could then be modified or read by the attacker.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-30742|2024-08-02T14:37:15.409Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 01:35:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33988|2024-08-02T15:54:14.157Z -- sap_se -- sap%20enable%20now
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33988</link>
      <description>In SAP Enable Now - versions WPB_MANAGER 1.0, WPB_MANAGER_CE 10, WPB_MANAGER_HANA 10, ENABLE_NOW_CONSUMP_DEL 1704, the Content-Security-Policy and X-XSS-Protection response headers are not implemented, allowing an unauthenticated attacker to attempt reflected cross-site scripting, which could result in disclosure or modification of information.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33988|2024-08-02T15:54:14.157Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 02:26:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37486|2024-08-02T17:16:29.972Z -- sap_se -- sap%20commerce%20%28occ%20api%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37486</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions SAP Commerce (OCC API) - versions HY_COM 2105, HY_COM 2205, COM_CLOUD 2211, endpoints allow an attacker to access information which would otherwise be restricted. On successful exploitation there could be a high impact on confidentiality with no impact on integrity and availability of the application.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37486|2024-08-02T17:16:29.972Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:56:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-36918|2024-08-02T17:01:10.053Z -- sap_se -- sap%20enable%20now
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36918</link>
      <description>In SAP Enable Now - versions WPB_MANAGER 1.0, WPB_MANAGER_CE 10, WPB_MANAGER_HANA 10, ENABLE_NOW_CONSUMP_DEL 1704, the X-Content-Type-Options response header is not implemented, allowing an unauthenticated attacker to trigger MIME type sniffing, which leads to Cross-Site Scripting, which could result in disclosure or modification of information.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-36918|2024-08-02T17:01:10.053Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 02:49:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33990|2024-08-02T15:54:14.178Z -- sap_se -- sap%20sql%20anywhere
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33990</link>
      <description>SAP SQL Anywhere - version 17.0, allows an attacker to prevent legitimate users from accessing the service by crashing the service. An attacker with low privileged account and access to the local system can write into the shared memory objects. This can be leveraged by an attacker to perform a Denial of Service. Further, an attacker might be able to modify sensitive data in shared memory objects.This issue only affects SAP SQL Anywhere on Windows. Other platforms are not impacted.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33990|2024-08-02T15:54:14.178Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 02:29:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-30744|2024-08-02T14:37:15.325Z -- sap_se -- sap%20as%20netweaver%20java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30744</link>
      <description>In SAP AS NetWeaver JAVA - versions SERVERCORE 7.50, J2EE-FRMW 7.50, CORE-TOOLS 7.50, an unauthenticated attacker can attach to an open interface and make use of an open naming and directory API to instantiate an object which has methods which can be called without further authorization and authentication.  A subsequent call to one of these methods can read or change the state of existing services without any effect on availability.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-30744|2024-08-02T14:37:15.325Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 01:36:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33984|2024-08-02T15:54:14.117Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20%28design%20time%20repository%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33984</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver (Design Time Repository) - version 7.50, returns an unfavorable content type for some versioned files, which could allow an authorized attacker to create a file with a malicious content and send a link to a victim in an email or instant message. Under certain circumstances, this could lead to Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33984|2024-08-02T15:54:14.117Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 02:44:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-23856|2024-08-02T10:42:26.673Z -- sap_se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20%28web%20intelligence%20ui%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23856</link>
      <description>In SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence (Web Intelligence user interface) - version 430, some calls return json with wrong content type in the header of the response. As a result, a custom application that calls directly the jsp of Web Intelligence DHTML may be vulnerable to XSS attacks. On successful exploitation an attacker can cause a low impact on integrity of the application.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-23856|2024-08-02T10:42:26.673Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35871|2024-08-02T16:30:45.378Z -- sap_se -- sap%20web%20dispatcher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35871</link>
      <description>The SAP Web Dispatcher - versions WEBDISP 7.53, WEBDISP 7.54, WEBDISP 7.77, WEBDISP 7.85, WEBDISP 7.89, WEBDISP 7.91, WEBDISP 7.92, WEBDISP 7.93, KERNEL 7.53, KERNEL 7.54 KERNEL 7.77, KERNEL 7.85, KERNEL 7.89, KERNEL 7.91, KERNEL 7.92, KERNEL 7.93, KRNL64UC 7.53, HDB 2.00, XS_ADVANCED_RUNTIME 1.00, SAP_EXTENDED_APP_SERVICES 1, has a vulnerability that can be exploited by an unauthenticated attacker to cause memory corruption through logical errors in memory management this may leads to information disclosure or system crashes, which can have low impact on confidentiality and high impact on the integrity and availability of the system.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35871|2024-08-02T16:30:45.378Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 02:41:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33987|2024-08-02T15:54:14.177Z -- sap_se -- sap%20web%20dispatcher
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33987</link>
      <description>An unauthenticated attacker in SAP Web Dispatcher - versions WEBDISP 7.49, WEBDISP 7.53, WEBDISP 7.54, WEBDISP 7.77, WEBDISP 7.81, WEBDISP 7.85, WEBDISP 7.88, WEBDISP 7.89, WEBDISP 7.90, KERNEL 7.49, KERNEL 7.53, KERNEL 7.54 KERNEL 7.77, KERNEL 7.81, KERNEL 7.85, KERNEL 7.88, KERNEL 7.89, KERNEL 7.90, KRNL64NUC 7.49, KRNL64UC 7.49, KRNL64UC 7.53, HDB 2.00, XS_ADVANCED_RUNTIME 1.00, SAP_EXTENDED_APP_SERVICES 1, can submit a malicious crafted request over a network to a front-end server which may, over several attempts, result in a back-end server confusing the boundaries of malicious and legitimate messages. This can result in the back-end server executing a malicious payload which can be used to read or modify information on the server or make it temporarily unavailable.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33987|2024-08-02T15:54:14.177Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 02:24:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33986|2024-08-02T15:54:14.200Z -- sap_se -- sap%20crm%20abap%20%28grantor%20management%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33986</link>
      <description>SAP CRM ABAP (Grantor Management) - versions 700, 701, 702, 712, 713, 714, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. After successful exploitation, an attacker can cause limited impact on confidentiality and integrity of the application.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33986|2024-08-02T15:54:14.200Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 02:45:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35872|2024-08-02T16:30:45.398Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20process%20integration%20%28message%20display%20tool%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35872</link>
      <description>The Message Display Tool (MDT) of SAP NetWeaver Process Integration - version SAP_XIAF 7.50, does not perform authentication checks for certain functionalities that require user identity. An unauthenticated user might access technical data about the product status and its configuration. The vulnerability does not allow access to sensitive information or administrative functionalities. On successful exploitation an attacker can cause limited impact on confidentiality and availability of the application.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35872|2024-08-02T16:30:45.398Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 02:41:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33993|2024-08-02T15:54:14.328Z -- sap_se -- sap%20business%20one%20%28b1i%20layer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33993</link>
      <description>B1i module of SAP Business One - version 10.0, application allows an authenticated user with deep knowledge to send crafted queries over the network to read or modify the SQL data. On successful exploitation, the attacker can cause high impact on confidentiality, integrity and availability of the application.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33993|2024-08-02T15:54:14.328Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:35:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32113|2024-08-02T15:03:28.857Z -- sap_se -- sap%20gui%20for%20windows
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32113</link>
      <description>SAP GUI for Windows - version 7.70, 8.0, allows an unauthorized attacker to gain NTLM authentication information of a victim by tricking it into clicking a prepared shortcut file. Depending on the authorizations of the victim, the attacker can read and modify potentially sensitive information after successful exploitation.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32113|2024-08-02T15:03:28.857Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 01:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35870|2024-08-02T16:30:45.390Z -- sap_se -- sap%20s%2F4hana%20%28manage%20journal%20entry%20template%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35870</link>
      <description>When creating a journal entry template in SAP S/4HANA (Manage Journal Entry Template) - versions S4CORE 104, 105, 106, 107, an attacker could intercept the save request and change the template, leading to an impact on confidentiality and integrity of the resource. Furthermore, a standard template could be deleted, hence making the resource temporarily unavailable.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35870|2024-08-02T16:30:45.390Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 02:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31405|2024-08-02T14:53:30.779Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20for%20java%20%28log%20viewer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31405</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver AS for Java - versions ENGINEAPI 7.50, SERVERCORE 7.50, J2EE-APPS 7.50, allows an unauthenticated attacker to craft a request over the network which can result in unwarranted modifications to a system log without user interaction. There is no ability to view any information or any effect on availability.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31405|2024-08-02T14:53:30.779Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 02:23:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31407|2024-08-02T14:53:31.053Z -- sap_se -- sap%20business%20planning%20and%20consolidation
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31407</link>
      <description>SAP Business Planning and Consolidation - versions 740, 750, allows an authorized attacker to upload a malicious file, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability. After successful exploitation, an attacker can cause limited impact on confidentiality and integrity of the application.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31407|2024-08-02T14:53:31.053Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 01:37:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6542|2024-08-02T08:35:13.594Z -- sap_se -- sap%20emarsys%20sdk%20android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6542</link>
      <description>Due to lack of proper authorization checks in Emarsys SDK for Android, an attacker can call a particular activity and can forward himself web pages and/or deep links without any validation directly from the host application. On successful attack, an attacker could navigate to arbitrary URL including application deep links on the device.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6542|2024-08-02T08:35:13.594Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 01:36:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-36917|2024-08-02T17:01:10.039Z -- sap_se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36917</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform - version 420, 430, allows an unauthorized attacker who had hijacked a user session, to be able to bypass the victim’s old password via brute force, due to unrestricted rate limit for password change functionality. Although the attack has no impact on integrity loss or system availability, this could lead to an attacker to completely takeover a victim’s account.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-36917|2024-08-02T17:01:10.039Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 02:48:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2827|2024-08-02T06:33:05.830Z -- sap_se -- sap%20plant%20connectivity
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2827</link>
      <description>SAP Plant Connectivity - version 15.5 (PCo) or the Production Connector for SAP Digital Manufacturing - version 1.0, do not validate the signature of the JSON Web Token (JWT) in the HTTP request sent from SAP Digital Manufacturing. Therefore, unauthorized callers from the internal network could send service requests to PCo or the Production Connector, which could have an impact on the integrity of the integration with SAP Digital Manufacturing.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2827|2024-08-02T06:33:05.830Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 02:36:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35873|2024-08-02T16:30:45.382Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20process%20integration%20%28runtime%20workbench%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35873</link>
      <description>The Runtime Workbench (RWB) of SAP NetWeaver Process Integration - version SAP_XITOOL 7.50, does not perform authentication checks for certain functionalities that require user identity. An unauthenticated user might access technical data about the product status and its configuration. The vulnerability does not allow access to sensitive information or administrative functionalities. On successful exploitation an attacker can cause limited impact on confidentiality and availability of the application.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35873|2024-08-02T16:30:45.382Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 02:42:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37483|2024-08-02T17:16:30.206Z -- sap_se -- sap%20powerdesigner
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37483</link>
      <description>SAP PowerDesigner - version 16.7, has improper access control which might allow an unauthenticated attacker to run arbitrary queries against the back-end database via Proxy.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37483|2024-08-02T17:16:30.206Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:39:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-36919|2024-08-02T17:01:10.010Z -- sap_se -- sap%20enable%20now
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36919</link>
      <description>In SAP Enable Now - versions WPB_MANAGER 1.0, WPB_MANAGER_CE 10, WPB_MANAGER_HANA 10, ENABLE_NOW_CONSUMP_DEL 1704, the Referrer-Policy response header is not implemented, allowing an unauthenticated attacker to obtain referrer details, resulting in information disclosure.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-36919|2024-08-02T17:01:10.010Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 02:54:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33989|2024-08-02T15:54:14.322Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20%28bi%20cont%20add%20on%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33989</link>
      <description>An attacker with non-administrative authorizations in SAP NetWeaver (BI CONT ADD ON) - versions 707, 737, 747, 757, can exploit a directory traversal flaw to over-write system files. Data from confidential files cannot be read but potentially some OS files can be over-written leading to system compromise.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33989|2024-08-02T15:54:14.322Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 02:28:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-36922|2024-08-02T17:01:09.981Z -- sap_se -- sap%20ecc%20and%20sap%20s%2F4hana%20%28is-oil%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36922</link>
      <description>Due to programming error in function module and report, IS-OIL component in SAP ECC and SAP S/4HANA allows an authenticated attacker to inject an arbitrary operating system command into an unprotected parameter in a common (default) extension.  On successful exploitation, the attacker can read or modify the system data as well as shut down the system.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-36922|2024-08-02T17:01:09.981Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 02:56:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33991|2024-08-02T15:54:14.185Z -- sap_se -- sap%20ui5%20variant%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33991</link>
      <description>SAP UI5 Variant Management - versions SAP_UI 750, SAP_UI 754, SAP_UI 755, SAP_UI 756, SAP_UI 757, UI_700 200, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs on reading data from the server, resulting in Stored Cross-Site Scripting (Stored XSS) vulnerability. After successful exploitation, an attacker with user level access can cause high impact on confidentiality, modify some information and can cause unavailability of the application at user level.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33991|2024-08-02T15:54:14.185Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 02:49:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-36921|2024-08-02T17:01:10.262Z -- sap_se -- sap%20solution%20manager%20%28diagnostic%20agent%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36921</link>
      <description>SAP Solution Manager (Diagnostics agent) - version 7.20, allows an attacker to tamper with headers in a client request. This misleads SAP Diagnostics Agent to serve poisoned content to the server. On successful exploitation, the attacker can cause a limited impact on confidentiality and availability of the application.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-36921|2024-08-02T17:01:10.262Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 02:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31404|2024-08-02T14:53:30.648Z -- sap_se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28central%20management%20service%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31404</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions, SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Central Management Service) - versions 420, 430, allows an attacker to access information which would otherwise be restricted. Some users with specific privileges could have access to credentials of other users. It could let them access data sources which would otherwise be restricted.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31404|2024-08-02T14:53:30.648Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 01:37:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28762|2024-08-02T13:51:37.301Z -- sap_se -- sap%20businessobjects%20intelligence%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28762</link>
      <description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform - versions 420, 430, allows an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to get the login token of any logged-in BI user over the network without any user interaction. The attacker can impersonate any user on the platform resulting into accessing and modifying data. The attacker can also make the system partially or entirely unavailable.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28762|2024-08-02T13:51:37.301Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 00:53:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37174|2024-08-02T03:50:55.134Z -- sap_se -- sap%20crm%20webclient%20ui</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37174</link>
      <description>Custom CSS support option in SAP CRM WebClient
UI does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs resulting in Cross-Site
Scripting vulnerability. On successful exploitation an attacker can cause
limited impact on confidentiality and integrity of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37174|2024-08-02T03:50:55.134Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:01:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37176|2024-08-02T03:50:54.783Z -- sap_se -- sap%20bw%2F4hana%20transformation%20and%20data%20transfer%20process</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37176</link>
      <description>SAP BW/4HANA Transformation and Data Transfer
Process (DTP) allows an authenticated attacker to gain higher access levels
than they should have by exploiting improper authorization checks. This results
in escalation of privileges. It has no impact on the confidentiality of data
but may have low impacts on the integrity and availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37176|2024-08-02T03:50:54.783Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37177|2024-08-02T03:50:55.219Z -- sap_se -- sap%20financial%20consolidation</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37177</link>
      <description>SAP Financial Consolidation allows data to enter
a Web application through an untrusted source. These endpoints are exposed over
the network and it allows the user to modify the content from the web site. On
successful exploitation, an attacker can cause significant impact to
confidentiality and integrity of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37177|2024-08-02T03:50:55.219Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 01:58:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37178|2024-08-02T03:50:55.238Z -- sap_se -- sap%20financial%20consolidation</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37178</link>
      <description>SAP Financial Consolidation does not
sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting
(XSS) vulnerability. These endpoints are exposed over the network. The
vulnerability can exploit resources beyond the vulnerable component. On
successful exploitation, an attacker can cause limited impact to
confidentiality of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37178|2024-08-02T03:50:55.238Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37175|2024-08-02T03:50:55.138Z -- sap_se -- sap%20crm%20webclient%20ui</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37175</link>
      <description>SAP CRM WebClient does not
perform necessary authorization check for an authenticated user, resulting in
escalation of privileges. This could allow an attacker to access some sensitive
information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37175|2024-08-02T03:50:55.138Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:07:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37172|2024-08-02T03:50:54.731Z -- sap_se -- sap%20s%2F4hana%20finance%20%28advanced%20payment%20management%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37172</link>
      <description>SAP S/4HANA Finance (Advanced Payment
Management) does not perform necessary authorization check for an authenticated
user, resulting in escalation of privileges. As a result, it has a low impact
to confidentiality and availability but there is no impact on the integrity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37172|2024-08-02T03:50:54.731Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37171|2024-08-02T03:50:54.664Z -- sap_se -- sap%20transportation%20management%20%28collaboration%20portal%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37171</link>
      <description>SAP Transportation Management (Collaboration
Portal) allows an attacker with non-administrative privileges to send a crafted
request from a vulnerable web application. This will trigger the application
handler to send a request to an unintended service, which may reveal
information about that service. The information obtained could be used to
target internal systems behind firewalls that are normally inaccessible to an
attacker from the external network, resulting in a Server-Side Request Forgery
vulnerability. There is no effect on integrity or availability of the
application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37171|2024-08-02T03:50:54.664Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:21:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37173|2024-08-02T03:50:54.682Z -- sap_se -- sap%20crm%20webclient%20ui</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37173</link>
      <description>Due to insufficient input validation, SAP
  CRM WebClient UI allows an unauthenticated attacker to craft a URL link which
  embeds a malicious script. When a victim clicks on this link, the script will
  be executed in the victim's browser giving the attacker the ability to access
  and/or modify information with no effect on availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37173|2024-08-02T03:50:54.682Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 03:57:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37180|2024-08-02T03:50:55.233Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20application%20server%20for%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37180</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions SAP NetWeaver
Application Server for ABAP and ABAP Platform allows an attacker to access
remote-enabled function module with no further authorization which would
otherwise be restricted, the function can be used to read non-sensitive
information with low impact on confidentiality of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37180|2024-08-02T03:50:55.233Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:41:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28164|2024-08-02T00:48:49.198Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20java</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28164</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver AS Java (CAF - Guided Procedures)
allows an unauthenticated user to access non-sensitive information about the
server which would otherwise be restricted causing low impact on
confidentiality of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28164|2024-08-02T00:48:49.198Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:18:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28167|2024-08-02T00:48:49.373Z -- sap_se -- sap%20group%20reporting%20data%20collection%20%28enter%20package%20data%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28167</link>
      <description>SAP Group Reporting Data Collection does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. On successful exploitation, specific data can be changed via the Enter Package Data app although the user does not have sufficient authorization causing high impact on Integrity of the appliction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28167|2024-08-02T00:48:49.373Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:55:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30218|2024-08-02T01:25:03.426Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30218</link>
      <description>The ABAP Application Server of SAP NetWeaver as well as ABAP Platform allows an attacker to prevent legitimate users from accessing a service, either by crashing or flooding the service. This leads to a considerable impact on availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30218|2024-08-02T01:25:03.426Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 01:04:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27898|2024-08-02T00:41:55.785Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27898</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver application, due to insufficient input validation, allows an attacker to send a crafted request from a vulnerable web application targeting internal systems behind firewalls that are normally inaccessible to an attacker from the external network, resulting in a Server-Side Request Forgery vulnerability. Thus, having a low impact on confidentiality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27898|2024-08-02T00:41:55.785Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:52:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30215|2024-08-02T01:25:03.369Z -- sap_se -- sap%20business%20connector</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30215</link>
      <description>The Resource Settings page allows a high privilege attacker to load exploitable payload to be stored and reflected whenever a User visits the page. In a successful attack, some information could be obtained and/or modified. However, the attacker does not have control over what information is obtained, or the amount or kind of loss is limited.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30215|2024-08-02T01:25:03.369Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:56:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27901|2024-08-02T00:41:55.774Z -- sap_se -- sap%20asset%20accounting</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27901</link>
      <description>SAP Asset Accounting could allow a high privileged attacker to exploit insufficient validation of path information provided by the users and pass it through to the file API's. Thus, causing a considerable impact on confidentiality, integrity and availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27901|2024-08-02T00:41:55.774Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:55:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27902|2024-08-02T00:41:55.900Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20abap%20applications%20based%20on%20sapgui%20for%20html%20%28webgui%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27902</link>
      <description>Applications based on SAP GUI for HTML in SAP NetWeaver AS ABAP - versions 7.89, 7.93, do not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. A successful attack can allow a malicious attacker to access and modify data through their ability to execute code in a user’s browser. There is no impact on the availability of the system</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27902|2024-08-02T00:41:55.900Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:45:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27900|2024-08-02T00:41:55.483Z -- sap_se -- sap%20abap%20platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27900</link>
      <description>Due to missing authorization check, attacker with business user account in SAP ABAP Platform - version 758, 795, can change the privacy setting of job templates from shared to private. As a result, the selected template would only be accessible to the owner.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27900|2024-08-02T00:41:55.483Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:44:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28163|2024-08-02T00:48:49.432Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20process%20integration%20%28support%20web%20pages%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28163</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions, Support Web Pages of SAP NetWeaver Process Integration (PI) - versions 7.50, allows an attacker to access information which would otherwise be restricted, causing low impact on Confidentiality with no impact on Integrity and Availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28163|2024-08-02T00:48:49.432Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:45:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30216|2024-08-02T01:25:03.367Z -- sap_se -- sap%20s%2F4%20hana%20%28cash%20management%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30216</link>
      <description>Cash Management in SAP S/4 HANA does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. By exploiting this vulnerability, attacker can add notes in the review request with 'completed' status affecting the integrity of the application. Confidentiality and Availability are not impacted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30216|2024-08-02T01:25:03.367Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 01:02:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30214|2024-08-02T01:25:03.428Z -- sap_se -- sap%20business%20connector</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30214</link>
      <description>The application allows a high privilege attacker to append a malicious GET query parameter to Service invocations, which are reflected in the server response. Under certain circumstances, if the parameter contains a JavaScript, the script could be processed on client side.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30214|2024-08-02T01:25:03.428Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:56:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28165|2024-08-02T00:48:49.373Z -- sap_se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28165</link>
      <description>SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform is vulnerable to stored XSS allowing an attacker to manipulate a parameter in the Opendocument URL which could lead to high impact on Confidentiality and Integrity of the application</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28165|2024-08-02T00:48:49.373Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 03:51:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27899|2024-08-02T00:41:55.550Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20java%20user%20management%20engine</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27899</link>
      <description>Self-Registration and Modify your own profile in User Admin Application of NetWeaver AS Java does not enforce proper security requirements for the content of the newly defined security answer. This can be leveraged by an attacker to cause profound impact on confidentiality and low impact on both integrity and availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27899|2024-08-02T00:41:55.550Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:54:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30217|2024-08-02T01:25:03.420Z -- sap_se -- sap%20s%2F4%20hana%20%28cash%20management%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30217</link>
      <description>Cash Management in SAP S/4 HANA does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. By exploiting this vulnerability, an attacker can approve or reject a bank account application affecting the integrity of the application. Confidentiality and Availability are not impacted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30217|2024-08-02T01:25:03.420Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 01:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28167|2024-08-01T20:35:37.803Z -- sap_se -- sap%20group%20reporting%20data%20collection%20%28enter%20package%20data%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28167</link>
      <description>SAP Group Reporting Data Collection does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. On successful exploitation, specific data can be changed via the Enter Package Data app although the user does not have sufficient authorization causing high impact on Integrity of the appliction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28167|2024-08-01T20:35:37.803Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:55:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4139|2024-08-01T20:33:52.507Z -- sap_se -- sap%20s%2F4%20hana%20%28manage%20bank%20statement%20reprocessing%20rules%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4139</link>
      <description>Manage Bank Statement ReProcessing Rules does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. By exploiting this vulnerability, an attacker can delete rules of other users affecting the integrity of the application. Confidentiality and Availability are not affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4139|2024-08-01T20:33:52.507Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 03:51:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4138|2024-08-01T20:33:52.538Z -- sap_se -- sap%20s%2F4%20hana%20%28manage%20bank%20statement%20reprocessing%20rules%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4138</link>
      <description>Manage Bank Statement ReProcessing Rules does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. By exploiting this vulnerability, an attacker can enable/disable the sharing rule of other users affecting the integrity of the application. Confidentiality and Availability are not affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4138|2024-08-01T20:33:52.538Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 03:53:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34691|2024-07-31T19:55:18.143Z -- sap_se -- sap%20s%2F4hana%20%28manage%20incoming%20payment%20files%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34691</link>
      <description>Manage Incoming Payment Files (F1680) of SAP
S/4HANA does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated
user, resulting in escalation of privileges. As a result, it has high impact on
integrity and no impact on the confidentiality and availability of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34691|2024-07-31T19:55:18.143Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:22:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30217|2024-07-29T16:05:47.691Z -- sap_se -- sap%20s%2F4%20hana%20%28cash%20management%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30217</link>
      <description>Cash Management in SAP S/4 HANA does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. By exploiting this vulnerability, an attacker can approve or reject a bank account application affecting the integrity of the application. Confidentiality and Availability are not impacted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30217|2024-07-29T16:05:47.691Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 01:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39592|2024-07-24T18:33:09.047Z -- sap_se -- sap%20pdce</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39592</link>
      <description>Elements of PDCE does not perform necessary
authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of
privileges.



This
allows an attacker to read sensitive information causing high impact on the
confidentiality of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39592|2024-07-24T18:33:09.047Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 03:45:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30214|2024-07-19T20:49:44.461Z -- sap_se -- sap%20business%20connector</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30214</link>
      <description>The application allows a high privilege attacker to append a malicious GET query parameter to Service invocations, which are reflected in the server response. Under certain circumstances, if the parameter contains a JavaScript, the script could be processed on client side.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30214|2024-07-19T20:49:44.461Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:56:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37173|2024-07-15T18:32:29.014Z -- sap_se -- sap%20crm%20webclient%20ui</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37173</link>
      <description>Due to insufficient input validation, SAP
  CRM WebClient UI allows an unauthenticated attacker to craft a URL link which
  embeds a malicious script. When a victim clicks on this link, the script will
  be executed in the victim's browser giving the attacker the ability to access
  and/or modify information with no effect on availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37173|2024-07-15T18:32:29.014Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 03:57:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39598|2024-07-10T21:04:24.524Z -- sap_se -- sap%20crm%20webclient%20ui</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39598</link>
      <description>SAP CRM (WebClient UI Framework) allows an
authenticated attacker to enumerate accessible HTTP endpoints in the internal
network by specially crafting HTTP requests. On successful exploitation this
can result in information disclosure. It has no impact on integrity and
availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39598|2024-07-10T21:04:24.524Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:04:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22126|2024-07-09T16:21:33.204Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20java%20%28user%20admin%20application%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22126</link>
      <description>The User Admin application of SAP NetWeaver AS for Java - version 7.50, insufficiently validates and improperly encodes the incoming URL parameters before including them into the redirect URL. This results in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability, leading to a high impact on confidentiality and mild impact on integrity and availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22126|2024-07-09T16:21:33.204Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 01:58:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39597|2024-07-09T16:20:38.023Z -- sap_se -- sap%20commerce</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39597</link>
      <description>In SAP Commerce, a user can misuse the forgotten
password functionality to gain access to a Composable Storefront B2B site for
which early login and registration is activated, without requiring the merchant
to approve the account beforehand. If the site is not configured as isolated
site, this can also grant access to other non-isolated early login sites, even
if registration is not enabled for those other sites.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39597|2024-07-09T16:20:38.023Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 03:48:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39599|2024-07-09T16:16:20.310Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20application%20server%20for%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39599</link>
      <description>Due to a Protection Mechanism Failure in SAP
NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP and ABAP Platform, a developer can bypass
the configured malware scanner API because of a programming error. This leads
to a low impact on the application's confidentiality, integrity, and
availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39599|2024-07-09T16:16:20.310Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:24:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39593|2024-07-09T14:03:52.791Z -- sap_se -- sap%20landscape%20management</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39593</link>
      <description>SAP Landscape Management allows an authenticated
user to read confidential data disclosed by the REST Provider Definition
response. Successful exploitation can cause high impact on confidentiality of
the managed entities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39593|2024-07-09T14:03:52.791Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 03:51:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37180|2024-07-09T14:43:18.463Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20application%20server%20for%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37180</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions SAP NetWeaver
Application Server for ABAP and ABAP Platform allows an attacker to access
remote-enabled function module with no further authorization which would
otherwise be restricted, the function can be used to read non-sensitive
information with low impact on confidentiality of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37180|2024-07-09T14:43:18.463Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:41:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39595|2024-07-09T14:54:14.485Z -- sap_se -- sap%20business%20warehouse%20-%20business%20planning%20and%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39595</link>
      <description>SAP Business Warehouse - Business Planning and
Simulation application does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs,
resulting in Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. This
vulnerability allows users to modify website content and on successful
exploitation, an attacker can cause low impact to the confidentiality and
integrity of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39595|2024-07-09T14:54:14.485Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39596|2024-07-09T13:59:14.488Z -- sap_se -- sap%20enable%20now</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39596</link>
      <description>Due to missing authorization checks, SAP Enable
Now allows an author to escalate privileges to access information which should
otherwise be restricted. On successful exploitation, the attacker can cause
limited impact on confidentiality of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39596|2024-07-09T13:59:14.488Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34685|2024-07-09T03:53:38.517Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20knowledge%20management%20xmleditor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34685</link>
      <description>Due to weak encoding of user-controlled input in
SAP NetWeaver Knowledge Management XMLEditor which allows malicious scripts can
be executed in the application, potentially leading to a Cross-Site Scripting
(XSS) vulnerability. This has no impact on the availability of the application
but it has a low impact on its confidentiality and integrity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34685|2024-07-09T03:53:38.517Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 03:53:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39593|2024-07-09T03:51:46.533Z -- sap_se -- sap%20landscape%20management</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39593</link>
      <description>SAP Landscape Management allows an authenticated
user to read confidential data disclosed by the REST Provider Definition
response. Successful exploitation can cause high impact on confidentiality of
the managed entities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39593|2024-07-09T03:51:46.533Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 03:51:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39597|2024-07-09T03:48:11.488Z -- sap_se -- sap%20commerce</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39597</link>
      <description>In SAP Commerce, a user can misuse the forgotten
password functionality to gain access to a Composable Storefront B2B site for
which early login and registration is activated, without requiring the merchant
to approve the account beforehand. If the site is not configured as isolated
site, this can also grant access to other non-isolated early login sites, even
if registration is not enabled for those other sites.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39597|2024-07-09T03:48:11.488Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 03:48:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39592|2024-07-09T03:45:56.018Z -- sap_se -- sap%20pdce</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39592</link>
      <description>Elements of PDCE does not perform necessary
authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of
privileges.



This
allows an attacker to read sensitive information causing high impact on the
confidentiality of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39592|2024-07-09T03:45:56.018Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 03:45:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22131|2024-06-28T16:05:04.503Z -- sap_se -- sap%20aba%20%28application%20basis%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22131</link>
      <description>In SAP ABA (Application Basis) - versions 700, 701, 702, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 75C, 75I, an attacker authenticated as a user with a remote execution authorization can use a vulnerable interface. This allows the attacker to use the interface to invoke an application function to perform actions which they would not normally be permitted to perform.  Depending on the function executed, the attack can read or modify any user/business data and can make the entire system unavailable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22131|2024-06-28T16:05:04.503Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28167|2024-04-09T00:55:46.326Z -- sap_se -- sap%20group%20reporting%20data%20collection%20%28enter%20package%20data%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-28167</link>
      <description>SAP Group Reporting Data Collection does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. On successful exploitation, specific data can be changed via the Enter Package Data app although the user does not have sufficient authorization causing high impact on Integrity of the appliction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28167|2024-04-09T00:55:46.326Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:55:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28165|2024-06-04T18:03:32.671Z -- sap_se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-28165</link>
      <description>SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform is vulnerable to stored XSS allowing an attacker to manipulate a parameter in the Opendocument URL which could lead to high impact on Confidentiality and Integrity of the application</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28165|2024-06-04T18:03:32.671Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 03:51:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28164|2024-06-11T10:10:35.316Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20java</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-28164</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver AS Java (CAF - Guided Procedures)
allows an unauthenticated user to access non-sensitive information about the
server which would otherwise be restricted causing low impact on
confidentiality of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28164|2024-06-11T10:10:35.316Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:18:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28163|2024-03-12T00:45:42.419Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20process%20integration%20%28support%20web%20pages%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-28163</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions, Support Web Pages of SAP NetWeaver Process Integration (PI) - versions 7.50, allows an attacker to access information which would otherwise be restricted, causing low impact on Confidentiality with no impact on Integrity and Availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28163|2024-03-12T00:45:42.419Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:45:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4139|2024-06-04T17:55:21.514Z -- sap_se -- sap%20s%2F4%20hana%20%28manage%20bank%20statement%20reprocessing%20rules%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4139</link>
      <description>Manage Bank Statement ReProcessing Rules does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. By exploiting this vulnerability, an attacker can delete rules of other users affecting the integrity of the application. Confidentiality and Availability are not affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4139|2024-06-04T17:55:21.514Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 03:51:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4138|2024-06-04T17:55:13.334Z -- sap_se -- sap%20s%2F4%20hana%20%28manage%20bank%20statement%20reprocessing%20rules%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4138</link>
      <description>Manage Bank Statement ReProcessing Rules does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. By exploiting this vulnerability, an attacker can enable/disable the sharing rule of other users affecting the integrity of the application. Confidentiality and Availability are not affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4138|2024-06-04T17:55:13.334Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 03:53:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22130|2024-02-13T02:29:51.706Z -- sap_se -- sap%20crm%20webclient%20ui</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22130</link>
      <description>Print preview option in SAP CRM WebClient UI - versions S4FND 102, S4FND 103, S4FND 104, S4FND 105, S4FND 106, S4FND 107, S4FND 108, WEBCUIF 700, WEBCUIF 701, WEBCUIF 730, WEBCUIF 731, WEBCUIF 746, WEBCUIF 747, WEBCUIF 748, WEBCUIF 800, WEBCUIF 801, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability. An attacker with low privileges can cause limited impact to confidentiality and integrity of the appliaction data after successful exploitation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22130|2024-02-13T02:29:51.706Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:29:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22126|2024-02-13T01:58:27.745Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20java%20%28user%20admin%20application%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22126</link>
      <description>The User Admin application of SAP NetWeaver AS for Java - version 7.50, insufficiently validates and improperly encodes the incoming URL parameters before including them into the redirect URL. This results in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability, leading to a high impact on confidentiality and mild impact on integrity and availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22126|2024-02-13T01:58:27.745Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 01:58:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22127|2024-03-12T00:29:37.694Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20java%20%28administrator%20log%20viewer%20plug-in%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22127</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver Administrator AS Java (Administrator Log Viewer plug-in) - version 7.50, allows an attacker with high privileges to upload potentially dangerous files which leads to command injection vulnerability. This would enable the attacker to run commands which can cause high impact on confidentiality, integrity and availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22127|2024-03-12T00:29:37.694Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:29:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22131|2024-02-13T02:30:51.886Z -- sap_se -- sap%20aba%20%28application%20basis%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22131</link>
      <description>In SAP ABA (Application Basis) - versions 700, 701, 702, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 75C, 75I, an attacker authenticated as a user with a remote execution authorization can use a vulnerable interface. This allows the attacker to use the interface to invoke an application function to perform actions which they would not normally be permitted to perform.  Depending on the function executed, the attack can read or modify any user/business data and can make the entire system unavailable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22131|2024-02-13T02:30:51.886Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22132|2024-02-13T02:33:01.622Z -- sap_se -- sap%20ides%20systems</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22132</link>
      <description>SAP IDES ECC-systems contain code that permits the execution of arbitrary program code of user's choice.An attacker can therefore control the behaviour of the system by executing malicious code which can potentially escalate privileges with low impact on confidentiality, integrity and availability of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22132|2024-02-13T02:33:01.622Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:33:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22128|2024-06-04T17:52:30.808Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20business%20client%20for%20html</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22128</link>
      <description>SAP NWBC for HTML - versions SAP_UI 754, SAP_UI 755, SAP_UI 756, SAP_UI 757, SAP_UI 758, SAP_BASIS 700, SAP_BASIS 701, SAP_BASIS 702, SAP_BASIS 731, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker can inject malicious javascript to cause limited impact to confidentiality and integrity of the application data after successful exploitation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22128|2024-06-04T17:52:30.808Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:02:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22129|2024-06-04T17:52:24.034Z -- sap_se -- sap%20companion</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22129</link>
      <description>SAP Companion - version &lt;3.1.38, has a URL with parameter that could be vulnerable to XSS attack. The attacker could send a malicious link to a user that would possibly allow an attacker to retrieve the sensitive information and cause minor impact on the integrity of the web application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22129|2024-06-04T17:52:24.034Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 03:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22133|2024-06-04T17:52:21.492Z -- sap_se -- sap%20fiori%20front%20end%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22133</link>
      <description>SAP Fiori Front End Server - version 605, allows altering of approver details on the read-only field when sending leave request information. This could lead to creation of request with incorrect approver causing low impact on Confidentiality and Integrity with no impact on Availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22133|2024-06-04T17:52:21.492Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:32:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32730|2024-06-04T17:51:30.558Z -- sap_se -- sap%20enable%20now</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-32730</link>
      <description>SAP Enable Now Manager does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. On successful exploitation, the attacker with the role 'Learner' could gain access to other user's data in manager which will lead to a high impact to the confidentiality of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32730|2024-06-04T17:51:30.558Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 16:06:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32731|2024-05-14T03:38:59.839Z -- sap_se -- sap%20my%20travel%20requests</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-32731</link>
      <description>SAP My Travel Requests does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. On successful exploitation, the attacker can upload a malicious attachment to a business trip request which will lead to a low impact on the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32731|2024-05-14T03:38:59.839Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 03:07:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32733|2024-06-04T17:50:43.945Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20application%20server%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-32733</link>
      <description>Due to missing input validation and output encoding of untrusted data, SAP NetWeaver Application Server ABAP and ABAP Platform allows an unauthenticated attacker to inject malicious JavaScript code into the dynamically crafted web page. On successful exploitation the attacker can access or modify sensitive information with no impact on availability of the application</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32733|2024-06-04T17:50:43.945Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 03:38:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27902|2024-06-04T17:47:26.941Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20abap%20applications%20based%20on%20sapgui%20for%20html%20%28webgui%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27902</link>
      <description>Applications based on SAP GUI for HTML in SAP NetWeaver AS ABAP - versions 7.89, 7.93, do not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. A successful attack can allow a malicious attacker to access and modify data through their ability to execute code in a user’s browser. There is no impact on the availability of the system</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27902|2024-06-04T17:47:26.941Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:45:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27898|2024-04-09T00:52:54.390Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27898</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver application, due to insufficient input validation, allows an attacker to send a crafted request from a vulnerable web application targeting internal systems behind firewalls that are normally inaccessible to an attacker from the external network, resulting in a Server-Side Request Forgery vulnerability. Thus, having a low impact on confidentiality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27898|2024-04-09T00:52:54.390Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:52:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27899|2024-06-04T17:47:04.705Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20java%20user%20management%20engine</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27899</link>
      <description>Self-Registration and Modify your own profile in User Admin Application of NetWeaver AS Java does not enforce proper security requirements for the content of the newly defined security answer. This can be leveraged by an attacker to cause profound impact on confidentiality and low impact on both integrity and availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27899|2024-06-04T17:47:04.705Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:54:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27900|2024-06-04T17:46:37.529Z -- sap_se -- sap%20abap%20platform</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27900</link>
      <description>Due to missing authorization check, attacker with business user account in SAP ABAP Platform - version 758, 795, can change the privacy setting of job templates from shared to private. As a result, the selected template would only be accessible to the owner.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27900|2024-06-04T17:46:37.529Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:44:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27901|2024-04-09T00:55:03.642Z -- sap_se -- sap%20asset%20accounting</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27901</link>
      <description>SAP Asset Accounting could allow a high privileged attacker to exploit insufficient validation of path information provided by the users and pass it through to the file API's. Thus, causing a considerable impact on confidentiality, integrity and availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27901|2024-04-09T00:55:03.642Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:55:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37178|2024-06-11T14:24:19.964Z -- sap_se -- sap%20financial%20consolidation</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-37178</link>
      <description>SAP Financial Consolidation does not
sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting
(XSS) vulnerability. These endpoints are exposed over the network. The
vulnerability can exploit resources beyond the vulnerable component. On
successful exploitation, an attacker can cause limited impact to
confidentiality of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37178|2024-06-11T14:24:19.964Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37176|2024-06-11T14:16:58.729Z -- sap_se -- sap%20bw%2F4hana%20transformation%20and%20data%20transfer%20process</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-37176</link>
      <description>SAP BW/4HANA Transformation and Data Transfer
Process (DTP) allows an authenticated attacker to gain higher access levels
than they should have by exploiting improper authorization checks. This results
in escalation of privileges. It has no impact on the confidentiality of data
but may have low impacts on the integrity and availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37176|2024-06-11T14:16:58.729Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37177|2024-06-11T17:52:04.447Z -- sap_se -- sap%20financial%20consolidation</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-37177</link>
      <description>SAP Financial Consolidation allows data to enter
a Web application through an untrusted source. These endpoints are exposed over
the network and it allows the user to modify the content from the web site. On
successful exploitation, an attacker can cause significant impact to
confidentiality and integrity of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37177|2024-06-11T17:52:04.447Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 01:58:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-33002|2024-06-04T17:45:19.318Z -- sap_se -- sap%20s%2F4hana%20%28document%20service%20handler%20for%20dps%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-33002</link>
      <description>Document Service handler (obsolete) in Data Provisioning Service does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability with low impact on Confidentiality and Integrity of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33002|2024-06-04T17:45:19.318Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 03:49:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-33009|2024-06-04T17:44:54.956Z -- sap_se -- sap%20global%20label%20management%20%28glm%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-33009</link>
      <description>SAP Global Label Management is vulnerable to SQL injection. On exploitation the attacker can use specially crafted inputs to modify database commands resulting in the retrieval of additional information persisted by the system. This could lead to low impact on Confidentiality and Integrity of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33009|2024-06-04T17:44:54.956Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 03:58:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-33008|2024-06-04T17:44:52.357Z -- sap_se -- sap%20replication%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-33008</link>
      <description>SAP Replication Server allows an attacker to use gateway for executing some commands to RSSD. This could result in crashing the Replication Server due to memory corruption with high impact on Availability of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33008|2024-06-04T17:44:52.357Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 03:46:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-33004|2024-06-04T17:44:43.596Z -- sap_se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28webservices%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-33004</link>
      <description>SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform is vulnerable to Insecure Storage as dynamic web pages are getting cached even after logging out. On successful exploitation, the attacker can see the sensitive information through cache and can open the pages causing limited impact on Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33004|2024-06-04T17:44:43.596Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 04:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-33007|2024-06-04T17:44:35.380Z -- sap_se -- sapui5%20%28pdfviewer%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-33007</link>
      <description>PDFViewer is a control delivered as part of SAPUI5 product which shows the PDF content in an embedded mode by default. If a PDF document contains embedded JavaScript (or any harmful client-side script), the PDFViewer will execute the JavaScript embedded in the PDF which can cause a potential security threat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33007|2024-06-04T17:44:35.380Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 03:44:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-33006|2024-06-04T17:44:12.903Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20application%20server%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-33006</link>
      <description>An unauthenticated attacker can upload a malicious file to the server which when accessed by a victim can allow an attacker to completely compromise system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33006|2024-06-04T17:44:12.903Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 04:16:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-33001|2024-06-11T02:05:00.333Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20and%20abap%20platform</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-33001</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver and ABAP platform allows an
attacker to impede performance for legitimate users by crashing or flooding the
service.



An
impact of this Denial of Service vulnerability might be long response delays
and service interruptions, thus degrading the service quality experienced by
legitimate users causing high impact on availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33001|2024-06-11T02:05:00.333Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-33000|2024-06-04T17:43:49.177Z -- sap_se -- sap%20bank%20account%20management</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-33000</link>
      <description>SAP Bank Account Management does not perform necessary authorization check for an authorized user, resulting in escalation of privileges. As a result, it has a low impact to confidentiality to the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33000|2024-06-04T17:43:49.177Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 03:46:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-24742|2024-06-04T17:43:29.079Z -- sap_se -- sap%20crm%20%28webclient%20ui%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-24742</link>
      <description>SAP CRM WebClient UI - version S4FND 102, S4FND 103, S4FND 104, S4FND 105, S4FND 106, WEBCUIF 701, WEBCUIF 731, WEBCUIF 746, WEBCUIF 747, WEBCUIF 748, WEBCUIF 800, WEBCUIF 801, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. An attacker with low privileges can cause limited impact to integrity of the application data after successful exploitation. There is no impact on confidentiality and availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24742|2024-06-04T17:43:29.079Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-24739|2024-02-13T02:34:17.247Z -- sap_se -- sap%20bam%20%28bank%20account%20management%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-24739</link>
      <description>SAP Bank Account Management (BAM) allows an authenticated user with restricted access to use functions which can result in escalation of privileges with low impact on confidentiality, integrity and availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24739|2024-02-13T02:34:17.247Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:34:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-24743|2024-02-13T02:43:40.755Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20java%20%28guided%20procedures%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-24743</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver AS Java (CAF - Guided Procedures) - version 7.50, allows an unauthenticated attacker to submit a malicious request with a crafted XML file over the network, which when parsed will enable him to access sensitive files and data but not modify them. There are expansion limits in place so that availability is not affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24743|2024-02-13T02:43:40.755Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:43:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-24740|2024-02-13T02:35:21.224Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20application%20server%20abap%20%28sap%20kernel%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-24740</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver Application Server (ABAP) - versions KERNEL 7.53, KERNEL 7.54, KERNEL 7.77, KERNEL 7.85, KERNEL 7.89, KERNEL 7.93, KERNEL 7.94, KRNL64UC 7.53, under certain conditions, allows an attacker to access information which could otherwise be restricted with low impact on confidentiality of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24740|2024-02-13T02:35:21.224Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:35:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-24741|2024-06-04T17:43:06.598Z -- sap_se -- sap%20master%20data%20governance%20material</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-24741</link>
      <description>SAP Master Data Governance for Material Data - versions 618, 619, 620, 621, 622, 800, 801, 802, 803, 804, does not perform necessary authorization check for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. This could allow an attacker to read some sensitive information but no impact to integrity and availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24741|2024-06-04T17:43:06.598Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 03:43:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34683|2024-06-11T13:35:47.339Z -- sap_se -- sap%20document%20builder</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-34683</link>
      <description>An authenticated attacker can upload malicious
file to SAP Document Builder service. When the victim accesses this file, the
attacker is allowed to access, modify, or make the related information
unavailable in the victim’s browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34683|2024-06-11T13:35:47.339Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34688|2024-06-11T13:40:34.530Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20java</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-34688</link>
      <description>Due to unrestricted access to the Meta Model
Repository services in SAP NetWeaver AS Java, attackers can perform DoS attacks
on the application, which may prevent legitimate users from accessing it. This
can result in no impact on confidentiality and integrity but a high impact on
the availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34688|2024-06-11T13:40:34.530Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34684|2024-06-11T15:54:55.656Z -- sap_se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-34684</link>
      <description>On Unix, SAP BusinessObjects Business
Intelligence Platform (Scheduling) allows an authenticated attacker with
administrator access on the local server to access the password of a local
account. As a result, an attacker can obtain non-administrative user
credentials, which will allow them to read or modify the remote server files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34684|2024-06-11T15:54:55.656Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:20:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34691|2024-06-11T02:22:24.435Z -- sap_se -- sap%20s%2F4hana%20%28manage%20incoming%20payment%20files%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-34691</link>
      <description>Manage Incoming Payment Files (F1680) of SAP
S/4HANA does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated
user, resulting in escalation of privileges. As a result, it has high impact on
integrity and no impact on the confidentiality and availability of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34691|2024-06-11T02:22:24.435Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:22:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34687|2024-06-04T17:41:49.331Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20application%20server%20for%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-34687</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP and ABAP Platform do not sufficiently encode user controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.
An attacker can control code that is executed within a user’s browser, which could result in modification, deletion of data, including accessing or deleting files, or stealing session cookies which an attacker could use to hijack a user’s session. Hence, this could have impact on Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34687|2024-06-04T17:41:49.331Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 03:56:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34686|2024-06-11T13:41:52.606Z -- sap_se -- sap%20crm%20webclient%20ui</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-34686</link>
      <description>Due to insufficient input validation, SAP CRM
WebClient UI allows an unauthenticated attacker to craft a URL link which
embeds a malicious script. When a victim clicks on this link, the script will
be executed in the victim's browser giving the attacker the ability to access
and/or modify information with no effect on availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34686|2024-06-11T13:41:52.606Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:11:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34690|2024-06-11T14:23:56.078Z -- sap_se -- sap%20student%20life%20cycle%20management</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-34690</link>
      <description>SAP Student Life Cycle
Management (SLcM) fails to conduct proper authorization checks for
authenticated users, leading to the potential escalation of privileges. On
successful exploitation it could allow an attacker to access and edit
non-sensitive report variants that are typically restricted, causing minimal
impact on the confidentiality and integrity of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34690|2024-06-11T14:23:56.078Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30214|2024-04-09T00:56:29.336Z -- sap_se -- sap%20business%20connector</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30214</link>
      <description>The application allows a high privilege attacker to append a malicious GET query parameter to Service invocations, which are reflected in the server response. Under certain circumstances, if the parameter contains a JavaScript, the script could be processed on client side.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30214|2024-04-09T00:56:29.336Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:56:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30218|2024-06-04T17:39:20.427Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30218</link>
      <description>The ABAP Application Server of SAP NetWeaver as well as ABAP Platform allows an attacker to prevent legitimate users from accessing a service, either by crashing or flooding the service. This leads to a considerable impact on availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30218|2024-06-04T17:39:20.427Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 01:04:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30215|2024-06-04T17:39:05.622Z -- sap_se -- sap%20business%20connector</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30215</link>
      <description>The Resource Settings page allows a high privilege attacker to load exploitable payload to be stored and reflected whenever a User visits the page. In a successful attack, some information could be obtained and/or modified. However, the attacker does not have control over what information is obtained, or the amount or kind of loss is limited.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30215|2024-06-04T17:39:05.622Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:56:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30216|2024-06-04T17:38:58.000Z -- sap_se -- sap%20s%2F4%20hana%20%28cash%20management%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30216</link>
      <description>Cash Management in SAP S/4 HANA does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. By exploiting this vulnerability, attacker can add notes in the review request with 'completed' status affecting the integrity of the application. Confidentiality and Availability are not impacted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30216|2024-06-04T17:38:58.000Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 01:02:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30217|2024-04-09T01:03:20.926Z -- sap_se -- sap%20s%2F4%20hana%20%28cash%20management%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30217</link>
      <description>Cash Management in SAP S/4 HANA does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. By exploiting this vulnerability, an attacker can approve or reject a bank account application affecting the integrity of the application. Confidentiality and Availability are not impacted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30217|2024-04-09T01:03:20.926Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 01:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25646|2024-06-04T17:35:27.307Z -- sap_se -- sap%20businessobjects%20web%20intelligence</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25646</link>
      <description>Due to improper validation, SAP BusinessObject Business Intelligence Launch Pad allows an authenticated attacker to access operating system information using crafted document. On successful exploitation there could be a considerable impact on confidentiality of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25646|2024-06-04T17:35:27.307Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:47:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25645|2024-06-04T17:35:22.989Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20%28enterprise%20portal%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25645</link>
      <description>Under certain condition SAP NetWeaver (Enterprise Portal) - version 7.50 allows an attacker to access information which would otherwise be restricted causing low impact on confidentiality of the application and with no impact on Integrity and Availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25645|2024-06-04T17:35:22.989Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:53:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25644|2024-03-12T00:33:44.473Z -- sap_se -- netweaver%20%28wsrm%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25644</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions SAP NetWeaver WSRM - version 7.50, allows an attacker to access information which would otherwise be restricted, causing low impact on Confidentiality with no impact on Integrity and Availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25644|2024-03-12T00:33:44.473Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:33:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25643|2024-06-04T17:35:09.212Z -- sap_se -- sap%20fiori%20app%20%28my%20overtime%20requests%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25643</link>
      <description>The SAP Fiori app (My Overtime Request) - version 605, does not perform the necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user which may result in an escalation of privileges. It is possible to manipulate the URLs of data requests to access information that the user should not have access to. There is no impact on integrity and availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25643|2024-06-04T17:35:09.212Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 03:37:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25642|2024-02-13T02:44:20.284Z -- sap_se -- sap%20cloud%20connector</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25642</link>
      <description>Due to improper validation of certificate in SAP Cloud Connector - version 2.0, attacker can impersonate the genuine servers to interact with SCC breaking the mutual authentication. Hence, the attacker can intercept the request to view/modify sensitive information. There is no impact on the availability of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25642|2024-02-13T02:44:20.284Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:44:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32731|2024-06-12T18:41:33.655Z -- sap_se -- sap%20my%20travel%20requests</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-32731</link>
      <description>SAP My Travel Requests does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. On successful exploitation, the attacker can upload a malicious attachment to a business trip request which will lead to a low impact on the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32731|2024-06-12T18:41:33.655Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 03:07:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28164|2024-07-03T16:44:43.157Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20java</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28164</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver AS Java (CAF - Guided Procedures)
allows an unauthenticated user to access non-sensitive information about the
server which would otherwise be restricted causing low impact on
confidentiality of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28164|2024-07-03T16:44:43.157Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:18:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39596|2024-07-09T04:25:57.251Z -- sap_se -- sap%20enable%20now</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39596</link>
      <description>Due to missing authorization checks, SAP Enable
Now allows an author to escalate privileges to access information which should
otherwise be restricted. On successful exploitation, the attacker can cause
limited impact on confidentiality of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39596|2024-07-09T04:25:57.251Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39598|2024-07-09T04:04:41.283Z -- sap_se -- sap%20crm%20webclient%20ui</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39598</link>
      <description>SAP CRM (WebClient UI Framework) allows an
authenticated attacker to enumerate accessible HTTP endpoints in the internal
network by specially crafting HTTP requests. On successful exploitation this
can result in information disclosure. It has no impact on integrity and
availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39598|2024-07-09T04:04:41.283Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:04:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39595|2024-07-09T04:13:49.560Z -- sap_se -- sap%20business%20warehouse%20-%20business%20planning%20and%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39595</link>
      <description>SAP Business Warehouse - Business Planning and
Simulation application does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs,
resulting in Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. This
vulnerability allows users to modify website content and on successful
exploitation, an attacker can cause low impact to the confidentiality and
integrity of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39595|2024-07-09T04:13:49.560Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39599|2024-07-09T04:24:31.103Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20application%20server%20for%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39599</link>
      <description>Due to a Protection Mechanism Failure in SAP
NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP and ABAP Platform, a developer can bypass
the configured malware scanner API because of a programming error. This leads
to a low impact on the application's confidentiality, integrity, and
availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39599|2024-07-09T04:24:31.103Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:24:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37180|2024-07-09T04:41:32.313Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20application%20server%20for%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37180</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions SAP NetWeaver
Application Server for ABAP and ABAP Platform allows an attacker to access
remote-enabled function module with no further authorization which would
otherwise be restricted, the function can be used to read non-sensitive
information with low impact on confidentiality of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37180|2024-07-09T04:41:32.313Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:41:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37171|2024-07-09T04:21:21.292Z -- sap_se -- sap%20transportation%20management%20%28collaboration%20portal%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37171</link>
      <description>SAP Transportation Management (Collaboration
Portal) allows an attacker with non-administrative privileges to send a crafted
request from a vulnerable web application. This will trigger the application
handler to send a request to an unintended service, which may reveal
information about that service. The information obtained could be used to
target internal systems behind firewalls that are normally inaccessible to an
attacker from the external network, resulting in a Server-Side Request Forgery
vulnerability. There is no effect on integrity or availability of the
application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37171|2024-07-09T04:21:21.292Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:21:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34689|2024-07-09T04:18:21.258Z -- sap_se -- sap%20business%20workflow%20%28webflow%20services%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34689</link>
      <description>WebFlow Services of SAP Business Workflow allows
an authenticated attacker to enumerate accessible HTTP endpoints in the
internal network by specially crafting HTTP requests. On successful
exploitation this can result in information disclosure. It has no impact on
integrity and availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34689|2024-07-09T04:18:21.258Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:18:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39594|2024-07-09T04:10:40.727Z -- sap_se -- sap%20business%20warehouse%20-%20business%20planning%20and%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39594</link>
      <description>SAP Business Warehouse - Business Planning and
Simulation application does not sufficiently encode user controlled inputs,
resulting in Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. After
successful exploitation, an attacker can cause low impact on the confidentiality
and integrity of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39594|2024-07-09T04:10:40.727Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37172|2024-07-09T04:15:22.833Z -- sap_se -- sap%20s%2F4hana%20finance%20%28advanced%20payment%20management%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37172</link>
      <description>SAP S/4HANA Finance (Advanced Payment
Management) does not perform necessary authorization check for an authenticated
user, resulting in escalation of privileges. As a result, it has a low impact
to confidentiality and availability but there is no impact on the integrity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37172|2024-07-09T04:15:22.833Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39600|2024-07-09T04:19:47.498Z -- sap_se -- sap%20gui%20for%20windows</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39600</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions, the memory of SAP GUI
for Windows contains the password used to log on to an SAP system, which might
allow an attacker to get hold of the password and impersonate the affected
user. As a result, it has a high impact on the confidentiality but there is no
impact on the integrity and availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39600|2024-07-09T04:19:47.498Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:19:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37174|2024-07-09T04:01:21.084Z -- sap_se -- sap%20crm%20webclient%20ui</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37174</link>
      <description>Custom CSS support option in SAP CRM WebClient
UI does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs resulting in Cross-Site
Scripting vulnerability. On successful exploitation an attacker can cause
limited impact on confidentiality and integrity of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37174|2024-07-09T04:01:21.084Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:01:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34692|2024-07-09T04:43:05.361Z -- sap_se -- sap%20enable%20now</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34692</link>
      <description>Due to missing verification of file type or
content, SAP Enable Now allows an authenticated attacker to upload arbitrary
files. These files include executables which might be downloaded and executed
by the user which could host malware. On successful exploitation an attacker
can cause limited impact on confidentiality and Integrity of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34692|2024-07-09T04:43:05.361Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:43:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37173|2024-07-09T03:57:15.928Z -- sap_se -- sap%20crm%20webclient%20ui</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37173</link>
      <description>Due to insufficient input validation, SAP
  CRM WebClient UI allows an unauthenticated attacker to craft a URL link which
  embeds a malicious script. When a victim clicks on this link, the script will
  be executed in the victim's browser giving the attacker the ability to access
  and/or modify information with no effect on availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37173|2024-07-09T03:57:15.928Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 03:57:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37175|2024-07-09T04:07:21.612Z -- sap_se -- sap%20crm%20webclient%20ui</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37175</link>
      <description>SAP CRM WebClient does not
perform necessary authorization check for an authenticated user, resulting in
escalation of privileges. This could allow an attacker to access some sensitive
information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37175|2024-07-09T04:07:21.612Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:07:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39600|2024-07-09T15:13:54.457Z -- sap_se -- sap%20gui%20for%20windows</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39600</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions, the memory of SAP GUI
for Windows contains the password used to log on to an SAP system, which might
allow an attacker to get hold of the password and impersonate the affected
user. As a result, it has a high impact on the confidentiality but there is no
impact on the integrity and availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39600|2024-07-09T15:13:54.457Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:19:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37172|2024-07-09T15:16:18.449Z -- sap_se -- sap%20s%2F4hana%20finance%20%28advanced%20payment%20management%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37172</link>
      <description>SAP S/4HANA Finance (Advanced Payment
Management) does not perform necessary authorization check for an authenticated
user, resulting in escalation of privileges. As a result, it has a low impact
to confidentiality and availability but there is no impact on the integrity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37172|2024-07-09T15:16:18.449Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37174|2024-07-10T16:31:22.567Z -- sap_se -- sap%20crm%20webclient%20ui</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37174</link>
      <description>Custom CSS support option in SAP CRM WebClient
UI does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs resulting in Cross-Site
Scripting vulnerability. On successful exploitation an attacker can cause
limited impact on confidentiality and integrity of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37174|2024-07-10T16:31:22.567Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:01:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37175|2024-07-11T14:35:21.200Z -- sap_se -- sap%20crm%20webclient%20ui</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37175</link>
      <description>SAP CRM WebClient does not
perform necessary authorization check for an authenticated user, resulting in
escalation of privileges. This could allow an attacker to access some sensitive
information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37175|2024-07-11T14:35:21.200Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:07:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39594|2024-07-15T20:21:58.159Z -- sap_se -- sap%20business%20warehouse%20-%20business%20planning%20and%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39594</link>
      <description>SAP Business Warehouse - Business Planning and
Simulation application does not sufficiently encode user controlled inputs,
resulting in Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. After
successful exploitation, an attacker can cause low impact on the confidentiality
and integrity of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39594|2024-07-15T20:21:58.159Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37171|2024-07-23T14:50:55.956Z -- sap_se -- sap%20transportation%20management%20%28collaboration%20portal%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37171</link>
      <description>SAP Transportation Management (Collaboration
Portal) allows an attacker with non-administrative privileges to send a crafted
request from a vulnerable web application. This will trigger the application
handler to send a request to an unintended service, which may reveal
information about that service. The information obtained could be used to
target internal systems behind firewalls that are normally inaccessible to an
attacker from the external network, resulting in a Server-Side Request Forgery
vulnerability. There is no effect on integrity or availability of the
application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37171|2024-07-23T14:50:55.956Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:21:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34685|2024-07-23T14:51:35.988Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20knowledge%20management%20xmleditor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34685</link>
      <description>Due to weak encoding of user-controlled input in
SAP NetWeaver Knowledge Management XMLEditor which allows malicious scripts can
be executed in the application, potentially leading to a Cross-Site Scripting
(XSS) vulnerability. This has no impact on the availability of the application
but it has a low impact on its confidentiality and integrity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34685|2024-07-23T14:51:35.988Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 03:53:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34692|2024-07-23T14:41:29.721Z -- sap_se -- sap%20enable%20now</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34692</link>
      <description>Due to missing verification of file type or
content, SAP Enable Now allows an authenticated attacker to upload arbitrary
files. These files include executables which might be downloaded and executed
by the user which could host malware. On successful exploitation an attacker
can cause limited impact on confidentiality and Integrity of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34692|2024-07-23T14:41:29.721Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:43:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34689|2024-07-25T14:38:25.505Z -- sap_se -- sap%20business%20workflow%20%28webflow%20services%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34689</link>
      <description>WebFlow Services of SAP Business Workflow allows
an authenticated attacker to enumerate accessible HTTP endpoints in the
internal network by specially crafting HTTP requests. On successful
exploitation this can result in information disclosure. It has no impact on
integrity and availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34689|2024-07-25T14:38:25.505Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:18:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-33001|2024-07-30T17:29:13.906Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20and%20abap%20platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33001</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver and ABAP platform allows an
attacker to impede performance for legitimate users by crashing or flooding the
service.



An
impact of this Denial of Service vulnerability might be long response delays
and service interruptions, thus degrading the service quality experienced by
legitimate users causing high impact on availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33001|2024-07-30T17:29:13.906Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22132|2024-08-01T17:30:59.546Z -- sap_se -- sap%20ides%20systems</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22132</link>
      <description>SAP IDES ECC-systems contain code that permits the execution of arbitrary program code of user's choice.An attacker can therefore control the behaviour of the system by executing malicious code which can potentially escalate privileges with low impact on confidentiality, integrity and availability of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22132|2024-08-01T17:30:59.546Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:33:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22126|2024-08-01T22:35:34.804Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20java%20%28user%20admin%20application%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22126</link>
      <description>The User Admin application of SAP NetWeaver AS for Java - version 7.50, insufficiently validates and improperly encodes the incoming URL parameters before including them into the redirect URL. This results in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability, leading to a high impact on confidentiality and mild impact on integrity and availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22126|2024-08-01T22:35:34.804Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 01:58:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22127|2024-08-01T22:35:34.821Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20java%20%28administrator%20log%20viewer%20plug-in%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22127</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver Administrator AS Java (Administrator Log Viewer plug-in) - version 7.50, allows an attacker with high privileges to upload potentially dangerous files which leads to command injection vulnerability. This would enable the attacker to run commands which can cause high impact on confidentiality, integrity and availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22127|2024-08-01T22:35:34.821Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:29:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22132|2024-08-01T22:35:34.859Z -- sap_se -- sap%20ides%20systems</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22132</link>
      <description>SAP IDES ECC-systems contain code that permits the execution of arbitrary program code of user's choice.An attacker can therefore control the behaviour of the system by executing malicious code which can potentially escalate privileges with low impact on confidentiality, integrity and availability of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22132|2024-08-01T22:35:34.859Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:33:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22133|2024-08-01T22:35:34.933Z -- sap_se -- sap%20fiori%20front%20end%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22133</link>
      <description>SAP Fiori Front End Server - version 605, allows altering of approver details on the read-only field when sending leave request information. This could lead to creation of request with incorrect approver causing low impact on Confidentiality and Integrity with no impact on Availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22133|2024-08-01T22:35:34.933Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:32:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22130|2024-08-01T22:35:34.802Z -- sap_se -- sap%20crm%20webclient%20ui</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22130</link>
      <description>Print preview option in SAP CRM WebClient UI - versions S4FND 102, S4FND 103, S4FND 104, S4FND 105, S4FND 106, S4FND 107, S4FND 108, WEBCUIF 700, WEBCUIF 701, WEBCUIF 730, WEBCUIF 731, WEBCUIF 746, WEBCUIF 747, WEBCUIF 748, WEBCUIF 800, WEBCUIF 801, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability. An attacker with low privileges can cause limited impact to confidentiality and integrity of the appliaction data after successful exploitation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22130|2024-08-01T22:35:34.802Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:29:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22128|2024-08-01T22:35:34.814Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20business%20client%20for%20html</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22128</link>
      <description>SAP NWBC for HTML - versions SAP_UI 754, SAP_UI 755, SAP_UI 756, SAP_UI 757, SAP_UI 758, SAP_BASIS 700, SAP_BASIS 701, SAP_BASIS 702, SAP_BASIS 731, does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker can inject malicious javascript to cause limited impact to confidentiality and integrity of the application data after successful exploitation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22128|2024-08-01T22:35:34.814Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:02:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22131|2024-08-01T22:35:34.897Z -- sap_se -- sap%20aba%20%28application%20basis%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22131</link>
      <description>In SAP ABA (Application Basis) - versions 700, 701, 702, 731, 740, 750, 751, 752, 75C, 75I, an attacker authenticated as a user with a remote execution authorization can use a vulnerable interface. This allows the attacker to use the interface to invoke an application function to perform actions which they would not normally be permitted to perform.  Depending on the function executed, the attack can read or modify any user/business data and can make the entire system unavailable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22131|2024-08-01T22:35:34.897Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22129|2024-08-01T22:35:34.889Z -- sap_se -- sap%20companion</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22129</link>
      <description>SAP Companion - version &lt;3.1.38, has a URL with parameter that could be vulnerable to XSS attack. The attacker could send a malicious link to a user that would possibly allow an attacker to retrieve the sensitive information and cause minor impact on the integrity of the web application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22129|2024-08-01T22:35:34.889Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 03:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-33007|2024-08-02T02:27:53.283Z -- sap_se -- sapui5%20%28pdfviewer%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33007</link>
      <description>PDFViewer is a control delivered as part of SAPUI5 product which shows the PDF content in an embedded mode by default. If a PDF document contains embedded JavaScript (or any harmful client-side script), the PDFViewer will execute the JavaScript embedded in the PDF which can cause a potential security threat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33007|2024-08-02T02:27:53.283Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 03:44:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34689|2024-08-02T02:59:22.630Z -- sap_se -- sap%20business%20workflow%20%28webflow%20services%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34689</link>
      <description>WebFlow Services of SAP Business Workflow allows
an authenticated attacker to enumerate accessible HTTP endpoints in the
internal network by specially crafting HTTP requests. On successful
exploitation this can result in information disclosure. It has no impact on
integrity and availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34689|2024-08-02T02:59:22.630Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:18:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34688|2024-08-02T02:59:22.017Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20as%20java</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34688</link>
      <description>Due to unrestricted access to the Meta Model
Repository services in SAP NetWeaver AS Java, attackers can perform DoS attacks
on the application, which may prevent legitimate users from accessing it. This
can result in no impact on confidentiality and integrity but a high impact on
the availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34688|2024-08-02T02:59:22.017Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34685|2024-08-02T02:59:21.683Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20knowledge%20management%20xmleditor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34685</link>
      <description>Due to weak encoding of user-controlled input in
SAP NetWeaver Knowledge Management XMLEditor which allows malicious scripts can
be executed in the application, potentially leading to a Cross-Site Scripting
(XSS) vulnerability. This has no impact on the availability of the application
but it has a low impact on its confidentiality and integrity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34685|2024-08-02T02:59:21.683Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 03:53:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-33008|2024-08-02T02:27:53.435Z -- sap_se -- sap%20replication%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33008</link>
      <description>SAP Replication Server allows an attacker to use gateway for executing some commands to RSSD. This could result in crashing the Replication Server due to memory corruption with high impact on Availability of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33008|2024-08-02T02:27:53.435Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 03:46:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34683|2024-08-02T02:59:22.208Z -- sap_se -- sap%20document%20builder</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34683</link>
      <description>An authenticated attacker can upload malicious
file to SAP Document Builder service. When the victim accesses this file, the
attacker is allowed to access, modify, or make the related information
unavailable in the victim’s browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34683|2024-08-02T02:59:22.208Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34684|2024-08-02T02:59:21.825Z -- sap_se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34684</link>
      <description>On Unix, SAP BusinessObjects Business
Intelligence Platform (Scheduling) allows an authenticated attacker with
administrator access on the local server to access the password of a local
account. As a result, an attacker can obtain non-administrative user
credentials, which will allow them to read or modify the remote server files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34684|2024-08-02T02:59:21.825Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:20:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-33000|2024-08-02T02:27:53.212Z -- sap_se -- sap%20bank%20account%20management</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33000</link>
      <description>SAP Bank Account Management does not perform necessary authorization check for an authorized user, resulting in escalation of privileges. As a result, it has a low impact to confidentiality to the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33000|2024-08-02T02:27:53.212Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 03:46:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-33001|2024-08-02T02:27:53.403Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20and%20abap%20platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33001</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver and ABAP platform allows an
attacker to impede performance for legitimate users by crashing or flooding the
service.



An
impact of this Denial of Service vulnerability might be long response delays
and service interruptions, thus degrading the service quality experienced by
legitimate users causing high impact on availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33001|2024-08-02T02:27:53.403Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32731|2024-08-02T02:20:35.313Z -- sap_se -- sap%20my%20travel%20requests</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32731</link>
      <description>SAP My Travel Requests does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. On successful exploitation, the attacker can upload a malicious attachment to a business trip request which will lead to a low impact on the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32731|2024-08-02T02:20:35.313Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 03:07:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34686|2024-08-02T02:59:22.207Z -- sap_se -- sap%20crm%20webclient%20ui</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34686</link>
      <description>Due to insufficient input validation, SAP CRM
WebClient UI allows an unauthenticated attacker to craft a URL link which
embeds a malicious script. When a victim clicks on this link, the script will
be executed in the victim's browser giving the attacker the ability to access
and/or modify information with no effect on availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34686|2024-08-02T02:59:22.207Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:11:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-33009|2024-08-02T02:27:53.583Z -- sap_se -- sap%20global%20label%20management%20%28glm%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33009</link>
      <description>SAP Global Label Management is vulnerable to SQL injection. On exploitation the attacker can use specially crafted inputs to modify database commands resulting in the retrieval of additional information persisted by the system. This could lead to low impact on Confidentiality and Integrity of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33009|2024-08-02T02:27:53.583Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 03:58:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32733|2024-08-02T02:20:35.550Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20application%20server%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32733</link>
      <description>Due to missing input validation and output encoding of untrusted data, SAP NetWeaver Application Server ABAP and ABAP Platform allows an unauthenticated attacker to inject malicious JavaScript code into the dynamically crafted web page. On successful exploitation the attacker can access or modify sensitive information with no impact on availability of the application</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32733|2024-08-02T02:20:35.550Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 03:38:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34691|2024-08-02T02:59:22.219Z -- sap_se -- sap%20s%2F4hana%20%28manage%20incoming%20payment%20files%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34691</link>
      <description>Manage Incoming Payment Files (F1680) of SAP
S/4HANA does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated
user, resulting in escalation of privileges. As a result, it has high impact on
integrity and no impact on the confidentiality and availability of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34691|2024-08-02T02:59:22.219Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:22:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32730|2024-08-02T02:20:34.695Z -- sap_se -- sap%20enable%20now</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32730</link>
      <description>SAP Enable Now Manager does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. On successful exploitation, the attacker with the role 'Learner' could gain access to other user's data in manager which will lead to a high impact to the confidentiality of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32730|2024-08-02T02:20:34.695Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 16:06:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-33002|2024-08-02T02:27:53.478Z -- sap_se -- sap%20s%2F4hana%20%28document%20service%20handler%20for%20dps%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33002</link>
      <description>Document Service handler (obsolete) in Data Provisioning Service does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability with low impact on Confidentiality and Integrity of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33002|2024-08-02T02:27:53.478Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 03:49:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34687|2024-08-02T02:59:22.228Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20application%20server%20for%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34687</link>
      <description>SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP and ABAP Platform do not sufficiently encode user controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability.
An attacker can control code that is executed within a user’s browser, which could result in modification, deletion of data, including accessing or deleting files, or stealing session cookies which an attacker could use to hijack a user’s session. Hence, this could have impact on Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34687|2024-08-02T02:59:22.228Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 03:56:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34692|2024-08-02T02:59:22.200Z -- sap_se -- sap%20enable%20now</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34692</link>
      <description>Due to missing verification of file type or
content, SAP Enable Now allows an authenticated attacker to upload arbitrary
files. These files include executables which might be downloaded and executed
by the user which could host malware. On successful exploitation an attacker
can cause limited impact on confidentiality and Integrity of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34692|2024-08-02T02:59:22.200Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:43:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34690|2024-08-02T02:59:21.880Z -- sap_se -- sap%20student%20life%20cycle%20management</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34690</link>
      <description>SAP Student Life Cycle
Management (SLcM) fails to conduct proper authorization checks for
authenticated users, leading to the potential escalation of privileges. On
successful exploitation it could allow an attacker to access and edit
non-sensitive report variants that are typically restricted, causing minimal
impact on the confidentiality and integrity of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34690|2024-08-02T02:59:21.880Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-33004|2024-08-02T02:27:53.306Z -- sap_se -- sap%20businessobjects%20business%20intelligence%20platform%20%28webservices%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33004</link>
      <description>SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform is vulnerable to Insecure Storage as dynamic web pages are getting cached even after logging out. On successful exploitation, the attacker can see the sensitive information through cache and can open the pages causing limited impact on Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33004|2024-08-02T02:27:53.306Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 04:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-33006|2024-08-02T02:27:53.232Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20application%20server%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33006</link>
      <description>An unauthenticated attacker can upload a malicious file to the server which when accessed by a victim can allow an attacker to completely compromise system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-33006|2024-08-02T02:27:53.232Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 04:16:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39599|2024-08-02T04:26:16.192Z -- sap_se -- sap%20netweaver%20application%20server%20for%20abap%20and%20abap%20platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39599</link>
      <description>Due to a Protection Mechanism Failure in SAP
NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP and ABAP Platform, a developer can bypass
the configured malware scanner API because of a programming error. This leads
to a low impact on the application's confidentiality, integrity, and
availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39599|2024-08-02T04:26:16.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:24:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39592|2024-08-02T04:26:15.969Z -- sap_se -- sap%20pdce</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39592</link>
      <description>Elements of PDCE does not perform necessary
authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of
privileges.



This
allows an attacker to read sensitive information causing high impact on the
confidentiality of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39592|2024-08-02T04:26:15.969Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 03:45:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39600|2024-08-02T04:26:16.037Z -- sap_se -- sap%20gui%20for%20windows</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39600</link>
      <description>Under certain conditions, the memory of SAP GUI
for Windows contains the password used to log on to an SAP system, which might
allow an attacker to get hold of the password and impersonate the affected
user. As a result, it has a high impact on the confidentiality but there is no
impact on the integrity and availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39600|2024-08-02T04:26:16.037Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:19:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39595|2024-08-02T04:26:16.023Z -- sap_se -- sap%20business%20warehouse%20-%20business%20planning%20and%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39595</link>
      <description>SAP Business Warehouse - Business Planning and
Simulation application does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs,
resulting in Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. This
vulnerability allows users to modify website content and on successful
exploitation, an attacker can cause low impact to the confidentiality and
integrity of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39595|2024-08-02T04:26:16.023Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39594|2024-08-02T04:26:16.083Z -- sap_se -- sap%20business%20warehouse%20-%20business%20planning%20and%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39594</link>
      <description>SAP Business Warehouse - Business Planning and
Simulation application does not sufficiently encode user controlled inputs,
resulting in Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. After
successful exploitation, an attacker can cause low impact on the confidentiality
and integrity of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39594|2024-08-02T04:26:16.083Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39598|2024-08-02T04:26:15.953Z -- sap_se -- sap%20crm%20webclient%20ui</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39598</link>
      <description>SAP CRM (WebClient UI Framework) allows an
authenticated attacker to enumerate accessible HTTP endpoints in the internal
network by specially crafting HTTP requests. On successful exploitation this
can result in information disclosure. It has no impact on integrity and
availability of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39598|2024-08-02T04:26:15.953Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:04:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39597|2024-08-02T04:26:15.985Z -- sap_se -- sap%20commerce</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39597</link>
      <description>In SAP Commerce, a user can misuse the forgotten
password functionality to gain access to a Composable Storefront B2B site for
which early login and registration is activated, without requiring the merchant
to approve the account beforehand. If the site is not configured as isolated
site, this can also grant access to other non-isolated early login sites, even
if registration is not enabled for those other sites.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39597|2024-08-02T04:26:15.985Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 03:48:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39593|2024-08-02T04:26:15.997Z -- sap_se -- sap%20landscape%20management</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39593</link>
      <description>SAP Landscape Management allows an authenticated
user to read confidential data disclosed by the REST Provider Definition
response. Successful exploitation can cause high impact on confidentiality of
the managed entities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39593|2024-08-02T04:26:15.997Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 03:51:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39596|2024-08-02T04:26:16.017Z -- sap_se -- sap%20enable%20now</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39596</link>
      <description>Due to missing authorization checks, SAP Enable
Now allows an author to escalate privileges to access information which should
otherwise be restricted. On successful exploitation, the attacker can cause
limited impact on confidentiality of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39596|2024-08-02T04:26:16.017Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
