<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for formtools.org -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/formtools.org/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for formtools.org -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 12:25:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6937|2024-07-22T11:26:09.857Z -- formtools.org -- form%20tools
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6937</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in formtools.org Form Tools 3.1.1. Affected is the function curl_exec of the file /admin/forms/option_lists/edit.php of the component Import Option List. The manipulation of the argument url leads to file inclusion. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-271992. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in formtools.org Form Tools 3.1.1 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um die Funktion curl_exec der Datei /admin/forms/option_lists/edit.php der Komponente Import Option List. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments url mit unbekannten Daten kann eine file inclusion-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6937|2024-07-22T11:26:09.857Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 04:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6935|2024-07-21T02:00:05.241Z -- formtools.org -- form%20tools</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6935</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in formtools.org Form Tools 3.1.1. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/clients/ of the component User Settings Page. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-271990 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In formtools.org Form Tools 3.1.1 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei /admin/clients/ der Komponente User Settings Page. Durch Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6935|2024-07-21T02:00:05.241Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 02:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6934|2024-07-21T01:31:03.697Z -- formtools.org -- form%20tools</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6934</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in formtools.org Form Tools 3.1.1. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/forms/add/step2.php?submission_type=direct. The manipulation of the argument Form URL leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-271989 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in formtools.org Form Tools 3.1.1 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei /admin/forms/add/step2.php?submission_type=direct. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments Form URL mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6934|2024-07-21T01:31:03.697Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 01:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6936|2024-07-21T03:31:03.662Z -- formtools.org -- form%20tools</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6936</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in formtools.org Form Tools 3.1.1. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/settings/index.php?page=accounts of the component Setting Handler. The manipulation of the argument Page Theme leads to code injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-271991. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in formtools.org Form Tools 3.1.1 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei /admin/settings/index.php?page=accounts der Komponente Setting Handler. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments Page Theme mit unbekannten Daten kann eine code injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6936|2024-07-21T03:31:03.662Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 03:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6937|2024-07-21T04:00:06.431Z -- formtools.org -- form%20tools</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6937</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in formtools.org Form Tools 3.1.1. Affected is the function curl_exec of the file /admin/forms/option_lists/edit.php of the component Import Option List. The manipulation of the argument url leads to file inclusion. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-271992. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in formtools.org Form Tools 3.1.1 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um die Funktion curl_exec der Datei /admin/forms/option_lists/edit.php der Komponente Import Option List. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments url mit unbekannten Daten kann eine file inclusion-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6937|2024-07-21T04:00:06.431Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 04:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
