<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for CESNET -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cesnet/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for CESNET -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:19:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-15014|2024-08-06T03:47:34.921Z -- cesnet -- theme-cesnet
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-15014</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in CESNET theme-cesnet up to 1.x on ownCloud and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file cesnet/core/lostpassword/templates/resetpassword.php. The manipulation leads to insufficiently protected credentials. Attacking locally is a requirement. Upgrading to version 2.0.0 is able to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is 2b857f2233ce5083b4d5bc9bfc4152f933c3e4a6. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-217633 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In CESNET theme-cesnet bis 1.x für ownCloud wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei cesnet/core/lostpassword/templates/resetpassword.php. Durch das Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine insufficiently protected credentials-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff muss lokal angegangen werden. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 2.0.0 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als 2b857f2233ce5083b4d5bc9bfc4152f933c3e4a6 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-15014|2024-08-06T03:47:34.921Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 19:42:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
