<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for symfony -- symfony</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/symfony/symfony.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for symfony -- symfony</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 22:22:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-46735|2024-09-03T15:24:36.945Z -- symfony -- symfony
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46735</link>
      <description>Symfony is a PHP framework for web and console applications and a set of reusable PHP components. Starting in version 6.0.0 and prior to version 6.3.8, the error message in `WebhookController` returns unescaped user-submitted input. As of version 6.3.8, `WebhookController` now doesn't return any user-submitted input in its response.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-46735|2024-09-03T15:24:36.945Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 17:58:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-46734|2024-09-03T15:36:18.165Z -- symfony -- symfony
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46734</link>
      <description>Symfony is a PHP framework for web and console applications and a set of reusable PHP components. Starting in versions 2.0.0, 5.0.0, and 6.0.0 and prior to versions 4.4.51, 5.4.31, and 6.3.8, some Twig filters in CodeExtension use `is_safe=html` but don't actually ensure their input is safe. As of versions 4.4.51, 5.4.31, and 6.3.8, Symfony now escapes the output of the affected filters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-46734|2024-09-03T15:36:18.165Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 17:49:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-46733|2024-09-03T15:36:38.571Z -- symfony -- symfony
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46733</link>
      <description>Symfony is a PHP framework for web and console applications and a set of reusable PHP components. Starting in versions 5.4.21 and 6.2.7 and prior to versions 5.4.31 and 6.3.8, `SessionStrategyListener` does not migrate the session after every successful login. It does so only in case the logged in user changes by means of checking the user identifier. In some use cases, the user identifier doesn't change between the verification phase and the successful login, while the token itself changes from one type (partially-authenticated) to another (fully-authenticated). When this happens, the session id should be regenerated to prevent possible session fixations, which is not the case at the moment. As of versions 5.4.31 and 6.3.8, Symfony now checks the type of the token in addition to the user identifier before deciding whether the session id should be regenerated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-46733|2024-09-03T15:36:38.571Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 17:09:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
