<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for timstrifler -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/timstrifler/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for timstrifler -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 22:21:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4618|2024-06-06T19:50:45.214Z -- timstrifler -- exclusive%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4618</link>
      <description>The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Team Member widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.9.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied 'url' attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4618|2024-06-06T19:50:45.214Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 01:56:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2503|2024-05-02T16:51:54.571Z -- timstrifler -- exclusive%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2503</link>
      <description>The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Post Grid Widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.9.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied tags. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. CVE-2024-32557 is likely a duplicate of this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2503|2024-05-02T16:51:54.571Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:51:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
