<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for timstrifler -- Exclusive Addons for Elementor</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/timstrifler/exclusive%20addons%20for%20elementor.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for timstrifler -- Exclusive Addons for Elementor</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 15:22:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1414|2024-06-24T14:54:12.187Z -- timstrifler -- exclusive%20addons%20for%20elementor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1414</link>
      <description>The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Call To Action widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1414|2024-06-24T14:54:12.187Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:26:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1234|2024-06-24T14:57:58.854Z -- timstrifler -- exclusive%20addons%20for%20elementor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1234</link>
      <description>The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via data attribute in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1234|2024-06-24T14:57:58.854Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:26:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2028|2024-06-24T14:49:51.437Z -- timstrifler -- exclusive%20addons%20for%20elementor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2028</link>
      <description>The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Covid-19 Stats Widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2028|2024-06-24T14:49:51.437Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:27:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1413|2024-06-04T18:01:34.818Z -- timstrifler -- exclusive%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1413</link>
      <description>The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Countdown Timer widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1413|2024-06-04T18:01:34.818Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:27:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1234|2024-03-13T15:26:35.418Z -- timstrifler -- exclusive%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1234</link>
      <description>The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via data attribute in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1234|2024-03-13T15:26:35.418Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:26:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1414|2024-03-13T15:26:55.395Z -- timstrifler -- exclusive%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1414</link>
      <description>The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Call To Action widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1414|2024-03-13T15:26:55.395Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:26:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0824|2024-01-27T04:31:30.268Z -- timstrifler -- exclusive%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0824</link>
      <description>The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Link Anything functionality in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0824|2024-01-27T04:31:30.268Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 04:31:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0823|2024-02-05T21:21:38.824Z -- timstrifler -- exclusive%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0823</link>
      <description>The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'Link To' url in carousels in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0823|2024-02-05T21:21:38.824Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:21:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4618|2024-06-06T19:50:45.214Z -- timstrifler -- exclusive%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4618</link>
      <description>The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Team Member widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.9.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied 'url' attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4618|2024-06-06T19:50:45.214Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 01:56:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3985|2024-05-02T16:51:52.006Z -- timstrifler -- exclusive%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3985</link>
      <description>The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Call to Action widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.9.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3985|2024-05-02T16:51:52.006Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:51:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3489|2024-06-04T17:31:35.106Z -- timstrifler -- exclusive%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3489</link>
      <description>The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the Countdown Expired Title in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.9.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3489|2024-06-04T17:31:35.106Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2751|2024-05-02T16:52:49.617Z -- timstrifler -- exclusive%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2751</link>
      <description>The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘exad_infobox_animating_mask_style’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.9.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2751|2024-05-02T16:52:49.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2028|2024-03-13T15:27:17.490Z -- timstrifler -- exclusive%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2028</link>
      <description>The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Covid-19 Stats Widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2028|2024-03-13T15:27:17.490Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:27:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2750|2024-06-04T17:30:31.005Z -- timstrifler -- exclusive%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2750</link>
      <description>The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the URL attribute of the Button widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.9.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2750|2024-06-04T17:30:31.005Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:51:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2503|2024-06-04T17:29:50.780Z -- timstrifler -- exclusive%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2503</link>
      <description>The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Post Grid Widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.9.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied tags. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. CVE-2024-32557 is likely a duplicate of this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2503|2024-06-04T17:29:50.780Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:51:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2751|2024-06-18T15:28:41.829Z -- timstrifler -- exclusive%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2751</link>
      <description>The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘exad_infobox_animating_mask_style’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.9.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2751|2024-06-18T15:28:41.829Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
