<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for metabase -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/metabase/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for metabase -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 14:22:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39359|2024-08-03T12:00:44.147Z -- metabase -- metabase
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39359</link>
      <description>Metabase is data visualization software. Prior to versions 0.44.5, 1.44.5, 0.43.7, 1.43.7, 0.42.6, 1.42.6, 0.41.9, and 1.41.9, custom GeoJSON map URL address would follow redirects to addresses that were otherwise disallowed, like link-local or private-network. This issue is patched in versions 0.44.5, 1.44.5, 0.43.7, 1.43.7, 0.42.6, 1.42.6, 0.41.9, and 1.41.9. Metabase no longer follow redirects on GeoJSON map URLs. An environment variable `MB_CUSTOM_GEOJSON_ENABLED` was also added to disable custom GeoJSON completely (`true` by default).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39359|2024-08-03T12:00:44.147Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39361|2024-08-03T12:00:44.174Z -- metabase -- metabase
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39361</link>
      <description>Metabase is data visualization software. Prior to versions 0.44.5, 1.44.5, 0.43.7, 1.43.7, 0.42.6, 1.42.6, 0.41.9, and 1.41.9, H2 (Sample Database) could allow Remote Code Execution (RCE), which can be abused by users able to write SQL queries on H2 databases. This issue is patched in versions 0.44.5, 1.44.5, 0.43.7, 1.43.7, 0.42.6, 1.42.6, 0.41.9, and 1.41.9. Metabase no longer allows DDL statements in H2 native queries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39361|2024-08-03T12:00:44.174Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24855|2024-08-03T04:20:50.503Z -- metabase -- metabase
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24855</link>
      <description>Metabase is an open source business intelligence and analytics application. In affected versions Metabase ships with an internal development endpoint `/_internal` that can allow for cross site scripting (XSS) attacks, potentially leading to phishing attempts with malicious links that could lead to account takeover. Users are advised to either upgrade immediately, or block access in your firewall to `/_internal` endpoints for Metabase. The following patches (or greater versions) are available: 0.42.4 and 1.42.4, 0.41.7 and 1.41.7, 0.40.8 and 1.40.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24855|2024-08-03T04:20:50.503Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 21:35:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39360|2024-08-03T12:00:44.174Z -- metabase -- metabase
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39360</link>
      <description>Metabase is data visualization software. Prior to versions 0.44.5, 1.44.5, 0.43.7, 1.43.7, 0.42.6, 1.42.6, 0.41.9, and 1.41.9 single sign on (SSO) users were able to do password resets on Metabase, which could allow a user access without going through the SSO IdP. This issue is patched in versions 0.44.5, 1.44.5, 0.43.7, 1.43.7, 0.42.6, 1.42.6, 0.41.9, and 1.41.9. Metabase now blocks password reset for all users who use SSO for their Metabase login.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39360|2024-08-03T12:00:44.174Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24854|2024-08-03T04:20:50.469Z -- metabase -- metabase
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24854</link>
      <description>Metabase is an open source business intelligence and analytics application. SQLite has an FDW-like feature called `ATTACH DATABASE`, which allows connecting multiple SQLite databases via the initial connection. If the attacker has SQL permissions to at least one SQLite database, then it can attach this database to a second database, and then it can query across all the tables. To be able to do that the attacker also needs to know the file path to the second database. Users are advised to upgrade as soon as possible. If you're unable to upgrade, you can modify your SQLIte connection strings to contain the url argument `?limit_attached=0`, which will disallow making connections to other SQLite databases. Only users making use of SQLite are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24854|2024-08-03T04:20:50.469Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 21:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39358|2024-08-03T12:00:44.120Z -- metabase -- metabase
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39358</link>
      <description>Metabase is data visualization software. Prior to versions 0.44.5, 1.44.5, 0.43.7, 1.43.7, 0.42.6, and 1.42.6, it was possible to circumvent locked parameters when requesting data for a question in an embedded dashboard by constructing a malicious request to the backend. This issue is patched in versions 0.44.5, 1.44.5, 0.43.7, 1.43.7, 0.42.6, and 1.42.6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39358|2024-08-03T12:00:44.120Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24853|2024-08-03T04:20:50.543Z -- metabase -- metabase
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24853</link>
      <description>Metabase is an open source business intelligence and analytics application. Metabase has a proxy to load arbitrary URLs for JSON maps as part of our GeoJSON support. While we do validation to not return contents of arbitrary URLs, there is a case where a particularly crafted request could result in file access on windows, which allows enabling an `NTLM relay attack`, potentially allowing an attacker to receive the system password hash. If you use Windows and are on this version of Metabase, please upgrade immediately. The following patches (or greater versions) are available: 0.42.4 and 1.42.4, 0.41.7 and 1.41.7, 0.40.8 and 1.40.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24853|2024-08-03T04:20:50.543Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 21:45:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39362|2024-08-03T12:00:44.081Z -- metabase -- metabase
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39362</link>
      <description>Metabase is data visualization software. Prior to versions 0.44.5, 1.44.5, 0.43.7, 1.43.7, 0.42.6, 1.42.6, 0.41.9, and 1.41.9, unsaved SQL queries are auto-executed, which could pose a possible attack vector. This issue is patched in versions 0.44.5, 1.44.5, 0.43.7, 1.43.7, 0.42.6, 1.42.6, 0.41.9, and 1.41.9. Metabase no longer automatically executes ad-hoc native queries. Now the native editor shows the query and gives the user the option to manually run the query if they want.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39362|2024-08-03T12:00:44.081Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
