<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Byzoro -- Smart S80</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/byzoro/smart%20s80.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Byzoro -- Smart S80</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 18:25:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6274|2024-08-02T08:28:20.357Z -- byzoro -- smart%20s80
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6274</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Byzoro Smart S80 up to 20231108. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /sysmanage/updatelib.php of the component PHP File Handler. The manipulation of the argument file_upload leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-246103. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Byzoro Smart S80 bis 20231108 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei /sysmanage/updatelib.php der Komponente PHP File Handler. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments file_upload mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6274|2024-08-02T08:28:20.357Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 14:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3346|2024-08-01T20:05:08.498Z -- byzoro -- smart%20s80</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3346</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Byzoro Smart S80 up to 20240328. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /log/webmailattach.php. The manipulation of the argument mail_file_path leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259450 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Byzoro Smart S80 bis 20240328 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei /log/webmailattach.php. Durch Manipulation des Arguments mail_file_path mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3346|2024-08-01T20:05:08.498Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 15:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3346|2024-06-04T17:32:30.398Z -- byzoro -- smart%20s80</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3346</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Byzoro Smart S80 up to 20240328. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /log/webmailattach.php. The manipulation of the argument mail_file_path leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259450 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Byzoro Smart S80 bis 20240328 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei /log/webmailattach.php. Durch Manipulation des Arguments mail_file_path mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3346|2024-06-04T17:32:30.398Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 15:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
