<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Byzoro -- Smart S85F Management Platform</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/byzoro/smart%20s85f%20management%20platform.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Byzoro -- Smart S85F Management Platform</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5683|2024-04-09T08:34:38.781Z -- byzoro -- smart%20s85f%20management%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5683</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Byzoro Smart S85F Management Platform up to 20231010 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /sysmanage/importconf.php. The manipulation of the argument btn_file_renew leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-243059. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Byzoro Smart S85F Management Platform bis 20231010 gefunden. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei /sysmanage/importconf.php. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments btn_file_renew mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5683|2024-04-09T08:34:38.781Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 05:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5959|2024-04-09T08:34:24.035Z -- byzoro -- smart%20s85f%20management%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5959</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Byzoro Smart S85F Management Platform V31R02B10-01. Affected is an unknown function of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument txt_newpwd leads to weak password recovery. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-244992. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Byzoro Smart S85F Management Platform V31R02B10-01 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei /login.php. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments txt_newpwd mit unbekannten Daten kann eine weak password recovery-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5959|2024-04-09T08:34:24.035Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 09:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5684|2024-04-09T08:34:22.707Z -- byzoro -- smart%20s85f%20management%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5684</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Byzoro Smart S85F Management Platform up to 20231012. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /importexport.php. The manipulation leads to os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-243061 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Byzoro Smart S85F Management Platform bis 20231012 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei /importexport.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine os command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5684|2024-04-09T08:34:22.707Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 07:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4544|2024-04-09T08:34:28.248Z -- byzoro -- smart%20s85f%20management%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4544</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Byzoro Smart S85F Management Platform up to 20230809. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /config/php.ini. The manipulation leads to direct request. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-238049 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Byzoro Smart S85F Management Platform bis 20230809 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei /config/php.ini. Durch das Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine direct request-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4544|2024-04-09T08:34:28.248Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 05:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4739|2024-04-09T08:34:36.222Z -- byzoro -- smart%20s85f%20management%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4739</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Byzoro Smart S85F Management Platform up to 20230820. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /sysmanage/updateos.php. The manipulation of the argument 1_file_upload leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-238628. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Byzoro Smart S85F Management Platform bis 20230820 entdeckt. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei /sysmanage/updateos.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments 1_file_upload mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4739|2024-04-09T08:34:36.222Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 19:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4546|2024-04-09T08:34:13.211Z -- byzoro -- smart%20s85f%20management%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4546</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Byzoro Smart S85F Management Platform up to 20230816. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /sysmanage/licence.php. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-238057 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In Byzoro Smart S85F Management Platform bis 20230816 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei /sysmanage/licence.php. Mittels Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine improper access controls-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4546|2024-04-09T08:34:13.211Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 07:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4120|2024-04-09T08:34:41.336Z -- byzoro -- smart%20s85f%20management%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4120</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Byzoro Smart S85F Management Platform up to 20230722 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file importhtml.php. The manipulation of the argument sql leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-235967. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Byzoro Smart S85F Management Platform bis 20230722 gefunden. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei importhtml.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments sql mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4120|2024-04-09T08:34:41.336Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 09:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4121|2024-04-09T08:34:18.604Z -- byzoro -- smart%20s85f%20management%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4121</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Byzoro Smart S85F Management Platform up to 20230722. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function. The manipulation of the argument file_upload leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-235968. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Byzoro Smart S85F Management Platform bis 20230722 ausgemacht. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments file_upload mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4121|2024-04-09T08:34:18.604Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 09:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4414|2024-04-09T08:34:40.086Z -- byzoro -- smart%20s85f%20management%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4414</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Byzoro Smart S85F Management Platform up to 20230807. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /log/decodmail.php. The manipulation of the argument file leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-237517 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Byzoro Smart S85F Management Platform bis 20230807 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei /log/decodmail.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments file mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4414|2024-04-09T08:34:40.086Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 16:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
