<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Hitachi Energy -- TXpert Hub CoreTec 4 version</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/hitachi%20energy/txpert%20hub%20coretec%204%20version.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Hitachi Energy -- TXpert Hub CoreTec 4 version</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 13:23:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35530|2024-08-04T00:40:46.698Z -- hitachi%20energy -- txpert%20hub%20coretec%204%20version
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35530</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the application authentication and authorization mechanism in Hitachi Energy's TXpert Hub CoreTec 4, that depends on a token validation of the session identifier, allows an unauthorized modified message to be executed in the server enabling an unauthorized actor to change an existing user password, and further gain authorized access into the system via login mechanism. This issue affects: Hitachi Energy TXpert Hub CoreTec 4 version 2.0.0 2.1.0; 2.1.0; 2.1.1; 2.1.2; 2.1.3; 2.2.0; 2.2.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35530|2024-08-04T00:40:46.698Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35531|2024-08-04T00:40:46.422Z -- hitachi%20energy -- txpert%20hub%20coretec%204%20version
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35531</link>
      <description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in a particular configuration setting field of Hitachi Energy TXpert Hub CoreTec 4 product, allows an attacker with access to an authorized user with ADMIN or ENGINEER role rights to inject an OS command that is executed by the system. This issue affects: Hitachi Energy TXpert Hub CoreTec 4 version 2.0.0; 2.0.1; 2.1.0; 2.1.1; 2.1.2; 2.1.3; 2.2.0; 2.2.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35531|2024-08-04T00:40:46.422Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35532|2024-08-04T00:40:46.763Z -- hitachi%20energy -- txpert%20hub%20coretec%204%20version
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35532</link>
      <description>A vulnerability exists in the file upload validation part of Hitachi Energy TXpert Hub CoreTec 4 product. The vulnerability allows an attacker or malicious agent who manages to gain access to the system and obtain an account with sufficient privilege to upload a malicious firmware to the product. This issue affects: Hitachi Energy TXpert Hub CoreTec 4 version 2.0.0; 2.0.1; 2.1.0; 2.1.1; 2.1.2; 2.1.3; 2.2.0; 2.2.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35532|2024-08-04T00:40:46.763Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
