<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for rizinorg -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/rizinorg/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for rizinorg -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 18:24:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36043|2024-08-03T09:52:00.507Z -- rizinorg -- rizin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36043</link>
      <description>Rizin is a UNIX-like reverse engineering framework and command-line toolset. Versions 0.4.0 and prior are vulnerable to a double free in bobj.c:rz_bin_reloc_storage_free() when freeing relocations generated from qnx binary plugin. A user opening a malicious qnx binary could be affected by this vulnerability, allowing an attacker to execute code on the user's machine. Commit number a3d50c1ea185f3f642f2d8180715f82d98840784 contains a patch for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36043|2024-08-03T09:52:00.507Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36042|2024-08-03T09:52:00.511Z -- rizinorg -- rizin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36042</link>
      <description>Rizin is a UNIX-like reverse engineering framework and command-line toolset. Versions 0.4.0 and prior are vulnerable to an out-of-bounds write when getting data from dyld cache files. A user opening a malicious dyld cache file could be affected by this vulnerability, allowing an attacker to execute code on the user's machine. Commit number 556ca2f9eef01ec0f4a76d1fbacfcf3a87a44810 contains a patch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36042|2024-08-03T09:52:00.511Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36041|2024-08-03T09:52:00.654Z -- rizinorg -- rizin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36041</link>
      <description>Rizin is a UNIX-like reverse engineering framework and command-line toolset. Versions 0.4.0 and prior are vulnerable to an out-of-bounds write when parsing Mach-O files. A user opening a malicious Mach-O file could be affected by this vulnerability, allowing an attacker to execute code on the user's machine. Commit number 7323e64d68ecccfb0ed3ee480f704384c38676b2 contains a patch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36041|2024-08-03T09:52:00.654Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36044|2024-08-03T09:52:00.490Z -- rizinorg -- rizin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36044</link>
      <description>Rizin is a UNIX-like reverse engineering framework and command-line toolset. Versions 0.4.0 and prior are vulnerable to an out-of-bounds write when getting data from Luac files. A user opening a malicious Luac file could be affected by this vulnerability, allowing an attacker to execute code on the user's machine. Commits 07b43bc8aa1ffebd9b68d60624c9610cf7e460c7 and 05bbd147caccc60162d6fba9baaaf24befa281cd contain fixes for the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36044|2024-08-03T09:52:00.490Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36040|2024-08-03T09:51:59.995Z -- rizinorg -- rizin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36040</link>
      <description>Rizin is a UNIX-like reverse engineering framework and command-line toolset. Versions 0.4.0 and prior are vulnerable to an out-of-bounds write when getting data from PYC(python) files. A user opening a malicious PYC file could be affected by this vulnerability, allowing an attacker to execute code on the user's machine. Commit number 68948017423a12786704e54227b8b2f918c2fd27 contains a patch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36040|2024-08-03T09:51:59.995Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36039|2024-08-03T09:52:00.495Z -- rizinorg -- rizin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36039</link>
      <description>Rizin is a UNIX-like reverse engineering framework and command-line toolset. Versions 0.4.0 and prior are vulnerable to out-of-bounds write when parsing DEX files. A user opening a malicious DEX file could be affected by this vulnerability, allowing an attacker to execute code on the user's machine. A patch is available on the `dev` branch of the repository.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36039|2024-08-03T09:52:00.495Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 19:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
