<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Bestwebsoft -- Relevant Plugin</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/bestwebsoft/relevant%20plugin.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Bestwebsoft -- Relevant Plugin</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 18:24:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-125102|2024-08-06T14:10:56.647Z -- bestwebsoft -- relevant%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125102</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Bestwebsoft Relevant Plugin up to 1.0.7 on WordPress. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Thumbnail Handler. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack can be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 1.0.8 is able to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is 860d1891025548cf0f5f97364c1f51a888f523c3. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-230113 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In Bestwebsoft Relevant Plugin bis 1.0.7 für WordPress wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Komponente Thumbnail Handler. Durch Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine information disclosure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 1.0.8 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als 860d1891025548cf0f5f97364c1f51a888f523c3 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-125102|2024-08-06T14:10:56.647Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 22:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
