<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for BestWebSoft -- Twitter Plugin</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/bestwebsoft/twitter%20plugin.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for BestWebSoft -- Twitter Plugin</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 18:24:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-125103|2024-08-06T14:10:56.764Z -- bestwebsoft -- twitter%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125103</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in BestWebSoft Twitter Plugin up to 1.3.2 on WordPress. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function twttr_settings_page of the file twitter.php. The manipulation of the argument twttr_url_twitter/bws_license_key/bws_license_plugin leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 1.3.7 is able to address this issue. The patch is named e04d59ab578316ffeb204cf32dc71c0d0e1ff77c. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-230155.
In BestWebSoft Twitter Plugin bis 1.3.2 für WordPress wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Es geht um die Funktion twttr_settings_page der Datei twitter.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments twttr_url_twitter/bws_license_key/bws_license_plugin mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 1.3.7 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als e04d59ab578316ffeb204cf32dc71c0d0e1ff77c bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-125103|2024-08-06T14:10:56.764Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 03:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
