<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for BestWebSoft -- Twitter Plugin</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/bestwebsoft/twitter%20plugin.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for BestWebSoft -- Twitter Plugin</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 23:22:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2012-10015|2024-08-06T21:36:02.356Z -- bestwebsoft -- twitter%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10015</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in BestWebSoft Twitter Plugin up to 2.14 on WordPress. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is the function twttr_settings_page of the file twitter.php of the component Settings Page. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 2.15 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as a6d4659cbb2cbf18ccb0fb43549d5113d74e0146. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-230154 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in BestWebSoft Twitter Plugin bis 2.14 für WordPress ausgemacht. Betroffen hiervon ist die Funktion twttr_settings_page der Datei twitter.php der Komponente Settings Page. Dank Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross-site request forgery-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 2.15 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als a6d4659cbb2cbf18ccb0fb43549d5113d74e0146 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2012-10015|2024-08-06T21:36:02.356Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 23:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-125103|2024-08-06T14:10:56.764Z -- bestwebsoft -- twitter%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125103</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in BestWebSoft Twitter Plugin up to 1.3.2 on WordPress. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function twttr_settings_page of the file twitter.php. The manipulation of the argument twttr_url_twitter/bws_license_key/bws_license_plugin leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 1.3.7 is able to address this issue. The patch is named e04d59ab578316ffeb204cf32dc71c0d0e1ff77c. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-230155.
In BestWebSoft Twitter Plugin bis 1.3.2 für WordPress wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Es geht um die Funktion twttr_settings_page der Datei twitter.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments twttr_url_twitter/bws_license_key/bws_license_plugin mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 1.3.7 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als e04d59ab578316ffeb204cf32dc71c0d0e1ff77c bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-125103|2024-08-06T14:10:56.764Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 03:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
