<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for charmbracelet -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/charmbracelet/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for charmbracelet -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 17:29:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43809|2023-10-04T20:40:41.822Z -- charmbracelet -- soft-serve
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43809</link>
      <description>Soft Serve is a self-hostable Git server for the command line. Prior to version 0.6.2, a security vulnerability in Soft Serve could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass public key authentication when keyboard-interactive SSH authentication is active, through the `allow-keyless` setting, and the public key requires additional client-side verification for example using FIDO2 or GPG. This is due to insufficient validation procedures of the public key step during SSH request handshake, granting unauthorized access if the keyboard-interaction mode is utilized. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by presenting manipulated SSH requests using keyboard-interactive authentication mode. This could potentially result in unauthorized access to the Soft Serve. Users should upgrade to the latest Soft Serve version `v0.6.2` to receive the patch for this issue. To workaround this vulnerability without upgrading, users can temporarily disable Keyboard-Interactive SSH Authentication using the `allow-keyless` setting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43809|2023-10-04T20:40:41.822Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 20:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
