<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Recipes -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/recipes/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Recipes -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 21:43:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23073|2024-09-16T17:38:44.584Z -- recipes -- recipes
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23073</link>
      <description>In Recipes, versions 1.0.5 through 1.2.5 are vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS), in copy to clipboard functionality. When a victim accesses the food list page, then adds a new Food with a malicious javascript payload in the ‘Name’ parameter and clicks on the clipboard icon, an XSS payload will trigger. A low privileged attacker will have the victim's API key and can lead to admin's account takeover.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23073|2024-09-16T17:38:44.584Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 08:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23074|2024-09-16T18:55:57.596Z -- recipes -- recipes
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23074</link>
      <description>In Recipes, versions 0.17.0 through 1.2.5 are vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS), in the ‘Name’ field of Keyword, Food and Unit components. When a victim accesses the Keyword/Food/Unit endpoints, the XSS payload will trigger. A low privileged attacker will have the victim's API key and can lead to admin's account takeover.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23074|2024-09-16T18:55:57.596Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 09:20:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23072|2024-09-16T17:57:56.973Z -- recipes -- recipes
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23072</link>
      <description>In Recipes, versions 1.0.5 through 1.2.5 are vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS), in “Add to Cart” functionality. When a victim accesses the food list page, then adds a new Food with a malicious javascript payload in the ‘Name’ parameter and clicks on the Add to Shopping Cart icon, an XSS payload will trigger. A low privileged attacker will have the victim's API key and can lead to admin's account takeover.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23072|2024-09-16T17:57:56.973Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 08:10:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
