<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Arista Networks -- EOS</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/arista%20networks/eos.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Arista Networks -- EOS</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 23:23:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28507|2024-08-03T21:47:32.599Z -- arista%20networks -- eos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28507</link>
      <description>An issue has recently been discovered in Arista EOS where, under certain conditions, the service ACL configured for OpenConfig gNOI and OpenConfig RESTCONF might be bypassed, which results in the denied requests being forwarded to the agent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28507|2024-08-03T21:47:32.599Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28504|2024-08-03T21:47:32.630Z -- arista%20networks -- eos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28504</link>
      <description>On Arista Strata family products which have “TCAM profile” feature enabled when Port IPv4 access-list has a rule which matches on “vxlan” as protocol then that rule and subsequent rules ( rules declared after it in ACL ) do not match on IP protocol field as expected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28504|2024-08-03T21:47:32.630Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 22:17:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28510|2024-08-03T21:47:32.671Z -- arista%20networks -- eos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28510</link>
      <description>For certain systems running EOS, a Precision Time Protocol (PTP) packet of a management/signaling message with an invalid Type-Length-Value (TLV) causes the PTP agent to restart. Repeated restarts of the service will make the service unavailable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28510|2024-08-03T21:47:32.671Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28511|2024-08-03T21:47:31.812Z -- arista%20networks -- eos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28511</link>
      <description>This advisory documents the impact of an internally found vulnerability in Arista EOS for security ACL bypass. The impact of this vulnerability is that the security ACL drop rule might be bypassed if a NAT ACL rule filter with permit action matches the packet flow. This could allow a host with an IP address in a range that matches the range allowed by a NAT ACL and a range denied by a Security ACL to be forwarded incorrectly as it should have been denied by the Security ACL. This can enable an ACL bypass.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28511|2024-08-03T21:47:31.812Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28505|2024-08-03T21:47:32.647Z -- arista%20networks -- eos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28505</link>
      <description>On affected Arista EOS platforms, if a VXLAN match rule exists in an IPv4 access-list that is applied to the ingress of an L2 or an L3 port/SVI, the VXLAN rule and subsequent ACL rules in that access list will ignore the specified IP protocol.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28505|2024-08-03T21:47:32.647Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28506|2024-08-03T21:47:32.674Z -- arista%20networks -- eos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28506</link>
      <description>An issue has recently been discovered in Arista EOS where certain gNOI APIs incorrectly skip authorization and authentication which could potentially allow a factory reset of the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28506|2024-08-03T21:47:32.674Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
