<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for shopware -- platform</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/shopware/platform.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for shopware -- platform</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 14:22:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24748|2024-08-03T04:20:49.934Z -- shopware -- platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24748</link>
      <description>Shopware is an open commerce platform based on the Symfony php Framework and the Vue javascript framework. In versions prior to 6.4.8.2 it is possible to modify customers and to create orders without App Permission. This issue is a result of improper api route checking. Users are advised to upgrade to version 6.4.8.2. There are no known workarounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24748|2024-08-03T04:20:49.934Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 22:25:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24745|2024-08-03T04:20:50.203Z -- shopware -- platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24745</link>
      <description>Shopware is an open commerce platform based on the Symfony php Framework and the Vue javascript framework. In affected versions guest sessions are shared between customers when HTTP cache is enabled. This can lead to inconsistent experiences for guest users. Setups with Varnish are not affected by this issue. This issue has been resolved in version 6.4.8.2. Users unable to upgrade should disable the HTTP Cache.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24745|2024-08-03T04:20:50.203Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 22:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24871|2024-08-03T04:29:00.197Z -- shopware -- platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24871</link>
      <description>Shopware is an open commerce platform based on Symfony Framework and Vue. In affected versions an attacker can abuse the Admin SDK functionality on the server to read or update internal resources. Users are advised to update to the current version 6.4.10.1. For older versions of 6.1, 6.2, and 6.3, corresponding security measures are also available via a plugin. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24871|2024-08-03T04:29:00.197Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 19:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24744|2024-08-03T04:20:50.204Z -- shopware -- platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24744</link>
      <description>Shopware is an open commerce platform based on the Symfony php Framework and the Vue javascript framework. In affected versions user sessions are not logged out if the password is reset via password recovery. This issue has been resolved in version 6.4.8.1. For older versions of 6.1, 6.2, and 6.3, corresponding security measures are also available via a plugin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24744|2024-08-03T04:20:50.204Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 22:25:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24747|2024-08-03T04:20:50.206Z -- shopware -- platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24747</link>
      <description>Shopware is an open commerce platform based on the Symfony php Framework and the Vue javascript framework. Affected versions of shopware do no properly set sensitive HTTP headers to be non-cacheable. If there is an HTTP cache between the server and client then headers may be exposed via HTTP caches. This issue has been resolved in version 6.4.8.2. There are no known workarounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24747|2024-08-03T04:20:50.206Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 22:25:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24746|2024-08-03T04:20:50.458Z -- shopware -- platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24746</link>
      <description>Shopware is an open commerce platform based on the Symfony php Framework and the Vue javascript framework. In affected versions it is possible to inject code via the voucher code form. This issue has been patched in version 6.4.8.1. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24746|2024-08-03T04:20:50.458Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 22:25:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24872|2024-08-03T04:29:00.723Z -- shopware -- platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24872</link>
      <description>Shopware is an open commerce platform based on Symfony Framework and Vue. Permissions set to sales channel context by admin-api are still usable within normal user session. Users are advised to update to the current version 6.4.10.1. For older versions of 6.1, 6.2, and 6.3, corresponding security measures are also available via a plugin. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24872|2024-08-03T04:29:00.723Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 19:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
