<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for shopware -- platform</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/shopware/platform.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for shopware -- platform</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 17:22:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22733|2024-08-02T10:13:50.192Z -- shopware -- platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22733</link>
      <description>Shopware is an open source commerce platform based on Symfony Framework and Vue js. In affected versions the log module would write out all kind of sent mails. An attacker with access to either the local system logs or a centralized logging store may have access to other users accounts. This issue has been addressed in version 6.4.18.1. For older versions of 6.1, 6.2, and 6.3, corresponding security measures are also available via a plugin. For the full range of functions, we recommend updating to the latest Shopware version. Users unable to upgrade may remove from all users the log module ACL rights or disable logging.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22733|2024-08-02T10:13:50.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 21:37:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22730|2024-08-02T10:13:50.235Z -- shopware -- platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22730</link>
      <description>Shopware is an open source commerce platform based on Symfony Framework and Vue js. In affected versions It was possible to put the same line item multiple times in the cart using the AP. The Cart Validators checked the line item's individuality and the user was able to bypass quantity limits in sales. This problem has been fixed with version 6.4.18.1. Users on major versions 6.1, 6.2, and 6.3 may also obtain this fix via a plugin. 
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22730|2024-08-02T10:13:50.235Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 21:27:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22734|2024-08-02T10:13:50.203Z -- shopware -- platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22734</link>
      <description>Shopware is an open source commerce platform based on Symfony Framework and Vue js. The newsletter double opt-in validation was not checked properly, and it was possible to skip the complete double opt in process. As a result operators may have inconsistencies in their newsletter systems. This problem has been fixed with version 6.4.18.1. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade may find security measures are available via a plugin for major versions 6.1, 6.2, and 6.3. Users may also disable newsletter registration completely.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22734|2024-08-02T10:13:50.203Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 21:21:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22732|2024-08-02T10:13:50.234Z -- shopware -- platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22732</link>
      <description>Shopware is an open source commerce platform based on Symfony Framework and Vue js. The Administration session expiration was set to one week, when an attacker has stolen the session cookie they could use it for a long period of time. In version 6.4.18.1 an automatic logout into the Administration session has been added. As a result the user will be logged out when they are inactive. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this issue.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22732|2024-08-02T10:13:50.234Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 21:34:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22731|2024-08-02T10:13:50.227Z -- shopware -- platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22731</link>
      <description>Shopware is an open source commerce platform based on Symfony Framework and Vue js. In a Twig environment **without the Sandbox extension**, it is possible to refer to PHP functions in twig filters like `map`, `filter`, `sort`. This allows a template to call any global PHP function and thus execute arbitrary code. The attacker must have access to a Twig environment in order to exploit this vulnerability. This problem has been fixed with 6.4.18.1 with an override of the specified filters until the integration of the Sandbox extension has been finished. Users are advised to upgrade. Users of major versions 6.1, 6.2, and 6.3 may also receive this fix via a plugin.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22731|2024-08-02T10:13:50.227Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 21:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
