<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for shopware -- shopware</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/shopware/shopware.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for shopware -- shopware</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 15:22:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36102|2024-08-03T09:52:00.659Z -- shopware -- shopware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36102</link>
      <description>Shopware is an open source e-commerce software. In affected versions if backend admin controllers are called with a certain notation, the ACL could be bypassed. Users could execute actions, which they are normally not able to do. Users are advised to update to the current version (5.7.15). Users can get the update via the Auto-Updater or directly via the download overview. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36102|2024-08-03T09:52:00.659Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 20:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21651|2024-08-03T02:46:39.541Z -- shopware -- shopware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21651</link>
      <description>Shopware is an open source e-commerce software platform. An open redirect vulnerability has been discovered. Users may be arbitrary redirected due to incomplete URL handling in the shopware router. This issue has been resolved in version 5.7.7. There is no workaround and users are advised to upgrade as soon as possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21651|2024-08-03T02:46:39.541Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 19:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24879|2024-08-03T04:29:00.197Z -- shopware -- shopware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24879</link>
      <description>Shopware is an open source e-commerce software platform. Versions prior to 5.7.9 are vulnerable to malfunction of cross-site request forgery (CSRF) token validation. Under certain circumstances, the CSRF tokens were not generated anew and not validated correctly. This issue is fixed in version 5.7.9. Users of older versions may attempt to mitigate the vulnerability by using the Shopware security plugin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24879|2024-08-03T04:29:00.197Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 14:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21652|2024-08-03T02:46:39.393Z -- shopware -- shopware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21652</link>
      <description>Shopware is an open source e-commerce software platform. In affected versions shopware would not invalidate a user session in the event of a password change. With version 5.7.7 the session validation was adjusted, so that sessions created prior to the latest password change of a customer account can't be used to login with said account. This also means, that upon a password change, all existing sessions for a given customer account are automatically considered invalid. There is no workaround for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21652|2024-08-03T02:46:39.393Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 19:20:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24892|2024-08-03T04:29:00.669Z -- shopware -- shopware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24892</link>
      <description>Shopware is an open source e-commerce software platform. Starting with version 5.0.4 and before version 5.7.9, multiple tokens for password reset can be requested. All tokens can be used to change the password. This makes it possible for an attacker to take over the victim's account if they somehow gain access to the victims email account and find an unused password reset token in the emails. This issue is fixed in version 5.7.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24892|2024-08-03T04:29:00.669Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 14:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24873|2024-08-03T04:29:00.662Z -- shopware -- shopware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24873</link>
      <description>Shopware is an open source e-commerce software platform. Prior to version 5.7.9, Shopware is vulnerable to non-stored cross-site scripting in the storefront. This issue is fixed in version 5.7.9. Users of older versions may attempt to mitigate the vulnerability by using the Shopware security plugin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24873|2024-08-03T04:29:00.662Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 13:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36101|2024-08-03T09:52:00.539Z -- shopware -- shopware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36101</link>
      <description>Shopware is an open source e-commerce software. In affected versions the request for the customer detail view in the backend administration contained sensitive data like the hashed password and the session ID. These fields are now explicitly unset in version 5.7.15. Users are advised to update and may get the update either via the Auto-Updater or directly via the download overview. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36101|2024-08-03T09:52:00.539Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 20:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31057|2024-08-03T07:03:40.213Z -- shopware -- shopware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31057</link>
      <description>Shopware is an open source e-commerce software made in Germany. Versions of Shopware 5 prior to version 5.7.12 are subject to an authenticated Stored XSS in Administration. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31057|2024-08-03T07:03:40.213Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 19:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31148|2024-08-03T07:11:39.572Z -- shopware -- shopware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31148</link>
      <description>Shopware is an open source e-commerce software. In versions from 5.7.0 a persistent cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the customer module. Users are recommend to update to the current version 5.7.14. You can get the update to 5.7.14 regularly via the Auto-Updater or directly via the download overview. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31148|2024-08-03T07:11:39.572Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 17:10:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27917|2024-08-02T00:41:55.530Z -- shopware -- shopware</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27917</link>
      <description>Shopware is an open commerce platform based on Symfony Framework and Vue. The Symfony Session Handler pops the Session Cookie and assigns it to the Response. Since Shopware 6.5.8.0, the 404 pages are cached to improve the performance of 404 pages. So the cached Response which contains a Session Cookie when the Browser accessing the 404 page, has no cookies yet. The Symfony Session Handler is in use, when no explicit Session configuration has been done. When Redis is in use for Sessions using the PHP Redis extension, this exploiting code is not used. Shopware version 6.5.8.7 contains a patch for this issue. As a workaround, use Redis for Sessions, as this does not trigger the exploit code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27917|2024-08-02T00:41:55.530Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 19:36:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27917|2024-03-06T19:36:27.357Z -- shopware -- shopware</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27917</link>
      <description>Shopware is an open commerce platform based on Symfony Framework and Vue. The Symfony Session Handler pops the Session Cookie and assigns it to the Response. Since Shopware 6.5.8.0, the 404 pages are cached to improve the performance of 404 pages. So the cached Response which contains a Session Cookie when the Browser accessing the 404 page, has no cookies yet. The Symfony Session Handler is in use, when no explicit Session configuration has been done. When Redis is in use for Sessions using the PHP Redis extension, this exploiting code is not used. Shopware version 6.5.8.7 contains a patch for this issue. As a workaround, use Redis for Sessions, as this does not trigger the exploit code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27917|2024-03-06T19:36:27.357Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 19:36:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31447|2024-04-08T15:48:24.047Z -- shopware -- shopware</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31447</link>
      <description>Shopware 6 is an open commerce platform based on Symfony Framework and Vue. Starting in version 6.3.5.0 and prior to versions 6.6.1.0 and 6.5.8.8, when a authenticated request is made to `POST /store-api/account/logout`, the cart will be cleared, but the User won't be logged out. This affects only the direct store-api usage, as the PHP Storefront listens additionally on `CustomerLogoutEvent` and invalidates the session additionally. The problem has been fixed in Shopware 6.6.1.0 and 6.5.8.8. Those who are unable to update can install the latest version of the Shopware Security Plugin as a workaround.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31447|2024-04-08T15:48:24.047Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 15:39:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31447|2024-08-02T01:52:56.942Z -- shopware -- shopware</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31447</link>
      <description>Shopware 6 is an open commerce platform based on Symfony Framework and Vue. Starting in version 6.3.5.0 and prior to versions 6.6.1.0 and 6.5.8.8, when a authenticated request is made to `POST /store-api/account/logout`, the cart will be cleared, but the User won't be logged out. This affects only the direct store-api usage, as the PHP Storefront listens additionally on `CustomerLogoutEvent` and invalidates the session additionally. The problem has been fixed in Shopware 6.6.1.0 and 6.5.8.8. Those who are unable to update can install the latest version of the Shopware Security Plugin as a workaround.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31447|2024-08-02T01:52:56.942Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 15:39:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
