<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Halulu -- simple-download-button-shortcode Plugin</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/halulu/simple-download-button-shortcode%20plugin.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Halulu -- simple-download-button-shortcode Plugin</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 23:22:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2012-10016|2024-08-06T21:36:02.312Z -- halulu -- simple-download-button-shortcode%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10016</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Halulu simple-download-button-shortcode Plugin 1.0 on WordPress. Affected is an unknown function of the file simple-download-button_dl.php of the component Download Handler. The manipulation of the argument file leads to information disclosure. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 1.1 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as e648a8706818297cf02a665ae0bae1c069dea5f1. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-242190 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in Halulu simple-download-button-shortcode Plugin 1.0 für WordPress entdeckt. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei simple-download-button_dl.php der Komponente Download Handler. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments file mit unbekannten Daten kann eine information disclosure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 1.1 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als e648a8706818297cf02a665ae0bae1c069dea5f1 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2012-10016|2024-08-06T21:36:02.312Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 23:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
