<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for livemesh -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/livemesh/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for livemesh -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50370|2023-12-14T13:52:22.096Z -- livemesh -- wpbakery%20page%20builder%20addons%20by%20livemesh
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50370</link>
      <description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Livemesh WPBakery Page Builder Addons by Livemesh allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WPBakery Page Builder Addons by Livemesh: from n/a through 3.5.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50370|2023-12-14T13:52:22.096Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 13:42:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1464|2024-04-09T18:59:01.486Z -- livemesh -- elementor%20addons%20by%20livemesh
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1464</link>
      <description>The Elementor Addons by Livemesh plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘style’ attribute of the Posts Slider widget in all versions up to, and including, 8.3.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1464|2024-04-09T18:59:01.486Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:59:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1235|2024-06-04T18:01:20.517Z -- livemesh -- elementor%20addons%20by%20livemesh
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1235</link>
      <description>The Elementor Addons by Livemesh plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the custom class field in all versions up to, and including, 8.3.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1235|2024-06-04T18:01:20.517Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:56:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1465|2024-06-04T18:01:15.791Z -- livemesh -- elementor%20addons%20by%20livemesh
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1465</link>
      <description>The Elementor Addons by Livemesh plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘carousel_skin’ attribute of the Posts Carousel widget in all versions up to, and including, 8.3.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1465|2024-06-04T18:01:15.791Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:59:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1458|2024-06-04T18:00:55.566Z -- livemesh -- elementor%20addons%20by%20livemesh
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1458</link>
      <description>The Elementor Addons by Livemesh plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘text_alignment’ attribute of the Animated Text widget in all versions up to, and including, 8.3.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1458|2024-06-04T18:00:55.566Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:59:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1461|2024-06-04T17:59:55.168Z -- livemesh -- elementor%20addons%20by%20livemesh
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1461</link>
      <description>The Elementor Addons by Livemesh plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘style’ attribute of the Team Members widget in all versions up to, and including, 8.3.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1461|2024-06-04T17:59:55.168Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:59:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1466|2024-06-04T17:59:41.870Z -- livemesh -- elementor%20addons%20by%20livemesh
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1466</link>
      <description>The Elementor Addons by Livemesh plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘slider_style’ attribute of the Posts Multislider widget in all versions up to, and including, 8.3.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. CVE-2024-27986 may be a duplicate of this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1466|2024-06-04T17:59:41.870Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:58:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0448|2024-02-05T21:21:30.732Z -- livemesh -- elementor%20addons%20by%20livemesh
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0448</link>
      <description>The Elementor Addons by Livemesh plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's widget URL parameters in all versions up to, and including, 8.3.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor access or higher to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0448|2024-02-05T21:21:30.732Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:21:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27986|2024-06-04T17:47:12.030Z -- livemesh -- elementor%20addons%20by%20livemesh
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27986</link>
      <description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Livemesh Elementor Addons by Livemesh allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Elementor Addons by Livemesh: from n/a through 8.3.5.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27986|2024-06-04T17:47:12.030Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 08:23:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30183|2024-03-27T11:47:23.318Z -- livemesh -- livemesh%20addons%20for%20wpbakery%20page%20builder
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30183</link>
      <description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Livemesh Livemesh Addons for WPBakery Page Builder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Livemesh Addons for WPBakery Page Builder: from n/a through 3.7.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30183|2024-03-27T11:47:23.318Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 11:47:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25598|2024-03-15T13:07:37.793Z -- livemesh -- livemesh%20addons%20for%20elementor
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25598</link>
      <description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Livemesh Livemesh Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Livemesh Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 8.3.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25598|2024-03-15T13:07:37.793Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 13:07:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2655|2024-04-10T05:32:22.955Z -- livemesh -- elementor%20addons%20by%20livemesh
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2655</link>
      <description>The Elementor Addons by Livemesh plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Post widgets in all versions up to, and including, 8.3.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on author display names. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2655|2024-04-10T05:32:22.955Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 05:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2079|2024-06-04T17:30:17.461Z -- livemesh -- wpbakery%20page%20builder%20addons%20by%20livemesh
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2079</link>
      <description>The WPBakery Page Builder Addons by Livemesh plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'per_line_mobile' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2079|2024-06-04T17:30:17.461Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 21:32:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2539|2024-06-06T18:28:46.727Z -- livemesh -- elementor%20addons%20by%20livemesh
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2539</link>
      <description>The Elementor Addons by Livemesh plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via widget '_id' attributes in all versions up to, and including, 8.3.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2539|2024-06-06T18:28:46.727Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 05:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
