<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Kashipara -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/kashipara/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Kashipara -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5368|2024-06-04T18:02:59.614Z -- kashipara -- college%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5368</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file delete_faculty.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266280.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in Kashipara College Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei delete_faculty.php. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5368|2024-06-04T18:02:59.614Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 16:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5372|2024-05-26T18:31:03.943Z -- kashipara -- college%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5372</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file submit_extracurricular_activity.php. The manipulation of the argument activity_contact leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266284.
In Kashipara College Management System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei submit_extracurricular_activity.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments activity_contact mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5372|2024-05-26T18:31:03.943Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 18:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5373|2024-06-04T18:02:53.279Z -- kashipara -- college%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5373</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file submit_login.php. The manipulation of the argument usertype leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-266285 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Kashipara College Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei submit_login.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments usertype mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5373|2024-06-04T18:02:53.279Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 19:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5369|2024-06-07T19:54:24.525Z -- kashipara -- college%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5369</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file submit_admin.php. The manipulation of the argument admin_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-266281 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In Kashipara College Management System 1.0 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei submit_admin.php. Durch Manipulation des Arguments admin_name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5369|2024-06-07T19:54:24.525Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 16:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5374|2024-05-26T19:31:03.468Z -- kashipara -- college%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5374</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file submit_new_faculty.php. The manipulation of the argument address leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-266286 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Kashipara College Management System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei submit_new_faculty.php. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments address mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5374|2024-05-26T19:31:03.468Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 19:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5375|2024-06-04T18:02:25.118Z -- kashipara -- college%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5375</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file submit_student.php. The manipulation of the argument address leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266287.
In Kashipara College Management System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei submit_student.php. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments address mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5375|2024-06-04T18:02:25.118Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 20:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5376|2024-06-04T18:02:19.838Z -- kashipara -- college%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5376</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file view_each_faculty.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266288.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Kashipara College Management System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei view_each_faculty.php. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5376|2024-06-04T18:02:19.838Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 20:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5370|2024-06-04T18:01:52.843Z -- kashipara -- college%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5370</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file submit_enroll_staff.php. The manipulation of the argument class_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-266282 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in Kashipara College Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei submit_enroll_staff.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments class_name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5370|2024-06-04T18:01:52.843Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 17:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5371|2024-06-04T18:01:47.483Z -- kashipara -- college%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5371</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file submit_enroll_student.php. The manipulation of the argument class_name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266283.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Kashipara College Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei submit_enroll_student.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments class_name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5371|2024-06-04T18:01:47.483Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 18:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5367|2024-06-04T18:01:45.992Z -- kashipara -- college%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5367</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file each_extracurricula_activities.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-266279.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in Kashipara College Management System 1.0 gefunden. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei each_extracurricula_activities.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5367|2024-06-04T18:01:45.992Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 15:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0280|2024-01-07T14:31:03.462Z -- kashipara -- food%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0280</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file item_type_submit.php. The manipulation of the argument type_name leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249835.
In Kashipara Food Management System bis 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei item_type_submit.php. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments type_name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0280|2024-01-07T14:31:03.462Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 14:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0279|2024-01-07T14:00:04.215Z -- kashipara -- food%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0279</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file item_list_edit.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249834 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Kashipara Food Management System bis 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei item_list_edit.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0279|2024-01-07T14:00:04.215Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 14:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0306|2024-01-08T09:00:07.071Z -- kashipara -- dynamic%20lab%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0306</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Dynamic Lab Management System up to 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/admin_login_process.php. The manipulation of the argument admin_password leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249873 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Kashipara Dynamic Lab Management System bis 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei /admin/admin_login_process.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments admin_password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0306|2024-01-08T09:00:07.071Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0275|2024-01-07T12:00:05.191Z -- kashipara -- food%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0275</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file item_edit_submit.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249830 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Kashipara Food Management System bis 1.0 ausgemacht. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei item_edit_submit.php. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0275|2024-01-07T12:00:05.191Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 12:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0274|2024-01-07T11:31:03.585Z -- kashipara -- food%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0274</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file billAjax.php. The manipulation of the argument item_name leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249829 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In Kashipara Food Management System bis 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei billAjax.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments item_name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0274|2024-01-07T11:31:03.585Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 11:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0307|2024-01-08T09:31:03.531Z -- kashipara -- dynamic%20lab%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0307</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Dynamic Lab Management System up to 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file login_process.php. The manipulation of the argument password leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249874 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In Kashipara Dynamic Lab Management System bis 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei login_process.php. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0307|2024-01-08T09:31:03.531Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0278|2024-01-07T13:31:03.800Z -- kashipara -- food%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0278</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file partylist_edit_submit.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249833 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Kashipara Food Management System bis 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei partylist_edit_submit.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0278|2024-01-07T13:31:03.800Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 13:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0281|2024-01-07T15:00:06.256Z -- kashipara -- food%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0281</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file loginCheck.php. The manipulation of the argument password leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249836.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Kashipara Food Management System bis 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei loginCheck.php. Durch Manipulation des Arguments password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0281|2024-01-07T15:00:06.256Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 15:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0273|2024-01-07T11:00:05.780Z -- kashipara -- food%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0273</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file addwaste_entry.php. The manipulation of the argument item_name leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249828.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Kashipara Food Management System bis 1.0 ausgemacht. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei addwaste_entry.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments item_name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0273|2024-01-07T11:00:05.780Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0290|2024-02-09T19:05:12.276Z -- kashipara -- food%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0290</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Kashipara Food Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file stock_edit.php. The manipulation of the argument item_type leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249851.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Kashipara Food Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei stock_edit.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments item_type mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0290|2024-02-09T19:05:12.276Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 00:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0496|2024-06-04T17:58:55.821Z -- kashipara -- billing%20software
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0496</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Billing Software 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file item_list_edit.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250601 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Kashipara Billing Software 1.0 gefunden. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei item_list_edit.php der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0496|2024-06-04T17:58:55.821Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 17:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0287|2024-02-09T19:05:11.024Z -- kashipara -- food%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0287</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Food Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file itemBillPdf.php. The manipulation of the argument printid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249848.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Kashipara Food Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei itemBillPdf.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments printid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0287|2024-02-09T19:05:11.024Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 23:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0268|2024-01-07T07:31:04.120Z -- kashipara -- hospital%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0268</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Kashipara Hospital Management System up to 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file registration.php. The manipulation of the argument name/email/pass/gender/age/city leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249824.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Kashipara Hospital Management System bis 1.0 entdeckt. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei registration.php. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments name/email/pass/gender/age/city mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0268|2024-01-07T07:31:04.120Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 07:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0272|2024-01-07T10:31:03.624Z -- kashipara -- food%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0272</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file addmaterialsubmit.php. The manipulation of the argument material_name leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249827.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Kashipara Food Management System bis 1.0 gefunden. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei addmaterialsubmit.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments material_name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0272|2024-01-07T10:31:03.624Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 10:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0271|2024-01-07T08:31:03.929Z -- kashipara -- food%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0271</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file addmaterial_edit.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249826 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In Kashipara Food Management System bis 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle gefunden. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei addmaterial_edit.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0271|2024-01-07T08:31:03.929Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 08:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0267|2024-01-07T06:00:06.814Z -- kashipara -- hospital%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0267</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Kashipara Hospital Management System up to 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file login.php of the component Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument email/password leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249823.
In Kashipara Hospital Management System bis 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei login.php der Komponente Parameter Handler. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments email/password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0267|2024-01-07T06:00:06.814Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 06:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0288|2024-02-09T19:05:13.486Z -- kashipara -- food%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0288</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Kashipara Food Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file rawstock_used_damaged_submit.php. The manipulation of the argument product_name leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249849 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Kashipara Food Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei rawstock_used_damaged_submit.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments product_name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0288|2024-02-09T19:05:13.486Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 23:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0494|2024-01-13T16:00:05.140Z -- kashipara -- billing%20software
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0494</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Kashipara Billing Software 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file material_bill.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument itemtypeid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250599.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Kashipara Billing Software 1.0 gefunden. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei material_bill.php der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments itemtypeid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0494|2024-01-13T16:00:05.140Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 16:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0284|2024-01-07T17:00:05.778Z -- kashipara -- food%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0284</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file party_submit.php. The manipulation of the argument party_address leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249839.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Kashipara Food Management System bis 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei party_submit.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments party_address mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0284|2024-01-07T17:00:05.778Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 17:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0495|2024-01-13T16:31:03.345Z -- kashipara -- billing%20software
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0495</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Kashipara Billing Software 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file party_submit.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument party_name leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250600.
In Kashipara Billing Software 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle gefunden. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei party_submit.php der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments party_name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0495|2024-01-13T16:31:03.345Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 16:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0289|2024-02-09T19:05:19.587Z -- kashipara -- food%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0289</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Kashipara Food Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file stock_entry_submit.php. The manipulation of the argument itemype leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249850 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In Kashipara Food Management System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei stock_entry_submit.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments itemype mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0289|2024-02-09T19:05:19.587Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 00:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0270|2024-01-07T08:00:04.999Z -- kashipara -- food%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0270</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file item_list_submit.php. The manipulation of the argument item_name leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249825 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Kashipara Food Management System bis 1.0 gefunden. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei item_list_submit.php. Durch Manipulation des Arguments item_name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0270|2024-01-07T08:00:04.999Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 08:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0492|2024-01-13T15:00:06.351Z -- kashipara -- billing%20software
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0492</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Kashipara Billing Software 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file buyer_detail_submit.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument gstn_no leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250597 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In Kashipara Billing Software 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei buyer_detail_submit.php der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments gstn_no mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0492|2024-01-13T15:00:06.351Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 15:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0282|2024-01-07T15:31:03.431Z -- kashipara -- food%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0282</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file addmaterialsubmit.php. The manipulation of the argument tin leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249837 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Kashipara Food Management System bis 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei addmaterialsubmit.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments tin mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0282|2024-01-07T15:31:03.431Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 15:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0277|2024-01-07T13:00:05.458Z -- kashipara -- food%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0277</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file party_submit.php. The manipulation of the argument party_name leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249832.
In Kashipara Food Management System bis 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei party_submit.php. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments party_name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0277|2024-01-07T13:00:05.458Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 13:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0276|2024-01-07T12:31:04.048Z -- kashipara -- food%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0276</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file rawstock_used_damaged_smt.php. The manipulation of the argument product_name leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249831.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Kashipara Food Management System bis 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei rawstock_used_damaged_smt.php. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments product_name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0276|2024-01-07T12:31:04.048Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 12:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0283|2024-01-07T16:00:05.025Z -- kashipara -- food%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0283</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Food Management System up to 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file party_details.php. The manipulation of the argument party_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249838 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In Kashipara Food Management System bis 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei party_details.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments party_name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0283|2024-01-07T16:00:05.025Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 16:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0493|2024-01-13T15:31:03.467Z -- kashipara -- billing%20software
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0493</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Kashipara Billing Software 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file submit_delivery_list.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument customer_details leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250598 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Kashipara Billing Software 1.0 entdeckt. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei submit_delivery_list.php der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments customer_details mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0493|2024-01-13T15:31:03.467Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 15:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4806|2024-06-04T17:56:37.334Z -- kashipara -- college%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4806</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file each_extracurricula_activities.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-263926 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In Kashipara College Management System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei each_extracurricula_activities.php. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4806|2024-06-04T17:56:37.334Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 23:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4807|2024-06-04T17:55:48.306Z -- kashipara -- college%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4807</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file delete_user.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263927.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Kashipara College Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei delete_user.php. Durch Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4807|2024-06-04T17:55:48.306Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 23:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4070|2024-06-04T17:55:38.769Z -- kashipara -- online%20furniture%20shopping%20ecommerce%20website
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4070</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Kashipara Online Furniture Shopping Ecommerce Website 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file prodList.php. The manipulation of the argument prodType leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261796.
In Kashipara Online Furniture Shopping Ecommerce Website 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle gefunden. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei prodList.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments prodType mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4070|2024-06-04T17:55:38.769Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 22:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4800|2024-06-04T17:55:33.254Z -- kashipara -- college%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4800</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file submit_student.php. The manipulation of the argument date_of_birth leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263920.
In Kashipara College Management System 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle gefunden. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei submit_student.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments date_of_birth mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4800|2024-06-04T17:55:33.254Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 21:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4905|2024-06-04T17:55:08.120Z -- kashipara -- college%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4905</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file view_students_each_detail.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-264438 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Kashipara College Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei view_students_each_detail.php. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4905|2024-06-04T17:55:08.120Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4801|2024-06-04T17:55:04.196Z -- kashipara -- college%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4801</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file submit_new_faculty.php. The manipulation of the argument address leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-263921 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Kashipara College Management System 1.0 gefunden. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei submit_new_faculty.php. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments address mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4801|2024-06-04T17:55:04.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 22:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4071|2024-04-23T22:00:07.212Z -- kashipara -- online%20furniture%20shopping%20ecommerce%20website
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4071</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Online Furniture Shopping Ecommerce Website 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file prodInfo.php. The manipulation of the argument prodId leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-261797 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Kashipara Online Furniture Shopping Ecommerce Website 1.0 gefunden. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei prodInfo.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments prodId mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4071|2024-04-23T22:00:07.212Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 22:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4072|2024-04-23T22:31:04.805Z -- kashipara -- online%20furniture%20shopping%20ecommerce%20website
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4072</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Online Furniture Shopping Ecommerce Website 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file search.php. The manipulation of the argument txtSearch leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-261798 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in Kashipara Online Furniture Shopping Ecommerce Website 1.0 ausgemacht. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei search.php. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments txtSearch mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4072|2024-04-23T22:31:04.805Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 22:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4802|2024-06-04T17:54:22.280Z -- kashipara -- college%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4802</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file submit_extracurricular_activity.php. The manipulation of the argument activity_datetime leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-263922 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Kashipara College Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei submit_extracurricular_activity.php. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments activity_datetime mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4802|2024-06-04T17:54:22.280Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 22:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4803|2024-06-04T17:54:20.107Z -- kashipara -- college%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4803</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file submit_admin.php. The manipulation of the argument phone leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263923.
In Kashipara College Management System 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei submit_admin.php. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments phone mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4803|2024-06-04T17:54:20.107Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 22:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4069|2024-06-04T17:54:09.090Z -- kashipara -- online%20furniture%20shopping%20ecommerce%20website
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4069</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Kashipara Online Furniture Shopping Ecommerce Website 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file search.php. The manipulation of the argument txtSearch leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261795.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Kashipara Online Furniture Shopping Ecommerce Website 1.0 gefunden. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei search.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments txtSearch mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4069|2024-06-04T17:54:09.090Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 21:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4073|2024-04-23T22:31:06.209Z -- kashipara -- online%20furniture%20shopping%20ecommerce%20website
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4073</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Online Furniture Shopping Ecommerce Website 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file prodList.php. The manipulation of the argument prodType leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261799.
In Kashipara Online Furniture Shopping Ecommerce Website 1.0 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei prodList.php. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments prodType mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4073|2024-04-23T22:31:06.209Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 22:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4804|2024-06-04T17:53:41.134Z -- kashipara -- college%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4804</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file edit_user.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263924.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Kashipara College Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei edit_user.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4804|2024-06-04T17:53:41.134Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 23:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4074|2024-04-23T23:00:05.201Z -- kashipara -- online%20furniture%20shopping%20ecommerce%20website
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4074</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Online Furniture Shopping Ecommerce Website 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file prodInfo.php. The manipulation of the argument prodId leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261800.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in Kashipara Online Furniture Shopping Ecommerce Website 1.0 ausgemacht. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei prodInfo.php. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments prodId mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4074|2024-04-23T23:00:05.201Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 23:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4799|2024-06-04T17:53:33.745Z -- kashipara -- college%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4799</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file view_each_faculty.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263919.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Kashipara College Management System 1.0 gefunden. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei view_each_faculty.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4799|2024-06-04T17:53:33.745Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 18:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4808|2024-05-13T00:00:04.682Z -- kashipara -- college%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4808</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file delete_faculty.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263928.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Kashipara College Management System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei delete_faculty.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4808|2024-05-13T00:00:04.682Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 00:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4075|2024-04-23T23:00:06.799Z -- kashipara -- online%20furniture%20shopping%20ecommerce%20website
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4075</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Kashipara Online Furniture Shopping Ecommerce Website 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file login.php. The manipulation of the argument txtAddress leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-261801 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Kashipara Online Furniture Shopping Ecommerce Website 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei login.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments txtAddress mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4075|2024-04-23T23:00:06.799Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 23:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4805|2024-06-04T17:53:11.729Z -- kashipara -- college%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4805</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Kashipara College Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file edit_faculty.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-263925 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Kashipara College Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei edit_faculty.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4805|2024-06-04T17:53:11.729Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 23:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
