<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for Kashipara -- Billing Software</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/kashipara/billing%20software.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for Kashipara -- Billing Software</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 21:54:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-0496|2024-01-13T17:00:05.402Z -- Kashipara -- Billing Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0496</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kashipara Billing Software 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file item_list_edit.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250601 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Kashipara Billing Software 1.0 gefunden. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei item_list_edit.php der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0496|2024-01-13T17:00:05.402Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 17:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0494|2024-01-13T16:00:05.140Z -- Kashipara -- Billing Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0494</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Kashipara Billing Software 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file material_bill.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument itemtypeid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250599.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Kashipara Billing Software 1.0 gefunden. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei material_bill.php der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments itemtypeid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0494|2024-01-13T16:00:05.140Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 16:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0495|2024-01-13T16:31:03.345Z -- Kashipara -- Billing Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0495</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Kashipara Billing Software 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file party_submit.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument party_name leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250600.
In Kashipara Billing Software 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle gefunden. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei party_submit.php der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments party_name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0495|2024-01-13T16:31:03.345Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 16:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0492|2024-01-13T15:00:06.351Z -- Kashipara -- Billing Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0492</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Kashipara Billing Software 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file buyer_detail_submit.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument gstn_no leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250597 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In Kashipara Billing Software 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei buyer_detail_submit.php der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments gstn_no mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0492|2024-01-13T15:00:06.351Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 15:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0493|2024-01-13T15:31:03.467Z -- Kashipara -- Billing Software
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0493</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Kashipara Billing Software 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file submit_delivery_list.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument customer_details leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250598 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Kashipara Billing Software 1.0 entdeckt. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei submit_delivery_list.php der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments customer_details mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0493|2024-01-13T15:31:03.467Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 15:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>