<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for Kashipara -- Hospital Management System</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/kashipara/hospital%20management%20system.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for Kashipara -- Hospital Management System</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 16:28:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-0268|2024-01-07T07:31:04.120Z -- Kashipara -- Hospital Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0268</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Kashipara Hospital Management System up to 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file registration.php. The manipulation of the argument name/email/pass/gender/age/city leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249824.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Kashipara Hospital Management System bis 1.0 entdeckt. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei registration.php. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments name/email/pass/gender/age/city mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0268|2024-01-07T07:31:04.120Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 07:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0267|2024-01-07T06:00:06.814Z -- Kashipara -- Hospital Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0267</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Kashipara Hospital Management System up to 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file login.php of the component Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument email/password leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249823.
In Kashipara Hospital Management System bis 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei login.php der Komponente Parameter Handler. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments email/password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0267|2024-01-07T06:00:06.814Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 06:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>