<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Bdtask -- Hospital AutoManager</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/bdtask/hospital%20automanager.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Bdtask -- Hospital AutoManager</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2317|2024-03-08T12:00:07.323Z -- bdtask -- hospital%20automanager
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2317</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Bdtask Hospital AutoManager up to 20240227 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /prescription/prescription/delete/ of the component Prescription Page. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256271. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in Bdtask Hospital AutoManager bis 20240227 gefunden. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei /prescription/prescription/delete/ der Komponente Prescription Page. Durch Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine improper authorization-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2317|2024-03-08T12:00:07.323Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 12:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2316|2024-03-08T11:31:04.188Z -- bdtask -- hospital%20automanager
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2316</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Bdtask Hospital AutoManager up to 20240227 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /billing/bill/edit/ of the component Update Bill Page. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-256270 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Bdtask Hospital AutoManager bis 20240227 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle gefunden. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei /billing/bill/edit/ der Komponente Update Bill Page. Durch die Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross-site request forgery-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2316|2024-03-08T11:31:04.188Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 11:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
