<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for Bdtask -- Hospita AutoManager</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/bdtask/hospita%20automanager.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for Bdtask -- Hospita AutoManager</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 21:24:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-2134|2024-03-03T00:31:04.866Z -- Bdtask -- Hospita AutoManager
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2134</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Bdtask Hospita AutoManager up to 20240223 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /investigation/delete/ of the component Investigation Report Handler. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-255496. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Bdtask Hospita AutoManager bis 20240223 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle gefunden. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei /investigation/delete/ der Komponente Investigation Report Handler. Durch Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross-site request forgery-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2134|2024-03-03T00:31:04.866Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 00:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2135|2024-03-03T03:00:06.445Z -- Bdtask -- Hospita AutoManager
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2135</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Bdtask Hospita AutoManager up to 20240223 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /hospital_activities/birth/form of the component Hospital Activities Page. The manipulation of the argument Description with the input &lt;img src=a onerror=alert(1)&gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-255497 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in Bdtask Hospita AutoManager bis 20240223 gefunden. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei /hospital_activities/birth/form der Komponente Hospital Activities Page. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments Description mit der Eingabe &lt;img src=a onerror=alert(1)&gt; mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2135|2024-03-03T03:00:06.445Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 03:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>