<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for Bdtask -- Multi-Store Inventory Management System</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/bdtask/multi-store%20inventory%20management%20system.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for Bdtask -- Multi-Store Inventory Management System</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 16:28:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-3151|2024-04-02T17:00:04.919Z -- Bdtask -- Multi-Store Inventory Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3151</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Bdtask Multi-Store Inventory Management System up to 20240325. Affected is an unknown function of the file /stockmovment/stockmovment/delete/ of the component Stock Movement Page. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-258924. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Bdtask Multi-Store Inventory Management System bis 20240325 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei /stockmovment/stockmovment/delete/ der Komponente Stock Movement Page. Mittels Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross-site request forgery-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3151|2024-04-02T17:00:04.919Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 17:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2998|2024-03-27T20:31:06.107Z -- Bdtask -- Multi-Store Inventory Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2998</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Bdtask Multi-Store Inventory Management System up to 20240320. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Store Update Page. The manipulation of the argument Store Name/Store Address leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-258200. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in Bdtask Multi-Store Inventory Management System bis 20240320 ausgemacht. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Komponente Store Update Page. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments Store Name/Store Address mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2998|2024-03-27T20:31:06.107Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 20:31:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2997|2024-03-27T20:31:04.490Z -- Bdtask -- Multi-Store Inventory Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2997</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Bdtask Multi-Store Inventory Management System up to 20240320. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality. The manipulation of the argument Category Name/Model Name/Brand Name/Unit Name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-258199. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Bdtask Multi-Store Inventory Management System bis 20240320 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments Category Name/Model Name/Brand Name/Unit Name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2997|2024-03-27T20:31:04.490Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 20:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2996|2024-03-27T20:00:08.232Z -- Bdtask -- Multi-Store Inventory Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2996</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Bdtask Multi-Store Inventory Management System up to 20240320. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the component Page Title Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-258198 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in Bdtask Multi-Store Inventory Management System bis 20240320 ausgemacht. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Komponente Page Title Handler. Mittels Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2996|2024-03-27T20:00:08.232Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 20:00:08 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>