<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for ACD Systems -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/acd%20systems/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for ACD Systems -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 09:23:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3870|2024-08-05T04:57:24.500Z -- acd%20systems -- canvas%20draw
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3870</link>
      <description>An exploitable out-of-bounds write exists in the PCX parsing functionality of Canvas Draw version 4.0.0. A specially crafted PCX image processed via the application can lead to an out-of-bounds write, overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker can deliver a PCX image to trigger this vulnerability and gain code execution. A different vulnerability than CVE-2018-3871.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3870|2024-08-05T04:57:24.500Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3857|2024-08-05T04:57:24.319Z -- acd%20systems -- canvas%20draw
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3857</link>
      <description>An exploitable heap overflow exists in the TIFF parsing functionality of Canvas Draw version 4.0.0. A specially crafted TIFF image processed via the application can lead to an out-of-bounds write, overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker can deliver a TIFF image to trigger this vulnerability and gain code execution. A different vulnerability than CVE-2018-3858.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3857|2024-08-05T04:57:24.319Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3859|2024-08-05T04:57:24.066Z -- acd%20systems -- canvas%20draw
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3859</link>
      <description>An exploitable out-of-bounds write exists in the TIFF parsing functionality of Canvas Draw version 4.0.0. A specially crafted TIFF image processed via the application can lead to an out-of-bounds write, overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker can deliver a TIFF image to trigger this vulnerability and gain code execution. A different vulnerability than CVE-2018-3860.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3859|2024-08-05T04:57:24.066Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3871|2024-08-05T04:57:24.145Z -- acd%20systems -- canvas%20draw
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3871</link>
      <description>An exploitable out-of-bounds write exists in the PCX parsing functionality of Canvas Draw version 4.0.0. A specially crafted PCX image processed via the application can lead to an out-of-bounds write, overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker can deliver a PCX image to trigger this vulnerability and gain code execution. A different vulnerability than CVE-2018-3870.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3871|2024-08-05T04:57:24.145Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3860|2024-08-05T04:57:23.791Z -- acd%20systems -- canvas%20draw
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3860</link>
      <description>An exploitable out-of-bounds write exists in the TIFF parsing functionality of Canvas Draw version 4.0.0. A specially crafted TIFF image processed via the application can lead to an out-of-bounds write, overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker can deliver a TIFF image to trigger this vulnerability and gain the ability to execute code. A different vulnerability than CVE-2018-3859.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3860|2024-08-05T04:57:23.791Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3858|2024-08-05T04:57:24.251Z -- acd%20systems -- canvas%20draw
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3858</link>
      <description>An exploitable heap overflow exists in the TIFF parsing functionality of Canvas Draw version 4.0.0. A specially crafted TIFF image processed via the application can lead to an out-of-bounds write, overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker can deliver a TIFF image to trigger this vulnerability and gain the ability to execute code. A different vulnerability than CVE-2018-3857.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3858|2024-08-05T04:57:24.251Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
