<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for PDF-XChange -- PDF-XChange Editor</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/pdf-xchange/pdf-xchange%20editor.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for PDF-XChange -- PDF-XChange Editor</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 19:19:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40468|2024-08-02T18:31:53.852Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40468</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files. Crafted data in an EMF file can trigger a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20620.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40468|2024-08-02T18:31:53.852Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39499|2024-08-02T18:10:21.074Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39499</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor JPG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPG files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19949.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39499|2024-08-02T18:10:21.074Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39487|2024-08-02T18:10:20.669Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39487</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor util Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of util objects. By performing actions in JavaScript, an attacker can trigger a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19483.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39487|2024-08-02T18:10:20.669Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39492|2024-08-02T18:10:21.378Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39492</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19640.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39492|2024-08-02T18:10:21.378Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40472|2024-08-02T18:31:54.021Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40472</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor JavaScript String Untrusted Pointer Dereference Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of strings. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied value prior to dereferencing it as a pointer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20730.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40472|2024-08-02T18:31:54.021Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39495|2024-08-02T18:10:21.092Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39495</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor readFileIntoStream Exposed Dangerous Function Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the readFileIntoStream method. The issue results from the exposure of a dangerous function. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-19657.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39495|2024-08-02T18:10:21.092Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39506|2024-08-02T18:10:21.369Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39506</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor createDataObject Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the createDataObject method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-20594.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39506|2024-08-02T18:10:21.369Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40469|2024-08-02T18:31:53.912Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40469</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor XPS File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of XPS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20621.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40469|2024-08-02T18:31:53.912Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39491|2024-08-02T18:10:20.906Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39491</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor TIF File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of TIF files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19638.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39491|2024-08-02T18:10:20.906Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39494|2024-08-02T18:10:21.338Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39494</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor OXPS File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of OXPS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19655.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39494|2024-08-02T18:10:21.338Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39502|2024-08-02T18:10:21.124Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39502</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor OXPS File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of OXPS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20035.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39502|2024-08-02T18:10:21.124Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39484|2024-08-02T18:10:20.928Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39484</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Uninitialized Variable Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of memory prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18493.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39484|2024-08-02T18:10:20.928Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39503|2024-08-02T18:10:21.130Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39503</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor OXPS File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of OXPS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20036.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39503|2024-08-02T18:10:21.130Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39485|2024-08-02T18:10:20.708Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39485</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor JP2 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JP2 files. Crafted data in a JP2 file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19189.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39485|2024-08-02T18:10:20.708Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39504|2024-08-02T18:10:21.113Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39504</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor OXPS File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of OXPS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20037.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39504|2024-08-02T18:10:21.113Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39498|2024-08-02T18:10:21.360Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39498</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor JPG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPG files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19948.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39498|2024-08-02T18:10:21.360Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39497|2024-08-02T18:10:21.123Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39497</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor JPG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPG files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19947.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39497|2024-08-02T18:10:21.123Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39505|2024-08-02T18:10:21.130Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39505</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor Net.HTTP.requests Exposed Dangerous Function Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the Net.HTTP.requests method. The issue results from the exposure of a dangerous function. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-20211.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39505|2024-08-02T18:10:21.130Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40470|2024-08-02T18:31:53.899Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40470</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor JP2 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JP2 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20622.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40470|2024-08-02T18:31:53.899Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40471|2024-08-02T18:31:53.826Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40471</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor App Untrusted Pointer Dereference Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of App objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied value prior to dereferencing it as a pointer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20729.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40471|2024-08-02T18:31:53.826Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39501|2024-08-02T18:10:21.094Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39501</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor OXPS File Parsing Untrusted Pointer Dereference Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of OXPS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied value prior to dereferencing it as a pointer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20034.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39501|2024-08-02T18:10:21.094Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39489|2024-08-02T18:10:21.021Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39489</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor TIF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of TIF files. Crafted data in a TIF file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19488.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39489|2024-08-02T18:10:21.021Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39496|2024-08-02T18:10:21.379Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39496</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor TIF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of TIF files. Crafted data in a TIF file can trigger a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19658.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39496|2024-08-02T18:10:21.379Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40473|2024-08-02T18:31:53.986Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40473</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor Doc Object Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. By performing actions in JavaScript, an attacker can trigger a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20891.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40473|2024-08-02T18:31:53.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39483|2024-08-02T18:10:20.675Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39483</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor J2K File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of J2K files. Crafted data in a J2K file can trigger a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18308.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39483|2024-08-02T18:10:20.675Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39486|2024-08-02T18:10:20.686Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39486</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor JP2 File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JP2 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19264.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39486|2024-08-02T18:10:20.686Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39500|2024-08-02T18:10:21.237Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39500</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor JPG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPG files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19950.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39500|2024-08-02T18:10:21.237Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39488|2024-08-02T18:10:20.802Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39488</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor TIF File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of TIF files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19487.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39488|2024-08-02T18:10:20.802Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39490|2024-08-02T18:10:20.967Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39490</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. Crafted data in a PDF file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19636.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39490|2024-08-02T18:10:20.967Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39493|2024-08-02T18:10:21.106Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39493</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor exportAsText Exposed Dangerous Method Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the exportAsText method. The application exposes a JavaScript interface that allows writing arbitrary files. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-19649.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39493|2024-08-02T18:10:21.106Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27345|2024-08-02T12:09:43.301Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27345</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. Crafted data in a PDF file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19303.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27345|2024-08-02T12:09:43.301Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27337|2024-08-02T12:09:43.277Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27337</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. Crafted data in a PDF file can trigger a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18494.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27337|2024-08-02T12:09:43.277Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27338|2024-08-02T12:09:43.026Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27338</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor TIF File Parsing Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of TIF files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18612.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27338|2024-08-02T12:09:43.026Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27348|2024-08-02T12:09:43.334Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27348</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor TIF File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of TIF files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19108.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27348|2024-08-02T12:09:43.334Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27344|2024-08-02T12:09:43.412Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27344</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. Crafted data in a PDF file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19302.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27344|2024-08-02T12:09:43.412Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27341|2024-08-02T12:09:43.280Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27341</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor TIF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of TIF files. Crafted data in a TIF file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18729.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27341|2024-08-02T12:09:43.280Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27343|2024-08-02T12:09:43.413Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27343</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files. Crafted data in a EMF can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18790.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27343|2024-08-02T12:09:43.413Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27340|2024-08-02T12:09:43.333Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27340</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor PNG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PNG files. Crafted data in a PNG file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18665.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27340|2024-08-02T12:09:43.333Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27339|2024-08-02T12:09:43.038Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27339</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor PNG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PNG files. Crafted data in a PNG file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18663.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27339|2024-08-02T12:09:43.038Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27342|2024-08-02T12:09:43.402Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27342</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Untrusted Pointer Dereference Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied value prior to dereferencing it as a pointer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18766.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27342|2024-08-02T12:09:43.402Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42044|2024-07-24T20:42:16.539Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42044</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. his vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20889.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42044|2024-07-24T20:42:16.539Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42088|2024-07-23T17:13:03.784Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42088</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor JPG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPG files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22088.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42088|2024-07-23T17:13:03.784Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39486|2024-07-23T17:13:14.370Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39486</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor JP2 File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JP2 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19264.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39486|2024-07-23T17:13:14.370Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27323|2024-06-19T19:25:27.382Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27323</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor Updater Improper Certificate Validation Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the update functionality. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the certificate presented by the server. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-22224.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27323|2024-06-19T19:25:27.382Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:48:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39487|2024-06-04T17:27:08.722Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39487</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor util Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of util objects. By performing actions in JavaScript, an attacker can trigger a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19483.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39487|2024-06-04T17:27:08.722Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39491|2024-06-04T17:27:08.293Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39491</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor TIF File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of TIF files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19638.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39491|2024-06-04T17:27:08.293Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39501|2024-06-04T17:27:07.871Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39501</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor OXPS File Parsing Untrusted Pointer Dereference Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of OXPS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied value prior to dereferencing it as a pointer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20034.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39501|2024-06-04T17:27:07.871Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39500|2024-06-04T17:27:06.994Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39500</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor JPG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPG files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19950.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39500|2024-06-04T17:27:06.994Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39490|2024-06-04T17:27:06.546Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39490</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. Crafted data in a PDF file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19636.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39490|2024-06-04T17:27:06.546Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39486|2024-05-03T02:10:49.509Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39486</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor JP2 File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JP2 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19264.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39486|2024-05-03T02:10:49.509Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39497|2024-06-04T17:27:04.465Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39497</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor JPG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPG files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19947.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39497|2024-06-04T17:27:04.465Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39506|2024-06-05T20:36:50.330Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39506</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor createDataObject Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the createDataObject method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-20594.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39506|2024-06-05T20:36:50.330Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39496|2024-06-04T17:27:01.016Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39496</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor TIF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of TIF files. Crafted data in a TIF file can trigger a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19658.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39496|2024-06-04T17:27:01.016Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39505|2024-06-04T17:27:00.580Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39505</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor Net.HTTP.requests Exposed Dangerous Function Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the Net.HTTP.requests method. The issue results from the exposure of a dangerous function. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-20211.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39505|2024-06-04T17:27:00.580Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39495|2024-06-04T17:27:00.161Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39495</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor readFileIntoStream Exposed Dangerous Function Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the readFileIntoStream method. The issue results from the exposure of a dangerous function. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-19657.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39495|2024-06-04T17:27:00.161Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39483|2024-06-04T17:26:59.704Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39483</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor J2K File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of J2K files. Crafted data in a J2K file can trigger a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18308.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39483|2024-06-04T17:26:59.704Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39499|2024-06-04T17:26:58.873Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39499</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor JPG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPG files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19949.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39499|2024-06-04T17:26:58.873Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39498|2024-06-04T17:26:57.617Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39498</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor JPG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPG files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19948.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39498|2024-06-04T17:26:57.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39494|2024-06-05T20:36:09.628Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39494</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor OXPS File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of OXPS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19655.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39494|2024-06-05T20:36:09.628Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39504|2024-06-04T17:26:56.329Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39504</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor OXPS File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of OXPS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20037.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39504|2024-06-04T17:26:56.329Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39489|2024-06-04T17:26:55.476Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39489</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor TIF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of TIF files. Crafted data in a TIF file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19488.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39489|2024-06-04T17:26:55.476Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39503|2024-06-04T17:26:54.634Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39503</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor OXPS File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of OXPS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20036.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39503|2024-06-04T17:26:54.634Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39493|2024-06-05T20:33:30.335Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39493</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor exportAsText Exposed Dangerous Method Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the exportAsText method. The application exposes a JavaScript interface that allows writing arbitrary files. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-19649.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39493|2024-06-05T20:33:30.335Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39485|2024-06-04T17:26:53.393Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39485</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor JP2 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JP2 files. Crafted data in a JP2 file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19189.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39485|2024-06-04T17:26:53.393Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39484|2024-06-04T17:26:52.983Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39484</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Uninitialized Variable Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of memory prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18493.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39484|2024-06-04T17:26:52.983Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39492|2024-06-05T20:33:57.433Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39492</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19640.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39492|2024-06-05T20:33:57.433Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39502|2024-06-04T17:26:52.111Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39502</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor OXPS File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of OXPS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20035.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39502|2024-06-04T17:26:52.111Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39488|2024-06-04T17:26:51.690Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39488</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor TIF File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of TIF files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19487.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39488|2024-06-04T17:26:51.690Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:10:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32160|2024-06-04T17:26:29.675Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32160</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. Crafted data in a PDF file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-17767.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32160|2024-06-04T17:26:29.675Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32161|2024-06-04T17:26:28.372Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32161</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. Crafted data in a PDF file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-17778.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32161|2024-06-04T17:26:28.372Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32158|2024-06-04T17:26:08.767Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32158</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. Crafted data in a PDF file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-17764.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32158|2024-06-04T17:26:08.767Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32159|2024-06-04T17:26:08.348Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32159</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. Crafted data in a PDF file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-17765.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32159|2024-06-04T17:26:08.348Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42080|2024-06-04T17:25:43.019Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42080</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21877.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42080|2024-06-04T17:25:43.019Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42079|2024-06-04T17:25:40.763Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42079</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor J2K File Parsing Uninitialized Variable Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of J2K files. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of memory prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21851.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42079|2024-06-04T17:25:40.763Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42055|2024-06-04T17:25:39.880Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42055</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20928.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42055|2024-06-04T17:25:39.880Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42110|2024-06-04T17:25:39.455Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42110</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22137.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42110|2024-06-04T17:25:39.455Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42043|2024-06-04T17:25:38.976Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42043</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20887.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42043|2024-06-04T17:25:38.976Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42106|2024-06-04T17:25:38.533Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42106</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files.
The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22133.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42106|2024-06-04T17:25:38.533Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42063|2024-06-04T17:25:37.640Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42063</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20943.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42063|2024-06-04T17:25:37.640Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42075|2024-06-04T17:25:36.754Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42075</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor JPG File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPG files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21691.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42075|2024-06-04T17:25:36.754Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42059|2024-06-04T17:25:36.289Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42059</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor U3D File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.
. Was ZDI-CAN-20932.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42059|2024-06-04T17:25:36.289Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42058|2024-06-04T17:25:35.857Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42058</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files.
The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20931.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42058|2024-06-04T17:25:35.857Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42074|2024-06-04T17:25:35.407Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42074</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor addScript Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the addScript method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a type confusion condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21338.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42074|2024-06-04T17:25:35.407Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42062|2024-06-04T17:25:34.468Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42062</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor U3D File Parsing Uninitialized Variable Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of memory prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20935.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42062|2024-06-04T17:25:34.468Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42042|2024-06-06T12:30:05.962Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42042</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor App Object Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of App objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20848.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42042|2024-06-06T12:30:05.962Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42107|2024-06-04T17:25:33.603Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42107</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files.
The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22134.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42107|2024-06-04T17:25:33.603Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42054|2024-06-04T17:25:33.192Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42054</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20927.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42054|2024-06-04T17:25:33.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42111|2024-06-04T17:25:32.754Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42111</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor JPG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPG files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22138.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42111|2024-06-04T17:25:32.754Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42078|2024-06-04T17:25:31.438Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42078</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor JP2 File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JP2 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21850.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42078|2024-06-04T17:25:31.438Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42081|2024-06-04T17:25:30.582Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42081</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21878.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42081|2024-06-04T17:25:30.582Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42065|2024-06-04T17:25:29.682Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42065</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor JP2 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JP2 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20973.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42065|2024-06-04T17:25:29.682Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42073|2024-06-04T17:25:28.349Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42073</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor Doc Object Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. By performing actions in JavaScript, an attacker can trigger a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21323.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42073|2024-06-04T17:25:28.349Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42049|2024-06-06T12:31:01.943Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42049</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20920.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42049|2024-06-06T12:31:01.943Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42086|2024-06-04T17:25:26.993Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42086</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22062.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42086|2024-06-04T17:25:26.993Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42069|2024-06-04T17:25:26.563Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42069</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21166.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42069|2024-06-04T17:25:26.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42053|2024-06-04T17:25:25.687Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42053</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20926.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42053|2024-06-04T17:25:25.687Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42045|2024-06-04T17:25:25.226Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42045</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor J2K File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of J2K files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20906.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42045|2024-06-04T17:25:25.226Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42044|2024-05-03T02:12:29.609Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42044</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. his vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20889.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42044|2024-05-03T02:12:29.609Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42052|2024-06-04T17:25:24.334Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42052</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20925.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42052|2024-06-04T17:25:24.334Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42087|2024-06-04T17:25:22.134Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42087</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22064.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42087|2024-06-04T17:25:22.134Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42068|2024-06-04T17:25:21.658Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42068</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor JB2 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JB2 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. . Was ZDI-CAN-20985.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42068|2024-06-04T17:25:21.658Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42048|2024-06-04T17:25:21.210Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42048</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor J2K File Parsing Uninitialized Variable Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of J2K files. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of memory prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20909.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42048|2024-06-04T17:25:21.210Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42072|2024-05-03T02:12:51.058Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42072</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor JPC File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPC files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21311.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42072|2024-05-03T02:12:51.058Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42064|2024-06-04T17:25:19.917Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42064</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20944.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42064|2024-06-04T17:25:19.917Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42071|2024-06-04T17:25:18.579Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42071</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21291.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42071|2024-06-04T17:25:18.579Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42067|2024-06-04T17:25:18.152Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42067</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor JB2 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JB2 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20984.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42067|2024-06-04T17:25:18.152Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42088|2024-05-03T02:13:02.897Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42088</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor JPG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPG files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22088.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42088|2024-05-03T02:13:02.897Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42047|2024-06-04T17:25:17.291Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42047</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor JP2 File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JP2 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20908.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42047|2024-06-04T17:25:17.291Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42051|2024-06-04T17:25:16.412Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42051</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20924.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42051|2024-06-04T17:25:16.412Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42084|2024-06-04T17:25:15.528Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42084</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21974.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42084|2024-06-04T17:25:15.528Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42085|2024-06-04T17:25:15.082Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42085</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files.  The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22061.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42085|2024-06-04T17:25:15.082Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42050|2024-06-04T17:25:14.247Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42050</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20921.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42050|2024-06-04T17:25:14.247Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42046|2024-06-06T12:30:44.525Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42046</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor J2K File Parsing Uninitialized Variable Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of J2K files. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of memory prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20907.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42046|2024-06-06T12:30:44.525Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42066|2024-06-04T17:25:12.957Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42066</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor J2K File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of J2K files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20974.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42066|2024-06-04T17:25:12.957Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42070|2024-06-04T17:25:11.612Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42070</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor Doc Object Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21179.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42070|2024-06-04T17:25:11.612Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42041|2024-06-04T17:25:10.334Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42041</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20845.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42041|2024-06-04T17:25:10.334Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42112|2024-06-04T17:25:09.892Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42112</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files.
The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22146.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42112|2024-06-04T17:25:09.892Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42057|2024-05-03T02:12:39.677Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42057</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20930.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42057|2024-05-03T02:12:39.677Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42082|2024-06-04T17:25:08.179Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42082</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor JPG File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPG files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21944.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42082|2024-06-04T17:25:08.179Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42108|2024-06-04T17:25:07.727Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42108</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22135.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42108|2024-06-04T17:25:07.727Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42077|2024-06-04T17:25:07.283Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42077</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21818.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42077|2024-06-04T17:25:07.283Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42061|2024-06-04T17:25:05.552Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42061</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20934.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42061|2024-06-04T17:25:05.552Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42060|2024-06-04T17:25:05.130Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42060</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20933.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42060|2024-06-04T17:25:05.130Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42076|2024-06-04T17:25:04.132Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42076</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21762.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42076|2024-06-04T17:25:04.132Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42109|2024-06-04T17:25:03.709Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42109</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22136.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42109|2024-06-04T17:25:03.709Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42083|2024-06-04T17:25:02.843Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42083</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor JPG File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPG files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21967.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42083|2024-06-04T17:25:02.843Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42113|2024-06-04T17:25:01.979Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42113</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22147.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42113|2024-06-04T17:25:01.979Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42056|2024-06-04T17:25:01.575Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42056</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor U3D File Parsing Uninitialized Variable Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of memory prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20929.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42056|2024-06-04T17:25:01.575Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42040|2024-06-04T17:25:00.729Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42040</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor mailForm Use-After-Free Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the mailForm method. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20663.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42040|2024-06-04T17:25:00.729Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27342|2024-06-04T17:25:00.355Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27342</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Untrusted Pointer Dereference Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied value prior to dereferencing it as a pointer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18766.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27342|2024-06-04T17:25:00.355Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27339|2024-06-04T17:24:59.883Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27339</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor PNG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PNG files. Crafted data in a PNG file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18663.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27339|2024-06-04T17:24:59.883Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27338|2024-06-04T17:24:55.760Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27338</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor TIF File Parsing Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of TIF files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18612.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27338|2024-06-04T17:24:55.760Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27343|2024-06-04T17:24:55.323Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27343</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files. Crafted data in a EMF can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18790.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27343|2024-06-04T17:24:55.323Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27348|2024-06-04T17:24:54.916Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27348</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor TIF File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of TIF files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19108.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27348|2024-06-04T17:24:54.916Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27344|2024-06-04T17:24:53.240Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27344</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. Crafted data in a PDF file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19302.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27344|2024-06-04T17:24:53.240Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27345|2024-06-04T17:24:50.390Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27345</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. Crafted data in a PDF file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19303.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27345|2024-06-04T17:24:50.390Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27340|2024-06-04T17:24:44.556Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27340</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor PNG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PNG files. Crafted data in a PNG file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18665.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27340|2024-06-04T17:24:44.556Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27337|2024-06-04T17:24:43.747Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27337</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. Crafted data in a PDF file can trigger a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18494.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27337|2024-06-04T17:24:43.747Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27341|2024-06-04T17:24:42.517Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27341</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor TIF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of TIF files. Crafted data in a TIF file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18729.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27341|2024-06-04T17:24:42.517Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40473|2024-06-04T17:19:08.690Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40473</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor Doc Object Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. By performing actions in JavaScript, an attacker can trigger a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20891.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40473|2024-06-04T17:19:08.690Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40469|2024-06-05T20:37:32.451Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40469</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor XPS File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of XPS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20621.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40469|2024-06-05T20:37:32.451Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40468|2024-06-04T17:19:04.999Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40468</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files. Crafted data in an EMF file can trigger a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20620.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40468|2024-06-04T17:19:04.999Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40472|2024-06-04T17:19:03.214Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40472</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor JavaScript String Untrusted Pointer Dereference Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of strings. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied value prior to dereferencing it as a pointer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20730.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40472|2024-06-04T17:19:03.214Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40471|2024-06-05T20:37:49.751Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40471</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor App Untrusted Pointer Dereference Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of App objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied value prior to dereferencing it as a pointer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20729.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40471|2024-06-05T20:37:49.751Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40470|2024-06-04T17:18:54.497Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40470</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor JP2 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JP2 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20622.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40470|2024-06-04T17:18:54.497Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:11:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27332|2024-04-01T21:51:21.781Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27332</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor JPG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPG files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22288.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27332|2024-04-01T21:51:21.781Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:51:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27324|2024-06-04T17:47:32.018Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27324</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor TIF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of TIF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22270.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27324|2024-06-04T17:47:32.018Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:49:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27328|2024-06-04T17:47:27.757Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27328</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of EMF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22280.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27328|2024-06-04T17:47:27.757Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:50:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27329|2024-06-04T17:47:26.103Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27329</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor XPS File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of XPS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22285.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27329|2024-06-04T17:47:26.103Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:50:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27325|2024-06-04T17:47:20.571Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27325</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22275.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27325|2024-06-04T17:47:20.571Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:49:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27323|2024-04-01T21:48:49.889Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27323</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor Updater Improper Certificate Validation Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the update functionality. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the certificate presented by the server. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-22224.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27323|2024-04-01T21:48:49.889Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:48:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27326|2024-06-04T17:46:42.524Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27326</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor XPS File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of XPS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22276.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27326|2024-06-04T17:46:42.524Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:49:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27330|2024-06-04T17:46:40.860Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27330</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22286.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27330|2024-06-04T17:46:40.860Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:50:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27331|2024-04-01T21:51:10.605Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27331</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22287.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27331|2024-04-01T21:51:10.605Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:51:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27327|2024-04-01T21:50:07.123Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27327</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22277.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27327|2024-04-01T21:50:07.123Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:50:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32159|2024-06-18T18:24:29.788Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32159</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. Crafted data in a PDF file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-17765.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32159|2024-06-18T18:24:29.788Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27327|2024-07-19T21:07:20.480Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27327</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22277.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27327|2024-07-19T21:07:20.480Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:50:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42072|2024-07-24T17:27:06.823Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42072</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor JPC File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPC files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21311.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42072|2024-07-24T17:27:06.823Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42057|2024-07-24T17:30:44.226Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42057</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20930.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42057|2024-07-24T17:30:44.226Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27327|2024-08-02T00:34:51.416Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27327</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22277.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27327|2024-08-02T00:34:51.416Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:50:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27330|2024-08-02T00:34:51.378Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27330</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22286.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27330|2024-08-02T00:34:51.378Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:50:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27324|2024-08-02T00:34:50.997Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27324</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor TIF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of TIF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22270.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27324|2024-08-02T00:34:50.997Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:49:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27323|2024-08-02T00:34:51.004Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27323</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor Updater Improper Certificate Validation Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the update functionality. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the certificate presented by the server. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-22224.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27323|2024-08-02T00:34:51.004Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:48:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27331|2024-08-02T00:34:51.407Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27331</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22287.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27331|2024-08-02T00:34:51.407Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:51:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27329|2024-08-02T00:34:51.395Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27329</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor XPS File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of XPS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22285.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27329|2024-08-02T00:34:51.395Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:50:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27326|2024-08-02T00:34:51.382Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27326</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor XPS File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of XPS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22276.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27326|2024-08-02T00:34:51.382Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:49:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27332|2024-08-02T00:34:51.377Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27332</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor JPG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPG files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22288.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27332|2024-08-02T00:34:51.377Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:51:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27328|2024-08-02T00:34:51.335Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27328</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of EMF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22280.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27328|2024-08-02T00:34:51.335Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:50:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27325|2024-08-02T00:34:51.003Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27325</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22275.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27325|2024-08-02T00:34:51.003Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:49:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32159|2024-08-02T15:10:23.757Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32159</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. Crafted data in a PDF file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-17765.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32159|2024-08-02T15:10:23.757Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32160|2024-08-02T15:10:23.644Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32160</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. Crafted data in a PDF file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-17767.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32160|2024-08-02T15:10:23.644Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32161|2024-08-02T15:10:23.817Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32161</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. Crafted data in a PDF file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-17778.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32161|2024-08-02T15:10:23.817Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32158|2024-08-02T15:10:23.976Z -- pdf-xchange -- pdf-xchange%20editor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32158</link>
      <description>PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. Crafted data in a PDF file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-17764.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32158|2024-08-02T15:10:23.976Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
