<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for PDF-XChange -- PDF-XChange Editor</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/pdf-xchange/pdf-xchange%20editor.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for PDF-XChange -- PDF-XChange Editor</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 21:54:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-27332|2024-04-01T21:51:21.781Z -- PDF-XChange -- PDF-XChange Editor
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27332</link><description>PDF-XChange Editor JPG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPG files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22288.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27332|2024-04-01T21:51:21.781Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:51:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27324|2024-04-01T21:49:02.786Z -- PDF-XChange -- PDF-XChange Editor
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27324</link><description>PDF-XChange Editor TIF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of TIF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22270.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27324|2024-04-01T21:49:02.786Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:49:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27328|2024-04-01T21:50:17.719Z -- PDF-XChange -- PDF-XChange Editor
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27328</link><description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of EMF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22280.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27328|2024-04-01T21:50:17.719Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:50:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27329|2024-04-01T21:50:29.908Z -- PDF-XChange -- PDF-XChange Editor
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27329</link><description>PDF-XChange Editor XPS File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of XPS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22285.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27329|2024-04-01T21:50:29.908Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:50:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27325|2024-04-01T21:49:14.636Z -- PDF-XChange -- PDF-XChange Editor
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27325</link><description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22275.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27325|2024-04-01T21:49:14.636Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:49:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27323|2024-04-01T21:48:49.889Z -- PDF-XChange -- PDF-XChange Editor
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27323</link><description>PDF-XChange Editor Updater Improper Certificate Validation Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the update functionality. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the certificate presented by the server. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-22224.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27323|2024-04-01T21:48:49.889Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:48:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27326|2024-04-01T21:49:28.789Z -- PDF-XChange -- PDF-XChange Editor
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27326</link><description>PDF-XChange Editor XPS File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of XPS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22276.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27326|2024-04-01T21:49:28.789Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27330|2024-04-01T21:50:56.687Z -- PDF-XChange -- PDF-XChange Editor
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27330</link><description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22286.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27330|2024-04-01T21:50:56.687Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:50:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27331|2024-04-01T21:51:10.605Z -- PDF-XChange -- PDF-XChange Editor
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27331</link><description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22287.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27331|2024-04-01T21:51:10.605Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:51:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27327|2024-04-01T21:50:07.123Z -- PDF-XChange -- PDF-XChange Editor
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27327</link><description>PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22277.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27327|2024-04-01T21:50:07.123Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:50:07 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>