<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for pjsip -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/pjsip/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for pjsip -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 08:23:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23608|2024-08-03T03:43:46.964Z -- pjsip -- pjproject
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23608</link>
      <description>PJSIP is a free and open source multimedia communication library written in C language implementing standard based protocols such as SIP, SDP, RTP, STUN, TURN, and ICE. In versions up to and including 2.11.1 when in a dialog set (or forking) scenario, a hash key shared by multiple UAC dialogs can potentially be prematurely freed when one of the dialogs is destroyed . The issue may cause a dialog set to be registered in the hash table multiple times (with different hash keys) leading to undefined behavior such as dialog list collision which eventually leading to endless loop. A patch is available in commit db3235953baa56d2fb0e276ca510fefca751643f which will be included in the next release. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23608|2024-08-03T03:43:46.964Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23537|2024-08-03T03:43:46.453Z -- pjsip -- pjproject
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23537</link>
      <description>PJSIP is a free and open source multimedia communication library written in C language implementing standard based protocols such as SIP, SDP, RTP, STUN, TURN, and ICE. Buffer overread is possible when parsing a specially crafted STUN message with unknown attribute. The vulnerability affects applications that uses STUN including PJNATH and PJSUA-LIB. The patch is available as a commit in the master branch (2.13.1).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23537|2024-08-03T03:43:46.453Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 18:50:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24786|2024-08-03T04:20:50.463Z -- pjsip -- pjproject
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24786</link>
      <description>PJSIP is a free and open source multimedia communication library written in C. PJSIP versions 2.12 and prior do not parse incoming RTCP feedback RPSI (Reference Picture Selection Indication) packet, but any app that directly uses pjmedia_rtcp_fb_parse_rpsi() will be affected. A patch is available in the `master` branch of the `pjsip/pjproject` GitHub repository. There are currently no known workarounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24786|2024-08-03T04:20:50.463Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24764|2024-08-03T04:20:50.535Z -- pjsip -- pjproject
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24764</link>
      <description>PJSIP is a free and open source multimedia communication library written in C. Versions 2.12 and prior contain a stack buffer overflow vulnerability that affects PJSUA2 users or users that call the API `pjmedia_sdp_print(), pjmedia_sdp_media_print()`. Applications that do not use PJSUA2 and do not directly call `pjmedia_sdp_print()` or `pjmedia_sdp_media_print()` should not be affected. A patch is available on the `master` branch of the `pjsip/pjproject` GitHub repository. There are currently no known workarounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24764|2024-08-03T04:20:50.535Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23547|2024-08-03T03:43:46.563Z -- pjsip -- pjproject
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23547</link>
      <description>PJSIP is a free and open source multimedia communication library written in C language implementing standard based protocols such as SIP, SDP, RTP, STUN, TURN, and ICE. This issue is similar to GHSA-9pfh-r8x4-w26w. Possible buffer overread when parsing a certain STUN message. The vulnerability affects applications that uses STUN including PJNATH and PJSUA-LIB. The patch is available as commit in the master branch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23547|2024-08-03T03:43:46.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 14:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24793|2024-08-03T04:20:50.432Z -- pjsip -- pjproject
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24793</link>
      <description>PJSIP is a free and open source multimedia communication library written in C. A buffer overflow vulnerability in versions 2.12 and prior affects applications that use PJSIP DNS resolution. It doesn't affect PJSIP users who utilize an external resolver. This vulnerability is related to CVE-2023-27585. The difference is that this issue is in parsing the query record `parse_rr()`, while the issue in CVE-2023-27585 is in `parse_query()`. A patch is available in the `master` branch of the `pjsip/pjproject` GitHub repository. A workaround is to disable DNS resolution in PJSIP config (by setting `nameserver_count` to zero) or use an external resolver instead.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24793|2024-08-03T04:20:50.432Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21722|2024-08-03T02:53:35.473Z -- pjsip -- pjproject
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21722</link>
      <description>PJSIP is a free and open source multimedia communication library written in C language implementing standard based protocols such as SIP, SDP, RTP, STUN, TURN, and ICE. In version 2.11.1 and prior, there are various cases where it is possible that certain incoming RTP/RTCP packets can potentially cause out-of-bound read access. This issue affects all users that use PJMEDIA and accept incoming RTP/RTCP. A patch is available as a commit in the `master` branch. There are no known workarounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21722|2024-08-03T02:53:35.473Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31031|2024-08-03T07:03:40.299Z -- pjsip -- pjproject
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31031</link>
      <description>PJSIP is a free and open source multimedia communication library written in C language implementing standard based protocols such as SIP, SDP, RTP, STUN, TURN, and ICE. In versions prior to and including 2.12.1 a stack buffer overflow vulnerability affects PJSIP users that use STUN in their applications, either by: setting a STUN server in their account/media config in PJSUA/PJSUA2 level, or directly using `pjlib-util/stun_simple` API. A patch is available in commit 450baca which should be included in the next release. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31031|2024-08-03T07:03:40.299Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24754|2024-08-03T04:20:50.210Z -- pjsip -- pjproject
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24754</link>
      <description>PJSIP is a free and open source multimedia communication library written in C language. In versions prior to and including 2.12 PJSIP there is a stack-buffer overflow vulnerability which only impacts PJSIP users who accept hashed digest credentials (credentials with data_type `PJSIP_CRED_DATA_DIGEST`). This issue has been patched in the master branch of the PJSIP repository and will be included with the next release. Users unable to upgrade need to check that the hashed digest data length must be equal to `PJSIP_MD5STRLEN` before passing to PJSIP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24754|2024-08-03T04:20:50.210Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24763|2024-08-03T04:20:50.527Z -- pjsip -- pjproject
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24763</link>
      <description>PJSIP is a free and open source multimedia communication library written in the C language. Versions 2.12 and prior contain a denial-of-service vulnerability that affects PJSIP users that consume PJSIP's XML parsing in their apps. Users are advised to update. There are no known workarounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24763|2024-08-03T04:20:50.527Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24792|2024-08-03T04:20:50.513Z -- pjsip -- pjproject
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24792</link>
      <description>PJSIP is a free and open source multimedia communication library written in C. A denial-of-service vulnerability affects applications on a 32-bit systems that use PJSIP versions 2.12 and prior to play/read invalid WAV files. The vulnerability occurs when reading WAV file data chunks with length greater than 31-bit integers. The vulnerability does not affect 64-bit apps and should not affect apps that only plays trusted WAV files. A patch is available on the `master` branch of the `pjsip/project` GitHub repository. As a workaround, apps can reject a WAV file received from an unknown source or validate the file first.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24792|2024-08-03T04:20:50.513Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21723|2024-08-03T02:53:35.431Z -- pjsip -- pjproject
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21723</link>
      <description>PJSIP is a free and open source multimedia communication library written in C language implementing standard based protocols such as SIP, SDP, RTP, STUN, TURN, and ICE. In versions 2.11.1 and prior, parsing an incoming SIP message that contains a malformed multipart can potentially cause out-of-bound read access. This issue affects all PJSIP users that accept SIP multipart. The patch is available as commit in the `master` branch. There are no known workarounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21723|2024-08-03T02:53:35.431Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
