<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for jupyter-server -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/jupyter-server/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for jupyter-server -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 09:23:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24757|2024-08-03T04:20:50.212Z -- jupyter-server -- jupyter_server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24757</link>
      <description>The Jupyter Server provides the backend (i.e. the core services, APIs, and REST endpoints) for Jupyter web applications. Prior to version 1.15.4, unauthorized actors can access sensitive information from server logs. Anytime a 5xx error is triggered, the auth cookie and other header values are recorded in Jupyter Server logs by default. Considering these logs do not require root access, an attacker can monitor these logs, steal sensitive auth/cookie information, and gain access to the Jupyter server. Jupyter Server version 1.15.4 contains a patch for this issue. There are currently no known workarounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24757|2024-08-03T04:20:50.212Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 20:20:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29241|2024-08-03T06:17:54.365Z -- jupyter-server -- jupyter_server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29241</link>
      <description>Jupyter Server provides the backend (i.e. the core services, APIs, and REST endpoints) for Jupyter web applications like Jupyter Notebook. Prior to version 1.17.1, if notebook server is started with a value of `root_dir` that contains the starting user's home directory, then the underlying REST API can be used to leak the access token assigned at start time by guessing/brute forcing the PID of the jupyter server. While this requires an authenticated user session, this URL can be used from a cross-site scripting payload or from a hooked or otherwise compromised browser to leak this access token to a malicious third party. This token can be used along with the REST API to interact with Jupyter services/notebooks such as modifying or overwriting critical files, such as .bashrc or .ssh/authorized_keys, allowing a malicious user to read potentially sensitive data and possibly gain control of the impacted system. This issue is patched in version 1.17.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29241|2024-08-03T06:17:54.365Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 20:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-35178|2024-08-02T03:07:46.873Z -- jupyter-server -- jupyter_server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35178</link>
      <description>The Jupyter Server provides the backend for Jupyter web applications. Jupyter Server on Windows has a vulnerability that lets unauthenticated attackers leak the NTLMv2 password hash of the Windows user running the Jupyter server. An attacker can crack this password to gain access to the Windows machine hosting the Jupyter server, or access other network-accessible machines or 3rd party services using that credential. Or an attacker perform an NTLM relay attack without cracking the credential to gain access to other network-accessible machines. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.14.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-35178|2024-08-02T03:07:46.873Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 15:37:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28188|2024-06-04T18:03:51.931Z -- jupyter-server -- jupyter-scheduler</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-28188</link>
      <description>Jupyter Scheduler is collection of extensions for programming jobs to run now or run on a schedule. The list of conda environments of `jupyter-scheduler` users maybe be exposed, potentially revealing information about projects that a specific user may be working on. This vulnerability has been patched in version(s) 1.1.6, 1.2.1, 1.8.2 and 2.5.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28188|2024-06-04T18:03:51.931Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:54:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-35178|2024-06-06T17:42:14.836Z -- jupyter-server -- jupyter_server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-35178</link>
      <description>The Jupyter Server provides the backend for Jupyter web applications. Jupyter Server on Windows has a vulnerability that lets unauthenticated attackers leak the NTLMv2 password hash of the Windows user running the Jupyter server. An attacker can crack this password to gain access to the Windows machine hosting the Jupyter server, or access other network-accessible machines or 3rd party services using that credential. Or an attacker perform an NTLM relay attack without cracking the credential to gain access to other network-accessible machines. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.14.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-35178|2024-06-06T17:42:14.836Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 15:37:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28188|2024-08-02T00:48:49.472Z -- jupyter-server -- jupyter-scheduler</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28188</link>
      <description>Jupyter Scheduler is collection of extensions for programming jobs to run now or run on a schedule. The list of conda environments of `jupyter-scheduler` users maybe be exposed, potentially revealing information about projects that a specific user may be working on. This vulnerability has been patched in version(s) 1.1.6, 1.2.1, 1.8.2 and 2.5.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28188|2024-08-02T00:48:49.472Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:54:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
