<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Parallels -- Access</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/parallels/access.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Parallels -- Access</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 20:22:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-34902|2024-08-03T09:22:10.726Z -- parallels -- access
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34902</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Access 6.5.4 (39316) Agent. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the Desktop Control Agent service. The service loads Qt plugins from an unsecured location. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-15787.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-34902|2024-08-03T09:22:10.726Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 14:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-34899|2024-08-03T09:22:10.747Z -- parallels -- access
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34899</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Access 6.5.4 (39316) Agent. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target host system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the Parallels service. By creating a symbolic link, an attacker can abuse the service to execute a file. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-16134.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-34899|2024-08-03T09:22:10.747Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 14:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-34900|2024-08-03T09:22:10.823Z -- parallels -- access
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34900</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Access 6.5.3 (39313) Agent. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the Dispatcher service. The service loads an OpenSSL configuration file from an unsecured location. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-15213.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-34900|2024-08-03T09:22:10.823Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 14:17:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-34901|2024-08-03T09:22:10.743Z -- parallels -- access
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34901</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Access 6.5.4 (39316) Agent. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target host system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the Parallels Service. The service executes files from an unsecured location. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-16137.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-34901|2024-08-03T09:22:10.743Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 14:17:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
