<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Parallels -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/parallels/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Parallels -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:22:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34857|2024-08-04T00:26:54.213Z -- parallels -- desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34857</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop 16.1.3 (49160). An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the Toolgate component. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the hypervisor. Was ZDI-CAN-13601.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34857|2024-08-04T00:26:54.213Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 17:10:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34867|2024-08-04T00:26:54.586Z -- parallels -- desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34867</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop 16.1.3-49160. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the Toolgate component. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in an uncontrolled memory allocation. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the hypervisor. Was ZDI-CAN-13672.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34867|2024-08-04T00:26:54.586Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 15:30:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17398|2024-08-04T13:53:16.541Z -- parallels -- desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17398</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose information on affected installations of Parallels Desktop 15.1.4. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the prl_hypervisor kext. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the kernel. Was ZDI-CAN-11302.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17398|2024-08-04T13:53:16.541Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 20:20:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34855|2024-08-04T00:26:54.672Z -- parallels -- desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34855</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Parallels Desktop 16.1.3 (49160). An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the Toolgate component. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of memory prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the hypervisor. Was ZDI-CAN-13592.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34855|2024-08-04T00:26:54.672Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 17:10:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17393|2024-08-04T13:53:16.561Z -- parallels -- desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17393</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose information on affected installations of Parallels Desktop 15.1.3-47255. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the prl_hypervisor kext. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result a pointer to be leaked after the handler is done. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the kernel. Was ZDI-CAN-10520.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17393|2024-08-04T13:53:16.561Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 20:20:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17401|2024-08-04T13:53:17.427Z -- parallels -- desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17401</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose sensitive informations on affected installations of Parallels Desktop 15.1.4. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the VGA virtual device. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated array. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to escalate privileges and execute code in the context of the hypervisor. Was ZDI-CAN-11363.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17401|2024-08-04T13:53:17.427Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 20:20:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8872|2024-08-04T10:12:10.964Z -- parallels -- desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8872</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Parallels Desktop 15.1.1-47117. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the xHCI component. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the hypervisor. Was ZDI-CAN-9428.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8872|2024-08-04T10:12:10.964Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 17:30:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17399|2024-08-04T13:53:17.053Z -- parallels -- desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17399</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop 15.1.4. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the prl_hypervisor kext. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute code in the context of the kernel. Was ZDI-CAN-11303.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17399|2024-08-04T13:53:17.053Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 20:20:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17402|2024-08-04T13:53:17.371Z -- parallels -- desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17402</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Parallels Desktop 15.1.4 (47270). An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the prl_hypervisor kext. By examining a log file, an attacker can disclose a memory address. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to escalate privileges and execute code in the context of the kernel. Was ZDI-CAN-11063.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17402|2024-08-04T13:53:17.371Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 20:20:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17396|2024-08-04T13:53:17.056Z -- parallels -- desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17396</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop 15.1.4. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the prl_hypervisor module. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in an integer overflow before allocating a buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute code in the context of the kernel. Was ZDI-CAN-11217.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17396|2024-08-04T13:53:17.056Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 20:20:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17391|2024-08-04T13:53:16.935Z -- parallels -- desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17391</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose information on affected installations of Parallels Desktop 15.1.3-47255. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handler for HOST_IOCTL_INIT_HYPERVISOR in the prl_hypervisor kext. The issue results from the exposure of dangerous method or function to the unprivileged user. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the kernel. Was ZDI-CAN-10518.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17391|2024-08-04T13:53:16.935Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 20:20:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8871|2024-08-04T10:12:10.962Z -- parallels -- desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8871</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop 15.1.0-47107 . An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the VGA virtual device. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute code in the context of the hypervisor. Was ZDI-CAN-9403.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8871|2024-08-04T10:12:10.962Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 17:30:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34854|2024-08-04T00:26:54.223Z -- parallels -- desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34854</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop 16.1.3 (49160). An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the Toolgate component. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in an uncontrolled memory allocation. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the hypervisor. Was ZDI-CAN-13544.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34854|2024-08-04T00:26:54.223Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 17:10:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8873|2024-08-04T10:12:10.985Z -- parallels -- desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8873</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop 15.1.2-47123. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the xHCI component. The issue results from the lack of proper locking when performing operations on an object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute code in the context of the hypervisor. Was ZDI-CAN-10031.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8873|2024-08-04T10:12:10.985Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 17:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34987|2024-08-04T00:26:55.806Z -- parallels -- desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34987</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop 16.5.1 (49187). An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the HDAudio virtual device. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the hypervisor. Was ZDI-CAN-14969.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34987|2024-08-04T00:26:55.806Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 19:05:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34868|2024-08-04T00:26:54.683Z -- parallels -- desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34868</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop 16.1.3-49160. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the Toolgate component. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in an uncontrolled memory allocation. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the hypervisor. Was ZDI-CAN-13712.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34868|2024-08-04T00:26:54.683Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 15:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17390|2024-08-04T13:53:16.481Z -- parallels -- desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17390</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop 15.1.2-47123. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the hypervisor kernel extension. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute code in the context of the hypervisor. Was ZDI-CAN-10030.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17390|2024-08-04T13:53:16.481Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 20:20:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34869|2024-08-04T00:26:54.668Z -- parallels -- desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34869</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop 16.1.3-49160. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the Toolgate component. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in an uncontrolled memory allocation. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the hypervisor. Was ZDI-CAN-13797.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34869|2024-08-04T00:26:54.668Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 15:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17392|2024-08-04T13:53:17.087Z -- parallels -- desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17392</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop 15.1.3-47255. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handler for HOST_IOCTL_SET_KERNEL_SYMBOLS in the prl_hypervisor kext. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied value prior to dereferencing it as a pointer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute code in the context of the kernel. Was ZDI-CAN-10519.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17392|2024-08-04T13:53:17.087Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 20:20:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34864|2024-08-04T00:26:54.660Z -- parallels -- desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34864</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop 16.1.3 (49160). An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the WinAppHelper component. The issue results from the lack of proper access control. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the hypervisor. Was ZDI-CAN-13543.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34864|2024-08-04T00:26:54.660Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 17:10:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17395|2024-08-04T13:53:17.015Z -- parallels -- desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17395</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop 15.1.4. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the prl_naptd process. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in an integer underflow before writing to memory. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute code in the context of the hypervisor. Was ZDI-CAN-11134.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17395|2024-08-04T13:53:17.015Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 20:20:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17394|2024-08-04T13:53:16.962Z -- parallels -- desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17394</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Parallels Desktop 15.1.4. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the OEMNet component. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to escalate privileges and execute code in the context of the hypervisor. Was ZDI-CAN-11132.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17394|2024-08-04T13:53:16.962Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 20:20:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17400|2024-08-04T13:53:16.542Z -- parallels -- desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17400</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop 15.1.4. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the prl_hypervisor kext. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute code in the context of the hypervisor. Was ZDI-CAN-11304.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17400|2024-08-04T13:53:16.542Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 20:20:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8876|2024-08-04T10:12:10.973Z -- parallels -- desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8876</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose information on affected installations of Parallels Desktop 15.1.2-47123. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the IOCTL handler. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the kernel. Was ZDI-CAN-10029.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8876|2024-08-04T10:12:10.973Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 17:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8875|2024-08-04T10:12:10.949Z -- parallels -- desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8875</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop 15.1.2-47123. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the IOCTL handler. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute code in the context of the kernel. Was ZDI-CAN-10028.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8875|2024-08-04T10:12:10.949Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 17:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34986|2024-08-04T00:26:55.736Z -- parallels -- desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34986</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop 16.5.0 (49183). An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the Parallels Service. By creating a symbolic link, an attacker can abuse the service to execute a file. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-13932.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34986|2024-08-04T00:26:55.736Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 19:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8874|2024-08-04T10:12:10.963Z -- parallels -- desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8874</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop 15.1.2-47123. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the xHCI component. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in an integer overflow before allocating a buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute code in the context of the hypervisor. Was ZDI-CAN-10032.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8874|2024-08-04T10:12:10.963Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 17:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-17397|2024-08-04T13:53:17.327Z -- parallels -- desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-17397</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop 15.1.4. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of network packets. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute code in the context of the hypervisor. Was ZDI-CAN-11253.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-17397|2024-08-04T13:53:17.327Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 20:20:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34856|2024-08-04T00:26:54.203Z -- parallels -- desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34856</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop 16.1.3 (49160). An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the virtio-gpu virtual device. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the hypervisor. Was ZDI-CAN-13581.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34856|2024-08-04T00:26:54.203Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 17:10:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8968|2024-08-04T10:19:19.490Z -- parallels -- parallels%20remote%20application%20server%20%28client%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8968</link>
      <description>Parallels Remote Application Server (RAS) allows a local attacker to retrieve certain profile password in clear text format by uploading a previously stored cyphered file by Parallels RAS. The confidentiality, availability and integrity of the information of the user could be compromised if an attacker is able to recover the profile password.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8968|2024-08-04T10:19:19.490Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50226|2024-08-02T22:09:49.693Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50226</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Updater Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target host system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Updater service. By creating a symbolic link, an attacker can abuse the service to move arbitrary files. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21227.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50226|2024-08-02T22:09:49.693Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50228|2024-08-02T22:09:49.714Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50228</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Updater Improper Verification of Cryptographic Signature Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target host system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Updater service. The issue results from the lack of proper verification of a cryptographic signature. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21817.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50228|2024-08-02T22:09:49.714Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50227|2024-08-02T22:09:49.804Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50227</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop virtio-gpu Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target in a guest system must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the virtio-gpu virtual device. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the hypervisor. Was ZDI-CAN-21260.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50227|2024-08-02T22:09:49.804Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6153|2024-08-01T21:33:04.986Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6153</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Updater Protection Mechanism Failure Software Downgrade Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to downgrade Parallels software on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target host system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Updater service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of version information before performing an update. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-19481.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6153|2024-08-01T21:33:04.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 20:12:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6154|2024-08-01T21:33:05.150Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6154</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Toolgate Heap-based Buffer Overflow Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Toolgate component. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user on the host system. Was ZDI-CAN-20450.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6154|2024-08-01T21:33:05.150Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 20:13:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6240|2024-08-01T21:33:05.241Z -- parallels -- parallels%20desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6240</link>
      <description>Improper privilege management vulnerability in Parallels Desktop Software, which affects versions earlier than 19.3.0. An attacker could add malicious code in a script and populate the BASH_ENV environment variable with the path to the malicious script, executing on application startup. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to escalate privileges on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6240|2024-08-01T21:33:05.241Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 13:33:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6154|2024-06-26T19:37:15.317Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6154</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Toolgate Heap-based Buffer Overflow Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Toolgate component. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user on the host system. Was ZDI-CAN-20450.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6154|2024-06-26T19:37:15.317Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 20:13:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6240|2024-06-21T13:33:53.197Z -- parallels -- parallels%20desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6240</link>
      <description>Improper privilege management vulnerability in Parallels Desktop Software, which affects versions earlier than 19.3.0. An attacker could add malicious code in a script and populate the BASH_ENV environment variable with the path to the malicious script, executing on application startup. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to escalate privileges on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6240|2024-06-21T13:33:53.197Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 13:33:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27323|2024-06-04T17:24:57.796Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27323</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Updater Time-Of-Check Time-Of-Use Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target host system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Updater service. By creating a symbolic link, an attacker can abuse the service to execute a file. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18150.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27323|2024-06-04T17:24:57.796Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27322|2024-06-04T17:24:57.377Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27322</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Service Improper Initialization Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target host system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Parallels Service. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of environment variables. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-17751.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27322|2024-06-04T17:24:57.377Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27325|2024-06-04T17:24:53.665Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27325</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Updater Improper Initialization Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target host system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Updater service. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of environment variables. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18253.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27325|2024-06-04T17:24:53.665Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27328|2024-06-04T17:24:51.606Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27328</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Toolgate XML Injection Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Toolgate component. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct an XML document. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the hypervisor. Was ZDI-CAN-19187.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27328|2024-06-04T17:24:51.606Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27324|2024-06-04T17:24:49.976Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27324</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Updater Improper Initialization Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target host system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Updater service. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of environment variables. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18229.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27324|2024-06-04T17:24:49.976Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27327|2024-06-04T17:24:47.922Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27327</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Toolgate Time-Of-Check Time-Of-Use Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Toolgate component. The issue results from the lack of proper locking when performing operations on an object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user on the host system. Was ZDI-CAN-18964.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27327|2024-06-04T17:24:47.922Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27326|2024-06-04T17:24:44.973Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27326</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Toolgate Directory Traversal Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Toolgate component. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user on the host system. Was ZDI-CAN-18933.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27326|2024-06-04T17:24:44.973Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50228|2024-06-04T17:18:08.643Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50228</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Updater Improper Verification of Cryptographic Signature Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target host system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Updater service. The issue results from the lack of proper verification of a cryptographic signature. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21817.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50228|2024-06-04T17:18:08.643Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50226|2024-06-04T17:17:41.724Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50226</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Updater Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target host system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Updater service. By creating a symbolic link, an attacker can abuse the service to move arbitrary files. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21227.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50226|2024-06-04T17:17:41.724Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50227|2024-06-04T17:17:39.918Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50227</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop virtio-gpu Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target in a guest system must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the virtio-gpu virtual device. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the hypervisor. Was ZDI-CAN-21260.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50227|2024-06-04T17:17:39.918Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6153|2024-06-20T20:12:35.143Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6153</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Updater Protection Mechanism Failure Software Downgrade Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to downgrade Parallels software on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target host system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Updater service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of version information before performing an update. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-19481.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6153|2024-06-20T20:12:35.143Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 20:12:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6154|2024-06-20T20:13:01.326Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6154</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Toolgate Heap-based Buffer Overflow Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Toolgate component. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user on the host system. Was ZDI-CAN-20450.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6154|2024-06-20T20:13:01.326Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 20:13:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6153|2024-06-21T14:16:56.822Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6153</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Updater Protection Mechanism Failure Software Downgrade Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to downgrade Parallels software on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target host system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Updater service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of version information before performing an update. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-19481.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6153|2024-06-21T14:16:56.822Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 20:12:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6240|2024-06-21T14:49:13.000Z -- parallels -- parallels%20desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6240</link>
      <description>Improper privilege management vulnerability in Parallels Desktop Software, which affects versions earlier than 19.3.0. An attacker could add malicious code in a script and populate the BASH_ENV environment variable with the path to the malicious script, executing on application startup. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to escalate privileges on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6240|2024-06-21T14:49:13.000Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 13:33:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6153|2024-06-28T03:55:25.310Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6153</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Updater Protection Mechanism Failure Software Downgrade Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to downgrade Parallels software on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target host system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Updater service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of version information before performing an update. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-19481.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6153|2024-06-28T03:55:25.310Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 20:12:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6154|2024-06-28T03:55:26.342Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6154</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Toolgate Heap-based Buffer Overflow Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Toolgate component. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user on the host system. Was ZDI-CAN-20450.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6154|2024-06-28T03:55:26.342Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 20:13:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27328|2024-08-02T12:09:43.366Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27328</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Toolgate XML Injection Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Toolgate component. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct an XML document. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the hypervisor. Was ZDI-CAN-19187.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27328|2024-08-02T12:09:43.366Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27322|2024-08-02T12:09:42.400Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27322</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Service Improper Initialization Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target host system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Parallels Service. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of environment variables. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-17751.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27322|2024-08-02T12:09:42.400Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27326|2024-08-02T12:09:43.417Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27326</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Toolgate Directory Traversal Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Toolgate component. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user on the host system. Was ZDI-CAN-18933.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27326|2024-08-02T12:09:43.417Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27325|2024-08-02T12:09:42.999Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27325</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Updater Improper Initialization Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target host system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Updater service. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of environment variables. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18253.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27325|2024-08-02T12:09:42.999Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27327|2024-08-02T12:09:42.300Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27327</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Toolgate Time-Of-Check Time-Of-Use Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Toolgate component. The issue results from the lack of proper locking when performing operations on an object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user on the host system. Was ZDI-CAN-18964.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27327|2024-08-02T12:09:42.300Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27324|2024-08-02T12:09:43.391Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27324</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Updater Improper Initialization Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target host system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Updater service. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of environment variables. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18229.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27324|2024-08-02T12:09:43.391Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27323|2024-08-02T12:09:42.882Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27323</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Updater Time-Of-Check Time-Of-Use Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target host system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Updater service. By creating a symbolic link, an attacker can abuse the service to execute a file. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18150.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27323|2024-08-02T12:09:42.882Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
