<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Parallels -- Desktop</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/parallels/desktop.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Parallels -- Desktop</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 20:22:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-34889|2024-08-03T09:22:10.733Z -- parallels -- desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34889</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop 17.1.1 (51537). An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the ACPI virtual device. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the hypervisor. Was ZDI-CAN-16554.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-34889|2024-08-03T09:22:10.733Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 20:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-34892|2024-08-03T09:22:10.650Z -- parallels -- desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34892</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop Parallels Desktop 17.1.1. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the update machanism. The issue results from the lack of proper locking when performing operations on an object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-16396.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-34892|2024-08-03T09:22:10.650Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 14:17:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-34891|2024-08-03T09:22:10.831Z -- parallels -- desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34891</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop Parallels Desktop 17.1.1. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the update machanism. The product sets incorrect permissions on sensitive files. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-16395.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-34891|2024-08-03T09:22:10.831Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 20:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-34890|2024-08-03T09:22:10.619Z -- parallels -- desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34890</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Parallels Desktop 17.1.1 (51537). An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the Parallels Tools component. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied value prior to dereferencing it as a pointer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the kernel. Was ZDI-CAN-16653.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-34890|2024-08-03T09:22:10.619Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 20:11:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27323|2024-08-02T12:09:42.882Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27323</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Updater Time-Of-Check Time-Of-Use Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target host system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Updater service. By creating a symbolic link, an attacker can abuse the service to execute a file. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18150.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27323|2024-08-02T12:09:42.882Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27324|2024-08-02T12:09:43.391Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27324</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Updater Improper Initialization Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target host system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Updater service. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of environment variables. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18229.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27324|2024-08-02T12:09:43.391Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27327|2024-08-02T12:09:42.300Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27327</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Toolgate Time-Of-Check Time-Of-Use Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Toolgate component. The issue results from the lack of proper locking when performing operations on an object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user on the host system. Was ZDI-CAN-18964.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27327|2024-08-02T12:09:42.300Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27325|2024-08-02T12:09:42.999Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27325</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Updater Improper Initialization Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target host system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Updater service. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of environment variables. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18253.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27325|2024-08-02T12:09:42.999Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27326|2024-08-02T12:09:43.417Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27326</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Toolgate Directory Traversal Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Toolgate component. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user on the host system. Was ZDI-CAN-18933.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27326|2024-08-02T12:09:43.417Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27322|2024-08-02T12:09:42.400Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27322</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Service Improper Initialization Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target host system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Parallels Service. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of environment variables. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-17751.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27322|2024-08-02T12:09:42.400Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27328|2024-08-02T12:09:43.366Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27328</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Toolgate XML Injection Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Toolgate component. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct an XML document. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the hypervisor. Was ZDI-CAN-19187.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27328|2024-08-02T12:09:43.366Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6154|2024-06-28T03:55:26.342Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6154</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Toolgate Heap-based Buffer Overflow Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Toolgate component. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user on the host system. Was ZDI-CAN-20450.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6154|2024-06-28T03:55:26.342Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 20:13:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6153|2024-06-28T03:55:25.310Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6153</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Updater Protection Mechanism Failure Software Downgrade Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to downgrade Parallels software on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target host system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Updater service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of version information before performing an update. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-19481.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6153|2024-06-28T03:55:25.310Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 20:12:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6153|2024-06-21T14:16:56.822Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6153</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Updater Protection Mechanism Failure Software Downgrade Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to downgrade Parallels software on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target host system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Updater service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of version information before performing an update. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-19481.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6153|2024-06-21T14:16:56.822Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 20:12:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27323|2024-06-04T17:24:57.796Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27323</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Updater Time-Of-Check Time-Of-Use Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target host system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Updater service. By creating a symbolic link, an attacker can abuse the service to execute a file. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18150.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27323|2024-06-04T17:24:57.796Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27322|2024-06-04T17:24:57.377Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27322</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Service Improper Initialization Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target host system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Parallels Service. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of environment variables. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-17751.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27322|2024-06-04T17:24:57.377Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27325|2024-06-04T17:24:53.665Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27325</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Updater Improper Initialization Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target host system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Updater service. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of environment variables. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18253.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27325|2024-06-04T17:24:53.665Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27328|2024-06-04T17:24:51.606Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27328</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Toolgate XML Injection Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Toolgate component. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct an XML document. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the hypervisor. Was ZDI-CAN-19187.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27328|2024-06-04T17:24:51.606Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27324|2024-06-04T17:24:49.976Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27324</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Updater Improper Initialization Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target host system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Updater service. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of environment variables. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18229.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27324|2024-06-04T17:24:49.976Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27327|2024-06-04T17:24:47.922Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27327</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Toolgate Time-Of-Check Time-Of-Use Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Toolgate component. The issue results from the lack of proper locking when performing operations on an object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user on the host system. Was ZDI-CAN-18964.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27327|2024-06-04T17:24:47.922Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27326|2024-06-04T17:24:44.973Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27326</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Toolgate Directory Traversal Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Toolgate component. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user on the host system. Was ZDI-CAN-18933.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27326|2024-06-04T17:24:44.973Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50228|2024-06-04T17:18:08.643Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50228</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Updater Improper Verification of Cryptographic Signature Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target host system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Updater service. The issue results from the lack of proper verification of a cryptographic signature. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21817.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50228|2024-06-04T17:18:08.643Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50226|2024-06-04T17:17:41.724Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50226</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Updater Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target host system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Updater service. By creating a symbolic link, an attacker can abuse the service to move arbitrary files. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21227.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50226|2024-06-04T17:17:41.724Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50227|2024-06-04T17:17:39.918Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50227</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop virtio-gpu Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target in a guest system must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the virtio-gpu virtual device. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the hypervisor. Was ZDI-CAN-21260.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50227|2024-06-04T17:17:39.918Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6153|2024-06-20T20:12:35.143Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6153</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Updater Protection Mechanism Failure Software Downgrade Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to downgrade Parallels software on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target host system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Updater service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of version information before performing an update. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-19481.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6153|2024-06-20T20:12:35.143Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 20:12:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6154|2024-06-20T20:13:01.326Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6154</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Toolgate Heap-based Buffer Overflow Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Toolgate component. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user on the host system. Was ZDI-CAN-20450.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6154|2024-06-20T20:13:01.326Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 20:13:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6154|2024-06-26T19:37:15.317Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6154</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Toolgate Heap-based Buffer Overflow Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Toolgate component. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user on the host system. Was ZDI-CAN-20450.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6154|2024-06-26T19:37:15.317Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 20:13:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6154|2024-08-01T21:33:05.150Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6154</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Toolgate Heap-based Buffer Overflow Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target guest system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Toolgate component. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user on the host system. Was ZDI-CAN-20450.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6154|2024-08-01T21:33:05.150Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 20:13:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6153|2024-08-01T21:33:04.986Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6153</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Updater Protection Mechanism Failure Software Downgrade Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to downgrade Parallels software on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target host system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Updater service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of version information before performing an update. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-19481.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6153|2024-08-01T21:33:04.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 20:12:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50227|2024-08-02T22:09:49.804Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50227</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop virtio-gpu Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target in a guest system must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the virtio-gpu virtual device. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the hypervisor. Was ZDI-CAN-21260.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50227|2024-08-02T22:09:49.804Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50228|2024-08-02T22:09:49.714Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50228</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Updater Improper Verification of Cryptographic Signature Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target host system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Updater service. The issue results from the lack of proper verification of a cryptographic signature. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21817.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50228|2024-08-02T22:09:49.714Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50226|2024-08-02T22:09:49.693Z -- parallels -- desktop</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50226</link>
      <description>Parallels Desktop Updater Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Parallels Desktop. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target host system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Updater service. By creating a symbolic link, an attacker can abuse the service to move arbitrary files. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-21227.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50226|2024-08-02T22:09:49.693Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
