<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Click Studios -- Passwordstate</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/click%20studios/passwordstate.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Click Studios -- Passwordstate</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 06:24:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4610|2024-08-03T01:48:38.943Z -- click%20studios -- passwordstate
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4610</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Click Studios Passwordstate and Passwordstate Browser Extension Chrome. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to risky cryptographic algorithm. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-216272.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4610|2024-08-03T01:48:38.943Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3875|2024-08-03T01:20:58.407Z -- click%20studios -- passwordstate
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3875</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Click Studios Passwordstate and Passwordstate Browser Extension Chrome. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component API. The manipulation leads to authentication bypass by assumed-immutable data. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-216244.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3875|2024-08-03T01:20:58.407Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3876|2024-08-03T01:20:58.476Z -- click%20studios -- passwordstate
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3876</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Click Studios Passwordstate and Passwordstate Browser Extension Chrome. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /api/browserextension/UpdatePassword/ of the component API. The manipulation of the argument PasswordID leads to authorization bypass. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-216245 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3876|2024-08-03T01:20:58.476Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4611|2024-08-03T01:48:38.704Z -- click%20studios -- passwordstate
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4611</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Click Studios Passwordstate and Passwordstate Browser Extension Chrome. This affects an unknown part. The manipulation leads to hard-coded credentials. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-216273 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in Click Studios Passwordstate and Passwordstate Browser Extension Chrome gefunden. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil. Mit der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine hard-coded credentials-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4611|2024-08-03T01:48:38.704Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4613|2024-08-03T01:48:38.997Z -- click%20studios -- passwordstate
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4613</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Click Studios Passwordstate and Passwordstate Browser Extension Chrome and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Browser Extension Provisioning. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-216275.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4613|2024-08-03T01:48:38.997Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4612|2024-08-03T01:48:38.894Z -- click%20studios -- passwordstate
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4612</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Click Studios Passwordstate and Passwordstate Browser Extension Chrome and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code. The manipulation leads to insufficiently protected credentials. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-216274 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4612|2024-08-03T01:48:38.894Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3877|2024-08-03T01:20:58.738Z -- click%20studios -- passwordstate
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3877</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Click Studios Passwordstate and Passwordstate Browser Extension Chrome. Affected is an unknown function of the component URL Field Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-216246 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3877|2024-08-03T01:20:58.738Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
