<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 23:22:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2553|2024-03-26T16:31:28.958Z -- sourcecodester -- product%20review%20rating%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2553</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Product Review Rating System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the component Rate Product Handler. The manipulation of the argument Your Name/Comment leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257052.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Product Review Rating System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Komponente Rate Product Handler. Durch Manipulation des Arguments Your Name/Comment mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2553|2024-03-26T16:31:28.958Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 04:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2575|2024-06-07T19:29:11.246Z -- sourcecodester -- employee%20task%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2575</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Employee Task Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /task-details.php. The manipulation of the argument task_id leads to authorization bypass. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-257078 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Employee Task Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei /task-details.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments task_id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine authorization bypass-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2575|2024-06-07T19:29:11.246Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 02:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
