<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Alphaware Simple E-Commerce System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/alphaware%20simple%20e-commerce%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Alphaware Simple E-Commerce System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 08:24:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1502|2024-08-02T05:49:11.674Z -- sourcecodester -- alphaware%20simple%20e-commerce%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1502</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Alphaware Simple E-Commerce System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file function/edit_customer.php. The manipulation of the argument firstname/mi/lastname with the input a' RLIKE SLEEP(5) AND 'dAbu'='dAbu leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-223406 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Alphaware Simple E-Commerce System 1.0 ausgemacht. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei function/edit_customer.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments firstname/mi/lastname mit der Eingabe a' RLIKE SLEEP(5) AND 'dAbu'='dAbu mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Sie ist schwierig ausnutzbar. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1502|2024-08-02T05:49:11.674Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 08:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1504|2024-08-02T05:49:11.654Z -- sourcecodester -- alphaware%20simple%20e-commerce%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1504</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Alphaware Simple E-Commerce System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code. The manipulation of the argument email/password with the input test1%40test.com ' AND (SELECT 6077 FROM (SELECT(SLEEP(5)))dltn) AND 'PhRa'='PhRa leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-223408.
In SourceCodester Alphaware Simple E-Commerce System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments email/password mit der Eingabe test1%40test.com ' AND (SELECT 6077 FROM (SELECT(SLEEP(5)))dltn) AND 'PhRa'='PhRa mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Das Ausnutzen gilt als schwierig. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1504|2024-08-02T05:49:11.654Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 08:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1503|2024-08-02T05:49:11.660Z -- sourcecodester -- alphaware%20simple%20e-commerce%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1503</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Alphaware Simple E-Commerce System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file admin/admin_index.php. The manipulation of the argument username/password with the input admin' AND (SELECT 8062 FROM (SELECT(SLEEP(5)))meUD)-- hLiX leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-223407.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Alphaware Simple E-Commerce System 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei admin/admin_index.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments username/password mit der Eingabe admin' AND (SELECT 8062 FROM (SELECT(SLEEP(5)))meUD)-- hLiX mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Sie ist schwierig auszunutzen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1503|2024-08-02T05:49:11.660Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 08:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0998|2024-08-02T05:32:46.085Z -- sourcecodester -- alphaware%20simple%20e-commerce%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0998</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Alphaware Simple E-Commerce System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /alphaware/summary.php of the component Payment Handler. The manipulation of the argument amount leads to improper access controls. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-221733 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Alphaware Simple E-Commerce System 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei /alphaware/summary.php der Komponente Payment Handler. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments amount mit unbekannten Daten kann eine improper access controls-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0998|2024-08-02T05:32:46.085Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 07:32:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
