<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Best Courier Management System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/best%20courier%20management%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Best Courier Management System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 22:22:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5272|2024-07-11T19:11:07.911Z -- sourcecodester -- best%20courier%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5272</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Best Courier Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file edit_parcel.php of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-240885 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Best Courier Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei edit_parcel.php der Komponente GET Parameter Handler. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5272|2024-07-11T19:11:07.911Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 16:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4945|2024-06-04T17:55:32.395Z -- sourcecodester -- best%20courier%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4945</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best Courier Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file view_parcel.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-264480.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Best Courier Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei view_parcel.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4945|2024-06-04T17:55:32.395Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 05:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
