<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Best Courier Management System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/best%20courier%20management%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Best Courier Management System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 08:24:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5272|2024-08-02T07:52:08.540Z -- sourcecodester -- best%20courier%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5272</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Best Courier Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file edit_parcel.php of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-240885 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Best Courier Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei edit_parcel.php der Komponente GET Parameter Handler. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5272|2024-08-02T07:52:08.540Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 16:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5270|2024-08-02T07:52:08.680Z -- sourcecodester -- best%20courier%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5270</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best Courier Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file view_parcel.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-240883.
In SourceCodester Best Courier Management System 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei view_parcel.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5270|2024-08-02T07:52:08.680Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 16:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5302|2024-08-02T07:52:08.526Z -- sourcecodester -- best%20courier%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5302</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in SourceCodester Best Courier Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Manage Account Page. The manipulation of the argument First Name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-240941 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Best Courier Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Komponente Manage Account Page. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments First Name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5302|2024-08-02T07:52:08.526Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 12:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5271|2024-08-02T07:52:08.477Z -- sourcecodester -- best%20courier%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5271</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best Courier Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file edit_parcel.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-240884.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Best Courier Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei edit_parcel.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments email mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5271|2024-08-02T07:52:08.477Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 16:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5273|2024-08-02T07:52:08.636Z -- sourcecodester -- best%20courier%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5273</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester Best Courier Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file manage_parcel_status.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-240886 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In SourceCodester Best Courier Management System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei manage_parcel_status.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5273|2024-08-02T07:52:08.636Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 16:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5269|2024-08-02T07:52:08.441Z -- sourcecodester -- best%20courier%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5269</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best Courier Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file parcel_list.php of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument s leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-240882 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Best Courier Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei parcel_list.php der Komponente GET Parameter Handler. Durch Manipulation des Arguments s mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5269|2024-08-02T07:52:08.441Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 15:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4945|2024-06-04T17:55:32.395Z -- sourcecodester -- best%20courier%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4945</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best Courier Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file view_parcel.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-264480.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Best Courier Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei view_parcel.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4945|2024-06-04T17:55:32.395Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 05:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4945|2024-08-01T20:55:10.344Z -- sourcecodester -- best%20courier%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4945</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best Courier Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file view_parcel.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-264480.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Best Courier Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei view_parcel.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4945|2024-08-01T20:55:10.344Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 05:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
