<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Best Courier Management System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/best%20courier%20management%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Best Courier Management System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 23:23:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6300|2024-10-10T20:33:30.982Z -- sourcecodester -- best%20courier%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6300</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Best Courier Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function. The manipulation of the argument page with the input &lt;/TiTlE&gt;&lt;ScRiPt&gt;alert(1)&lt;/ScRiPt&gt; leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-246126 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Best Courier Management System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock. Dank Manipulation des Arguments page mit der Eingabe &lt;/TiTlE&gt;&lt;ScRiPt&gt;alert(1)&lt;/ScRiPt&gt; mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6300|2024-10-10T20:33:30.982Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 23:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4945|2024-08-01T20:55:10.344Z -- sourcecodester -- best%20courier%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4945</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best Courier Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file view_parcel.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-264480.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Best Courier Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei view_parcel.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4945|2024-08-01T20:55:10.344Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 05:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4945|2024-06-04T17:55:32.395Z -- sourcecodester -- best%20courier%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4945</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best Courier Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file view_parcel.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-264480.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Best Courier Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei view_parcel.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4945|2024-06-04T17:55:32.395Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 05:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
