<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Book Store Management System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/book%20store%20management%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Book Store Management System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 13:22:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3452|2024-08-03T01:07:06.714Z -- sourcecodester -- book%20store%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3452</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Book Store Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /category.php. The manipulation of the argument category_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-210436.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3452|2024-08-03T01:07:06.714Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4229|2024-08-03T01:34:49.863Z -- sourcecodester -- book%20store%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4229</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Book Store Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /bsms_ci/index.php. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-214588.
In SourceCodester Book Store Management System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei /bsms_ci/index.php. Dank der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine improper access controls-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4229|2024-08-03T01:34:49.863Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4228|2024-08-03T01:34:49.879Z -- sourcecodester -- book%20store%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4228</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SourceCodester Book Store Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /bsms_ci/index.php/user/edit_user/. The manipulation of the argument password leads to information disclosure. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-214587.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Book Store Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei /bsms_ci/index.php/user/edit_user/. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine information disclosure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4228|2024-08-03T01:34:49.879Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3453|2024-08-03T01:07:06.644Z -- sourcecodester -- book%20store%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3453</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Book Store Management System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /transcation.php. The manipulation of the argument buyer_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The identifier VDB-210437 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3453|2024-08-03T01:07:06.644Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
