<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Canteen Management System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/canteen%20management%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Canteen Management System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 09:23:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1461|2024-08-02T05:49:11.454Z -- sourcecodester -- canteen%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1461</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Canteen Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function query of the file createCategories.php. The manipulation of the argument categoriesStatus leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. VDB-223306 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In SourceCodester Canteen Management System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Das betrifft die Funktion query der Datei createCategories.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments categoriesStatus mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1461|2024-08-02T05:49:11.454Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 08:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1475|2024-08-02T05:49:11.594Z -- sourcecodester -- canteen%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1475</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Canteen Management System 1.0. This issue affects the function query of the file createuser.php. The manipulation of the argument uemail leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-223337 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Canteen Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft die Funktion query der Datei createuser.php. Durch Manipulation des Arguments uemail mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1475|2024-08-02T05:49:11.594Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 14:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0679|2024-08-02T05:17:50.363Z -- sourcecodester -- canteen%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0679</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Canteen Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file removeUser.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-220220.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Canteen Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei removeUser.php. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Sie ist schwierig ausnutzbar. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0679|2024-08-02T05:17:50.363Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 12:56:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0781|2024-08-02T05:24:34.332Z -- sourcecodester -- canteen%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0781</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Canteen Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function query of the file removeOrder.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-220624.
In SourceCodester Canteen Management System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es die Funktion query der Datei removeOrder.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0781|2024-08-02T05:24:34.332Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 10:06:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1459|2024-08-02T05:49:11.539Z -- sourcecodester -- canteen%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1459</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Canteen Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file changeUsername.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-223304.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Canteen Management System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei changeUsername.php. Durch Manipulation des Arguments username mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1459|2024-08-02T05:49:11.539Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 07:48:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0571|2024-08-02T05:17:50.131Z -- sourcecodester -- canteen%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0571</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Canteen Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file createcustomer.php of the component Add Customer. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-219730 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In SourceCodester Canteen Management System 1.0 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle gefunden. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei createcustomer.php der Komponente Add Customer. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0571|2024-08-02T05:17:50.131Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 17:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
