<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Canteen Management System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/canteen%20management%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Canteen Management System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 15:22:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3584|2024-08-03T01:14:01.959Z -- sourcecodester -- canteen%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3584</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Canteen Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file edituser.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-211193 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3584|2024-08-03T01:14:01.959Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4234|2024-08-03T01:34:49.578Z -- sourcecodester -- canteen%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4234</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Canteen Management System. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects the function builtin_echo of the file youthappam/brand.php. The manipulation of the argument brand_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-214595.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4234|2024-08-03T01:34:49.578Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3583|2024-08-03T01:14:02.488Z -- sourcecodester -- canteen%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3583</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Canteen Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file login.php. The manipulation of the argument business leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-211192.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3583|2024-08-03T01:14:02.488Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4403|2024-08-03T01:41:44.383Z -- sourcecodester -- canteen%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4403</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Canteen Management System. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file ajax_represent.php. The manipulation of the argument customer_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-215272.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4403|2024-08-03T01:41:44.383Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4222|2024-08-03T01:34:49.688Z -- sourcecodester -- canteen%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4222</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Canteen Management System. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function query of the file ajax_invoice.php of the component POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument search leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-214523.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4222|2024-08-03T01:34:49.688Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4091|2024-08-03T01:27:54.504Z -- sourcecodester -- canteen%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4091</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Canteen Management System. It has been classified as problematic. This affects the function query of the file food.php. The manipulation of the argument product_name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-214359.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4091|2024-08-03T01:27:54.504Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4253|2024-08-03T01:34:49.949Z -- sourcecodester -- canteen%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4253</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Canteen Management System. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function builtin_echo of the file customer.php. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-214630 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4253|2024-08-03T01:34:49.949Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4252|2024-08-03T01:34:49.927Z -- sourcecodester -- canteen%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4252</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Canteen Management System. It has been classified as problematic. This affects the function builtin_echo of the file categories.php. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-214629 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4252|2024-08-03T01:34:49.927Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
