<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- E-Commerce System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/e-commerce%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- E-Commerce System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1506|2023-10-21T09:49:53.569Z -- sourcecodester -- e-commerce%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1506</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester E-Commerce System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file login.php. The manipulation of the argument U_USERNAME leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-223410 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in SourceCodester E-Commerce System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei login.php. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments U_USERNAME mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Sie gilt als schwierig auszunutzen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1506|2023-10-21T09:49:53.569Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 09:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1507|2023-10-21T09:51:06.750Z -- sourcecodester -- e-commerce%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1507</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester E-Commerce System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /ecommerce/admin/category/controller.php of the component Category Name Handler. The manipulation of the argument CATEGORY leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-223411.
In SourceCodester E-Commerce System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei /ecommerce/admin/category/controller.php der Komponente Category Name Handler. Dank Manipulation des Arguments CATEGORY mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1507|2023-10-21T09:51:06.750Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 10:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1557|2023-10-21T10:35:43.825Z -- sourcecodester -- e-commerce%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1557</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester E-Commerce System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /ecommerce/admin/user/controller.php?action=edit of the component Username Handler. The manipulation of the argument USERID leads to improper access controls. The attack may be launched remotely. VDB-223550 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester E-Commerce System 1.0 ausgemacht. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei /ecommerce/admin/user/controller.php?action=edit der Komponente Username Handler. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments USERID mit unbekannten Daten kann eine improper access controls-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1557|2023-10-21T10:35:43.825Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 10:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1569|2023-10-21T10:49:09.120Z -- sourcecodester -- e-commerce%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1569</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester E-Commerce System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file admin/user/controller.php?action=edit. The manipulation of the argument U_NAME with the input &lt;script&gt;alert('1')&lt;/script&gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-223561 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In SourceCodester E-Commerce System 1.0 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei admin/user/controller.php?action=edit. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments U_NAME mit der Eingabe &lt;script&gt;alert('1')&lt;/script&gt; mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1569|2023-10-21T10:49:09.120Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 14:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1505|2023-10-21T09:48:40.442Z -- sourcecodester -- e-commerce%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1505</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester E-Commerce System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /ecommerce/admin/settings/setDiscount.php. The manipulation of the argument id with the input 201737 AND (SELECT 8973 FROM (SELECT(SLEEP(5)))OoAD) leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-223409 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester E-Commerce System 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei /ecommerce/admin/settings/setDiscount.php. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments id mit der Eingabe 201737 AND (SELECT 8973 FROM (SELECT(SLEEP(5)))OoAD) mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Die Ausnutzbarkeit gilt als schwierig. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1505|2023-10-21T09:48:40.442Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 09:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
