<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Electronic Medical Records System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/electronic%20medical%20records%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Electronic Medical Records System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 18:25:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1151|2024-08-02T05:40:57.960Z -- sourcecodester -- electronic%20medical%20records%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1151</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Electronic Medical Records System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file administrator.php of the component Cookie Handler. The manipulation of the argument userid leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-222163.
In SourceCodester Electronic Medical Records System 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei administrator.php der Komponente Cookie Handler. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments userid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1151|2024-08-02T05:40:57.960Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 06:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
