<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Employee Payslip Generator with Sending Mail</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/employee%20payslip%20generator%20with%20sending%20mail.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Employee Payslip Generator with Sending Mail</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 10:23:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1360|2024-08-02T05:49:10.335Z -- sourcecodester -- employee%20payslip%20generator%20with%20sending%20mail
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1360</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Employee Payslip Generator with Sending Mail 1.2.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file classes/Users.php?f=save of the component New User Creation. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-222863.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Employee Payslip Generator with Sending Mail 1.2.0 gefunden. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei classes/Users.php?f=save der Komponente New User Creation. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments username mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1360|2024-08-02T05:49:10.335Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 08:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
