<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Engineers Online Portal</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/engineers%20online%20portal.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Engineers Online Portal</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 22:02:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-0347|2024-01-09T21:31:04.011Z -- SourceCodester -- Engineers Online Portal
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0347</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Engineers Online Portal 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file signup_teacher.php. The manipulation of the argument Password leads to weak password requirements. The attack may be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250115.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Engineers Online Portal 1.0 gefunden. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei signup_teacher.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments Password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine weak password requirements-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Die Ausnutzbarkeit gilt als schwierig. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0347|2024-01-09T21:31:04.011Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 21:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0351|2024-01-09T23:00:05.670Z -- SourceCodester -- Engineers Online Portal
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0351</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SourceCodester Engineers Online Portal 1.0. This affects an unknown part. The manipulation leads to session fixiation. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250119.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Engineers Online Portal 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf. Dank Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine session fixiation-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Sie ist schwierig auszunutzen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0351|2024-01-09T23:00:05.670Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 23:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0350|2024-01-09T22:31:04.857Z -- SourceCodester -- Engineers Online Portal
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0350</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Engineers Online Portal 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to session expiration. The attack may be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250118 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Engineers Online Portal 1.0 ausgemacht. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess. Dank der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine session expiration-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Sie ist schwierig ausnutzbar. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0350|2024-01-09T22:31:04.857Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 22:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0182|2024-02-20T12:05:33.214Z -- SourceCodester -- Engineers Online Portal
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0182</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Engineers Online Portal 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/ of the component Admin Login. The manipulation of the argument username/password leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249440.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Engineers Online Portal 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei /admin/ der Komponente Admin Login. Durch Manipulation des Arguments username/password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0182|2024-02-20T12:05:33.214Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 21:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0349|2024-01-09T22:31:03.824Z -- SourceCodester -- Engineers Online Portal
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0349</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Engineers Online Portal 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to sensitive cookie without secure attribute. The attack can be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250117 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In SourceCodester Engineers Online Portal 1.0 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung. Durch Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sensitive cookie without secure attribute-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Sie gilt als schwierig ausnutzbar. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0349|2024-01-09T22:31:03.824Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 22:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0260|2024-01-07T00:00:07.682Z -- SourceCodester -- Engineers Online Portal
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0260</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Engineers Online Portal 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file change_password_teacher.php of the component Password Change. The manipulation leads to session expiration. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249816.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Engineers Online Portal 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei change_password_teacher.php der Komponente Password Change. Mittels Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine session expiration-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0260|2024-01-07T00:00:07.682Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 00:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0348|2024-01-09T22:00:04.969Z -- SourceCodester -- Engineers Online Portal
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0348</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Engineers Online Portal 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the component File Upload Handler. The manipulation leads to resource consumption. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250116.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Engineers Online Portal 1.0 ausgemacht. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Komponente File Upload Handler. Durch das Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine resource consumption-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0348|2024-01-09T22:00:04.969Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 22:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>