<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Establishment Billing Management System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/establishment%20billing%20management%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Establishment Billing Management System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 04:21:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7285|2024-07-31T03:31:04.494Z -- sourcecodester -- establishment%20billing%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7285</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=save_settings. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273154 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System 1.0 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle gefunden. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei /admin/ajax.php?action=save_settings. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7285|2024-07-31T03:31:04.494Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 03:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7286|2024-07-31T04:00:08.887Z -- sourcecodester -- establishment%20billing%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7286</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=login of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273155.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Establishment Billing Management System 1.0 gefunden. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei /admin/ajax.php?action=login der Komponente Login. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments username mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7286|2024-07-31T04:00:08.887Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 04:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
