<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- FAQ Management System</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/faq%20management%20system.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- FAQ Management System</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 22:02:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-2069|2024-03-01T15:31:05.882Z -- SourceCodester -- FAQ Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2069</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester FAQ Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /endpoint/delete-faq.php. The manipulation of the argument faq leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-255384.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in SourceCodester FAQ Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei /endpoint/delete-faq.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments faq mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2069|2024-03-01T15:31:05.882Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 15:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2071|2024-03-01T16:31:04.519Z -- SourceCodester -- FAQ Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2071</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in SourceCodester FAQ Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Update FAQ. The manipulation of the argument Frequently Asked Question leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. VDB-255386 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester FAQ Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Komponente Update FAQ. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments Frequently Asked Question mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2071|2024-03-01T16:31:04.519Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 16:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2070|2024-03-01T16:00:07.399Z -- SourceCodester -- FAQ Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2070</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester FAQ Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /endpoint/add-faq.php. The manipulation of the argument question/answer leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-255385 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In SourceCodester FAQ Management System 1.0 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei /endpoint/add-faq.php. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments question/answer mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2070|2024-03-01T16:00:07.399Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 16:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>