<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Free Hospital Management System for Small Practices</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/free%20hospital%20management%20system%20for%20small%20practices.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Free Hospital Management System for Small Practices</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 23:22:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4440|2024-08-02T07:24:04.630Z -- sourcecodester -- free%20hospital%20management%20system%20for%20small%20practices
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4440</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Free Hospital Management System for Small Practices 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file appointment.php. The manipulation of the argument sheduledate leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-237561 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Free Hospital Management System for Small Practices 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei appointment.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments sheduledate mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4440|2024-08-02T07:24:04.630Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 23:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4443|2024-08-02T07:24:04.705Z -- sourcecodester -- free%20hospital%20management%20system%20for%20small%20practices
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4443</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Free Hospital Management System for Small Practices 1.0/5.0.12. Affected is an unknown function of the file vm\doctor\edit-doc.php. The manipulation of the argument id00/nic/oldemail/email/spec/Tele leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-237564.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Free Hospital Management System for Small Practices 1.0/5.0.12 entdeckt. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei vm\doctor\edit-doc.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments id00/nic/oldemail/email/spec/Tele mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4443|2024-08-02T07:24:04.705Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 00:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4179|2024-08-02T07:17:11.941Z -- sourcecodester -- free%20hospital%20management%20system%20for%20small%20practices
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4179</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Free Hospital Management System for Small Practices 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /vm/doctor/doctors.php?action=view. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-236214 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Free Hospital Management System for Small Practices 1.0 entdeckt. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei /vm/doctor/doctors.php?action=view. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4179|2024-08-02T07:17:11.941Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 07:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5587|2024-08-02T08:07:31.646Z -- sourcecodester -- free%20hospital%20management%20system%20for%20small%20practices
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5587</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Free Hospital Management System for Small Practices 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /vm/admin/doctors.php of the component Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument search leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-242186 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Free Hospital Management System for Small Practices 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei /vm/admin/doctors.php der Komponente Parameter Handler. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments search mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5587|2024-08-02T08:07:31.646Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 22:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4181|2024-08-02T07:17:12.174Z -- sourcecodester -- free%20hospital%20management%20system%20for%20small%20practices
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4181</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Free Hospital Management System for Small Practices 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /vm/admin/delete-doctor.php?id=2 of the component Redirect Handler. The manipulation leads to enforcement of behavioral workflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-236216.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Free Hospital Management System for Small Practices 1.0 entdeckt. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei /vm/admin/delete-doctor.php?id=2 der Komponente Redirect Handler. Mit der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine enforcement of behavioral workflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4181|2024-08-02T07:17:12.174Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 08:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4442|2024-08-02T07:24:04.666Z -- sourcecodester -- free%20hospital%20management%20system%20for%20small%20practices
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4442</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Free Hospital Management System for Small Practices 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file \vm\patient\booking-complete.php. The manipulation of the argument userid/apponum/scheduleid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-237563.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Free Hospital Management System for Small Practices 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei \vm\patient\booking-complete.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments userid/apponum/scheduleid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4442|2024-08-02T07:24:04.666Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 00:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4444|2024-08-02T07:24:04.935Z -- sourcecodester -- free%20hospital%20management%20system%20for%20small%20practices
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4444</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Free Hospital Management System for Small Practices 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file vm\patient\edit-user.php. The manipulation of the argument id00/nic/oldemail/email/spec/Tele leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-237565 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In SourceCodester Free Hospital Management System for Small Practices 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei vm\patient\edit-user.php. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments id00/nic/oldemail/email/spec/Tele mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4444|2024-08-02T07:24:04.935Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 00:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4441|2024-08-02T07:24:04.720Z -- sourcecodester -- free%20hospital%20management%20system%20for%20small%20practices
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4441</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Free Hospital Management System for Small Practices 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /patient/appointment.php. The manipulation of the argument sheduledate leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. VDB-237562 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In SourceCodester Free Hospital Management System for Small Practices 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei /patient/appointment.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments sheduledate mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4441|2024-08-02T07:24:04.720Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 23:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4180|2024-08-02T07:17:12.155Z -- sourcecodester -- free%20hospital%20management%20system%20for%20small%20practices
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4180</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Free Hospital Management System for Small Practices 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /vm/login.php. The manipulation of the argument useremail/userpassword leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-236215.
In SourceCodester Free Hospital Management System for Small Practices 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei /vm/login.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments useremail/userpassword mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4180|2024-08-02T07:17:12.155Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 08:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
