<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Free and Open Source Inventory Management System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/free%20and%20open%20source%20inventory%20management%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Free and Open Source Inventory Management System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 13:24:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6305|2024-08-02T08:28:20.351Z -- sourcecodester -- free%20and%20open%20source%20inventory%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6305</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Free and Open Source Inventory Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file ample/app/ajax/suppliar_data.php. The manipulation of the argument columns leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-246131.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Free and Open Source Inventory Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei ample/app/ajax/suppliar_data.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments columns mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6305|2024-08-02T08:28:20.351Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 00:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4449|2024-08-02T07:24:05.075Z -- sourcecodester -- free%20and%20open%20source%20inventory%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4449</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Free and Open Source Inventory Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /index.php?page=member. The manipulation of the argument columns[0][data] leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-237570 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Free and Open Source Inventory Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei /index.php?page=member. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments columns[0][data] mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4449|2024-08-02T07:24:05.075Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 02:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7157|2024-08-02T08:50:08.293Z -- sourcecodester -- free%20and%20open%20source%20inventory%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7157</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Free and Open Source Inventory Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /app/ajax/sell_return_data.php. The manipulation of the argument columns[0][data] leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249179.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Free and Open Source Inventory Management System 1.0 gefunden. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei /app/ajax/sell_return_data.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments columns[0][data] mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7157|2024-08-02T08:50:08.293Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 06:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6306|2024-08-02T08:28:21.276Z -- sourcecodester -- free%20and%20open%20source%20inventory%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6306</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Free and Open Source Inventory Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /ample/app/ajax/member_data.php. The manipulation of the argument columns leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-246132.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Free and Open Source Inventory Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei /ample/app/ajax/member_data.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments columns mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6306|2024-08-02T08:28:21.276Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 01:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7155|2024-08-02T08:50:08.318Z -- sourcecodester -- free%20and%20open%20source%20inventory%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7155</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Free and Open Source Inventory Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /ample/app/action/edit_product.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249177 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Free and Open Source Inventory Management System 1.0 gefunden. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei /ample/app/action/edit_product.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7155|2024-08-02T08:50:08.318Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 05:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1926|2024-08-01T18:56:22.545Z -- sourcecodester -- free%20and%20open%20source%20inventory%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1926</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Free and Open Source Inventory Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /app/ajax/search_sales_report.php. The manipulation of the argument customer leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-254861 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Free and Open Source Inventory Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei /app/ajax/search_sales_report.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments customer mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1926|2024-08-01T18:56:22.545Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 17:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1926|2024-02-27T17:00:12.007Z -- sourcecodester -- free%20and%20open%20source%20inventory%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1926</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Free and Open Source Inventory Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /app/ajax/search_sales_report.php. The manipulation of the argument customer leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-254861 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Free and Open Source Inventory Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei /app/ajax/search_sales_report.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments customer mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1926|2024-02-27T17:00:12.007Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 17:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1926|2024-07-05T17:22:03.750Z -- sourcecodester -- free%20and%20open%20source%20inventory%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1926</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Free and Open Source Inventory Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /app/ajax/search_sales_report.php. The manipulation of the argument customer leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-254861 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Free and Open Source Inventory Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei /app/ajax/search_sales_report.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments customer mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1926|2024-07-05T17:22:03.750Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 17:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
