<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Free Hospital Management System for Small Practices</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/free%20hospital%20management%20system%20for%20small%20practices.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Free Hospital Management System for Small Practices</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 18:24:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5587|2024-07-09T17:53:23.553Z -- sourcecodester -- free%20hospital%20management%20system%20for%20small%20practices
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5587</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Free Hospital Management System for Small Practices 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /vm/admin/doctors.php of the component Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument search leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-242186 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Free Hospital Management System for Small Practices 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei /vm/admin/doctors.php der Komponente Parameter Handler. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments search mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5587|2024-07-09T17:53:23.553Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 22:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
