<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Gadget Works Online Ordering System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/gadget%20works%20online%20ordering%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Gadget Works Online Ordering System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 21:21:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1433|2024-07-22T20:55:58.061Z -- sourcecodester -- gadget%20works%20online%20ordering%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1433</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Gadget Works Online Ordering System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file admin/products/controller.php?action=add of the component Products Handler. The manipulation of the argument filename leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-223215.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Gadget Works Online Ordering System 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei admin/products/controller.php?action=add der Komponente Products Handler. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments filename mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1433|2024-07-22T20:55:58.061Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 12:55:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
