<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Grade Point Average GPA Calculator</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/grade%20point%20average%20gpa%20calculator.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Grade Point Average GPA Calculator</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 17:22:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1769|2024-08-02T05:57:25.249Z -- sourcecodester -- grade%20point%20average%20gpa%20calculator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1769</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Grade Point Average GPA Calculator 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file index.php. The manipulation of the argument page with the input php://filter/read=convert.base64-encode/resource=grade_table leads to information disclosure. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-224670 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Grade Point Average GPA Calculator 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei index.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments page mit der Eingabe php://filter/read=convert.base64-encode/resource=grade_table mit unbekannten Daten kann eine information disclosure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1769|2024-08-02T05:57:25.249Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1743|2024-08-02T05:57:25.176Z -- sourcecodester -- grade%20point%20average%20gpa%20calculator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1743</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SourceCodester Grade Point Average GPA Calculator 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file index.php. The manipulation of the argument page leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-224631.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Grade Point Average GPA Calculator 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei index.php. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments page mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1743|2024-08-02T05:57:25.176Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 22:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1771|2024-08-02T05:57:24.985Z -- sourcecodester -- grade%20point%20average%20gpa%20calculator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1771</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Grade Point Average GPA Calculator 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function get_scale of the file Master.php. The manipulation of the argument perc leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-224672.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Grade Point Average GPA Calculator 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft die Funktion get_scale der Datei Master.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments perc mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1771|2024-08-02T05:57:24.985Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 11:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1770|2024-08-02T05:57:25.190Z -- sourcecodester -- grade%20point%20average%20gpa%20calculator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1770</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Grade Point Average GPA Calculator 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function get_scale of the file Master.php. The manipulation of the argument perc leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-224671.
In SourceCodester Grade Point Average GPA Calculator 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Das betrifft die Funktion get_scale der Datei Master.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments perc mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1770|2024-08-02T05:57:25.190Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 11:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
