<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Guest Management System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/guest%20management%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Guest Management System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 02:27:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2811|2024-08-03T00:52:58.931Z -- sourcecodester -- guest%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2811</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SourceCodester Guest Management System. This affects an unknown part of the file myform.php. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-206397 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2811|2024-08-03T00:52:58.931Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 10:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2813|2024-08-03T00:52:59.263Z -- sourcecodester -- guest%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2813</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Guest Management System. Affected is an unknown function. The manipulation leads to cleartext storage of passwords in the database. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-206400.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2813|2024-08-03T00:52:59.263Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 10:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2812|2024-08-03T00:52:59.103Z -- sourcecodester -- guest%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2812</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Guest Management System. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file index.php. The manipulation of the argument username/pass leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-206398 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2812|2024-08-03T00:52:59.103Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 10:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2847|2024-08-03T00:52:58.967Z -- sourcecodester -- guest%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2847</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Guest Management System. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /guestmanagement/front.php. The manipulation of the argument rid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-206489 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2847|2024-08-03T00:52:58.967Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 18:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
