<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Gym Management System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/gym%20management%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Gym Management System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:21:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2727|2024-08-03T00:46:03.982Z -- sourcecodester -- gym%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2727</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Gym Management System. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /mygym/admin/login.php. The manipulation of the argument admin_email/admin_pass leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-205855.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2727|2024-08-03T00:46:03.982Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 10:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2842|2024-08-03T00:52:59.586Z -- sourcecodester -- gym%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2842</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Gym Management System. This affects an unknown part of the file login.php. The manipulation of the argument user_email leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-206451.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2842|2024-08-03T00:52:59.586Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 18:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2728|2024-08-03T00:46:03.982Z -- sourcecodester -- gym%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2728</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Gym Management System. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /mygym/admin/index.php. The manipulation of the argument edit_tran leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-205856.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2728|2024-08-03T00:46:03.982Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 10:20:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2800|2024-08-03T00:46:04.550Z -- sourcecodester -- gym%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2800</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in SourceCodester Gym Management System. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to clickjacking. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-206246 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2800|2024-08-03T00:46:04.550Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 19:45:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2744|2024-08-03T00:46:04.501Z -- sourcecodester -- gym%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2744</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Gym Management System. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/add_exercises.php of the component Background Management. The manipulation of the argument exer_img leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-206012.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2744|2024-08-03T00:46:04.501Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 04:55:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2708|2024-08-03T00:46:03.862Z -- sourcecodester -- gym%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2708</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Gym Management System. This affects an unknown part of the file login.php. The manipulation of the argument user_login with the input 123@xx.com' OR (SELECT 9084 FROM(SELECT COUNT(*),CONCAT(0x7178767871,(SELECT (ELT(9084=9084,1))),0x71767a6271,FLOOR(RAND(0)*2))x FROM INFORMATION_SCHEMA.PLUGINS GROUP BY x)a)-- dPvW leads to sql injection. Access to the local network is required for this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-205833 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2708|2024-08-03T00:46:03.862Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 12:50:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2703|2024-08-03T00:46:04.007Z -- sourcecodester -- gym%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2703</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Gym Management System. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the component Exercises Module. The manipulation of the argument exer leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-205827.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2703|2024-08-03T00:46:04.007Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 12:50:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2745|2024-08-03T00:46:04.099Z -- sourcecodester -- gym%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2745</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Gym Management System. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/add_trainers.php of the component Add New Trainer. The manipulation of the argument trainer_name leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The identifier VDB-206013 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2745|2024-08-03T00:46:04.099Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 04:55:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2749|2024-08-03T00:46:04.033Z -- sourcecodester -- gym%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2749</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Gym Management System. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /mygym/admin/index.php?view_exercises. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-206017 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2749|2024-08-03T00:46:04.033Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 04:56:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2776|2024-08-03T00:46:04.587Z -- sourcecodester -- gym%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2776</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SourceCodester Gym Management System. Affected is an unknown function of the file delete_user.php. The manipulation of the argument delete_user leads to denial of service. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-206172.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2776|2024-08-03T00:46:04.587Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 11:51:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2687|2024-08-03T00:46:03.414Z -- sourcecodester -- gym%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2687</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Gym Management System. Affected is an unknown function. The manipulation of the argument user_pass leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-205734 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2687|2024-08-03T00:46:03.414Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 06:25:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2700|2024-08-03T00:46:03.466Z -- sourcecodester -- gym%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2700</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Gym Management System. This affects an unknown part of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument day leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-205821 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2700|2024-08-03T00:46:03.466Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 12:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
