<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- House Rental Management System</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/house%20rental%20management%20system.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- House Rental Management System</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 21:24:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-0500|2024-01-13T19:00:06.407Z -- SourceCodester -- House Rental Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0500</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester House Rental Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the component Manage Tenant Details. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250608.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in SourceCodester House Rental Management System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Komponente Manage Tenant Details. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments Name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0500|2024-01-13T19:00:06.407Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 19:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0501|2024-01-13T19:31:03.727Z -- SourceCodester -- House Rental Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0501</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester House Rental Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Manage Invoice Details. The manipulation of the argument Invoice leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250609 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In SourceCodester House Rental Management System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Komponente Manage Invoice Details. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments Invoice mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0501|2024-01-13T19:31:03.727Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 19:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0499|2024-01-13T18:31:04.101Z -- SourceCodester -- House Rental Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0499</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in SourceCodester House Rental Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file index.php. The manipulation of the argument page leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250607.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester House Rental Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei index.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments page mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0499|2024-01-13T18:31:04.101Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 18:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0502|2024-01-13T20:00:05.198Z -- SourceCodester -- House Rental Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0502</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester House Rental Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file manage_user.php of the component Edit User. The manipulation of the argument id/name/username leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250610 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester House Rental Management System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei manage_user.php der Komponente Edit User. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments id/name/username mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0502|2024-01-13T20:00:05.198Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 20:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>