<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Human Resource Management System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/human%20resource%20management%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Human Resource Management System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 11:20:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3472|2024-08-03T01:14:01.396Z -- sourcecodester -- human%20resource%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3472</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Human Resource Management System. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file city.php. The manipulation of the argument cityedit leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-210716.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3472|2024-08-03T01:14:01.396Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3470|2024-08-03T01:14:01.521Z -- sourcecodester -- human%20resource%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3470</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Human Resource Management System. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file getstatecity.php. The manipulation of the argument sc leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-210714 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3470|2024-08-03T01:14:01.521Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4273|2024-08-03T01:34:49.938Z -- sourcecodester -- human%20resource%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4273</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Human Resource Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /hrm/controller/employee.php of the component Content-Type Handler. The manipulation of the argument pfimg leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-214769 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4273|2024-08-03T01:34:49.938Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3471|2024-08-03T01:14:01.442Z -- sourcecodester -- human%20resource%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3471</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Human Resource Management System. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file city.php. The manipulation of the argument searccity leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-210715.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3471|2024-08-03T01:14:01.442Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3497|2024-08-03T01:14:02.353Z -- sourcecodester -- human%20resource%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3497</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Human Resource Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the component Master List. The manipulation of the argument city/state/country/position leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. VDB-210786 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3497|2024-08-03T01:14:02.353Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3458|2024-08-03T01:07:06.750Z -- sourcecodester -- human%20resource%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3458</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Human Resource Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /employeeview.php of the component Image File Handler. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-210559.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3458|2024-08-03T01:07:06.750Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3473|2024-08-03T01:14:01.456Z -- sourcecodester -- human%20resource%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3473</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Human Resource Management System. This affects an unknown part of the file getstatecity.php. The manipulation of the argument ci leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-210717 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3473|2024-08-03T01:14:01.456Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4278|2024-08-03T01:34:49.936Z -- sourcecodester -- human%20resource%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4278</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Human Resource Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /hrm/employeeadd.php. The manipulation of the argument empid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-214775.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4278|2024-08-03T01:34:49.936Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4279|2024-08-03T01:34:49.920Z -- sourcecodester -- human%20resource%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4279</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SourceCodester Human Resource Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /hrm/employeeview.php. The manipulation of the argument search leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-214776.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4279|2024-08-03T01:34:49.920Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3492|2024-08-03T01:14:01.426Z -- sourcecodester -- human%20resource%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3492</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Human Resource Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Profile Photo Handler. The manipulation of the argument parameter leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-210772.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3492|2024-08-03T01:14:01.426Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3493|2024-08-03T01:14:01.565Z -- sourcecodester -- human%20resource%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3493</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in SourceCodester Human Resource Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Add Employee Handler. The manipulation of the argument First Name/Middle Name/Last Name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The identifier VDB-210773 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3493|2024-08-03T01:14:01.565Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3496|2024-08-03T01:14:01.610Z -- sourcecodester -- human%20resource%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3496</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Human Resource Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file employeeadd.php of the component Admin Panel. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack may be initiated remotely. The identifier VDB-210785 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3496|2024-08-03T01:14:01.610Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
