<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Interactive Map with Marker</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/interactive%20map%20with%20marker.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Interactive Map with Marker</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 22:02:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-4968|2024-05-16T08:31:05.608Z -- SourceCodester -- Interactive Map with Marker
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4968</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Interactive Map with Marker 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file Marker Name of the component Add Marker. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-264536.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Interactive Map with Marker 1.0 ausgemacht. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei Marker Name der Komponente Add Marker. Durch Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4968|2024-05-16T08:31:05.608Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 08:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4967|2024-05-16T08:31:04.218Z -- SourceCodester -- Interactive Map with Marker
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4967</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Interactive Map with Marker 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /endpoint/delete-mark.php. The manipulation of the argument mark leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-264535.
In SourceCodester Interactive Map with Marker 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei /endpoint/delete-mark.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments mark mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4967|2024-05-16T08:31:04.218Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 08:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>