<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Internship Portal Management System</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/internship%20portal%20management%20system.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Internship Portal Management System</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 22:02:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-3253|2024-04-03T11:00:05.961Z -- SourceCodester -- Internship Portal Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3253</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Internship Portal Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file admin/add_admin.php. The manipulation of the argument name/username/password leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259102 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In SourceCodester Internship Portal Management System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei admin/add_admin.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments name/username/password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3253|2024-04-03T11:00:05.961Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3252|2024-04-03T10:00:07.120Z -- SourceCodester -- Internship Portal Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3252</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Internship Portal Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file admin/check_admin.php. The manipulation of the argument username/password leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259101 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Internship Portal Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei admin/check_admin.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments username/password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3252|2024-04-03T10:00:07.120Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 10:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3259|2024-04-03T13:31:05.141Z -- SourceCodester -- Internship Portal Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3259</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Internship Portal Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file admin/delete_activity.php. The manipulation of the argument activity_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259108.
In SourceCodester Internship Portal Management System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei admin/delete_activity.php. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments activity_id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3259|2024-04-03T13:31:05.141Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 13:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3255|2024-04-03T12:00:07.100Z -- SourceCodester -- Internship Portal Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3255</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Internship Portal Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file admin/edit_admin_query.php. The manipulation of the argument username/password/name/admin_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259104.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Internship Portal Management System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei admin/edit_admin_query.php. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments username/password/name/admin_id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3255|2024-04-03T12:00:07.100Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 12:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3254|2024-04-03T12:00:05.721Z -- SourceCodester -- Internship Portal Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3254</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Internship Portal Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file admin/edit_admin.php. The manipulation of the argument admin_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259103.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Internship Portal Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei admin/edit_admin.php. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments admin_id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3254|2024-04-03T12:00:05.721Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 12:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3258|2024-04-03T13:00:06.107Z -- SourceCodester -- Internship Portal Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3258</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Internship Portal Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file admin/add_activity.php. The manipulation of the argument title/description/start/end leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259107.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Internship Portal Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei admin/add_activity.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments title/description/start/end mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3258|2024-04-03T13:00:06.107Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 13:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3257|2024-04-03T13:00:04.668Z -- SourceCodester -- Internship Portal Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3257</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Internship Portal Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file admin/edit_activity_query.php. The manipulation of the argument title/description/start/end leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259106 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Internship Portal Management System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei admin/edit_activity_query.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments title/description/start/end mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3257|2024-04-03T13:00:04.668Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 13:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3256|2024-04-03T12:31:05.117Z -- SourceCodester -- Internship Portal Management System
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3256</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Internship Portal Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file admin/edit_activity.php. The manipulation of the argument activity_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259105 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In SourceCodester Internship Portal Management System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei admin/edit_activity.php. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments activity_id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3256|2024-04-03T12:31:05.117Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 12:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>