<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Library Management System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/library%20management%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Library Management System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 04:23:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2492|2024-08-03T00:39:07.823Z -- sourcecodester -- library%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2492</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Library Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument RollNo with the input admin' AND (SELECT 2625 FROM (SELECT(SLEEP(5)))MdIL) AND 'KXmq'='KXmq&amp;Password=1231312312 leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2492|2024-08-03T00:39:07.823Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 11:35:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2213|2024-08-03T00:32:09.200Z -- sourcecodester -- library%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2213</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Library Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/edit_admin_details.php?id=admin. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2213|2024-08-03T00:32:09.200Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 06:45:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2214|2024-08-03T00:32:09.368Z -- sourcecodester -- library%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2214</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Library Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /librarian/bookdetails.php. The manipulation of the argument id with the input ' AND (SELECT 9198 FROM (SELECT(SLEEP(5)))iqZA)-- PbtB leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2214|2024-08-03T00:32:09.368Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 06:45:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2212|2024-08-03T00:32:08.653Z -- sourcecodester -- library%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2212</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Library Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the component /card/index.php. The manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2212|2024-08-03T00:32:08.653Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 06:45:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2491|2024-08-03T00:39:07.704Z -- sourcecodester -- library%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2491</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Library Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file lab.php. The manipulation of the argument Section with the input 1' UNION ALL SELECT NULL,NULL,NULL,NULL,NULL,CONCAT(0x71716b7171,0x546e4444736b7743575a666d4873746a6450616261527a67627944426946507245664143694c6a4c,0x7162706b71),NULL,NULL,NULL,NULL# leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2491|2024-08-03T00:39:07.704Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 11:35:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2768|2024-08-03T00:46:04.441Z -- sourcecodester -- library%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2768</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester Library Management System. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /qr/I/. The manipulation of the argument error leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-206164.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2768|2024-08-03T00:46:04.441Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 11:50:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2774|2024-08-03T00:46:04.352Z -- sourcecodester -- library%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2774</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Library Management System. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file librarian/student.php. The manipulation of the argument title leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. VDB-206170 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2774|2024-08-03T00:46:04.352Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 11:51:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
