<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Life Insurance Management System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/life%20insurance%20management%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Life Insurance Management System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3165|2023-10-23T12:57:48.030Z -- sourcecodester -- life%20insurance%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3165</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Life Insurance Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file insertNominee.php of the component POST Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument nominee_id leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-231109 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In SourceCodester Life Insurance Management System 1.0 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei insertNominee.php der Komponente POST Parameter Handler. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments nominee_id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3165|2023-10-23T12:57:48.030Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 17:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3693|2023-10-23T15:30:48.702Z -- sourcecodester -- life%20insurance%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3693</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Life Insurance Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file login.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-234244.
In SourceCodester Life Insurance Management System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei login.php. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments username mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3693|2023-10-23T15:30:48.702Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 21:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
