<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Loan Management System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/loan%20management%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Loan Management System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 20:23:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6312|2024-08-02T08:28:21.623Z -- sourcecodester -- loan%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6312</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Loan Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function delete_user of the file deleteUser.php of the component Users Page. The manipulation of the argument user_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-246138 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Loan Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Dabei betrifft es die Funktion delete_user der Datei deleteUser.php der Komponente Users Page. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments user_id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6312|2024-08-02T08:28:21.623Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 02:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6311|2024-08-02T08:28:21.325Z -- sourcecodester -- loan%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6311</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Loan Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function delete_ltype of the file delete_ltype.php of the component Loan Type Page. The manipulation of the argument ltype_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-246137 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Loan Management System 1.0 gefunden. Dies betrifft die Funktion delete_ltype der Datei delete_ltype.php der Komponente Loan Type Page. Dank Manipulation des Arguments ltype_id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6311|2024-08-02T08:28:21.325Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 02:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6310|2024-08-02T08:28:21.339Z -- sourcecodester -- loan%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6310</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Loan Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function delete_borrower of the file deleteBorrower.php. The manipulation of the argument borrower_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-246136.
In SourceCodester Loan Management System 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle gefunden. Das betrifft die Funktion delete_borrower der Datei deleteBorrower.php. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments borrower_id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6310|2024-08-02T08:28:21.339Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 02:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
