<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Medical Certificate Generator App</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/medical%20certificate%20generator%20app.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Medical Certificate Generator App</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 23:22:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1006|2024-08-02T05:32:46.106Z -- sourcecodester -- medical%20certificate%20generator%20app
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1006</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Medical Certificate Generator App 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the component New Record Handler. The manipulation of the argument Firstname/Middlename/Lastname/Suffix/Nationality/Doctor Fullname/Doctor Suffix with the input "&gt;&lt;script&gt;prompt(1)&lt;/script&gt; leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-221739.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Medical Certificate Generator App 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Komponente New Record Handler. Dank Manipulation des Arguments Firstname/Middlename/Lastname/Suffix/Nationality/Doctor Fullname/Doctor Suffix mit der Eingabe "&gt;&lt;script&gt;prompt(1)&lt;/script&gt; mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1006|2024-08-02T05:32:46.106Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 08:21:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0706|2024-08-02T05:17:50.390Z -- sourcecodester -- medical%20certificate%20generator%20app
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0706</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Medical Certificate Generator App 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file manage_record.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-220340.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Medical Certificate Generator App 1.0 entdeckt. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei manage_record.php. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0706|2024-08-02T05:17:50.390Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 09:35:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0707|2024-08-02T05:17:50.388Z -- sourcecodester -- medical%20certificate%20generator%20app
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0707</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Medical Certificate Generator App 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function delete_record of the file function.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. VDB-220346 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Medical Certificate Generator App 1.0 ausgemacht. Es geht hierbei um die Funktion delete_record der Datei function.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0707|2024-08-02T05:17:50.388Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 12:32:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1566|2024-08-02T05:49:11.674Z -- sourcecodester -- medical%20certificate%20generator%20app
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1566</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Medical Certificate Generator App 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file action.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-223558 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In SourceCodester Medical Certificate Generator App 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei action.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1566|2024-08-02T05:49:11.674Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 13:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0774|2024-08-02T05:24:34.558Z -- sourcecodester -- medical%20certificate%20generator%20app
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0774</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Medical Certificate Generator App 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file action.php. The manipulation of the argument lastname leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-220558 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In SourceCodester Medical Certificate Generator App 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle gefunden. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei action.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments lastname mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0774|2024-08-02T05:24:34.558Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 11:52:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
