<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Music Gallery Site</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/music%20gallery%20site.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Music Gallery Site</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1053|2023-10-21T07:01:30.168Z -- sourcecodester -- music%20gallery%20site
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1053</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Music Gallery Site 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file view_category.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-221819.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Music Gallery Site 1.0 gefunden. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei view_category.php. Durch Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1053|2023-10-21T07:01:30.168Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 10:43:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1054|2023-10-21T07:02:43.355Z -- sourcecodester -- music%20gallery%20site
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1054</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Music Gallery Site 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/?page=user/manage. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-221820.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Music Gallery Site 1.0 ausgemacht. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei /admin/?page=user/manage. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1054|2023-10-21T07:02:43.355Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 10:43:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0961|2023-10-20T21:40:53.167Z -- sourcecodester -- music%20gallery%20site
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0961</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Music Gallery Site 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file view_music_details.php of the component GET Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-221631.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Music Gallery Site 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei view_music_details.php der Komponente GET Request Handler. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0961|2023-10-20T21:40:53.167Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 18:12:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0962|2023-10-20T21:42:06.390Z -- sourcecodester -- music%20gallery%20site
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0962</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Music Gallery Site 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file Master.php of the component GET Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-221632.
In SourceCodester Music Gallery Site 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei Master.php der Komponente GET Request Handler. Durch Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0962|2023-10-20T21:42:06.390Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 18:12:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0938|2023-10-20T21:34:42.503Z -- sourcecodester -- music%20gallery%20site
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0938</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Music Gallery Site 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file music_list.php of the component GET Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument cid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-221553 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Music Gallery Site 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei music_list.php der Komponente GET Request Handler. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments cid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0938|2023-10-20T21:34:42.503Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 09:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0963|2023-10-20T21:43:19.556Z -- sourcecodester -- music%20gallery%20site
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0963</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Music Gallery Site 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file Users.php of the component POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-221633 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Music Gallery Site 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei Users.php der Komponente POST Request Handler. Mittels dem Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine improper access controls-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0963|2023-10-20T21:43:19.556Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 18:12:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2930|2024-03-26T23:31:04.697Z -- sourcecodester -- music%20gallery%20site
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2930</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Music Gallery Site 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file classes/Master.php?f=save_music. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-258001 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In SourceCodester Music Gallery Site 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei classes/Master.php?f=save_music. Durch das Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2930|2024-03-26T23:31:04.697Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 23:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
