<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Online School Fees System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/online%20school%20fees%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Online School Fees System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 23:22:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3189|2024-08-02T06:48:07.833Z -- sourcecodester -- online%20school%20fees%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3189</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Online School Fees System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /paysystem/branch.php of the component POST Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument branch leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-231501 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Online School Fees System 1.0 gefunden. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei /paysystem/branch.php der Komponente POST Parameter Handler. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments branch mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3189|2024-08-02T06:48:07.833Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 05:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3381|2024-08-02T06:55:03.214Z -- sourcecodester -- online%20school%20fees%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3381</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester Online School Fees System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /paysystem/datatable.php of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument doj leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-232237 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In SourceCodester Online School Fees System 1.0 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei /paysystem/datatable.php der Komponente GET Parameter Handler. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments doj mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3381|2024-08-02T06:55:03.214Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 09:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3340|2024-08-02T06:55:03.477Z -- sourcecodester -- online%20school%20fees%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3340</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online School Fees System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file ajx.php of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument name_startsWith leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-232016.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Online School Fees System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei ajx.php der Komponente GET Parameter Handler. Durch Manipulation des Arguments name_startsWith mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3340|2024-08-02T06:55:03.477Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 15:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
