<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Online Jewelry Store</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/online%20jewelry%20store.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Online Jewelry Store</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 08:24:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2864|2024-08-02T06:33:05.643Z -- sourcecodester -- online%20jewelry%20store
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2864</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Jewelry Store 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file customer.php of the component POST Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument Custid leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-229820.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Online Jewelry Store 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei customer.php der Komponente POST Parameter Handler. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments Custid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2864|2024-08-02T06:33:05.643Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 10:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2815|2024-08-02T06:33:05.795Z -- sourcecodester -- online%20jewelry%20store
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2815</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Online Jewelry Store 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file supplier.php of the component POST Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument suppid leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-229429 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In SourceCodester Online Jewelry Store 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei supplier.php der Komponente POST Parameter Handler. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments suppid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2815|2024-08-02T06:33:05.795Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 16:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3985|2024-08-02T07:08:50.828Z -- sourcecodester -- online%20jewelry%20store
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3985</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Online Jewelry Store 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file login.php. The manipulation of the argument username/password leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-235606 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In SourceCodester Online Jewelry Store 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle gefunden. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei login.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments username/password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3985|2024-08-02T07:08:50.828Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 04:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
