<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Online Catering Reservation System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/online%20catering%20reservation%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Online Catering Reservation System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 15:23:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1100|2024-08-02T05:32:46.395Z -- sourcecodester -- online%20catering%20reservation%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1100</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Online Catering Reservation System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /reservation/add_message.php of the component POST Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument fullname leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-222003.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Online Catering Reservation System 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei /reservation/add_message.php der Komponente POST Parameter Handler. Dank Manipulation des Arguments fullname mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1100|2024-08-02T05:32:46.395Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 20:07:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
