<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Online Hospital Management System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/online%20hospital%20management%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Online Hospital Management System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 19:20:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4185|2024-08-02T07:17:12.148Z -- sourcecodester -- online%20hospital%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4185</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Hospital Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file patientlogin.php. The manipulation of the argument loginid/password leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-236220.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Online Hospital Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei patientlogin.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments loginid/password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4185|2024-08-02T07:17:12.148Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 13:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5362|2024-08-01T21:11:12.768Z -- sourcecodester -- online%20hospital%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5362</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Online Hospital Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file departmentDoctor.php. The manipulation of the argument deptid leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-266274 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Online Hospital Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei departmentDoctor.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments deptid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5362|2024-08-01T21:11:12.768Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 11:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5362|2024-06-04T18:02:41.934Z -- sourcecodester -- online%20hospital%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5362</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Online Hospital Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file departmentDoctor.php. The manipulation of the argument deptid leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-266274 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Online Hospital Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei departmentDoctor.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments deptid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5362|2024-06-04T18:02:41.934Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 11:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
