<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Online Graduate Tracer System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/online%20graduate%20tracer%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Online Graduate Tracer System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1394|2023-10-21T08:33:01.367Z -- sourcecodester -- online%20graduate%20tracer%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1394</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function mysqli_query of the file bsitemp.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-222981 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist die Funktion mysqli_query der Datei bsitemp.php. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1394|2023-10-21T08:33:01.367Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 14:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1854|2023-10-21T17:04:36.445Z -- sourcecodester -- online%20graduate%20tracer%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1854</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file admin/. The manipulation leads to session expiration. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-224994 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei admin/. Dank der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine session expiration-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1854|2023-10-21T17:04:36.445Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 07:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1310|2023-10-21T08:02:31.188Z -- sourcecodester -- online%20graduate%20tracer%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1310</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file admin/prof.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-222698 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System 1.0 entdeckt. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei admin/prof.php. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1310|2023-10-21T08:02:31.188Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 07:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1308|2023-10-21T08:00:04.773Z -- sourcecodester -- online%20graduate%20tracer%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1308</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file admin/adminlog.php. The manipulation of the argument user leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-222696.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System 1.0 entdeckt. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei admin/adminlog.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments user mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1308|2023-10-21T08:00:04.773Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 07:35:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1040|2024-02-13T07:52:07.902Z -- sourcecodester -- online%20graduate%20tracer%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1040</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file tracking/admin/add_acc.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-221798 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System 1.0 entdeckt. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei tracking/admin/add_acc.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1040|2024-02-13T07:52:07.902Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 11:55:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1309|2023-10-21T08:01:18.016Z -- sourcecodester -- online%20graduate%20tracer%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1309</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file admin/search_it.php. The manipulation of the argument input leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-222697 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei admin/search_it.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments input mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1309|2023-10-21T08:01:18.016Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 07:35:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1293|2024-02-13T07:47:45.789Z -- sourcecodester -- online%20graduate%20tracer%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-1293</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function mysqli_query of the file admin_cs.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-222647.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System 1.0 gefunden. Dies betrifft die Funktion mysqli_query der Datei admin_cs.php. Durch das Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Die Ausnutzbarkeit gilt als schwierig. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1293|2024-02-13T07:47:45.789Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 14:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4556|2023-10-24T14:58:40.658Z -- sourcecodester -- online%20graduate%20tracer%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4556</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function mysqli_query of the file sexit.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-238154 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Online Graduate Tracer System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei geht es um die Funktion mysqli_query der Datei sexit.php. Durch Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4556|2023-10-24T14:58:40.658Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 06:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
