<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Online Mobile Management Store</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/online%20mobile%20management%20store.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Online Mobile Management Store</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 21:54:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-2147|2024-03-03T16:31:04.629Z -- SourceCodester -- Online Mobile Management Store
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2147</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Mobile Management Store 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/login.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-255500.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Online Mobile Management Store 1.0 ausgemacht. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei /admin/login.php. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments username mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2147|2024-03-03T16:31:04.629Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 16:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2151|2024-03-03T23:31:04.610Z -- SourceCodester -- Online Mobile Management Store
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2151</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester Online Mobile Management Store 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Product Price Handler. The manipulation of the argument quantity with the input -1 leads to business logic errors. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-255583.
In SourceCodester Online Mobile Management Store 1.0 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Komponente Product Price Handler. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments quantity mit der Eingabe -1 mit unbekannten Daten kann eine business logic errors-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2151|2024-03-03T23:31:04.610Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 23:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2146|2024-03-03T14:31:04.104Z -- SourceCodester -- Online Mobile Management Store
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2146</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Mobile Management Store 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /?p=products. The manipulation of the argument search leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-255499.
In SourceCodester Online Mobile Management Store 1.0 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei /?p=products. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments search mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2146|2024-03-03T14:31:04.104Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 14:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2153|2024-03-04T00:31:04.600Z -- SourceCodester -- Online Mobile Management Store
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2153</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Online Mobile Management Store 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/orders/view_order.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-255585 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Online Mobile Management Store 1.0 gefunden. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei /admin/orders/view_order.php. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2153|2024-03-04T00:31:04.600Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 00:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2145|2024-03-03T14:00:07.669Z -- SourceCodester -- Online Mobile Management Store
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2145</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Mobile Management Store 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /endpoint/update-tracker.php. The manipulation of the argument firstname leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-255498 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Online Mobile Management Store 1.0 ausgemacht. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei /endpoint/update-tracker.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments firstname mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2145|2024-03-03T14:00:07.669Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 14:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2152|2024-03-04T00:00:09.912Z -- SourceCodester -- Online Mobile Management Store
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2152</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Online Mobile Management Store 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/product/manage_product.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-255584.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Online Mobile Management Store 1.0 entdeckt. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei /admin/product/manage_product.php. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2152|2024-03-04T00:00:09.912Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 00:00:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2148|2024-03-03T17:00:07.167Z -- SourceCodester -- Online Mobile Management Store
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2148</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Online Mobile Management Store 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /classes/Users.php. The manipulation of the argument img leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-255501 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Online Mobile Management Store 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei /classes/Users.php. Durch Manipulation des Arguments img mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2148|2024-03-03T17:00:07.167Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 17:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2332|2024-03-09T14:00:09.399Z -- SourceCodester -- Online Mobile Management Store
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2332</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Mobile Management Store 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/maintenance/manage_category.php of the component HTTP GET Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-256283.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Online Mobile Management Store 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei /admin/maintenance/manage_category.php der Komponente HTTP GET Request Handler. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2332|2024-03-09T14:00:09.399Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 14:00:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2154|2024-03-04T00:31:05.949Z -- SourceCodester -- Online Mobile Management Store
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2154</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Online Mobile Management Store 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file view_product.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-255586 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In SourceCodester Online Mobile Management Store 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle gefunden. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei view_product.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2154|2024-03-04T00:31:05.949Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 00:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>