<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Sanitization Management System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/sanitization%20management%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Sanitization Management System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 20:22:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3504|2024-08-03T01:14:02.534Z -- sourcecodester -- sanitization%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3504</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Sanitization Management System and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /php-sms/?p=services/view_service. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-210839.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3504|2024-08-03T01:14:02.534Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3672|2024-08-03T01:14:03.348Z -- sourcecodester -- sanitization%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3672</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in SourceCodester Sanitization Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /php-sms/classes/SystemSettings.php. The manipulation of the argument name/shortname leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-212015.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3672|2024-08-03T01:14:03.348Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4726|2024-08-03T01:48:40.396Z -- sourcecodester -- sanitization%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4726</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Sanitization Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Admin Login. The manipulation of the argument username/password leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-216739.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4726|2024-08-03T01:48:40.396Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3992|2024-08-03T01:27:54.077Z -- sourcecodester -- sanitization%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3992</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester Sanitization Management System. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file admin/?page=system_info of the component Banner Image Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-213571.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3992|2024-08-03T01:27:54.077Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3673|2024-08-03T01:14:03.308Z -- sourcecodester -- sanitization%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3673</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Sanitization Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /php-sms/classes/Master.php. The manipulation of the argument message leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-212016.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3673|2024-08-03T01:14:03.308Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3674|2024-08-03T01:14:03.268Z -- sourcecodester -- sanitization%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3674</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Sanitization Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to missing authentication. The attack can be launched remotely. The identifier VDB-212017 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3674|2024-08-03T01:14:03.268Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3518|2024-08-03T01:14:01.962Z -- sourcecodester -- sanitization%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3518</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SourceCodester Sanitization Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the component User Creation Handler. The manipulation of the argument First Name/Middle Name/Last Name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. VDB-211014 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3518|2024-08-03T01:14:01.962Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3942|2024-08-03T01:27:53.691Z -- sourcecodester -- sanitization%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3942</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Sanitization Management System and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file php-sms/?p=request_quote. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The identifier VDB-213449 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3942|2024-08-03T01:27:53.691Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3868|2024-08-03T01:20:58.789Z -- sourcecodester -- sanitization%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3868</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Sanitization Management System. Affected is an unknown function of the file /php-sms/classes/Master.php?f=save_quote. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-213012.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3868|2024-08-03T01:20:58.789Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3519|2024-08-03T01:14:02.418Z -- sourcecodester -- sanitization%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3519</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester Sanitization Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Quote Requests Tab. The manipulation of the argument Manage Remarks leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-211015.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3519|2024-08-03T01:14:02.418Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3505|2024-08-03T01:14:02.477Z -- sourcecodester -- sanitization%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3505</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Sanitization Management System. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /php-sms/admin/. The manipulation of the argument page leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-210840.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3505|2024-08-03T01:14:02.477Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
