<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- School Registration and Fee System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/school%20registration%20and%20fee%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- School Registration and Fee System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 23:22:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1675|2024-08-02T05:57:24.974Z -- sourcecodester -- school%20registration%20and%20fee%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1675</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester School Registration and Fee System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /bilal final/edit_stud.php of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-224232.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in SourceCodester School Registration and Fee System 1.0 ausgemacht. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei /bilal final/edit_stud.php der Komponente GET Parameter Handler. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1675|2024-08-02T05:57:24.974Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 21:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1674|2024-08-02T05:57:24.670Z -- sourcecodester -- school%20registration%20and%20fee%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1674</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester School Registration and Fee System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /bilal final/login.php of the component POST Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-224231.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester School Registration and Fee System 1.0 gefunden. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei /bilal final/login.php der Komponente POST Parameter Handler. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments username mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1674|2024-08-02T05:57:24.670Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 20:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
