<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Simple Inventory System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/simple%20inventory%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Simple Inventory System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5098|2024-06-04T18:02:57.899Z -- sourcecodester -- simple%20inventory%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5098</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Simple Inventory System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file login.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-265081 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In SourceCodester Simple Inventory System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei login.php. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments username mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5098|2024-06-04T18:02:57.899Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 06:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5099|2024-06-04T18:02:52.427Z -- sourcecodester -- simple%20inventory%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5099</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Simple Inventory System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file updateprice.php. The manipulation of the argument ITEM leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-265082 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Simple Inventory System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei updateprice.php. Durch Manipulation des Arguments ITEM mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5099|2024-06-04T18:02:52.427Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 08:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5100|2024-06-04T18:02:16.435Z -- sourcecodester -- simple%20inventory%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5100</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Simple Inventory System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file tableedit.php. The manipulation of the argument from/to leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-265083.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Simple Inventory System 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei tableedit.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments from/to mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5100|2024-06-04T18:02:16.435Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 11:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5101|2024-06-04T18:02:08.522Z -- sourcecodester -- simple%20inventory%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5101</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Simple Inventory System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file updateproduct.php. The manipulation of the argument ITEM leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-265084.
In SourceCodester Simple Inventory System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei updateproduct.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments ITEM mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5101|2024-06-04T18:02:08.522Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 14:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5097|2024-06-04T18:01:43.371Z -- sourcecodester -- simple%20inventory%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5097</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Simple Inventory System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /tableedit.php#page=editprice. The manipulation of the argument itemnumber leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-265080.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Simple Inventory System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei /tableedit.php#page=editprice. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments itemnumber mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross-site request forgery-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5097|2024-06-04T18:01:43.371Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 03:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
