<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Simple and Beautiful Shopping Cart System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/simple%20and%20beautiful%20shopping%20cart%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Simple and Beautiful Shopping Cart System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 10:23:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1739|2024-08-02T05:57:25.194Z -- sourcecodester -- simple%20and%20beautiful%20shopping%20cart%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1739</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Simple and Beautiful Shopping Cart System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file upload.php. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-224627.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Simple and Beautiful Shopping Cart System 1.0 gefunden. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei upload.php. Durch das Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1739|2024-08-02T05:57:25.194Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 20:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1940|2024-08-02T06:05:27.072Z -- sourcecodester -- simple%20and%20beautiful%20shopping%20cart%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1940</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Simple and Beautiful Shopping Cart System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file delete_user_query.php. The manipulation of the argument user_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-225316.
In SourceCodester Simple and Beautiful Shopping Cart System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei delete_user_query.php. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments user_id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1940|2024-08-02T06:05:27.072Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 17:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1941|2024-08-02T06:05:27.081Z -- sourcecodester -- simple%20and%20beautiful%20shopping%20cart%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1941</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Simple and Beautiful Shopping Cart System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file login.php. The manipulation of the argument username/password leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-225317 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Simple and Beautiful Shopping Cart System 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei login.php. Durch Manipulation des Arguments username/password mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1941|2024-08-02T06:05:27.081Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 17:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
