<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Simple E-Learning System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/simple%20e-learning%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Simple E-Learning System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 20:22:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2665|2024-08-03T00:46:03.696Z -- sourcecodester -- simple%20e-learning%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2665</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Simple E-Learning System. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file classroom.php. The manipulation of the argument post_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-205615.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2665|2024-08-03T00:46:03.696Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:45:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2699|2024-08-03T00:46:03.678Z -- sourcecodester -- simple%20e-learning%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2699</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Simple E-Learning System. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /claire_blake. The manipulation of the argument phoneNumber leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-205820.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2699|2024-08-03T00:46:03.678Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 12:25:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2701|2024-08-03T00:46:03.776Z -- sourcecodester -- simple%20e-learning%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2701</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester Simple E-Learning System. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /claire_blake. The manipulation of the argument Bio leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-205822 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2701|2024-08-03T00:46:03.776Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 12:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2490|2024-08-03T00:39:07.893Z -- sourcecodester -- simple%20e-learning%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2490</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Simple E-Learning System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file search.php. The manipulation of the argument classCode with the input 1'||(SELECT 0x74666264 WHERE 5610=5610 AND (SELECT 7504 FROM(SELECT COUNT(*),CONCAT(0x7171627a71,(SELECT (ELT(7504=7504,1))),0x71717a7071,FLOOR(RAND(0)*2))x FROM INFORMATION_SCHEMA.PLUGINS GROUP BY x)a))||' leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2490|2024-08-03T00:39:07.893Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 11:35:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2489|2024-08-03T00:39:07.676Z -- sourcecodester -- simple%20e-learning%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2489</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Simple E-Learning System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file classRoom.php. The manipulation of the argument classCode with the input 1'||(SELECT 0x6770715a WHERE 8795=8795 AND (SELECT 8342 FROM(SELECT COUNT(*),CONCAT(0x7171786b71,(SELECT (ELT(8342=8342,1))),0x717a7a7671,FLOOR(RAND(0)*2))x FROM INFORMATION_SCHEMA.PLUGINS GROUP BY x)a))||' leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2489|2024-08-03T00:39:07.676Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 11:35:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2704|2024-08-03T00:46:03.472Z -- sourcecodester -- simple%20e-learning%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2704</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Simple E-Learning System. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file downloadFiles.php. The manipulation of the argument download leads to information disclosure. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-205828.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2704|2024-08-03T00:46:03.472Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 12:50:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2697|2024-08-03T00:46:03.846Z -- sourcecodester -- simple%20e-learning%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2697</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Simple E-Learning System. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file comment_frame.php. The manipulation of the argument post_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-205818 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2697|2024-08-03T00:46:03.846Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 20:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2396|2024-08-03T00:39:07.538Z -- sourcecodester -- simple%20e-learning%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2396</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester Simple e-Learning System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /vcs/claire_blake. The manipulation of the argument Bio with the input "&gt;&lt;script&gt;alert(document.cookie)&lt;/script&gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2396|2024-08-03T00:39:07.538Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 12:06:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2698|2024-08-03T00:46:04.092Z -- sourcecodester -- simple%20e-learning%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2698</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Simple E-Learning System. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file search.php. The manipulation of the argument searchPost leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-205819.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2698|2024-08-03T00:46:04.092Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 20:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
