<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Simple Book Catalog App</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/simple%20book%20catalog%20app.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Simple Book Catalog App</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 11:20:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4847|2024-08-02T07:38:00.767Z -- sourcecodester -- simple%20book%20catalog%20app
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4847</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SourceCodester Simple Book Catalog App 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the component Update Book Form. The manipulation of the argument book_title/book_author leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-239256.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Simple Book Catalog App 1.0 entdeckt. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Komponente Update Book Form. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments book_title/book_author mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4847|2024-08-02T07:38:00.767Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 08:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4848|2024-08-02T07:38:00.905Z -- sourcecodester -- simple%20book%20catalog%20app
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4848</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Simple Book Catalog App 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file delete_book.php. The manipulation of the argument delete leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-239257 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In SourceCodester Simple Book Catalog App 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei delete_book.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments delete mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4848|2024-08-02T07:38:00.905Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 10:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
