<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Student Study Center Desk Management System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/student%20study%20center%20desk%20management%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Student Study Center Desk Management System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 22:22:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1568|2024-07-12T21:06:48.272Z -- sourcecodester -- student%20study%20center%20desk%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1568</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SourceCodester Student Study Center Desk Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/reports/index.php of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument date_to leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-223560.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Student Study Center Desk Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei /admin/reports/index.php der Komponente GET Parameter Handler. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments date_to mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1568|2024-07-12T21:06:48.272Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 14:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
