<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Tracking Monitoring Management System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/tracking%20monitoring%20management%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Tracking Monitoring Management System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 18:24:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7360|2024-08-01T17:31:04.038Z -- sourcecodester -- tracking%20monitoring%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7360</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SourceCodester Tracking Monitoring Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /ajax.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273339.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Tracking Monitoring Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei /ajax.php. Dank der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross-site request forgery-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7360|2024-08-01T17:31:04.038Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 17:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7359|2024-08-01T16:31:04.815Z -- sourcecodester -- tracking%20monitoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7359</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Tracking Monitoring Management System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /ajax.php?action=save_establishment. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273338 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Tracking Monitoring Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei /ajax.php?action=save_establishment. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7359|2024-08-01T16:31:04.815Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 16:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
