<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- User Registration and Login System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/user%20registration%20and%20login%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- User Registration and Login System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 11:20:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6464|2024-08-02T08:28:21.986Z -- sourcecodester -- user%20registration%20and%20login%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6464</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester User Registration and Login System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /endpoint/add-user.php. The manipulation of the argument user leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-246614 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester User Registration and Login System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei /endpoint/add-user.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments user mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6464|2024-08-02T08:28:21.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 09:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6462|2024-08-02T08:28:21.893Z -- sourcecodester -- user%20registration%20and%20login%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6462</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester User Registration and Login System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /endpoint/delete-user.php. The manipulation of the argument user leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-246612.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in SourceCodester User Registration and Login System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei /endpoint/delete-user.php. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments user mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6462|2024-08-02T08:28:21.893Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 21:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6463|2024-08-02T08:28:21.830Z -- sourcecodester -- user%20registration%20and%20login%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6463</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester User Registration and Login System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /endpoint/add-user.php. The manipulation of the argument first_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-246613 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In SourceCodester User Registration and Login System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei /endpoint/add-user.php. Durch Manipulation des Arguments first_name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6463|2024-08-02T08:28:21.830Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 22:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
