<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Vehicle Management System</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/vehicle%20management%20system.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Vehicle Management System</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 23:21:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-5377|2024-05-26T21:00:04.550Z -- SourceCodester -- Vehicle Management System</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5377</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Vehicle Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /newvehicle.php. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-266289 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Vehicle Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei /newvehicle.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments file mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5377|2024-05-26T21:00:04.550Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 21:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5145|2024-05-20T22:31:04.320Z -- SourceCodester -- Vehicle Management System</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5145</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Vehicle Management System up to 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /newdriver.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-265289 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Vehicle Management System bis 1.0 gefunden. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei /newdriver.php der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments file mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5145|2024-05-20T22:31:04.320Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 22:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>