<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Yoga Class Registration System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/yoga%20class%20registration%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Yoga Class Registration System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 13:23:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1395|2024-08-02T05:49:11.271Z -- sourcecodester -- yoga%20class%20registration%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1395</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Yoga Class Registration System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function query of the file admin/user/list.php. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-222982 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In SourceCodester Yoga Class Registration System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist die Funktion query der Datei admin/user/list.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1395|2024-08-02T05:49:11.271Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 14:33:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1366|2024-08-02T05:49:10.252Z -- sourcecodester -- yoga%20class%20registration%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1366</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Yoga Class Registration System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function query of the file admin/categories/manage_category.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-222873 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Yoga Class Registration System 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es die Funktion query der Datei admin/categories/manage_category.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1366|2024-08-02T05:49:10.252Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 08:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0982|2024-08-02T05:32:46.390Z -- sourcecodester -- yoga%20class%20registration%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0982</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Yoga Class Registration System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Add Class Entry. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The identifier VDB-221677 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In SourceCodester Yoga Class Registration System 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Komponente Add Class Entry. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0982|2024-08-02T05:32:46.390Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 11:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0981|2024-08-02T05:32:46.413Z -- sourcecodester -- yoga%20class%20registration%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0981</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Yoga Class Registration System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the component Delete User. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-221676.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Yoga Class Registration System 1.0 ausgemacht. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Komponente Delete User. Durch Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0981|2024-08-02T05:32:46.413Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 11:06:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0980|2024-08-02T05:32:46.380Z -- sourcecodester -- yoga%20class%20registration%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0980</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Yoga Class Registration System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file admin/registrations/update_status.php of the component Status Update Handler. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-221675.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Yoga Class Registration System 1.0 gefunden. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei admin/registrations/update_status.php der Komponente Status Update Handler. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0980|2024-08-02T05:32:46.380Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 11:06:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
