<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SourceCodester -- Young Entrepreneur E-Negosyo System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcecodester/young%20entrepreneur%20e-negosyo%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SourceCodester -- Young Entrepreneur E-Negosyo System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 17:22:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1735|2024-08-02T05:57:25.202Z -- sourcecodester -- young%20entrepreneur%20e-negosyo%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1735</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Young Entrepreneur E-Negosyo System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file passwordrecover.php. The manipulation of the argument phonenumber leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-224623.
In SourceCodester Young Entrepreneur E-Negosyo System 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei passwordrecover.php. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments phonenumber mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1735|2024-08-02T05:57:25.202Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 19:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1738|2024-08-02T05:57:25.013Z -- sourcecodester -- young%20entrepreneur%20e-negosyo%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1738</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Young Entrepreneur E-Negosyo System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file index.php?q=product. The manipulation of the argument search leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. VDB-224626 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In SourceCodester Young Entrepreneur E-Negosyo System 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle gefunden. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei index.php?q=product. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments search mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1738|2024-08-02T05:57:25.013Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 20:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1734|2024-08-02T05:57:25.139Z -- sourcecodester -- young%20entrepreneur%20e-negosyo%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1734</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Young Entrepreneur E-Negosyo System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file admin/products/controller.php?action=add. The manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. VDB-224622 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Young Entrepreneur E-Negosyo System 1.0 entdeckt. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei admin/products/controller.php?action=add. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments image mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1734|2024-08-02T05:57:25.139Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 19:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1736|2024-08-02T05:57:24.979Z -- sourcecodester -- young%20entrepreneur%20e-negosyo%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1736</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Young Entrepreneur E-Negosyo System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file cart/controller.php?action=add. The manipulation of the argument PROID leads to sql injection. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-224624.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Young Entrepreneur E-Negosyo System 1.0 entdeckt. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei cart/controller.php?action=add. Durch Manipulation des Arguments PROID mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1736|2024-08-02T05:57:24.979Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 19:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1737|2024-08-02T05:57:25.224Z -- sourcecodester -- young%20entrepreneur%20e-negosyo%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1737</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Young Entrepreneur E-Negosyo System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file login.php. The manipulation of the argument U_USERNAME leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The identifier VDB-224625 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Young Entrepreneur E-Negosyo System 1.0 gefunden. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei login.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments U_USERNAME mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1737|2024-08-02T05:57:25.224Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 20:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1485|2024-08-02T05:49:11.657Z -- sourcecodester -- young%20entrepreneur%20e-negosyo%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1485</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SourceCodester Young Entrepreneur E-Negosyo System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /bsenordering/index.php of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument category with the input &lt;script&gt;alert(222)&lt;/script&gt; leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-223371.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in SourceCodester Young Entrepreneur E-Negosyo System 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei /bsenordering/index.php der Komponente GET Parameter Handler. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments category mit der Eingabe &lt;script&gt;alert(222)&lt;/script&gt; mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1485|2024-08-02T05:49:11.657Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 20:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1686|2024-08-02T05:57:25.025Z -- sourcecodester -- young%20entrepreneur%20e-negosyo%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1686</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Young Entrepreneur E-Negosyo System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file bsenordering/admin/category/index.php of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument view with the input &lt;script&gt;alert(233)&lt;/script&gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-224243.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in SourceCodester Young Entrepreneur E-Negosyo System 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei bsenordering/admin/category/index.php der Komponente GET Parameter Handler. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments view mit der Eingabe &lt;script&gt;alert(233)&lt;/script&gt; mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1686|2024-08-02T05:57:25.025Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 07:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
