<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Symantec Corporation -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/symantec%20corporation/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Symantec Corporation -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:19:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-9097|2024-08-06T02:42:10.388Z -- symantec%20corporation -- symantec%20advanced%20secure%20gateway%20%28asg%29%20and%20proxysg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-9097</link>
      <description>The Symantec Advanced Secure Gateway (ASG) 6.6 prior to 6.6.5.8, ProxySG 6.5 prior 6.5.10.6, ProxySG 6.6 prior to 6.6.5.8, and ProxySG 6.7 prior to 6.7.1.2 management consoles do not, under certain circumstances, correctly authorize administrator users. A malicious administrator with read-only access can exploit this vulnerability to access management console functionality that requires read-write access privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-9097|2024-08-06T02:42:10.388Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-9099|2024-08-06T02:42:10.150Z -- symantec%20corporation -- asg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-9099</link>
      <description>Symantec Advanced Secure Gateway (ASG) 6.6, ASG 6.7 prior to 6.7.2.1, ProxySG 6.5 prior to 6.5.10.6, ProxySG 6.6, and ProxySG 6.7 prior to 6.7.2.1 are susceptible to an open redirection vulnerability. A remote attacker can use a crafted management console URL in a phishing attack to redirect the target user to a malicious web site.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-9099|2024-08-06T02:42:10.150Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10257|2024-08-06T03:14:42.820Z -- symantec%20corporation -- asg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10257</link>
      <description>The Symantec Advanced Secure Gateway (ASG) 6.6, ASG 6.7 (prior to 6.7.2.1), ProxySG 6.5 (prior to 6.5.10.6), ProxySG 6.6, and ProxySG 6.7 (prior to 6.7.2.1) management console is susceptible to a reflected XSS vulnerability. A remote attacker can use a crafted management console URL in a phishing attack to inject arbitrary JavaScript code into the management console web client application. This is a separate vulnerability from CVE-2016-10256.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10257|2024-08-06T03:14:42.820Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-9091|2024-08-06T02:42:10.359Z -- symantec%20corporation -- blue%20coat%20asg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-9091</link>
      <description>Blue Coat Advanced Secure Gateway (ASG) 6.6 before 6.6.5.4 and Content Analysis System (CAS) 1.3 before 1.3.7.4 are susceptible to an OS command injection vulnerability. An authenticated malicious administrator can execute arbitrary OS commands with elevated system privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-9091|2024-08-06T02:42:10.359Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10259|2024-08-06T03:14:42.997Z -- symantec%20corporation -- ssl%20visibility
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10259</link>
      <description>Symantec SSL Visibility (SSLV) 3.8.4FC, 3.9, 3.10 before 3.10.4.1, and 3.11 before 3.11.3.1 is susceptible to a denial-of-service vulnerability that impacts the SSL servers for intercepted SSL connections. A malicious SSL client can, under certain circumstances, temporarily exhaust the TCP connection pool of an SSL server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10259|2024-08-06T03:14:42.997Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-9093|2024-08-06T02:42:10.685Z -- symantec%20corporation -- endpoint%20protection
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-9093</link>
      <description>A version of the SymEvent Driver that shipped with Symantec Endpoint Protection 12.1 RU6 MP6 and earlier fails to properly sanitize logged-in user input. SEP 14.0 and later are not impacted by this issue. A non-admin user would need to be able to save an executable file to disk and then be able to successfully run that file. If properly constructed, the file could access the driver interface and potentially manipulate certain system calls. On all 32-bit systems and in most cases on 64-bit systems, this will result in a denial of service that will crash the system. In very narrow circumstances, and on 64-bit systems only, this could allow the user to run arbitrary code on the local machine with kernel-level privileges. This could result in a non-privileged user gaining privileged access on the local machine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-9093|2024-08-06T02:42:10.685Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-9100|2024-08-06T02:42:10.357Z -- symantec%20corporation -- asg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-9100</link>
      <description>Symantec Advanced Secure Gateway (ASG) 6.6 prior to 6.6.5.13, ASG 6.7 prior to 6.7.3.1, ProxySG 6.5 prior to 6.5.10.6, ProxySG 6.6 prior to 6.6.5.13, and ProxySG 6.7 prior to 6.7.3.1 are susceptible to an information disclosure vulnerability. An attacker with local access to the client host of an authenticated administrator user can, under certain circumstances, obtain sensitive authentication credential information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-9100|2024-08-06T02:42:10.357Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10258|2024-08-06T03:14:42.923Z -- symantec%20corporation -- advanced%20secure%20gateway%20%28asg%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10258</link>
      <description>Unrestricted file upload vulnerability in the Symantec Advanced Secure Gateway (ASG) and ProxySG management consoles. A malicious appliance administrator can upload arbitrary malicious files to the management console and trick another administrator user into downloading and executing malicious code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10258|2024-08-06T03:14:42.923Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10256|2024-08-06T03:14:42.882Z -- symantec%20corporation -- proxysg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10256</link>
      <description>The Symantec ProxySG 6.5 (prior to 6.5.10.6), 6.6, and 6.7 (prior to 6.7.2.1) management console is susceptible to a reflected XSS vulnerability. A remote attacker can use a crafted management console URL in a phishing attack to inject arbitrary JavaScript code into the management console web client application. This is a separate vulnerability from CVE-2016-10257.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10256|2024-08-06T03:14:42.882Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-9094|2024-08-06T02:42:10.411Z -- symantec%20corporation -- endpoint%20protection
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-9094</link>
      <description>Symantec Endpoint Protection clients place detected malware in quarantine as part of the intended product functionality. The quarantine logs can be exported for review by the user in a variety of formats including .CSV files. Prior to 14.0 MP1 and 12.1 RU6 MP7, the potential exists for file metadata to be interpreted and evaluated as a formula. Successful exploitation of an attack of this type requires considerable direct user-interaction from the user exporting and then opening the log files on the intended target client.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-9094|2024-08-06T02:42:10.411Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-9092|2024-08-06T02:42:10.913Z -- symantec%20corporation -- content%20analysis%20%28ca%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-9092</link>
      <description>The Symantec Content Analysis (CA) 1.3, 2.x prior to 2.2.1.1, and Mail Threat Defense (MTD) 1.1 management consoles are susceptible to a cross-site request forging (CSRF) vulnerability. A remote attacker can use phishing or other social engineering techniques to access the management console with the privileges of an authenticated administrator user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-9092|2024-08-06T02:42:10.913Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
