<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Symantec Corporation -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/symantec%20corporation/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Symantec Corporation -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 18:24:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5236|2024-08-05T05:33:43.685Z -- symantec%20corporation -- symantec%20endpoint%20protection
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5236</link>
      <description>Symantec Endpoint Protection prior to 14 RU1 MP1 or 12.1 RU6 MP10 may be susceptible to a race condition (or race hazard). This type of issue occurs in software where the output is dependent on the sequence or timing of other uncontrollable events.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5236|2024-08-05T05:33:43.685Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12243|2024-08-05T08:30:59.627Z -- symantec%20corporation -- symantec%20messaging%20gateway
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12243</link>
      <description>The Symantec Messaging Gateway product prior to 10.6.6 may be susceptible to a XML external entity (XXE) exploit, which is a type of issue where XML input containing a reference to an external entity is processed by a weakly configured XML parser. The attack uses file URI schemes or relative paths in the system identifier to access files that should not normally be accessible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12243|2024-08-05T08:30:59.627Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12242|2024-08-05T08:30:59.436Z -- symantec%20corporation -- symantec%20messaging%20gateway
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12242</link>
      <description>The Symantec Messaging Gateway product prior to 10.6.6 may be susceptible to an authentication bypass exploit, which is a type of issue that can allow attackers to potentially circumvent security mechanisms currently in place and gain access to the system or network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12242|2024-08-05T08:30:59.436Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12241|2024-08-05T08:30:58.999Z -- symantec%20corporation -- symantec%20security%20analytics%20%28sa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12241</link>
      <description>The Symantec Security Analytics (SA) 7.x prior to 7.3.4 Web UI is susceptible to a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability. A remote attacker with knowledge of the SA web UI hostname or IP address can craft a malicious URL for the SA web UI and target SA web UI users with phishing attacks or other social engineering techniques. A successful attack allows injecting malicious JavaScript code into the SA web UI client application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12241|2024-08-05T08:30:58.999Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6327|2024-08-05T15:25:49.090Z -- symantec%20corporation -- messaging%20gateway
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6327</link>
      <description>The Symantec Messaging Gateway before 10.6.3-267 can encounter an issue of remote code execution, which describes a situation whereby an individual may obtain the ability to execute commands remotely on a target machine or in a target process. In this type of occurrence, after gaining access to the system, the attacker may attempt to elevate their privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6327|2024-08-05T15:25:49.090Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6330|2024-08-05T15:25:49.142Z -- symantec%20corporation -- symantec%20encryption%20desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6330</link>
      <description>Symantec Encryption Desktop before SED 10.4.1MP2 can allow remote attackers to cause a denial of service (resource consumption) via crafted web requests."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6330|2024-08-05T15:25:49.142Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12238|2024-08-05T08:30:58.948Z -- symantec%20corporation -- norton%3B%20symantec%20endpoint%20protection%20%28sep%29%3B%20symantec%20endpoint%20protection%20small%20business%20edition%20%28sep%20sbe%29%3B%20symantec%20endpoint%20protection%20cloud%20%28sep%20cloud%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12238</link>
      <description>Norton prior to 22.15; Symantec Endpoint Protection (SEP) prior to 12.1.7454.7000 &amp; 14.2; Symantec Endpoint Protection Small Business Edition (SEP SBE) prior to NIS-22.15.1.8 &amp; SEP-12.1.7454.7000; and Symantec Endpoint Protection Cloud (SEP Cloud) prior to 22.15.1 may be susceptible to an AV bypass issue, which is a type of exploit that works to circumvent one of the virus detection engines to avoid a specific type of virus protection. One of the antivirus engines depends on a signature pattern from a database to identify malicious files and viruses; the antivirus bypass exploit looks to alter the file being scanned so it is not detected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12238|2024-08-05T08:30:58.948Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5234|2024-08-05T05:33:43.639Z -- symantec%20corporation -- norton%20core
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5234</link>
      <description>The Norton Core router prior to v237 may be susceptible to a command injection exploit. This is a type of attack in which the goal is execution of arbitrary commands on the host system via vulnerable software.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5234|2024-08-05T05:33:43.639Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12245|2024-08-05T08:30:59.056Z -- symantec%20corporation -- symantec%20endpoint%20protection%20%28sep%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12245</link>
      <description>Symantec Endpoint Protection prior to 14.2 MP1 may be susceptible to a DLL Preloading vulnerability, which in this case is an issue that can occur when an application being installed unintentionally loads a DLL provided by a potential attacker. Note that this particular type of exploit only manifests at install time; no remediation is required for software that has already been installed. This issue only impacted the Trialware media for Symantec Endpoint Protection, which has since been updated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12245|2024-08-05T08:30:59.056Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5235|2024-08-05T05:33:42.772Z -- symantec%20corporation -- norton%20utilities
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5235</link>
      <description>Norton Utilities (prior to 16.0.3.44) may be susceptible to a DLL Preloading vulnerability, which is a type of issue that can occur when an application looks to call a DLL for execution and an attacker provides a malicious DLL to use instead. Depending on how the application is configured, it will generally follow a specific search path to locate the DLL. The vulnerability can be exploited by a simple file write (or potentially an over-write) which results in a foreign DLL running under the context of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5235|2024-08-05T05:33:42.772Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18366|2024-08-05T11:08:21.470Z -- symantec%20corporation -- norton%20security
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18366</link>
      <description>Symantec Norton Security prior to 22.16.3, SEP (Windows client) prior to and including 12.1 RU6 MP9, and prior to 14.2 RU1, SEP SBE prior to Cloud Agent 3.00.31.2817, NIS-22.15.2.22, SEP-12.1.7484.7002 and SEP Cloud prior to 22.16.3 may be susceptible to a kernel memory disclosure, which is a type of issue where a specially crafted IRP request can cause the driver to return uninitialized memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18366|2024-08-05T11:08:21.470Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 19:13:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18380|2024-08-05T01:54:13.652Z -- symantec%20corporation -- industrial%20control%20system%20protection%20%28icsp%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18380</link>
      <description>Symantec Industrial Control System Protection (ICSP), versions 6.x.x, may be susceptible to an unauthorized access issue that could potentially allow a threat actor to create or modify application user accounts without proper authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18380|2024-08-05T01:54:13.652Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12237|2024-08-05T08:30:59.778Z -- symantec%20corporation -- symantec%20reporter
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12237</link>
      <description>The Symantec Reporter CLI 10.1 prior to 10.1.5.6 and 10.2 prior to 10.2.1.8 is susceptible to an OS command injection vulnerability. An authenticated malicious administrator with Enable mode access can execute arbitrary OS commands with elevated system privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12237|2024-08-05T08:30:59.778Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18369|2024-08-05T11:08:21.684Z -- symantec%20corporation -- norton%20security
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18369</link>
      <description>Norton Security (Windows client) prior to 22.16.3 and SEP SBE (Windows client) prior to Cloud Agent 3.00.31.2817, NIS-22.15.2.22 &amp; SEP-12.1.7484.7002, may be susceptible to a DLL Preloading vulnerability, which is a type of issue that can occur when an application looks to call a DLL for execution and an attacker provides a malicious DLL to use instead.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18369|2024-08-05T11:08:21.684Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 16:55:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12246|2024-08-05T08:30:59.484Z -- symantec%20corporation -- symantec%20web%20isolation
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12246</link>
      <description>Symantec Web Isolation (WI) 1.11 prior to 1.11.21 is susceptible to a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability. A remote attacker can target end users protected by WI with social engineering attacks using crafted URLs for legitimate web sites. A successful attack allows injecting malicious JavaScript code into the website's rendered copy running inside the end user's web browser. It does not allow injecting code into the real (isolated) copy of the website running on the WI Threat Isolation Engine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12246|2024-08-05T08:30:59.484Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5243|2024-08-05T05:33:43.760Z -- symantec%20corporation -- symantec%20encryption%20management%20server%20%28sems%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5243</link>
      <description>The Symantec Encryption Management Server (SEMS) product, prior to version 3.4.2 MP1, may be susceptible to a denial of service (DoS) exploit. A DoS attack is a type of attack whereby the perpetrator attempts to make a particular machine or network resource unavailable to its intended users by temporarily or indefinitely disrupting services of a specific host within a network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5243|2024-08-05T05:33:43.760Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6325|2024-08-05T15:25:49.167Z -- symantec%20corporation -- messaging%20gateway
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6325</link>
      <description>The Symantec Messaging Gateway can encounter a file inclusion vulnerability, which is a type of vulnerability that is most commonly found to affect web applications that rely on a scripting run time. This issue is caused when an application builds a path to executable code using an attacker-controlled variable in a way that allows the attacker to control which file is executed at run time. This file inclusion vulnerability subverts how an application loads code for execution. Successful exploitation of a file inclusion vulnerability will result in remote code execution on the web server that runs the affected web application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6325|2024-08-05T15:25:49.167Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12240|2024-08-05T08:30:59.391Z -- symantec%20corporation -- norton%20identity%20safe%20for%20android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12240</link>
      <description>The Norton Identity Safe product prior to 5.3.0.976 may be susceptible to a privilege escalation issue via a hard coded IV, which is a type of vulnerability that can potentially increase the likelihood of encrypted data being recovered without adequate credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12240|2024-08-05T08:30:59.391Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18371|2024-08-05T11:08:21.699Z -- symantec%20corporation -- symantec%20advanced%20secure%20gateway%20%28asg%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18371</link>
      <description>The ASG/ProxySG FTP proxy WebFTP mode allows intercepting FTP connections where a user accesses an FTP server via a ftp:// URL in a web browser. An information disclosure vulnerability in the WebFTP mode allows a malicious user to obtain plaintext authentication credentials for a remote FTP server from the ASG/ProxySG's web listing of the FTP server. Affected versions: ASG 6.6 and 6.7 prior to 6.7.4.2; ProxySG 6.5 prior to 6.5.10.15, 6.6, and 6.7 prior to 6.7.4.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18371|2024-08-05T11:08:21.699Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 22:14:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6323|2024-08-05T15:25:48.931Z -- symantec%20corporation -- itms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6323</link>
      <description>The Symantec Management Console prior to ITMS 8.1 RU1, ITMS 8.0_POST_HF6, and ITMS 7.6_POST_HF7 has an issue whereby XML input containing a reference to an external entity is processed by a weakly configured XML parser. This attack may lead to the disclosure of confidential data, denial of service, server side request forgery, port scanning from the perspective of the machine where the parser is located, and other system impacts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6323|2024-08-05T15:25:48.931Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6328|2024-08-05T15:25:49.165Z -- symantec%20corporation -- messaging%20gateway
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6328</link>
      <description>The Symantec Messaging Gateway before 10.6.3-267 can encounter an issue of cross site request forgery (also known as one-click attack and is abbreviated as CSRF or XSRF), which is a type of malicious exploit of a website where unauthorized commands are transmitted from a user that the web application trusts. A CSRF attack attempts to exploit the trust that a specific website has in a user's browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6328|2024-08-05T15:25:49.165Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18367|2024-08-05T11:08:21.714Z -- symantec%20corporation -- symantec%20endpoint%20protection%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18367</link>
      <description>Symantec Endpoint Protection Manager (SEPM) prior to and including 12.1 RU6 MP9 and prior to 14.2 RU1 may be susceptible to a DLL Preloading vulnerability, which is a type of issue that can occur when an application looks to call a DLL for execution and an attacker provides a malicious DLL to use instead.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18367|2024-08-05T11:08:21.714Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 19:22:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18364|2024-08-05T11:08:21.470Z -- symantec%20corporation -- ghost%20solution%20suite%20%28gss%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18364</link>
      <description>Symantec Ghost Solution Suite (GSS) versions prior to 3.3 RU1 may be susceptible to a DLL hijacking vulnerability, which is a type of issue whereby a potential attacker attempts to execute unexpected code on your machine. This occurs via placement of a potentially foreign file (DLL) that the attacker then attempts to run via a linked application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18364|2024-08-05T11:08:21.470Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5242|2024-08-05T05:33:44.127Z -- symantec%20corporation -- norton%20app%20lock
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5242</link>
      <description>Norton App Lock prior to version 1.3.0.329 can be susceptible to a bypass exploit. In this type of circumstance, the exploit can allow the user to circumvent the app to prevent it from locking the device, thereby allowing the individual to gain device access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5242|2024-08-05T05:33:44.127Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6324|2024-08-05T15:25:49.171Z -- symantec%20corporation -- messaging%20gateway
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6324</link>
      <description>The Symantec Messaging Gateway, when processing a specific email attachment, can allow a malformed or corrupted Word file with a potentially malicious macro through despite the administrator having the 'disarm' functionality enabled. This constitutes a 'bypass' of the disarm functionality resident to the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6324|2024-08-05T15:25:49.171Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6331|2024-08-05T15:25:49.127Z -- symantec%20corporation -- symantec%20endpoint%20protection
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6331</link>
      <description>Prior to SEP 14 RU1 Symantec Endpoint Protection product can encounter an issue of Tamper-Protection Bypass, which is a type of attack that bypasses the real time protection for the application that is run on servers and clients.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6331|2024-08-05T15:25:49.127Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5239|2024-08-05T05:33:42.731Z -- symantec%20corporation -- norton%20app%20lock
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5239</link>
      <description>Norton App Lock prior to v1.3.0.332 can be susceptible to a bypass exploit. In this type of circumstance, the exploit can allow the user to circumvent the app to prevent it from locking the device, thereby allowing the individual to gain device access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5239|2024-08-05T05:33:42.731Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12244|2024-08-05T08:30:59.637Z -- symantec%20corporation -- symantec%20endpoint%20protection%20%28mac%20client%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12244</link>
      <description>SEP (Mac client) prior to and including 12.1 RU6 MP9 and prior to 14.2 RU1 may be susceptible to a CSV/DDE injection (also known as formula injection) vulnerability, which is a type of issue whereby an application or website allows untrusted input into CSV files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12244|2024-08-05T08:30:59.637Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 18:49:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18363|2024-08-05T11:08:21.439Z -- symantec%20corporation -- norton%20app%20lock
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18363</link>
      <description>Norton App Lock prior to 1.4.0.445 can be susceptible to a bypass exploit. In this type of circumstance, the exploit can allow the user to circumvent the app to prevent it from locking the device, thereby allowing the individual to gain device access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18363|2024-08-05T11:08:21.439Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5240|2024-08-05T05:33:44.228Z -- symantec%20corporation -- inventory%20plugin%20for%20symantec%20management%20agent
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5240</link>
      <description>The Inventory Plugin for Symantec Management Agent prior to 7.6 POST HF7, 8.0 POST HF6, or 8.1 RU7 may be susceptible to a privilege escalation vulnerability, which is a type of issue that allows a user to gain elevated access to resources that are normally protected at lower access levels.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5240|2024-08-05T05:33:44.228Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5241|2024-08-05T05:33:42.763Z -- symantec%20corporation -- advanced%20secure%20gateway%20%28asg%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5241</link>
      <description>Symantec Advanced Secure Gateway (ASG) 6.6 and 6.7, and ProxySG 6.5, 6.6, and 6.7 are susceptible to a SAML authentication bypass vulnerability. The products can be configured with a SAML authentication realm to authenticate network users in intercepted proxy traffic. When parsing SAML responses, ASG and ProxySG incorrectly handle XML nodes with comments. A remote attacker can modify a valid SAML response without invalidating its cryptographic signature. This may allow the attacker to bypass user authentication security controls in ASG and ProxySG. This vulnerability only affects authentication of network users in intercepted traffic. It does not affect administrator user authentication for the ASG and ProxySG management consoles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5241|2024-08-05T05:33:42.763Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6329|2024-08-05T15:25:49.142Z -- symantec%20corporation -- vip%20access%20for%20desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6329</link>
      <description>Symantec VIP Access for Desktop prior to 2.2.4 can be susceptible to a DLL Pre-Loading vulnerability. These types of issues occur when an application looks to call a DLL for execution and an attacker provides a malicious DLL to use instead. Depending on how the application is configured, the application will generally follow a specific search path to locate the DLL. The exploitation of the vulnerability manifests as a simple file write (or potentially an over-write) which results in a foreign executable running under the context of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6329|2024-08-05T15:25:49.142Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5238|2024-08-05T05:33:42.717Z -- symantec%20corporation -- norton%20power%20eraser
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5238</link>
      <description>Norton Power Eraser (prior to 5.3.0.24) and SymDiag (prior to 2.1.242) may be susceptible to a DLL Preloading vulnerability, which is a type of issue that can occur when an application looks to call a DLL for execution and an attacker provides a malicious DLL to use instead. Depending on how the application is configured, it will generally follow a specific search path to locate the DLL. The vulnerability can be exploited by a simple file write (or potentially an over-write) which results in a foreign DLL running under the context of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5238|2024-08-05T05:33:42.717Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18370|2024-08-05T11:08:21.643Z -- symantec%20corporation -- symantec%20advanced%20secure%20gateway%20%28asg%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18370</link>
      <description>The ASG/ProxySG FTP proxy WebFTP mode allows intercepting FTP connections where a user accesses an FTP server via a ftp:// URL in a web browser. A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the WebFTP mode allows a remote attacker to inject malicious JavaScript code in ASG/ProxySG's web listing of a remote FTP server. Exploiting the vulnerability requires the attacker to be able to upload crafted files to the remote FTP server. Affected versions: ASG 6.6 and 6.7 prior to 6.7.4.2; ProxySG 6.5 prior to 6.5.10.15, 6.6, and 6.7 prior to 6.7.4.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18370|2024-08-05T11:08:21.643Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 22:13:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6326|2024-08-05T15:25:49.127Z -- symantec%20corporation -- messaging%20gateway
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6326</link>
      <description>The Symantec Messaging Gateway can encounter an issue of remote code execution, which describes a situation whereby an individual may obtain the ability to execute commands remotely on a target machine or in a target process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6326|2024-08-05T15:25:49.127Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18362|2024-08-05T11:08:21.415Z -- symantec%20corporation -- norton%20password%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18362</link>
      <description>Norton Password Manager for Android (formerly Norton Identity Safe) may be susceptible to a cross site scripting (XSS) exploit, which is a type of issue that can enable attackers to inject client-side scripts into web pages viewed by other users. A cross-site scripting vulnerability may be used by attackers to potentially bypass access controls such as the same-origin policy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18362|2024-08-05T11:08:21.415Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12239|2024-08-05T08:30:59.652Z -- symantec%20corporation -- norton%3B%20symantec%20endpoint%20protection%20%28sep%29%3B%20symantec%20endpoint%20protection%20small%20business%20edition%20%28sep%20sbe%29%3B%20symantec%20endpoint%20protection%20cloud%20%28sep%20cloud%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12239</link>
      <description>Norton prior to 22.15; Symantec Endpoint Protection (SEP) prior to 12.1.7454.7000 &amp; 14.2; Symantec Endpoint Protection Small Business Edition (SEP SBE) prior to NIS-22.15.1.8 &amp; SEP-12.1.7454.7000; and Symantec Endpoint Protection Cloud (SEP Cloud) prior to 22.15.1 may be susceptible to an AV bypass issue, which is a type of exploit that works to circumvent one of the virus detection engines to avoid a specific type of virus protection. One of the antivirus engines depends on a signature pattern from a database to identify malicious files and viruses; the antivirus bypass exploit looks to alter the file being scanned so it is not detected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12239|2024-08-05T08:30:59.652Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5237|2024-08-05T05:33:43.766Z -- symantec%20corporation -- symantec%20endpoint%20protection
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5237</link>
      <description>Symantec Endpoint Protection prior to 14 RU1 MP1 or 12.1 RU6 MP10 could be susceptible to a privilege escalation vulnerability, which is a type of issue that allows a user to gain elevated access to resources that are normally protected at lower access levels.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5237|2024-08-05T05:33:43.766Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
