<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Symantec Corporation -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/symantec%20corporation/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Symantec Corporation -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 22:22:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-13676|2024-09-16T21:09:03.016Z -- symantec%20corporation -- norton%20remove%20%26%20reinstall
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-13676</link>
      <description>Norton Remove &amp; Reinstall can be susceptible to a DLL preloading vulnerability. These types of issues occur when an application looks to call a DLL for execution and an attacker provides a malicious DLL to use instead. Depending on how the application is configured, it will generally follow a specific search path to locate the DLL. The vulnerability can be exploited by a simple file write (or potentially an over-write) which results in a foreign DLL running under the context of the application. A Norton Remove &amp; Reinstall update, version 4.4.0.58, has been released which addresses the aforementioned vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-13676|2024-09-16T21:09:03.016Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12243|2024-09-16T20:21:44.540Z -- symantec%20corporation -- symantec%20messaging%20gateway
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12243</link>
      <description>The Symantec Messaging Gateway product prior to 10.6.6 may be susceptible to a XML external entity (XXE) exploit, which is a type of issue where XML input containing a reference to an external entity is processed by a weakly configured XML parser. The attack uses file URI schemes or relative paths in the system identifier to access files that should not normally be accessible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12243|2024-09-16T20:21:44.540Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-15533|2024-09-16T18:44:44.614Z -- symantec%20corporation -- ssl%20visibility%20%28sslv%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-15533</link>
      <description>Symantec SSL Visibility (SSLV) 3.8.4FC, 3.10 prior to 3.10.4.1, 3.11, and 3.12 prior to 3.12.2.1 are vulnerable to the Return of the Bleichenbacher Oracle Threat (ROBOT) attack. All affected SSLV versions act as weak oracles according the oracle classification used in the ROBOT research paper. A remote attacker, who has captured a pre-recorded SSL session inspected by SSLV, can establish multiple millions of crafted SSL connections to the target and obtain the session keys required to decrypt the pre-recorded SSL session.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-15533|2024-09-16T18:44:44.614Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-15526|2024-09-16T17:17:36.450Z -- symantec%20corporation -- symantec%20endpoint%20encryption
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-15526</link>
      <description>Prior to SEE v11.1.3MP1, Symantec Endpoint Encryption can be susceptible to a null pointer de-reference issue, which can result in a NullPointerException that can lead to a privilege escalation scenario.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-15526|2024-09-16T17:17:36.450Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5240|2024-09-16T18:08:37.116Z -- symantec%20corporation -- inventory%20plugin%20for%20symantec%20management%20agent
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5240</link>
      <description>The Inventory Plugin for Symantec Management Agent prior to 7.6 POST HF7, 8.0 POST HF6, or 8.1 RU7 may be susceptible to a privilege escalation vulnerability, which is a type of issue that allows a user to gain elevated access to resources that are normally protected at lower access levels.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5240|2024-09-16T18:08:37.116Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-15534|2024-09-16T17:54:45.671Z -- symantec%20corporation -- norton%20app%20lock
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-15534</link>
      <description>The Norton App Lock prior to version 1.3.0.13 can be susceptible to an authentication bypass exploit. In this type of circumstance, the exploit can allow the user to kill the app to prevent it from locking the device, thereby allowing the individual to gain device access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-15534|2024-09-16T17:54:45.671Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-10257|2024-09-16T18:39:51.797Z -- symantec%20corporation -- asg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-10257</link>
      <description>The Symantec Advanced Secure Gateway (ASG) 6.6, ASG 6.7 (prior to 6.7.2.1), ProxySG 6.5 (prior to 6.5.10.6), ProxySG 6.6, and ProxySG 6.7 (prior to 6.7.2.1) management console is susceptible to a reflected XSS vulnerability. A remote attacker can use a crafted management console URL in a phishing attack to inject arbitrary JavaScript code into the management console web client application. This is a separate vulnerability from CVE-2016-10256.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-10257|2024-09-16T18:39:51.797Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5243|2024-09-16T17:24:18.090Z -- symantec%20corporation -- symantec%20encryption%20management%20server%20%28sems%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5243</link>
      <description>The Symantec Encryption Management Server (SEMS) product, prior to version 3.4.2 MP1, may be susceptible to a denial of service (DoS) exploit. A DoS attack is a type of attack whereby the perpetrator attempts to make a particular machine or network resource unavailable to its intended users by temporarily or indefinitely disrupting services of a specific host within a network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5243|2024-09-16T17:24:18.090Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-15532|2024-09-16T16:58:19.631Z -- symantec%20corporation -- messaging%20gateway
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-15532</link>
      <description>Prior to 10.6.4, Symantec Messaging Gateway may be susceptible to a path traversal attack (also known as directory traversal). These types of attacks aim to access files and directories that are stored outside the web root folder. By manipulating variables, it may be possible to access arbitrary files and directories stored on the file system including application source code or configuration and critical system files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-15532|2024-09-16T16:58:19.631Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-9094|2024-09-16T17:18:11.443Z -- symantec%20corporation -- endpoint%20protection
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-9094</link>
      <description>Symantec Endpoint Protection clients place detected malware in quarantine as part of the intended product functionality. The quarantine logs can be exported for review by the user in a variety of formats including .CSV files. Prior to 14.0 MP1 and 12.1 RU6 MP7, the potential exists for file metadata to be interpreted and evaluated as a formula. Successful exploitation of an attack of this type requires considerable direct user-interaction from the user exporting and then opening the log files on the intended target client.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-9094|2024-09-16T17:18:11.443Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-15531|2024-09-16T19:15:56.968Z -- symantec%20corporation -- reporter
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-15531</link>
      <description>Symantec Reporter 9.5 prior to 9.5.4.1 and 10.1 prior to 10.1.5.5 does not restrict excessive authentication attempts for management interface users.  A remote attacker can use brute force search to guess a user password and gain access to Reporter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-15531|2024-09-16T19:15:56.968Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-9093|2024-09-16T21:58:24.461Z -- symantec%20corporation -- endpoint%20protection
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-9093</link>
      <description>A version of the SymEvent Driver that shipped with Symantec Endpoint Protection 12.1 RU6 MP6 and earlier fails to properly sanitize logged-in user input. SEP 14.0 and later are not impacted by this issue. A non-admin user would need to be able to save an executable file to disk and then be able to successfully run that file. If properly constructed, the file could access the driver interface and potentially manipulate certain system calls. On all 32-bit systems and in most cases on 64-bit systems, this will result in a denial of service that will crash the system. In very narrow circumstances, and on 64-bit systems only, this could allow the user to run arbitrary code on the local machine with kernel-level privileges. This could result in a non-privileged user gaining privileged access on the local machine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-9093|2024-09-16T21:58:24.461Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6331|2024-09-16T19:15:59.592Z -- symantec%20corporation -- symantec%20endpoint%20protection
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6331</link>
      <description>Prior to SEP 14 RU1 Symantec Endpoint Protection product can encounter an issue of Tamper-Protection Bypass, which is a type of attack that bypasses the real time protection for the application that is run on servers and clients.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6331|2024-09-16T19:15:59.592Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-9097|2024-09-16T17:33:11.446Z -- symantec%20corporation -- symantec%20advanced%20secure%20gateway%20%28asg%29%20and%20proxysg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-9097</link>
      <description>The Symantec Advanced Secure Gateway (ASG) 6.6 prior to 6.6.5.8, ProxySG 6.5 prior 6.5.10.6, ProxySG 6.6 prior to 6.6.5.8, and ProxySG 6.7 prior to 6.7.1.2 management consoles do not, under certain circumstances, correctly authorize administrator users. A malicious administrator with read-only access can exploit this vulnerability to access management console functionality that requires read-write access privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-9097|2024-09-16T17:33:11.446Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2017 14:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-15530|2024-09-16T19:36:32.380Z -- symantec%20corporation -- norton%20family%20android%20app
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-15530</link>
      <description>Prior to 4.4.1.10, the Norton Family Android App can be susceptible to an Information Disclosure issue. Information disclosure is a very common issue that attackers will attempt to exploit as a first pass across the application. As they probe the application they will take note of anything that may seem out of place or any bit of information they can use to their advantage such as error messages, system information, user data, version numbers, component names, URL paths, or even simple typos and misspellings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-15530|2024-09-16T19:36:32.380Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5235|2024-09-16T20:31:27.130Z -- symantec%20corporation -- norton%20utilities
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5235</link>
      <description>Norton Utilities (prior to 16.0.3.44) may be susceptible to a DLL Preloading vulnerability, which is a type of issue that can occur when an application looks to call a DLL for execution and an attacker provides a malicious DLL to use instead. Depending on how the application is configured, it will generally follow a specific search path to locate the DLL. The vulnerability can be exploited by a simple file write (or potentially an over-write) which results in a foreign DLL running under the context of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5235|2024-09-16T20:31:27.130Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6329|2024-09-16T17:59:48.626Z -- symantec%20corporation -- vip%20access%20for%20desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6329</link>
      <description>Symantec VIP Access for Desktop prior to 2.2.4 can be susceptible to a DLL Pre-Loading vulnerability. These types of issues occur when an application looks to call a DLL for execution and an attacker provides a malicious DLL to use instead. Depending on how the application is configured, the application will generally follow a specific search path to locate the DLL. The exploitation of the vulnerability manifests as a simple file write (or potentially an over-write) which results in a foreign executable running under the context of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6329|2024-09-16T17:59:48.626Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12242|2024-09-16T18:55:16.447Z -- symantec%20corporation -- symantec%20messaging%20gateway
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12242</link>
      <description>The Symantec Messaging Gateway product prior to 10.6.6 may be susceptible to an authentication bypass exploit, which is a type of issue that can allow attackers to potentially circumvent security mechanisms currently in place and gain access to the system or network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12242|2024-09-16T18:55:16.447Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-9100|2024-09-16T20:42:42.195Z -- symantec%20corporation -- asg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-9100</link>
      <description>Symantec Advanced Secure Gateway (ASG) 6.6 prior to 6.6.5.13, ASG 6.7 prior to 6.7.3.1, ProxySG 6.5 prior to 6.5.10.6, ProxySG 6.6 prior to 6.6.5.13, and ProxySG 6.7 prior to 6.7.3.1 are susceptible to an information disclosure vulnerability. An attacker with local access to the client host of an authenticated administrator user can, under certain circumstances, obtain sensitive authentication credential information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-9100|2024-09-16T20:42:42.195Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2017 14:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-13680|2024-09-16T17:42:54.111Z -- symantec%20corporation -- symantec%20endpoint%20protection
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-13680</link>
      <description>Prior to SEP 12.1 RU6 MP9 &amp; SEP 14 RU1 Symantec Endpoint Protection Windows endpoint can encounter a situation whereby an attacker could use the product's UI to perform unauthorized file deletes on the resident file system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-13680|2024-09-16T17:42:54.111Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-18268|2024-09-16T17:47:49.551Z -- symantec%20corporation -- intelligencecenter
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-18268</link>
      <description>Symantec IntelligenceCenter 3.3 is vulnerable to the Return of the Bleichenbacher Oracle Threat (ROBOT) attack. A remote attacker, who has captured a pre-recorded SSL session inspected by SSLV, can establish large numbers of crafted SSL connections to the target and obtain the session keys required to decrypt the pre-recorded SSL session.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-18268|2024-09-16T17:47:49.551Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12237|2024-09-16T16:28:04.698Z -- symantec%20corporation -- symantec%20reporter
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12237</link>
      <description>The Symantec Reporter CLI 10.1 prior to 10.1.5.6 and 10.2 prior to 10.2.1.8 is susceptible to an OS command injection vulnerability. An authenticated malicious administrator with Enable mode access can execute arbitrary OS commands with elevated system privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12237|2024-09-16T16:28:04.698Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
