<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Symantec Corporation -- Messaging Gateway</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/symantec%20corporation/messaging%20gateway.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Symantec Corporation -- Messaging Gateway</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 20:22:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6327|2024-08-05T15:25:49.090Z -- symantec%20corporation -- messaging%20gateway
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6327</link>
      <description>The Symantec Messaging Gateway before 10.6.3-267 can encounter an issue of remote code execution, which describes a situation whereby an individual may obtain the ability to execute commands remotely on a target machine or in a target process. In this type of occurrence, after gaining access to the system, the attacker may attempt to elevate their privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6327|2024-08-05T15:25:49.090Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6325|2024-08-05T15:25:49.167Z -- symantec%20corporation -- messaging%20gateway
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6325</link>
      <description>The Symantec Messaging Gateway can encounter a file inclusion vulnerability, which is a type of vulnerability that is most commonly found to affect web applications that rely on a scripting run time. This issue is caused when an application builds a path to executable code using an attacker-controlled variable in a way that allows the attacker to control which file is executed at run time. This file inclusion vulnerability subverts how an application loads code for execution. Successful exploitation of a file inclusion vulnerability will result in remote code execution on the web server that runs the affected web application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6325|2024-08-05T15:25:49.167Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6328|2024-08-05T15:25:49.165Z -- symantec%20corporation -- messaging%20gateway
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6328</link>
      <description>The Symantec Messaging Gateway before 10.6.3-267 can encounter an issue of cross site request forgery (also known as one-click attack and is abbreviated as CSRF or XSRF), which is a type of malicious exploit of a website where unauthorized commands are transmitted from a user that the web application trusts. A CSRF attack attempts to exploit the trust that a specific website has in a user's browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6328|2024-08-05T15:25:49.165Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6324|2024-08-05T15:25:49.171Z -- symantec%20corporation -- messaging%20gateway
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6324</link>
      <description>The Symantec Messaging Gateway, when processing a specific email attachment, can allow a malformed or corrupted Word file with a potentially malicious macro through despite the administrator having the 'disarm' functionality enabled. This constitutes a 'bypass' of the disarm functionality resident to the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6324|2024-08-05T15:25:49.171Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6326|2024-08-05T15:25:49.127Z -- symantec%20corporation -- messaging%20gateway
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6326</link>
      <description>The Symantec Messaging Gateway can encounter an issue of remote code execution, which describes a situation whereby an individual may obtain the ability to execute commands remotely on a target machine or in a target process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6326|2024-08-05T15:25:49.127Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-15532|2024-08-05T19:57:26.486Z -- symantec%20corporation -- messaging%20gateway
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-15532</link>
      <description>Prior to 10.6.4, Symantec Messaging Gateway may be susceptible to a path traversal attack (also known as directory traversal). These types of attacks aim to access files and directories that are stored outside the web root folder. By manipulating variables, it may be possible to access arbitrary files and directories stored on the file system including application source code or configuration and critical system files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-15532|2024-08-05T19:57:26.486Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
