<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for vantage6 -- vantage6</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/vantage6/vantage6.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for vantage6 -- vantage6</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 21:54:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-22193|2024-01-30T15:50:09.928Z -- vantage6 -- vantage6
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22193</link><description>The vantage6 technology enables to manage and deploy privacy enhancing technologies like Federated Learning (FL) and Multi-Party Computation (MPC). There are no checks on whether the input is encrypted if a task is created in an encrypted collaboration. Therefore, a user may accidentally create a task with sensitive input data that will then be stored unencrypted in a database.  Users should ensure they set the encryption setting correctly.  This vulnerability is patched in 4.2.0.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22193|2024-01-30T15:50:09.928Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 15:50:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32969|2024-05-23T08:22:57.564Z -- vantage6 -- vantage6
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-32969</link><description>vantage6 is an open-source infrastructure for privacy preserving analysis. Collaboration administrators can add extra organizations to their collaboration that can extend their influence. For example, organizations that they include can then create new users for which they know the passwords, and use that to read task results of other collaborations that that organization is involved in.  This is only relatively trusted users - with access to manage a collaboration - are able to do this, which reduces the impact. This vulnerability was patched in version 4.5.0rc3.
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32969|2024-05-23T08:22:57.564Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 08:22:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23823|2024-03-14T18:47:50.328Z -- vantage6 -- vantage6
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23823</link><description>vantage6 is an open source framework built to enable, manage and deploy privacy enhancing technologies like Federated Learning and Multi-Party Computation. The vantage6 server has no restrictions on CORS settings. It should be possible for people to set the allowed origins of the server.  The impact is limited because v6 does not use session cookies. This issue has been addressed in commit `70bb4e1d8` and is expected to ship in subsequent releases. Users are advised to upgrade as soon as a new release is available. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23823|2024-03-14T18:47:50.328Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24770|2024-03-14T18:47:46.804Z -- vantage6 -- vantage6
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-24770</link><description>vantage6 is an open source framework built to enable, manage and deploy privacy enhancing technologies like Federated Learning and Multi-Party Computation. Much like GHSA-45gq-q4xh-cp53, it is possible to find which usernames exist in vantage6 by calling the API routes `/recover/lost` and `/2fa/lost`. These routes send emails to users if they have lost their password or MFA token. This issue has been addressed in commit `aecfd6d0e` and is expected to ship in subsequent releases. Users are advised to upgrade as soon as a new release is available. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24770|2024-03-14T18:47:46.804Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21653|2024-01-30T15:39:30.554Z -- vantage6 -- vantage6
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21653</link><description>The vantage6 technology enables to manage and deploy privacy enhancing technologies like Federated Learning (FL) and Multi-Party Computation (MPC).  Nodes and servers get a ssh config by default that permits root login with password authentication. In a proper deployment, the SSH service is not exposed so there is no risk, but not all deployments are ideal. The default should therefore be less permissive.  The vulnerability can be mitigated by removing the ssh part from the docker file and rebuilding the docker image.  Version 4.2.0 patches the vulnerability.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21653|2024-01-30T15:39:30.554Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 15:39:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21649|2024-01-30T15:34:49.560Z -- vantage6 -- vantage6
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21649</link><description>The vantage6 technology enables to manage and deploy privacy enhancing technologies like Federated Learning (FL) and Multi-Party Computation (MPC). Prior to 4.2.0, authenticated users could inject code into algorithm environment variables, resulting in remote code execution.  This vulnerability is patched in 4.2.0.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21649|2024-01-30T15:34:49.560Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 15:33:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21671|2024-01-30T15:43:06.789Z -- vantage6 -- vantage6
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21671</link><description>The vantage6 technology enables to manage and deploy privacy enhancing technologies like Federated Learning (FL) and Multi-Party Computation (MPC).  It is possible to find out usernames from the response time of login requests. This could aid attackers in credential attacks.  Version 4.2.0 patches this vulnerability.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21671|2024-01-30T15:43:06.789Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 15:43:06 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>