<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for NodeBB -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/nodebb/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for NodeBB -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 23:23:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36045|2024-08-03T09:52:00.523Z -- nodebb -- nodebb
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36045</link>
      <description>NodeBB Forum Software is powered by Node.js and supports either Redis, MongoDB, or a PostgreSQL database. It utilizes web sockets for instant interactions and real-time notifications. `utils.generateUUID`, a helper function available in essentially all versions of NodeBB (as far back as v1.0.1 and potentially earlier) used a cryptographically insecure Pseudo-random number generator (`Math.random()`), which meant that a specially crafted script combined with multiple invocations of the password reset functionality could enable an attacker to correctly calculate the reset code for an account they do not have access to. This vulnerability impacts all installations of NodeBB. The vulnerability allows for an attacker to take over any account without the involvement of the victim, and as such, the remediation should be applied immediately (either via NodeBB upgrade or cherry-pick of the specific changeset. The vulnerability has been patched in version 2.x and 1.19.x. There is no known workaround, but the patch sets listed above will fully patch the vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36045|2024-08-03T09:52:00.523Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 15:10:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-46164|2024-08-03T14:24:03.223Z -- nodebb -- nodebb
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-46164</link>
      <description>NodeBB is an open source Node.js based forum software. Due to a plain object with a prototype being used in socket.io message handling a specially crafted payload can be used to impersonate other users and takeover accounts. This vulnerability has been patched in version 2.6.1. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade may cherry-pick commit `48d143921753914da45926cca6370a92ed0c46b8` into their codebase to patch the exploit.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-46164|2024-08-03T14:24:03.223Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 20:52:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36076|2024-08-03T09:52:00.513Z -- nodebb -- nodebb
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36076</link>
      <description>NodeBB Forum Software is powered by Node.js and supports either Redis, MongoDB, or a PostgreSQL database. Due to an unnecessarily strict conditional in the code handling the first step of the SSO process, the pre-existing logic that added (and later checked) a nonce was inadvertently rendered opt-in instead of opt-out. This re-exposed a vulnerability in that a specially crafted Man-in-the-Middle (MITM) attack could theoretically take over another user account during the single sign-on process. The issue has been fully patched in version 1.17.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36076|2024-08-03T09:52:00.513Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 12:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
