<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Icinga -- icingaweb2</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/icinga/icingaweb2.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Icinga -- icingaweb2</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 12:25:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24715|2024-08-03T04:20:50.162Z -- icinga -- icingaweb2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24715</link>
      <description>Icinga Web 2 is an open source monitoring web interface, framework and command-line interface. Authenticated users, with access to the configuration, can create SSH resource files in unintended directories, leading to the execution of arbitrary code. This issue has been resolved in versions 2.8.6, 2.9.6 and 2.10 of Icinga Web 2. Users unable to upgrade should limit access to the Icinga Web 2 configuration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24715|2024-08-03T04:20:50.162Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24714|2024-08-03T04:20:49.162Z -- icinga -- icingaweb2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24714</link>
      <description>Icinga Web 2 is an open source monitoring web interface, framework and command-line interface. Installations of Icinga 2 with the IDO writer enabled are affected. If you use service custom variables in role restrictions, and you regularly decommission service objects, users with said roles may still have access to a collection of content. Note that this only applies if a role has implicitly permitted access to hosts, due to permitted access to at least one of their services. If access to a host is permitted by other means, no sensible information has been disclosed to unauthorized users. This issue has been resolved in versions 2.8.6, 2.9.6 and 2.10 of Icinga Web 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24714|2024-08-03T04:20:49.162Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 19:55:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24716|2024-08-03T04:20:49.887Z -- icinga -- icingaweb2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24716</link>
      <description>Icinga Web 2 is an open source monitoring web interface, framework and command-line interface. Unauthenticated users can leak the contents of files of the local system accessible to the web-server user, including `icingaweb2` configuration files with database credentials. This issue has been resolved in versions 2.9.6 and 2.10 of Icinga Web 2. Database credentials should be rotated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24716|2024-08-03T04:20:49.887Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
