<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for FreeBSD -- FreeBSD</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/freebsd/freebsd.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for FreeBSD -- FreeBSD</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 13:24:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17158|2024-08-05T10:39:59.632Z -- freebsd -- freebsd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17158</link>
      <description>In FreeBSD before 11.2-STABLE(r340854) and 11.2-RELEASE-p5, an integer overflow error can occur when handling the client address length field in an NFSv4 request. Unprivileged remote users with access to the NFS server can crash the system by sending a specially crafted NFSv4 request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17158|2024-08-05T10:39:59.632Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6919|2024-08-05T06:17:17.296Z -- freebsd -- freebsd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6919</link>
      <description>In FreeBSD before 11.1-STABLE, 11.1-RELEASE-p9, 10.4-STABLE, 10.4-RELEASE-p8 and 10.3-RELEASE-p28, due to insufficient initialization of memory copied to userland, small amounts of kernel memory may be disclosed to userland processes. Unprivileged users may be able to access small amounts privileged kernel data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6919|2024-08-05T06:17:17.296Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6922|2024-08-05T06:17:17.137Z -- freebsd -- freebsd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6922</link>
      <description>One of the data structures that holds TCP segments in all versions of FreeBSD prior to 11.2-RELEASE-p1, 11.1-RELEASE-p12, and 10.4-RELEASE-p10 uses an inefficient algorithm to reassemble the data. This causes the CPU time spent on segment processing to grow linearly with the number of segments in the reassembly queue. An attacker who has the ability to send TCP traffic to a victim system can degrade the victim system's network performance and/or consume excessive CPU by exploiting the inefficiency of TCP reassembly handling, with relatively small bandwidth cost.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6922|2024-08-05T06:17:17.137Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17160|2024-08-05T10:39:59.583Z -- freebsd -- freebsd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17160</link>
      <description>In FreeBSD before 11.2-STABLE(r341486) and 11.2-RELEASE-p6, insufficient bounds checking in one of the device models provided by bhyve can permit a guest operating system to overwrite memory in the bhyve host possibly permitting arbitrary code execution. A guest OS using a firmware image can cause the bhyve process to crash, or possibly execute arbitrary code on the host as root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17160|2024-08-05T10:39:59.583Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6917|2024-08-05T06:17:17.133Z -- freebsd -- freebsd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6917</link>
      <description>In FreeBSD before 11.1-STABLE, 11.1-RELEASE-p9, 10.4-STABLE, 10.4-RELEASE-p8 and 10.3-RELEASE-p28, insufficient validation of user-provided font parameters can result in an integer overflow, leading to the use of arbitrary kernel memory as glyph data. Unprivileged users may be able to access privileged kernel data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6917|2024-08-05T06:17:17.133Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17157|2024-08-05T10:39:59.601Z -- freebsd -- freebsd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17157</link>
      <description>In FreeBSD before 11.2-STABLE(r340854) and 11.2-RELEASE-p5, an integer overflow error when handling opcodes can cause memory corruption by sending a specially crafted NFSv4 request. Unprivileged remote users with access to the NFS server may be able to execute arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17157|2024-08-05T10:39:59.601Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17155|2024-08-05T10:39:59.567Z -- freebsd -- freebsd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17155</link>
      <description>In FreeBSD before 11.2-STABLE(r338983), 11.2-RELEASE-p4, 11.1-RELEASE-p15, 10.4-STABLE(r338984), and 10.4-RELEASE-p13, due to insufficient initialization of memory copied to userland in the getcontext and swapcontext system calls, small amounts of kernel memory may be disclosed to userland processes. Unprivileged authenticated local users may be able to access small amounts privileged kernel data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17155|2024-08-05T10:39:59.567Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17159|2024-08-05T10:39:59.559Z -- freebsd -- freebsd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17159</link>
      <description>In FreeBSD before 11.2-STABLE(r340854) and 11.2-RELEASE-p5, the NFS server lacks a bounds check in the READDIRPLUS NFS request. Unprivileged remote users with access to the NFS server can cause a resource exhaustion by forcing the server to allocate an arbitrarily large memory allocation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17159|2024-08-05T10:39:59.559Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6916|2024-08-05T06:17:17.355Z -- freebsd -- freebsd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6916</link>
      <description>In FreeBSD before 11.1-STABLE, 11.1-RELEASE-p7, 10.4-STABLE, 10.4-RELEASE-p7, and 10.3-RELEASE-p28, the kernel does not properly validate IPsec packets coming from a trusted host. Additionally, a use-after-free vulnerability exists in the IPsec AH handling code. This issue could cause a system crash or other unpredictable results.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6916|2024-08-05T06:17:17.355Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6923|2024-08-05T06:17:17.183Z -- freebsd -- freebsd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6923</link>
      <description>In FreeBSD before 11.1-STABLE, 11.2-RELEASE-p2, 11.1-RELEASE-p13, ip fragment reassembly code is vulnerable to a denial of service due to excessive system resource consumption. This issue can allow a remote attacker who is able to send an arbitrary ip fragments to cause the machine to consume excessive resources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6923|2024-08-05T06:17:17.183Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17161|2024-08-05T10:39:59.623Z -- freebsd -- freebsd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17161</link>
      <description>In FreeBSD before 11.2-STABLE(r348229), 11.2-RELEASE-p7, 12.0-STABLE(r342228), and 12.0-RELEASE-p1, insufficient validation of network-provided data in bootpd may make it possible for a malicious attacker to craft a bootp packet which could cause a stack buffer overflow. It is possible that the buffer overflow could lead to a Denial of Service or remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17161|2024-08-05T10:39:59.623Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6918|2024-08-05T06:17:17.259Z -- freebsd -- freebsd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6918</link>
      <description>In FreeBSD before 11.1-STABLE, 11.1-RELEASE-p9, 10.4-STABLE, 10.4-RELEASE-p8 and 10.3-RELEASE-p28, the length field of the ipsec option header does not count the size of the option header itself, causing an infinite loop when the length is zero. This issue can allow a remote attacker who is able to send an arbitrary packet to cause the machine to crash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6918|2024-08-05T06:17:17.259Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6920|2024-08-05T06:17:16.919Z -- freebsd -- freebsd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6920</link>
      <description>In FreeBSD before 11.1-STABLE(r332303), 11.1-RELEASE-p10, 10.4-STABLE(r332321), and 10.4-RELEASE-p9, due to insufficient initialization of memory copied to userland in the Linux subsystem and Atheros wireless driver, small amounts of kernel memory may be disclosed to userland processes. Unprivileged authenticated local users may be able to access small amounts of privileged kernel data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6920|2024-08-05T06:17:16.919Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6921|2024-08-05T06:17:16.622Z -- freebsd -- freebsd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6921</link>
      <description>In FreeBSD before 11.1-STABLE(r332066) and 11.1-RELEASE-p10, due to insufficient initialization of memory copied to userland in the network subsystem, small amounts of kernel memory may be disclosed to userland processes. Unprivileged authenticated local users may be able to access small amounts of privileged kernel data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6921|2024-08-05T06:17:16.622Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6924|2024-08-05T06:17:17.356Z -- freebsd -- freebsd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6924</link>
      <description>In FreeBSD before 11.1-STABLE, 11.2-RELEASE-p3, 11.1-RELEASE-p14, 10.4-STABLE, and 10.4-RELEASE-p12, insufficient validation in the ELF header parser could allow a malicious ELF binary to cause a kernel crash or disclose kernel memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6924|2024-08-05T06:17:17.356Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17156|2024-08-05T10:39:59.570Z -- freebsd -- freebsd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17156</link>
      <description>In FreeBSD before 11.2-STABLE(r340268) and 11.2-RELEASE-p5, due to incorrectly accounting for padding on 64-bit platforms, a buffer underwrite could occur when constructing an ICMP reply packet when using a non-standard value for the net.inet.icmp.quotelen sysctl.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17156|2024-08-05T10:39:59.570Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-6925|2024-08-05T06:17:17.338Z -- freebsd -- freebsd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-6925</link>
      <description>In FreeBSD before 11.2-STABLE(r338986), 11.2-RELEASE-p4, 11.1-RELEASE-p15, 10.4-STABLE(r338985), and 10.4-RELEASE-p13, due to improper maintenance of IPv6 protocol control block flags through various failure paths, an unprivileged authenticated local user may be able to cause a NULL pointer dereference causing the kernel to crash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-6925|2024-08-05T06:17:17.338Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17154|2024-08-05T10:39:59.675Z -- freebsd -- freebsd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17154</link>
      <description>In FreeBSD before 11.2-STABLE(r338987), 11.2-RELEASE-p4, and 11.1-RELEASE-p15, due to insufficient memory checking in the freebsd4_getfsstat system call, a NULL pointer dereference can occur. Unprivileged authenticated local users may be able to cause a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17154|2024-08-05T10:39:59.675Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23085|2024-07-17T18:56:18.267Z -- freebsd -- freebsd</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23085</link>
      <description>A user-provided integer option was passed to nmreq_copyin() without checking if it would overflow.  This insufficient bounds checking could lead to kernel memory corruption.

On systems configured to include netmap in their devfs_ruleset, a privileged process running in a jail can affect the host environment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23085|2024-07-17T18:56:18.267Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 04:52:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25941|2024-02-15T04:27:06.726Z -- freebsd -- freebsd</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25941</link>
      <description>The jail(2) system call has not limited a visiblity of allocated TTYs (the kern.ttys sysctl).  This gives rise to an information leak about processes outside the current jail.

Attacker can get information about TTYs allocated on the host or in other jails.  Effectively, the information printed by "pstat -t" may be leaked.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25941|2024-02-15T04:27:06.726Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 04:27:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25940|2024-06-04T17:35:21.630Z -- freebsd -- freebsd</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25940</link>
      <description>`bhyveload -h ` may be used to grant loader access to the  directory tree on the host.  Affected versions of bhyveload(8) do not make any attempt to restrict loader's access to , allowing the loader to read any file the host user has access to. In the bhyveload(8) model, the host supplies a userboot.so to boot with, but the loader scripts generally come from the guest image.  A maliciously crafted script could be used to exfiltrate sensitive data from the host accessible to the user running bhyhveload(8), which is often the system root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25940|2024-06-04T17:35:21.630Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 04:21:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23088|2024-07-30T17:39:58.825Z -- freebsd -- freebsd</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23088</link>
      <description>The 802.11 beacon handling routine failed to validate the length of an IEEE 802.11s Mesh ID before copying it to a heap-allocated buffer.

While a FreeBSD Wi-Fi client is in scanning mode (i.e., not associated with a SSID) a malicious beacon frame may overwrite kernel memory, leading to remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23088|2024-07-30T17:39:58.825Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 05:03:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23091|2024-08-03T03:28:43.503Z -- freebsd -- freebsd</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23091</link>
      <description>A particular case of memory sharing is mishandled in the virtual memory system.  This is very similar to SA-21:08.vm, but with a different root cause.

An unprivileged local user process can maintain a mapping of a page after it is freed, allowing that process to read private data belonging to other processes or the kernel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23091|2024-08-03T03:28:43.503Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 05:11:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23090|2024-08-03T03:28:43.512Z -- freebsd -- freebsd</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23090</link>
      <description>The aio_aqueue function, used by the lio_listio system call, fails to release a reference to a credential in an error case.

An attacker may cause the reference count to overflow, leading to a use after free (UAF).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23090|2024-08-03T03:28:43.512Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 05:09:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23088|2024-08-03T03:28:43.494Z -- freebsd -- freebsd</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23088</link>
      <description>The 802.11 beacon handling routine failed to validate the length of an IEEE 802.11s Mesh ID before copying it to a heap-allocated buffer.

While a FreeBSD Wi-Fi client is in scanning mode (i.e., not associated with a SSID) a malicious beacon frame may overwrite kernel memory, leading to remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23088|2024-08-03T03:28:43.494Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 05:03:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23086|2024-08-03T03:28:43.508Z -- freebsd -- freebsd</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23086</link>
      <description>Handlers for *_CFG_PAGE read / write ioctls in the mpr, mps, and mpt drivers allocated a buffer of a caller-specified size, but copied to it a fixed size header.  Other heap content would be overwritten if the specified size was too small.

Users with access to the mpr, mps or mpt device node may overwrite heap data, potentially resulting in privilege escalation.  Note that the device node is only accessible to root and members of the operator group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23086|2024-08-03T03:28:43.508Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 04:57:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23089|2024-08-03T03:28:43.522Z -- freebsd -- freebsd</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23089</link>
      <description>When dumping core and saving process information, proc_getargv() might return an sbuf which have a sbuf_len() of 0 or -1, which is not properly handled.

An out-of-bound read can happen when user constructs a specially crafted ps_string, which in turn can cause the kernel to crash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23089|2024-08-03T03:28:43.522Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 05:07:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23087|2024-08-03T03:28:43.494Z -- freebsd -- freebsd</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23087</link>
      <description>The e1000 network adapters permit a variety of modifications to an Ethernet packet when it is being transmitted.  These include the insertion of IP and TCP checksums, insertion of an Ethernet VLAN header, and TCP segmentation offload ("TSO").  The e1000 device model uses an on-stack buffer to generate the modified packet header when simulating these modifications on transmitted packets.

When checksum offload is requested for a transmitted packet, the e1000 device model used a guest-provided value to specify the checksum offset in the on-stack buffer.  The offset was not validated for certain packet types.

A misbehaving bhyve guest could overwrite memory in the bhyve process on the host, possibly leading to code execution in the host context.

The bhyve process runs in a Capsicum sandbox, which (depending on the FreeBSD version and bhyve configuration) limits the impact of exploiting this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23087|2024-08-03T03:28:43.494Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23092|2024-08-03T03:28:43.506Z -- freebsd -- freebsd</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23092</link>
      <description>The implementation of lib9p's handling of RWALK messages was missing a bounds check needed when unpacking the message contents.  The missing check means that the receipt of a specially crafted message will cause lib9p to overwrite unrelated memory.

The bug can be triggered by a malicious bhyve guest kernel to overwrite memory in the bhyve(8) process.  This could potentially lead to user-mode code execution on the host, subject to bhyve's Capsicum sandbox.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23092|2024-08-03T03:28:43.506Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 05:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23093|2024-08-03T03:28:43.499Z -- freebsd -- freebsd</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23093</link>
      <description>ping reads raw IP packets from the network to process responses in the pr_pack() function.  As part of processing a response ping has to reconstruct the IP header, the ICMP header and if present a "quoted packet," which represents the packet that generated an ICMP error.  The quoted packet again has an IP header and an ICMP header.

The pr_pack() copies received IP and ICMP headers into stack buffers for further processing.  In so doing, it fails to take into account the possible presence of IP option headers following the IP header in either the response or the quoted packet.  When IP options are present, pr_pack() overflows the destination buffer by up to 40 bytes.

The memory safety bugs described above can be triggered by a remote host, causing the ping program to crash.

The ping process runs in a capability mode sandbox on all affected versions of FreeBSD and is thus very constrained in how it can interact with the rest of the system at the point where the bug can occur.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23093|2024-08-03T03:28:43.499Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 05:18:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23085|2024-08-03T03:28:43.504Z -- freebsd -- freebsd</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23085</link>
      <description>A user-provided integer option was passed to nmreq_copyin() without checking if it would overflow.  This insufficient bounds checking could lead to kernel memory corruption.

On systems configured to include netmap in their devfs_ruleset, a privileged process running in a jail can affect the host environment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23085|2024-08-03T03:28:43.504Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 04:52:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23084|2024-08-03T03:28:43.503Z -- freebsd -- freebsd</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23084</link>
      <description>The total size of the user-provided nmreq to nmreq_copyin() was first computed and then trusted during the copyin.  This time-of-check to time-of-use bug could lead to kernel memory corruption.

On systems configured to include netmap in their devfs_ruleset, a privileged process running in a jail can affect the host environment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23084|2024-08-03T03:28:43.503Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 04:52:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
