<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for 7-card -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/7-card/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for 7-card -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 17:22:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7183|2024-08-02T08:50:08.197Z -- 7-card -- fakabao
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7183</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in 7-card Fakabao up to 1.0_build20230805 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file shop/alipay_notify.php. The manipulation of the argument out_trade_no leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249385 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In 7-card Fakabao bis 1.0_build20230805 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei shop/alipay_notify.php. Durch Manipulation des Arguments out_trade_no mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7183|2024-08-02T08:50:08.197Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 10:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7186|2024-08-02T08:57:34.087Z -- 7-card -- fakabao
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7186</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in 7-card Fakabao up to 1.0_build20230805. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file member/notify.php. The manipulation of the argument out_trade_no leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249388. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In 7-card Fakabao bis 1.0_build20230805 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei member/notify.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments out_trade_no mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7186|2024-08-02T08:57:34.087Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 13:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7184|2024-08-02T08:57:34.080Z -- 7-card -- fakabao
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7184</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in 7-card Fakabao up to 1.0_build20230805 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file shop/notify.php. The manipulation of the argument out_trade_no leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249386 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in 7-card Fakabao bis 1.0_build20230805 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei shop/notify.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments out_trade_no mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7184|2024-08-02T08:57:34.080Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7185|2024-08-02T08:57:34.115Z -- 7-card -- fakabao
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7185</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in 7-card Fakabao up to 1.0_build20230805. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file shop/wxpay_notify.php. The manipulation of the argument out_trade_no leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249387. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in 7-card Fakabao bis 1.0_build20230805 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei shop/wxpay_notify.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments out_trade_no mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7185|2024-08-02T08:57:34.115Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 11:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
