<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for pimcore -- customer-data-framework</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/pimcore/customer-data-framework.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for pimcore -- customer-data-framework</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-49076|2023-11-30T05:42:12.668Z -- pimcore -- customer-data-framework
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-49076</link>
      <description>Customer-data-framework allows management of customer data within Pimcore. There are no tokens or headers to prevent CSRF attacks from occurring, therefore an attacker could abuse this vulnerability to create new customers. This issue has been patched in version 4.0.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-49076|2023-11-30T05:42:12.668Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 05:42:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32075|2023-05-11T16:39:37.634Z -- pimcore -- customer-data-framework
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32075</link>
      <description>The Customer Management Framework (CMF) for Pimcore adds functionality for customer data management. In `pimcore/customer-management-framework-bundle` prior to version 3.3.9, business logic errors are possible in the `Conditions` tab since the counter can be a negative number. This vulnerability is capable of the unlogic in the counter value in the Conditions tab. Users should update to version 3.3.9 to receive a patch or, as a workaround, or apply the patch manually.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32075|2023-05-11T16:39:37.634Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 16:39:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21667|2024-01-11T01:05:35.979Z -- pimcore -- customer-data-framework
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21667</link>
      <description>pimcore/customer-data-framework is the Customer Management Framework for management of customer data within Pimcore. An authenticated and unauthorized user can access the GDPR data extraction feature and query over the information returned, leading to customer data exposure. Permissions are not enforced when reaching the `/admin/customermanagementframework/gdpr-data/search-data-objects` endpoint allowing an authenticated user without the permissions to access the endpoint and query the data available there. An unauthorized user can access PII data from customers. This vulnerability has been patched in version 4.0.6.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21667|2024-01-11T01:05:35.979Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 01:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21666|2024-01-11T00:45:44.520Z -- pimcore -- customer-data-framework
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21666</link>
      <description>The Customer Management Framework (CMF) for Pimcore adds functionality for customer data management, segmentation, personalization and marketing automation. An authenticated and unauthorized user can access the list of potential duplicate users and see their data. Permissions are enforced when reaching the `/admin/customermanagementframework/duplicates/list` endpoint allowing an authenticated user without the permissions to access the endpoint and query the data available there. Unauthorized user(s) can access PII data from customers. This vulnerability has been patched in version 4.0.6.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21666|2024-01-11T00:45:44.520Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 00:45:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
