<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for sigstore -- rekor</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sigstore/rekor.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for sigstore -- rekor</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 16:24:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-30551|2024-08-02T14:28:51.668Z -- sigstore -- rekor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30551</link>
      <description>Rekor is an open source software supply chain transparency log. Rekor prior to version 1.1.1 may crash due to out of memory (OOM) conditions caused by reading archive metadata files into memory without checking their sizes first. Verification of a JAR file submitted to Rekor can cause an out of memory crash if files within the META-INF directory of the JAR are sufficiently large. Parsing of an APK file submitted to Rekor can cause an out of memory crash if the .SIGN or .PKGINFO files within the APK are sufficiently large. The OOM crash has been patched in Rekor version 1.1.1. There are no known workarounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-30551|2024-08-02T14:28:51.668Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 15:52:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33199|2024-08-02T15:39:35.807Z -- sigstore -- rekor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33199</link>
      <description>Rekor's goals are to provide an immutable tamper resistant ledger of metadata generated within a software projects supply chain. A malformed proposed entry of the `intoto/v0.0.2` type can cause a panic on a thread within the Rekor process. The thread is recovered so the client receives a 500 error message and service still continues, so the availability impact of this is minimal. This has been fixed in v1.2.0 of Rekor. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33199|2024-08-02T15:39:35.807Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 22:52:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
