<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for mastodon -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/mastodon/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for mastodon -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28853|2023-04-04T21:14:53.350Z -- mastodon -- mastodon
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-28853</link>
      <description>Mastodon is a free, open-source social network server based on ActivityPub Mastodon allows configuration of LDAP for authentication. Starting in version 2.5.0 and prior to versions 3.5.8, 4.0.4, and 4.1.2, the LDAP query made during login is insecure and the attacker can perform LDAP injection attack to leak arbitrary attributes from LDAP database. This issue is fixed in versions 3.5.8, 4.0.4, and 4.1.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28853|2023-04-04T21:14:53.350Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 21:14:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-36461|2023-07-06T18:57:59.160Z -- mastodon -- mastodon
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-36461</link>
      <description>Mastodon is a free, open-source social network server based on ActivityPub. When performing outgoing HTTP queries, Mastodon sets a timeout on individual read operations. Prior to versions 3.5.9, 4.0.5, and 4.1.3, a malicious server can indefinitely extend the duration of the response through slowloris-type attacks. This vulnerability can be used to keep all Mastodon workers busy for an extended duration of time, leading to the server becoming unresponsive. Versions 3.5.9, 4.0.5, and 4.1.3 contain a patch for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-36461|2023-07-06T18:57:59.160Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 18:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-36460|2023-07-06T18:57:01.934Z -- mastodon -- mastodon
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-36460</link>
      <description>Mastodon is a free, open-source social network server based on ActivityPub. Starting in version 3.5.0 and prior to versions 3.5.9, 4.0.5, and 4.1.3, attackers using carefully crafted media files can cause Mastodon's media processing code to create arbitrary files at any location. This allows attackers to create and overwrite any file Mastodon has access to, allowing Denial of Service and arbitrary Remote Code Execution. Versions 3.5.9, 4.0.5, and 4.1.3 contain a patch for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-36460|2023-07-06T18:57:01.934Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 18:39:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-36459|2023-07-06T18:29:07.669Z -- mastodon -- mastodon
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-36459</link>
      <description>Mastodon is a free, open-source social network server based on ActivityPub. Starting in version 1.3 and prior to versions 3.5.9, 4.0.5, and 4.1.3, an attacker using carefully crafted oEmbed data can bypass the HTML sanitization performed by Mastodon and include arbitrary HTML in oEmbed preview cards. This introduces a vector for cross-site scripting (XSS) payloads that can be rendered in the user's browser when a preview card for a malicious link is clicked through. Versions 3.5.9, 4.0.5, and 4.1.3 contain a patch for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-36459|2023-07-06T18:29:07.669Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 18:29:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-36462|2023-07-06T19:16:37.617Z -- mastodon -- mastodon
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-36462</link>
      <description>Mastodon is a free, open-source social network server based on ActivityPub. Starting in version 2.6.0 and prior to versions 3.5.9, 4.0.5, and 4.1.3, an attacker can craft a verified profile link using specific formatting to conceal arbitrary parts of the link, enabling it to appear to link to a different URL altogether. The link is visually misleading, but clicking on it will reveal the actual link. This can still be used for phishing, though, similar to IDN homograph attacks. Versions 3.5.9, 4.0.5, and 4.1.3 contain a patch for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-36462|2023-07-06T19:16:37.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 19:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42452|2023-09-19T15:58:44.559Z -- mastodon -- mastodon
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42452</link>
      <description>Mastodon is a free, open-source social network server based on ActivityPub. In versions on the 4.x branch prior to versions 4.0.10, 4.2.8, and 4.2.0-rc2, under certain conditions, attackers can abuse the translation feature to bypass the server-side HTML sanitization, allowing unescaped HTML to execute in the browser. The impact is limited thanks to Mastodon's strict Content Security Policy, blocking inline scripts, etc. However a CSP bypass or loophole could be exploited to execute malicious XSS. Furthermore, it requires user interaction, as this can only occur upon clicking the “Translate” button on a malicious post. Versions 4.0.10, 4.2.8, and 4.2.0-rc2 contain a patch for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42452|2023-09-19T15:58:44.559Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 15:58:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42450|2023-09-25T14:32:40.787Z -- mastodon -- mastodon
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42450</link>
      <description>Mastodon is a free, open-source social network server based on ActivityPub. Starting in version 4.2.0-beta1 and prior to version 4.2.0-rc2, by crafting specific input, attackers can inject arbitrary data into HTTP requests issued by Mastodon. This can be used to perform confused deputy attacks if the server configuration includes `ALLOWED_PRIVATE_ADDRESSES` to allow access to local exploitable services. Version 4.2.0-rc2 has a patch for the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42450|2023-09-25T14:32:40.787Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 15:53:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42451|2023-09-19T15:56:46.962Z -- mastodon -- mastodon
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42451</link>
      <description>Mastodon is a free, open-source social network server based on ActivityPub. Prior to versions 3.5.14, 4.0.10, 4.1.8, and 4.2.0-rc2, under certain circumstances, attackers can exploit a flaw in domain name normalization to spoof domains they do not own. Versions 3.5.14, 4.0.10, 4.1.8, and 4.2.0-rc2 contain a patch for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42451|2023-09-19T15:56:46.962Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 15:56:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23832|2024-02-01T16:18:03.528Z -- mastodon -- mastodon
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23832</link>
      <description>Mastodon is a free, open-source social network server based on ActivityPub Mastodon allows configuration of LDAP for authentication. Due to insufficient origin validation in all Mastodon, attackers can impersonate and take over any remote account. Every Mastodon version prior to 3.5.17 is vulnerable, as well as 4.0.x versions prior to 4.0.13, 4.1.x version prior to 4.1.13, and 4.2.x versions prior to 4.2.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23832|2024-02-01T16:18:03.528Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 16:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25618|2024-02-14T20:45:50.621Z -- mastodon -- mastodon
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25618</link>
      <description>Mastodon is a free, open-source social network server based on ActivityPub. Mastodon allows new identities from configured authentication providers (CAS, SAML, OIDC) to attach to existing local users with the same e-mail address. This results in a possible account takeover if the authentication provider allows changing the e-mail address or multiple authentication providers are configured. When a user logs in through an external authentication provider for the first time, Mastodon checks the e-mail address passed by the provider to find an existing account. However, using the e-mail address alone means that if the authentication provider allows changing the e-mail address of an account, the Mastodon account can immediately be hijacked. All users logging in through external authentication providers are affected. The severity is medium, as it also requires the external authentication provider to misbehave. However, some well-known OIDC providers (like Microsoft Azure) make it very easy to accidentally allow unverified e-mail changes. Moreover, OpenID Connect also allows dynamic client registration. This issue has been addressed in versions 4.2.6, 4.1.14, 4.0.14, and 3.5.18. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25618|2024-02-14T20:45:50.621Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 20:45:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25623|2024-02-19T15:28:15.296Z -- mastodon -- mastodon
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25623</link>
      <description>Mastodon is a free, open-source social network server based on ActivityPub. Prior to versions 4.2.7, 4.1.15, 4.0.15, and 3.5.19, when fetching remote statuses, Mastodon doesn't check that the response from the remote server has a `Content-Type` header value of the Activity Streams media type, which allows a threat actor to upload a crafted Activity Streams document to a remote server and make a Mastodon server fetch it, if the remote server accepts arbitrary user uploads. The vulnerability allows a threat actor to impersonate an account on a remote server that satisfies all of the following properties: allows the attacker to register an account; accepts arbitrary user-uploaded documents and places them on the same domain as the ActivityPub actors; and serves user-uploaded document in response to requests with an `Accept` header value of the Activity Streams media type. Versions 4.2.7, 4.1.15, 4.0.15, and 3.5.19 contain a fix for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25623|2024-02-19T15:28:15.296Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 15:28:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25619|2024-06-04T17:34:59.800Z -- mastodon -- mastodon
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25619</link>
      <description>Mastodon is a free, open-source social network server based on ActivityPub. When an OAuth Application is destroyed, the streaming server wasn't being informed that the Access Tokens had also been destroyed, this could have posed security risks to users by allowing an application to continue listening to streaming after the application had been destroyed. Essentially this comes down to the fact that when Doorkeeper sets up the relationship between Applications and Access Tokens, it uses a `dependent: delete_all` configuration, which means the `after_commit` callback setup on `AccessTokenExtension` didn't actually fire, since `delete_all` doesn't trigger ActiveRecord callbacks. To mitigate, we need to add a `before_destroy` callback to `ApplicationExtension` which announces to streaming that all the Application's Access Tokens are being "killed". Impact should be negligible given the affected application had to be owned by the user. None the less this issue has been addressed in versions 4.2.6, 4.1.14, 4.0.14, and 3.5.18. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workaround for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25619|2024-06-04T17:34:59.800Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 20:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
