<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Fedora -- Extra Packages for Enterprise Linux</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/fedora/extra%20packages%20for%20enterprise%20linux.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Fedora -- Extra Packages for Enterprise Linux</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38253|2024-03-18T03:39:07.903Z -- fedora -- extra%20packages%20for%20enterprise%20linux
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38253</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read flaw was found in w3m, in the growbuf_to_Str function in indep.c. This issue may allow an attacker to cause a denial of service through a crafted HTML file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38253|2024-03-18T03:39:07.903Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 17:07:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29499|2023-09-14T19:06:17.810Z -- fedora -- extra%20packages%20for%20enterprise%20linux
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-29499</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in GLib. GVariant deserialization fails to validate that the input conforms to the expected format, leading to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29499|2023-09-14T19:06:17.810Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 19:06:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4256|2023-12-21T16:03:21.837Z -- fedora -- extra%20packages%20for%20enterprise%20linux
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4256</link>
      <description>Within tcpreplay's tcprewrite, a double free vulnerability has been identified in the tcpedit_dlt_cleanup() function within plugins/dlt_plugins.c. This vulnerability can be exploited by supplying a specifically crafted file to the tcprewrite binary. This flaw enables a local attacker to initiate a Denial of Service (DoS) attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4256|2023-12-21T16:03:21.837Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 16:03:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32627|2023-07-10T17:15:42.063Z -- fedora -- extra%20packages%20for%20enterprise%20linux
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32627</link>
      <description>A floating point exception vulnerability was found in sox, in the read_samples function at sox/src/voc.c:334:18. This flaw can lead to a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32627|2023-07-10T17:15:42.063Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 17:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32611|2023-09-14T19:07:19.011Z -- fedora -- extra%20packages%20for%20enterprise%20linux
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-32611</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in GLib. GVariant deserialization is vulnerable to a slowdown issue where a crafted GVariant can cause excessive processing, leading to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32611|2023-09-14T19:07:19.011Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 19:07:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3301|2023-09-13T16:09:36.861Z -- fedora -- extra%20packages%20for%20enterprise%20linux
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3301</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in QEMU. The async nature of hot-unplug enables a race scenario where the net device backend is cleared before the virtio-net pci frontend has been unplugged. A malicious guest could use this time window to trigger an assertion and cause a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3301|2023-09-13T16:09:36.861Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 16:09:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3430|2023-12-18T13:40:05.145Z -- fedora -- extra%20packages%20for%20enterprise%20linux
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3430</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in OpenImageIO, where a heap buffer overflow exists in the src/gif.imageio/gifinput.cpp file. This flaw allows a remote attacker to pass a specially crafted file to the application, which triggers a heap-based buffer overflow and could cause a crash, leading to a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3430|2023-12-18T13:40:05.145Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 13:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6395|2024-01-16T15:02:39.645Z -- fedora -- extra%20packages%20for%20enterprise%20linux
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6395</link>
      <description>The Mock software contains a vulnerability wherein an attacker could potentially exploit privilege escalation, enabling the execution of arbitrary code with root user privileges. This weakness stems from the absence of proper sandboxing during the expansion and execution of Jinja2 templates, which may be included in certain configuration parameters. While the Mock documentation advises treating users added to the mock group as privileged, certain build systems invoking mock on behalf of users might inadvertently permit less privileged users to define configuration tags. These tags could then be passed as parameters to mock during execution, potentially leading to the utilization of Jinja2 templates for remote privilege escalation and the execution of arbitrary code as the root user on the build server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6395|2024-01-16T15:02:39.645Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 14:33:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
