<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Insteon -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/insteon/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Insteon -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 09:23:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3832|2024-09-17T03:28:53.011Z -- insteon -- insteon
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3832</link>
      <description>An exploitable firmware update vulnerability exists in Insteon Hub running firmware version 1013. The HTTP server allows for uploading arbitrary MPFS binaries that could be modified to enable access to hidden resources which allow for uploading unsigned firmware images to the device. To trigger this vulnerability, an attacker can upload an MPFS binary via the '/mpfsupload' HTTP form and later on upload the firmware via a POST request to 'firmware.htm'.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3832|2024-09-17T03:28:53.011Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14452|2024-09-17T04:28:50.538Z -- insteon -- insteon%20hub%202245-222
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14452</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the PubNub message handler for the "control" channel of Insteon Hub running firmware version 1012. Specially crafted replies received from the PubNub service can cause buffer overflows on a global section overwriting arbitrary data. A strcpy overflows the buffer insteon_pubnub.channel_cc_r, which has a size of 16 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "c_r" parameter in order to exploit this vulnerability. An attacker should impersonate PubNub and answer an HTTPS GET request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14452|2024-09-17T04:28:50.538Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3833|2024-09-17T02:26:41.031Z -- insteon -- insteon
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3833</link>
      <description>An exploitable firmware downgrade vulnerability exists in Insteon Hub running firmware version 1013. The firmware upgrade functionality, triggered via PubNub, retrieves signed firmware binaries using plain HTTP requests. The device doesn't check the firmware version that is going to be installed and thus allows for flashing older firmware images. To trigger this vulnerability, an attacker needs to impersonate the remote server 'cache.insteon.com' and serve any signed firmware image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3833|2024-09-17T02:26:41.031Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16348|2024-09-17T01:16:39.733Z -- insteon -- insteon
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16348</link>
      <description>An exploitable denial of service vulnerability exists in Insteon Hub running firmware version 1012. Leftover demo functionality allows for arbitrarily rebooting the device without authentication. An attacker can send a UDP packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16348|2024-09-17T01:16:39.733Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14455|2024-09-17T00:11:16.184Z -- insteon -- insteon%20hub%202245-222
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14455</link>
      <description>On Insteon Hub 2245-222 devices with firmware version 1012, specially crafted replies received from the PubNub service can cause buffer overflows on a global section overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker should impersonate PubNub and answer an HTTPS GET request to trigger this vulnerability. A strcpy overflows the buffer insteon_pubnub.channel_ak, which has a size of 16 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "ak" parameter in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14455|2024-09-17T00:11:16.184Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
