<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Insteon -- Insteon</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/insteon/insteon.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Insteon -- Insteon</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 20:22:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3832|2024-08-05T04:57:24.353Z -- insteon -- insteon
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3832</link>
      <description>An exploitable firmware update vulnerability exists in Insteon Hub running firmware version 1013. The HTTP server allows for uploading arbitrary MPFS binaries that could be modified to enable access to hidden resources which allow for uploading unsigned firmware images to the device. To trigger this vulnerability, an attacker can upload an MPFS binary via the '/mpfsupload' HTTP form and later on upload the firmware via a POST request to 'firmware.htm'.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3832|2024-08-05T04:57:24.353Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3834|2024-08-05T04:57:23.574Z -- insteon -- insteon
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3834</link>
      <description>An exploitable permanent denial of service vulnerability exists in Insteon Hub running firmware version 1013. The firmware upgrade functionality, triggered via PubNub, retrieves signed firmware binaries using plain HTTP requests. The device doesn't check the kind of firmware image that is going to be installed and thus allows for flashing any signed firmware into any MCU. Since the device contains different and incompatible MCUs, flashing one firmware to the wrong MCU will result in a permanent brick condition. To trigger this vulnerability, an attacker needs to impersonate the remote server "cache.insteon.com" and serve a signed firmware image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3834|2024-08-05T04:57:23.574Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3833|2024-08-05T04:57:23.969Z -- insteon -- insteon
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3833</link>
      <description>An exploitable firmware downgrade vulnerability exists in Insteon Hub running firmware version 1013. The firmware upgrade functionality, triggered via PubNub, retrieves signed firmware binaries using plain HTTP requests. The device doesn't check the firmware version that is going to be installed and thus allows for flashing older firmware images. To trigger this vulnerability, an attacker needs to impersonate the remote server 'cache.insteon.com' and serve any signed firmware image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3833|2024-08-05T04:57:23.969Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14444|2024-08-05T19:27:40.454Z -- insteon -- insteon
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14444</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in Insteon Hub running firmware version 1012. The HTTP server implementation incorrectly handles the URL parameter during a firmware update request, leading to a buffer overflow on a global section. An attacker can send an HTTP GET request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14444|2024-08-05T19:27:40.454Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14446|2024-08-05T19:27:40.835Z -- insteon -- insteon
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14446</link>
      <description>An exploitable stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in Insteon Hub running firmware version 1012. The HTTP server implementation unsafely extracts parameters from the query string, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. An attacker can send an HTTP GET request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14446|2024-08-05T19:27:40.835Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14445|2024-08-05T19:27:40.486Z -- insteon -- insteon
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14445</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in Insteon Hub running firmware version 1012. The HTTP server implementation incorrectly handles the host parameter during a firmware update request, leading to a buffer overflow on a global section. An attacker can send an HTTP GET request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14445|2024-08-05T19:27:40.486Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
