<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Insteon -- Insteon Hub 2245-222</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/insteon/insteon%20hub%202245-222.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Insteon -- Insteon Hub 2245-222</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 22:23:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14452|2024-09-17T04:28:50.538Z -- insteon -- insteon%20hub%202245-222
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14452</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the PubNub message handler for the "control" channel of Insteon Hub running firmware version 1012. Specially crafted replies received from the PubNub service can cause buffer overflows on a global section overwriting arbitrary data. A strcpy overflows the buffer insteon_pubnub.channel_cc_r, which has a size of 16 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "c_r" parameter in order to exploit this vulnerability. An attacker should impersonate PubNub and answer an HTTPS GET request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14452|2024-09-17T04:28:50.538Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14455|2024-09-17T00:11:16.184Z -- insteon -- insteon%20hub%202245-222
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14455</link>
      <description>On Insteon Hub 2245-222 devices with firmware version 1012, specially crafted replies received from the PubNub service can cause buffer overflows on a global section overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker should impersonate PubNub and answer an HTTPS GET request to trigger this vulnerability. A strcpy overflows the buffer insteon_pubnub.channel_ak, which has a size of 16 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "ak" parameter in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14455|2024-09-17T00:11:16.184Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
