<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for webfactory -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/webfactory/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for webfactory -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 23:21:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-1501|2024-02-21T03:36:00.166Z -- webfactory -- Database Reset</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1501</link><description>The Database Reset plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.22. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the install_wpr() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to install the WP Reset Plugin via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1501|2024-02-21T03:36:00.166Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 03:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1075|2024-02-05T21:21:50.435Z -- webfactory -- Minimal Coming Soon – Coming Soon Page</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1075</link><description>The Minimal Coming Soon – Coming Soon Page plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to maintenance mode bypass and information disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 2.37. This is due to the plugin improperly validating the request path. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass maintenance mode and view pages that should be hidden.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1075|2024-02-05T21:21:50.435Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:21:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1340|2024-02-20T18:56:25.837Z -- webfactory -- Login Lockdown – Protect Login Form</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1340</link><description>The Login Lockdown – Protect Login Form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the generate_export_file function in all versions up to, and including, 2.08. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber access and higher, to export this plugin's settings that include whitelisted IP addresses as well as a global unlock key. With the global unlock key an attacker can add their IP address to the whitelist.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1340|2024-02-20T18:56:25.837Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:56:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6799|2024-05-10T15:56:42.718Z -- webfactory -- WP Reset – Most Advanced WordPress Reset Tool</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6799</link><description>The WP Reset – Most Advanced WordPress Reset Tool plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.0 via the use of insufficiently random snapshot names. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including site backups by brute-forcing the snapshot filenames. Please note that the vendor does not plan to do any further hardening on this functionality.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6799|2024-05-10T15:56:42.718Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:58:53 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>