<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for frenify -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/frenify/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for frenify -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 21:54:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-1653|2024-02-27T11:05:06.723Z -- frenify -- Categorify – WordPress Media Library Category &amp; File Manager
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1653</link><description>The Categorify plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the categorifyAjaxUpdateFolderPosition in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.7.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to update the folder position of categories as well as update the metadata of other taxonomies.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1653|2024-02-27T11:05:06.723Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 11:05:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1649|2024-02-27T11:05:10.127Z -- frenify -- Categorify – WordPress Media Library Category &amp; File Manager
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1649</link><description>The Categorify plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the categorifyAjaxDeleteCategory function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.7.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to delete categories.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1649|2024-02-27T11:05:10.127Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 11:05:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1652|2024-02-27T11:05:08.954Z -- frenify -- Categorify – WordPress Media Library Category &amp; File Manager
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1652</link><description>The Categorify plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the categorifyAjaxClearCategory function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.7.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to clear categories.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1652|2024-02-27T11:05:08.954Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 11:05:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1907|2024-02-27T11:05:06.027Z -- frenify -- Categorify – WordPress Media Library Category &amp; File Manager
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1907</link><description>The Categorify plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.7.4. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the categorifyAjaxDeleteCategory function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete categories via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1907|2024-02-27T11:05:06.027Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 11:05:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1906|2024-02-27T11:05:08.424Z -- frenify -- Categorify – WordPress Media Library Category &amp; File Manager
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1906</link><description>The Categorify plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.7.4. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the categorifyAjaxAddCategory function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add categories via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1906|2024-02-27T11:05:08.424Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 11:05:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1910|2024-02-27T11:05:09.553Z -- frenify -- Categorify – WordPress Media Library Category &amp; File Manager
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1910</link><description>The Categorify plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.7.4. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the categorifyAjaxClearCategory function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to clear categories via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1910|2024-02-27T11:05:09.553Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 11:05:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1909|2024-02-27T11:05:07.234Z -- frenify -- Categorify – WordPress Media Library Category &amp; File Manager
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1909</link><description>The Categorify plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.7.4. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the categorifyAjaxRenameCategory function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to rename categories via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1909|2024-02-27T11:05:07.234Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 11:05:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1912|2024-02-27T11:05:07.777Z -- frenify -- Categorify – WordPress Media Library Category &amp; File Manager
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1912</link><description>The Categorify plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.7.4. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the categorifyAjaxUpdateFolderPosition function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the folder position of categories as well as update the metadata of other taxonomies via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1912|2024-02-27T11:05:07.777Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 11:05:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1650|2024-02-27T11:05:10.630Z -- frenify -- Categorify – WordPress Media Library Category &amp; File Manager
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1650</link><description>The Categorify plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the categorifyAjaxRenameCategory function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.7.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to rename categories.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1650|2024-02-27T11:05:10.630Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 11:05:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0385|2024-03-13T15:26:35.905Z -- frenify -- Categorify – WordPress Media Library Category &amp; File Manager
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0385</link><description>The Categorify plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the categorifyAjaxAddCategory function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.7.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to add categories.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0385|2024-03-13T15:26:35.905Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:26:35 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>