<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Zyxel -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/zyxel/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Zyxel -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 17:21:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35031|2024-08-04T00:33:49.873Z -- zyxel -- gs1900%20series%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35031</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the TFTP client of Zyxel GS1900 series firmware, XGS1210 series firmware, and XGS1250 series firmware, which could allow an authenticated LAN user to execute arbitrary OS commands via the GUI of the vulnerable device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35031|2024-08-04T00:33:49.873Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 10:36:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35035|2024-08-04T00:33:49.910Z -- zyxel -- nbg6604%20series%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35035</link>
      <description>A cleartext storage of sensitive information vulnerability in the Zyxel NBG6604 firmware could allow a remote, authenticated attacker to obtain sensitive information from the configuration file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35035|2024-08-04T00:33:49.910Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 12:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35032|2024-08-04T00:33:49.889Z -- zyxel -- gs1900%20series%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35032</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the 'libsal.so' of the Zyxel GS1900 series firmware version 2.60 could allow an authenticated local user to execute arbitrary OS commands via a crafted function call.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35032|2024-08-04T00:33:49.889Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 10:42:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35034|2024-08-04T00:33:49.919Z -- zyxel -- nbg6604%20series%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35034</link>
      <description>An insufficient session expiration vulnerability in the CGI program of the Zyxel NBG6604 firmware could allow a remote attacker to access the device if the correct token can be intercepted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35034|2024-08-04T00:33:49.919Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 12:36:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35036|2024-08-04T00:33:49.906Z -- zyxel -- vmg3625-t50b%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35036</link>
      <description>A cleartext storage of information vulnerability in the Zyxel VMG3625-T50B firmware version V5.50(ABTL.0)b2k could allow an authenticated attacker to obtain sensitive information from the configuration file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35036|2024-08-04T00:33:49.906Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 06:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35033|2024-08-04T00:33:49.871Z -- zyxel -- nbg6818%20series%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35033</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in specific versions of Zyxel NBG6818, NBG7815, WSQ20, WSQ50, WSQ60, and WSR30 firmware with pre-configured password management could allow an attacker to obtain root access of the device, if the local attacker dismantles the device and uses a USB-to-UART cable to connect the device, or if the remote assistance feature had been enabled by an authenticated user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35033|2024-08-04T00:33:49.871Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 21:20:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35030|2024-08-04T00:33:49.831Z -- zyxel -- gs1900-8%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35030</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in the CGI program in Zyxel GS1900-8 firmware version V2.60, that did not properly sterilize packet contents and could allow an authenticated, local user to perform a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack via a crafted LLDP packet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35030|2024-08-04T00:33:49.831Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9054|2024-08-04T10:19:19.559Z -- zyxel -- nas326
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9054</link>
      <description>Multiple ZyXEL network-attached storage (NAS) devices running firmware version 5.21 contain a pre-authentication command injection vulnerability, which may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code on a vulnerable device. ZyXEL NAS devices achieve authentication by using the weblogin.cgi CGI executable. This program fails to properly sanitize the username parameter that is passed to it. If the username parameter contains certain characters, it can allow command injection with the privileges of the web server that runs on the ZyXEL device. Although the web server does not run as the root user, ZyXEL devices include a setuid utility that can be leveraged to run any command with root privileges. As such, it should be assumed that exploitation of this vulnerability can lead to remote code execution with root privileges. By sending a specially-crafted HTTP POST or GET request to a vulnerable ZyXEL device, a remote, unauthenticated attacker may be able to execute arbitrary code on the device. This may happen by directly connecting to a device if it is directly exposed to an attacker. However, there are ways to trigger such crafted requests even if an attacker does not have direct connectivity to a vulnerable devices. For example, simply visiting a website can result in the compromise of any ZyXEL device that is reachable from the client system. Affected products include: NAS326 before firmware V5.21(AAZF.7)C0 NAS520 before firmware V5.21(AASZ.3)C0 NAS540 before firmware V5.21(AATB.4)C0 NAS542 before firmware V5.21(ABAG.4)C0 ZyXEL has made firmware updates available for NAS326, NAS520, NAS540, and NAS542 devices. Affected models that are end-of-support: NSA210, NSA220, NSA220+, NSA221, NSA310, NSA310S, NSA320, NSA320S, NSA325 and NSA325v2</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9054|2024-08-04T10:19:19.559Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35028|2024-08-04T00:33:49.830Z -- zyxel -- zywall%20vpn2s%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35028</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability in the CGI program of the Zyxel VPN2S firmware version 1.12 could allow an authenticated, local user to execute arbitrary OS commands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35028|2024-08-04T00:33:49.830Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 10:35:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35029|2024-08-04T00:33:49.831Z -- zyxel -- usg%2Fzywall%20series%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35029</link>
      <description>An authentication bypasss vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Zyxel USG/Zywall series firmware versions 4.35 through 4.64 and USG Flex, ATP, and VPN series firmware versions 4.35 through 5.01, which could allow a remote attacker to execute arbitrary commands on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35029|2024-08-04T00:33:49.831Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 10:29:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35027|2024-08-04T00:26:55.923Z -- zyxel -- zywall%20vpn2s%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35027</link>
      <description>A directory traversal vulnerability in the web server of the Zyxel VPN2S firmware version 1.12 could allow a remote attacker to gain access to sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35027|2024-08-04T00:26:55.923Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 10:32:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6764|2024-08-02T08:42:07.430Z -- zyxel -- atp%20series%20firmware</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6764</link>
      <description>A format string vulnerability in a function of the IPSec VPN feature in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from 4.32 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG FLEX series firmware versions from 4.50 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions from 4.16 through 5.37 Patch 1, and USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions from 4.16 through 5.37 Patch 1 could allow an attacker to achieve unauthorized remote code execution by sending a sequence of specially crafted payloads containing an invalid pointer; however, such an attack would require detailed knowledge of an affected device’s memory layout and configuration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6764|2024-08-02T08:42:07.430Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 02:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6397|2024-08-02T08:28:21.794Z -- zyxel -- atp%20series%20firmware</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6397</link>
      <description>A null pointer dereference vulnerability in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from 4.32 through 5.37 Patch 1 and USG FLEX series firmware versions from 4.50 through 5.37 Patch 1 could allow a LAN-based attacker to cause denial-of-service (DoS) conditions by downloading a crafted RAR compressed file onto a LAN-side host if the firewall has the “Anti-Malware” feature enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6397|2024-08-02T08:28:21.794Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 01:19:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6399|2024-08-02T08:28:21.797Z -- zyxel -- atp%20series%20firmware</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6399</link>
      <description>A format string vulnerability in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from 4.32 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG FLEX series firmware versions from 4.50 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions from 4.16 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions from 4.16 through 5.37 Patch 1, and USG FLEX H series firmware versions from 1.10 through 1.10 Patch 1 could allow an authenticated IPSec VPN user to cause DoS conditions against the “deviceid” daemon by sending a crafted hostname to an affected device if it has the “Device Insight” feature enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6399|2024-08-02T08:28:21.797Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 01:42:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6398|2024-08-02T08:28:21.823Z -- zyxel -- atp%20series%20firmware</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6398</link>
      <description>A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the file upload binary in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from 4.32 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG FLEX series firmware versions from 4.50 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions from 4.16 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions from 4.16 through 5.37 Patch 1, 

USG FLEX H series firmware versions from 1.10 through 1.10 Patch 1,

NWA50AX firmware versions through 6.29(ABYW.3), WAC500 firmware versions through 6.65(ABVS.1), WAX300H firmware versions through 6.60(ACHF.1), and WBE660S firmware versions through 6.65(ACGG.1) could allow an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to execute some operating system (OS) commands on an affected device via FTP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6398|2024-08-02T08:28:21.823Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 01:34:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29974|2024-08-02T01:17:58.668Z -- zyxel -- nas326%20firmware</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29974</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED **
The remote code execution vulnerability in the CGI program “file_upload-cgi” in Zyxel NAS326 firmware versions before V5.21(AAZF.17)C0 and NAS542 firmware versions before V5.21(ABAG.14)C0 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code by uploading a crafted configuration file to a vulnerable device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29974|2024-08-02T01:17:58.668Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 01:34:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29976|2024-08-02T01:17:58.558Z -- zyxel -- nas326%20firmware</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29976</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED **
The improper privilege management vulnerability in the command “show_allsessions” in Zyxel NAS326 firmware versions before V5.21(AAZF.17)C0 and NAS542 firmware versions before V5.21(ABAG.14)C0 could allow an authenticated attacker to obtain a logged-in administrator’s session information containing cookies on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29976|2024-08-02T01:17:58.558Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 01:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29975|2024-08-02T01:17:58.589Z -- zyxel -- nas326%20firmware</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29975</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED **
The improper privilege management vulnerability in the SUID executable binary in Zyxel NAS326 firmware versions before V5.21(AAZF.17)C0 and NAS542 firmware versions before V5.21(ABAG.14)C0 could allow an authenticated local attacker with administrator privileges to execute some system commands as the “root” user on a vulnerable device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29975|2024-08-02T01:17:58.589Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 01:43:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29973|2024-08-02T01:17:58.484Z -- zyxel -- nas326%20firmware</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29973</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED **
The command injection vulnerability in the “setCookie” parameter in Zyxel NAS326 firmware versions before V5.21(AAZF.17)C0 and NAS542 firmware versions before V5.21(ABAG.14)C0 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute some operating system (OS) commands by sending a crafted HTTP POST request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29973|2024-08-02T01:17:58.484Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 01:29:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29972|2024-08-02T01:17:58.671Z -- zyxel -- nas326%20firmware</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29972</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED **
The command injection vulnerability in the CGI program "remote_help-cgi" in Zyxel NAS326 firmware versions before V5.21(AAZF.17)C0 and NAS542 firmware versions before V5.21(ABAG.14)C0 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute some operating system (OS) commands by sending a crafted HTTP POST request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29972|2024-08-02T01:17:58.671Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 01:24:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1575|2024-07-23T01:39:53.232Z -- zyxel -- wbe660s%20firmware</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1575</link>
      <description>The improper privilege management vulnerability in the Zyxel WBE660S firmware version 6.70(ACGG.3) and earlier versions could allow an authenticated user to escalate privileges and download the configuration files on a vulnerable device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1575|2024-07-23T01:39:53.232Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 01:39:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6764|2024-06-27T20:53:09.347Z -- zyxel -- atp%20series%20firmware</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6764</link>
      <description>A format string vulnerability in a function of the IPSec VPN feature in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from 4.32 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG FLEX series firmware versions from 4.50 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions from 4.16 through 5.37 Patch 1, and USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions from 4.16 through 5.37 Patch 1 could allow an attacker to achieve unauthorized remote code execution by sending a sequence of specially crafted payloads containing an invalid pointer; however, such an attack would require detailed knowledge of an affected device’s memory layout and configuration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6764|2024-06-27T20:53:09.347Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 02:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29973|2024-06-24T13:17:38.297Z -- zyxel -- nas326%20firmware</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29973</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED **
The command injection vulnerability in the “setCookie” parameter in Zyxel NAS326 firmware versions before V5.21(AAZF.17)C0 and NAS542 firmware versions before V5.21(ABAG.14)C0 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute some operating system (OS) commands by sending a crafted HTTP POST request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29973|2024-06-24T13:17:38.297Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 01:29:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37929|2024-06-20T15:16:52.551Z -- zyxel -- v5.50%28abpm.8%29c0%20firmware</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37929</link>
      <description>The buffer overflow vulnerability in the CGI program of the VMG3625-T50B firmware version V5.50(ABPM.8)C0 could allow an authenticated remote attacker to cause denial of service (DoS) conditions by sending a crafted HTTP request to a vulnerable device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37929|2024-06-20T15:16:52.551Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 01:23:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29972|2024-06-05T05:15:38.583Z -- zyxel -- nas326%20firmware</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-29972</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED **
The command injection vulnerability in the CGI program "remote_help-cgi" in Zyxel NAS326 firmware versions before V5.21(AAZF.17)C0 and NAS542 firmware versions before V5.21(ABAG.14)C0 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute some operating system (OS) commands by sending a crafted HTTP POST request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29972|2024-06-05T05:15:38.583Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 01:24:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29973|2024-06-05T04:01:28.607Z -- zyxel -- nas326%20firmware</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-29973</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED **
The command injection vulnerability in the “setCookie” parameter in Zyxel NAS326 firmware versions before V5.21(AAZF.17)C0 and NAS542 firmware versions before V5.21(ABAG.14)C0 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute some operating system (OS) commands by sending a crafted HTTP POST request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29973|2024-06-05T04:01:28.607Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 01:29:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29974|2024-06-05T05:15:39.188Z -- zyxel -- nas326%20firmware</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-29974</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED **
The remote code execution vulnerability in the CGI program “file_upload-cgi” in Zyxel NAS326 firmware versions before V5.21(AAZF.17)C0 and NAS542 firmware versions before V5.21(ABAG.14)C0 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code by uploading a crafted configuration file to a vulnerable device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29974|2024-06-05T05:15:39.188Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 01:34:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29975|2024-06-05T13:00:30.502Z -- zyxel -- nas326%20firmware</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-29975</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED **
The improper privilege management vulnerability in the SUID executable binary in Zyxel NAS326 firmware versions before V5.21(AAZF.17)C0 and NAS542 firmware versions before V5.21(ABAG.14)C0 could allow an authenticated local attacker with administrator privileges to execute some system commands as the “root” user on a vulnerable device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29975|2024-06-05T13:00:30.502Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 01:43:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29976|2024-06-06T15:45:01.336Z -- zyxel -- nas326%20firmware</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-29976</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED **
The improper privilege management vulnerability in the command “show_allsessions” in Zyxel NAS326 firmware versions before V5.21(AAZF.17)C0 and NAS542 firmware versions before V5.21(ABAG.14)C0 could allow an authenticated attacker to obtain a logged-in administrator’s session information containing cookies on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29976|2024-06-06T15:45:01.336Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 01:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0816|2024-06-04T17:58:43.786Z -- zyxel -- dx3300-t1%20firmware</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0816</link>
      <description>The buffer overflow vulnerability in the DX3300-T1 firmware version V5.50(ABVY.4)C0 could allow an authenticated local attacker to cause denial of service (DoS) conditions by executing the CLI command with crafted strings on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0816|2024-06-04T17:58:43.786Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 01:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6399|2024-02-21T09:20:18.921Z -- zyxel -- atp%20series%20firmware</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6399</link>
      <description>A format string vulnerability in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from 4.32 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG FLEX series firmware versions from 4.50 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions from 4.16 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions from 4.16 through 5.37 Patch 1, and USG FLEX H series firmware versions from 1.10 through 1.10 Patch 1 could allow an authenticated IPSec VPN user to cause DoS conditions against the “deviceid” daemon by sending a crafted hostname to an affected device if it has the “Device Insight” feature enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6399|2024-02-21T09:20:18.921Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 01:42:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6398|2024-02-21T09:17:30.230Z -- zyxel -- atp%20series%20firmware</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6398</link>
      <description>A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the file upload binary in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from 4.32 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG FLEX series firmware versions from 4.50 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions from 4.16 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions from 4.16 through 5.37 Patch 1, 

USG FLEX H series firmware versions from 1.10 through 1.10 Patch 1,

NWA50AX firmware versions through 6.29(ABYW.3), WAC500 firmware versions through 6.65(ABVS.1), WAX300H firmware versions through 6.60(ACHF.1), and WBE660S firmware versions through 6.65(ACGG.1) could allow an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to execute some operating system (OS) commands on an affected device via FTP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6398|2024-02-21T09:17:30.230Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 01:34:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6397|2024-06-04T17:17:11.624Z -- zyxel -- atp%20series%20firmware</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6397</link>
      <description>A null pointer dereference vulnerability in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from 4.32 through 5.37 Patch 1 and USG FLEX series firmware versions from 4.50 through 5.37 Patch 1 could allow a LAN-based attacker to cause denial-of-service (DoS) conditions by downloading a crafted RAR compressed file onto a LAN-side host if the firewall has the “Anti-Malware” feature enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6397|2024-06-04T17:17:11.624Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 01:19:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6764|2024-02-20T02:14:09.814Z -- zyxel -- atp%20series%20firmware</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6764</link>
      <description>A format string vulnerability in a function of the IPSec VPN feature in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from 4.32 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG FLEX series firmware versions from 4.50 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions from 4.16 through 5.37 Patch 1, and USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions from 4.16 through 5.37 Patch 1 could allow an attacker to achieve unauthorized remote code execution by sending a sequence of specially crafted payloads containing an invalid pointer; however, such an attack would require detailed knowledge of an affected device’s memory layout and configuration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6764|2024-02-20T02:14:09.814Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 02:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37929|2024-05-21T01:23:53.073Z -- zyxel -- v5.50%28abpm.8%29c0%20firmware</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37929</link>
      <description>The buffer overflow vulnerability in the CGI program of the VMG3625-T50B firmware version V5.50(ABPM.8)C0 could allow an authenticated remote attacker to cause denial of service (DoS) conditions by sending a crafted HTTP request to a vulnerable device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37929|2024-05-21T01:23:53.073Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 01:23:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29973|2024-06-22T03:55:26.681Z -- zyxel -- nas326%20firmware</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29973</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED **
The command injection vulnerability in the “setCookie” parameter in Zyxel NAS326 firmware versions before V5.21(AAZF.17)C0 and NAS542 firmware versions before V5.21(ABAG.14)C0 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute some operating system (OS) commands by sending a crafted HTTP POST request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29973|2024-06-22T03:55:26.681Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 01:29:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29973|2024-06-26T03:55:25.902Z -- zyxel -- nas326%20firmware</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29973</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED **
The command injection vulnerability in the “setCookie” parameter in Zyxel NAS326 firmware versions before V5.21(AAZF.17)C0 and NAS542 firmware versions before V5.21(ABAG.14)C0 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute some operating system (OS) commands by sending a crafted HTTP POST request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29973|2024-06-26T03:55:25.902Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 01:29:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29972|2024-06-26T03:55:24.711Z -- zyxel -- nas326%20firmware</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29972</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED **
The command injection vulnerability in the CGI program "remote_help-cgi" in Zyxel NAS326 firmware versions before V5.21(AAZF.17)C0 and NAS542 firmware versions before V5.21(ABAG.14)C0 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute some operating system (OS) commands by sending a crafted HTTP POST request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29972|2024-06-26T03:55:24.711Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 01:24:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6399|2024-07-05T17:21:43.465Z -- zyxel -- atp%20series%20firmware</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6399</link>
      <description>A format string vulnerability in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from 4.32 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG FLEX series firmware versions from 4.50 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions from 4.16 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions from 4.16 through 5.37 Patch 1, and USG FLEX H series firmware versions from 1.10 through 1.10 Patch 1 could allow an authenticated IPSec VPN user to cause DoS conditions against the “deviceid” daemon by sending a crafted hostname to an affected device if it has the “Device Insight” feature enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6399|2024-07-05T17:21:43.465Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 01:42:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1575|2024-07-23T13:18:27.277Z -- zyxel -- wbe660s%20firmware</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1575</link>
      <description>The improper privilege management vulnerability in the Zyxel WBE660S firmware version 6.70(ACGG.3) and earlier versions could allow an authenticated user to escalate privileges and download the configuration files on a vulnerable device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1575|2024-07-23T13:18:27.277Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 01:39:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1575|2024-08-01T18:40:21.490Z -- zyxel -- wbe660s%20firmware</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1575</link>
      <description>The improper privilege management vulnerability in the Zyxel WBE660S firmware version 6.70(ACGG.3) and earlier versions could allow an authenticated user to escalate privileges and download the configuration files on a vulnerable device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1575|2024-08-01T18:40:21.490Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 01:39:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0816|2024-08-01T18:18:18.882Z -- zyxel -- dx3300-t1%20firmware</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0816</link>
      <description>The buffer overflow vulnerability in the DX3300-T1 firmware version V5.50(ABVY.4)C0 could allow an authenticated local attacker to cause denial of service (DoS) conditions by executing the CLI command with crafted strings on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0816|2024-08-01T18:18:18.882Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 01:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37929|2024-08-02T17:23:27.734Z -- zyxel -- v5.50%28abpm.8%29c0%20firmware</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37929</link>
      <description>The buffer overflow vulnerability in the CGI program of the VMG3625-T50B firmware version V5.50(ABPM.8)C0 could allow an authenticated remote attacker to cause denial of service (DoS) conditions by sending a crafted HTTP request to a vulnerable device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37929|2024-08-02T17:23:27.734Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 01:23:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
