<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Zyxel -- ATP series firmware</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/zyxel/atp%20series%20firmware.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Zyxel -- ATP series firmware</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28767|2023-07-17T16:59:45.258Z -- zyxel -- atp%20series%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-28767</link>
      <description>The configuration parser fails to sanitize user-controlled input in the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 5.10 through 5.36, USG FLEX series firmware versions 5.00 through 5.36,  USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions 5.10 through 5.36, 

USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions 5.10 through 5.36, and VPN series firmware versions 5.00 through 5.36. An unauthenticated, LAN-based attacker could leverage the vulnerability to inject some operating system (OS) commands into the device configuration data on an affected device when the cloud management mode is enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28767|2023-07-17T16:59:45.258Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 16:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5650|2023-11-28T01:53:43.502Z -- zyxel -- atp%20series%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5650</link>
      <description>An improper privilege management vulnerability in the ZySH of the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 4.32 through 5.37, USG FLEX series firmware versions 4.50 through 5.37, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.37, USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.37, and VPN series firmware versions 4.30 through 5.37, could allow an authenticated local attacker to modify the URL of the registration page in the web GUI of an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5650|2023-11-28T01:53:43.502Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 01:53:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5797|2023-11-28T02:00:59.801Z -- zyxel -- atp%20series%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5797</link>
      <description>An improper privilege management vulnerability in the debug CLI command of the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 4.32 through 5.37, USG FLEX series firmware versions 4.50 through 5.37, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.37, USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.37, VPN series firmware versions 4.30 through 5.37, NWA50AX firmware version 6.29(ABYW.2), WAC500 firmware version 6.65(ABVS.1), WAX300H firmware version 6.60(ACHF.1), and WBE660S firmware version 6.65(ACGG.1), could allow an authenticated local attacker to access the administrator’s logs on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5797|2023-11-28T02:00:59.801Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 02:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4397|2023-11-28T01:42:00.951Z -- zyxel -- atp%20series%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4397</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow vulnerability in the Zyxel ATP series firmware version 5.37, USG FLEX series firmware version 5.37, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware version 5.37, and USG20(W)-VPN series firmware version 5.37, could allow an authenticated local attacker with administrator privileges to cause denial-of-service (DoS) conditions by executing the CLI command with crafted strings on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4397|2023-11-28T01:42:00.951Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 01:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4398|2023-11-28T01:48:28.586Z -- zyxel -- atp%20series%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4398</link>
      <description>An integer overflow vulnerability in the source code of the QuickSec IPSec toolkit used in the VPN feature of the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 4.32 through 5.37, USG FLEX series firmware versions 4.50 through 5.37, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.37, USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.37, and VPN series firmware versions 4.30 through 5.37, could allow an unauthenticated attacker to cause denial-of-service (DoS) conditions on an affected device by sending a crafted IKE packet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4398|2023-11-28T01:48:28.586Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 01:48:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22916|2023-04-24T00:00:00 -- zyxel -- atp%20series%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-22916</link>
      <description>The configuration parser of Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 5.10 through 5.35, USG FLEX series firmware versions 5.00 through 5.35, USG FLEX 50(W) firmware versions 5.10 through 5.35, USG20(W)-VPN firmware versions 5.10 through 5.35, and VPN series firmware versions 5.00 through 5.35, which fails to properly sanitize user input. A remote unauthenticated attacker could leverage the vulnerability to modify device configuration data, resulting in DoS conditions on an affected device if the attacker could trick an authorized administrator to switch the management mode to the cloud mode.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22916|2023-04-24T00:00:00</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22917|2023-04-24T00:00:00 -- zyxel -- atp%20series%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-22917</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow vulnerability in the “sdwan_iface_ipc” binary of Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 5.10 through 5.32, USG FLEX series firmware versions 5.00 through 5.32, USG FLEX 50(W) firmware versions 5.10 through 5.32, USG20(W)-VPN firmware versions 5.10 through 5.32, and VPN series firmware versions 5.00 through 5.35, which could allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to cause a core dump with a request error message on a vulnerable device by uploading a crafted configuration file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22917|2023-04-24T00:00:00</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22918|2023-04-24T00:00:00 -- zyxel -- atp%20series%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-22918</link>
      <description>A post-authentication information exposure vulnerability in the CGI program of Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 4.32 through 5.35, USG FLEX series firmware versions 4.50 through 5.35, USG FLEX 50(W) firmware versions 4.16 through 5.35, USG20(W)-VPN firmware versions 4.16 through 5.35, VPN series firmware versions 4.30 through 5.35, NWA110AX firmware version 6.50(ABTG.2) and earlier versions, WAC500 firmware version 6.50(ABVS.0) and earlier versions, and WAX510D firmware version 6.50(ABTF.2) and earlier versions, which could allow a remote authenticated attacker to retrieve encrypted information of the administrator on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22918|2023-04-24T00:00:00</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27991|2023-04-24T00:00:00 -- zyxel -- atp%20series%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27991</link>
      <description>The post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the CLI command of Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 4.32 through 5.35, USG FLEX series firmware versions 4.50 through 5.35, USG FLEX 50(W) firmware versions 4.16 through 5.35, USG20(W)-VPN firmware versions 4.16 through 5.35, and VPN series firmware versions 4.30 through 5.35, which could allow an authenticated attacker to execute some OS commands remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27991|2023-04-24T00:00:00</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27990|2023-12-29T06:45:53.586Z -- zyxel -- atp%20series%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27990</link>
      <description>The cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 4.32 through 5.35, USG FLEX series firmware versions 4.50 through 5.35, USG FLEX 50(W) firmware versions 4.16 through 5.35, USG20(W)-VPN firmware versions 4.16 through 5.35, and VPN series firmware versions 4.30 through 5.35, which could allow an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to store malicious scripts in a vulnerable device. A successful XSS attack could then result in the stored malicious scripts being executed when the user visits the Logs page of the GUI on the device.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27990|2023-12-29T06:45:53.586Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37925|2023-11-28T01:30:55.186Z -- zyxel -- atp%20series%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37925</link>
      <description>An improper privilege management vulnerability in the debug CLI command of the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 4.32 through 5.37, USG FLEX series firmware versions 4.50 through 5.37, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.37, USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.37, VPN series firmware versions 4.30 through 5.37, NWA50AX firmware version 6.29(ABYW.2), WAC500 firmware version 6.65(ABVS.1), WAX300H firmware version 6.60(ACHF.1), and WBE660S firmware version 6.65(ACGG.1), could allow an authenticated local attacker to access system files on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37925|2023-11-28T01:30:55.186Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 01:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37926|2023-11-28T01:37:19.483Z -- zyxel -- atp%20series%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37926</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow vulnerability in the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 4.32 through 5.37, USG FLEX series firmware versions 4.50 through 5.37, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.37, USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.37, and VPN series firmware versions 4.30 through 5.37, could allow an authenticated local attacker to cause denial-of-service (DoS) conditions by executing the CLI command to dump system logs on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37926|2023-11-28T01:37:19.483Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 01:37:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33012|2023-07-17T17:23:26.370Z -- zyxel -- atp%20series%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-33012</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability in the configuration parser of the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 5.10 through 5.36 Patch 2, USG FLEX series firmware versions 5.00 through 5.36 Patch 2,  USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions 5.10 through 5.36 Patch 2, USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions 5.10 through 5.36 Patch 2, and VPN series firmware versions 5.00 through 5.36 Patch 2, could allow an unauthenticated, LAN-based attacker to execute some OS commands by using a crafted GRE configuration when the cloud management mode is enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33012|2023-07-17T17:23:26.370Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 17:23:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33009|2023-06-15T06:17:00.675Z -- zyxel -- atp%20series%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-33009</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow vulnerability in the notification function in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 4.60 through 5.36 Patch 1, USG FLEX series firmware versions 4.60 through 5.36 Patch 1, USG FLEX 50(W) firmware versions 4.60 through 5.36 Patch 1, USG20(W)-VPN firmware versions 4.60 through 5.36 Patch 1, VPN series firmware versions 4.60 through 5.36 Patch 1, ZyWALL/USG series firmware versions 4.60 through 4.73 Patch 1, could allow an unauthenticated attacker to cause denial-of-service (DoS) conditions and even a remote code execution on an affected device.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33009|2023-06-15T06:17:00.675Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33010|2023-05-24T00:00:00 -- zyxel -- atp%20series%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-33010</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow vulnerability in the ID processing function in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 4.32 through 5.36 Patch 1, USG FLEX series firmware versions 4.50 through 5.36 Patch 1, USG FLEX 50(W) firmware versions 4.25 through 5.36 Patch 1, USG20(W)-VPN firmware versions 4.25 through 5.36 Patch 1, VPN series firmware versions 4.30 through 5.36 Patch 1, ZyWALL/USG series firmware versions 4.25 through 4.73 Patch 1, could allow an unauthenticated attacker to cause denial-of-service (DoS) conditions and even a remote code execution on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33010|2023-05-24T00:00:00</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33011|2023-07-17T17:15:45.876Z -- zyxel -- atp%20series%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-33011</link>
      <description>A format string vulnerability in the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 5.10 through 5.36 Patch 2, USG FLEX series firmware versions 5.00 through 5.36 Patch 2,  USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions 5.10 through 5.36 Patch 2, USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions 5.10 through 5.36 Patch 2, and VPN series firmware versions 5.00 through 5.36 Patch 2, could allow an unauthenticated, LAN-based attacker to execute some OS commands by using a crafted PPPoE configuration on an affected device when the cloud management mode is enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33011|2023-07-17T17:15:45.876Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 17:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34138|2023-07-17T18:01:33.075Z -- zyxel -- atp%20series%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34138</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability in the hotspot management feature of the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 4.60 through 5.36 Patch 2, USG FLEX series firmware versions 4.60 through 5.36 Patch 2,  USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions 4.60 through 5.36 Patch 2, USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions 4.60 through 5.36 Patch 2, and VPN series firmware versions 4.60 through 5.36 Patch 2, could allow an unauthenticated, LAN-based attacker to execute some OS commands on an affected device if the attacker could trick an authorized administrator to add their IP address to the list of trusted RADIUS clients in advance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34138|2023-07-17T18:01:33.075Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 17:31:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34141|2023-07-17T17:56:26.818Z -- zyxel -- atp%20series%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34141</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability in the access point (AP) management feature of the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 5.00 through 5.36 Patch 2, USG FLEX series firmware versions 5.00 through 5.36 Patch 2,  USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions 5.00 through 5.36 Patch 2, USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions 5.00 through 5.36 Patch 2, VPN series firmware versions 5.00 through 5.36 Patch 2, NXC2500 firmware versions 6.10(AAIG.0) through 6.10(AAIG.3), and NXC5500 firmware versions 6.10(AAOS.0) through 6.10(AAOS.4), could allow an unauthenticated, LAN-based attacker to execute some OS commands on an affected device if the attacker could trick an authorized administrator to add their IP address to the managed AP list in advance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34141|2023-07-17T17:56:26.818Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 17:56:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-34140|2023-07-17T17:49:38.175Z -- zyxel -- atp%20series%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-34140</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow vulnerability in the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 4.32 through 5.36 Patch 2, USG FLEX series firmware versions 4.50 through 5.36 Patch 2,  USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.36 Patch 2, USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.36 Patch 2, VPN series firmware versions 4.30 through 5.36 Patch 2, NXC2500 firmware versions 6.10(AAIG.0) through 6.10(AAIG.3), and NXC5500 firmware versions 6.10(AAOS.0) through 6.10(AAOS.4), could allow an unauthenticated, LAN-based attacker to cause denial of service (DoS) conditions by sending a crafted request to the CAPWAP daemon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-34140|2023-07-17T17:49:38.175Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 17:49:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35139|2023-11-28T01:22:07.985Z -- zyxel -- atp%20series%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35139</link>
      <description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the CGI program of the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 5.10 through 5.37, USG FLEX series firmware versions 5.00 through 5.37, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions 5.10 through 5.37, USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions 5.10 through 5.37, and VPN series firmware versions 5.00 through 5.37, could allow an unauthenticated LAN-based attacker to store malicious scripts in a vulnerable device. A successful XSS attack could then result in the stored malicious scripts being executed to steal cookies when the user visits the specific CGI used for dumping ZTP logs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35139|2023-11-28T01:22:07.985Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 01:22:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35136|2023-11-28T02:08:26.895Z -- zyxel -- atp%20series%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35136</link>
      <description>An improper input validation vulnerability in the “Quagga” package of the Zyxel ATP series firmware versions 4.32 through 5.37, USG FLEX series firmware versions 4.50 through 5.37, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.37, USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions 4.16 through 5.37, and VPN series firmware versions 4.30 through 5.37, could allow an authenticated local attacker to access configuration files on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35136|2023-11-28T02:08:26.895Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 01:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6764|2024-02-20T02:14:09.814Z -- zyxel -- atp%20series%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6764</link>
      <description>











A format string vulnerability in a function of the IPSec VPN feature in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from 4.32 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG FLEX series firmware versions from 4.50 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions from 4.16 through 5.37 Patch 1, and USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions from 4.16 through 5.37 Patch 1 could allow an attacker to achieve unauthorized remote code execution by sending a sequence of specially crafted payloads containing an invalid pointer; however, such an attack would require detailed knowledge of an affected device’s memory layout and configuration.



</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6764|2024-02-20T02:14:09.814Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 02:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6397|2024-06-04T17:17:11.624Z -- zyxel -- atp%20series%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6397</link>
      <description>











A null pointer dereference vulnerability in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from 4.32 through 5.37 Patch 1 and USG FLEX series firmware versions from 4.50 through 5.37 Patch 1 could allow a LAN-based attacker to cause denial-of-service (DoS) conditions by downloading a crafted RAR compressed file onto a LAN-side host if the firewall has the “Anti-Malware” feature enabled.



</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6397|2024-06-04T17:17:11.624Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 01:19:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6398|2024-02-21T09:17:30.230Z -- zyxel -- atp%20series%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6398</link>
      <description>A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the file upload binary in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from 4.32 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG FLEX series firmware versions from 4.50 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions from 4.16 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions from 4.16 through 5.37 Patch 1, 

USG FLEX H series firmware versions from 1.10 through 1.10 Patch 1,

NWA50AX firmware versions through 6.29(ABYW.3), WAC500 firmware versions through 6.65(ABVS.1), WAX300H firmware versions through 6.60(ACHF.1), and WBE660S firmware versions through 6.65(ACGG.1) could allow an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to execute some operating system (OS) commands on an affected device via FTP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6398|2024-02-21T09:17:30.230Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 01:34:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6399|2024-02-21T09:20:18.921Z -- zyxel -- atp%20series%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6399</link>
      <description>A format string vulnerability in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from 4.32 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG FLEX series firmware versions from 4.50 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions from 4.16 through 5.37 Patch 1, USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions from 4.16 through 5.37 Patch 1, and USG FLEX H series firmware versions from 1.10 through 1.10 Patch 1 could allow an authenticated IPSec VPN user to cause DoS conditions against the “deviceid” daemon by sending a crafted hostname to an affected device if it has the “Device Insight” feature enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6399|2024-02-21T09:20:18.921Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 01:42:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
