<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Zyxel -- USG FLEX series firmware</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/zyxel/usg%20flex%20series%20firmware.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Zyxel -- USG FLEX series firmware</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 15:23:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22913|2024-08-02T10:20:31.464Z -- zyxel -- usg%20flex%20series%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22913</link>
      <description>A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the “account_operator.cgi” CGI program of Zyxel USG FLEX series firmware versions 4.50 through 5.35, and VPN series firmware versions 4.30 through 5.35, which could allow a remote authenticated attacker to modify device configuration data, resulting in denial-of-service (DoS) conditions on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22913|2024-08-02T10:20:31.464Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22914|2024-08-02T10:20:31.461Z -- zyxel -- usg%20flex%20series%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22914</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability in the “account_print.cgi” CGI program of Zyxel USG FLEX series firmware versions 4.50 through 5.35, and VPN series firmware versions 4.30 through 5.35, which could allow a remote authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to execute unauthorized OS commands in the “tmp” directory by uploading a crafted file if the hotspot function were enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22914|2024-08-02T10:20:31.461Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5960|2024-08-02T08:14:25.225Z -- zyxel -- usg%20flex%20series%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5960</link>
      <description>An improper privilege management vulnerability in the hotspot feature of the Zyxel USG FLEX series firmware versions 4.50 through 5.37 and VPN series firmware versions 4.30 through 5.37 could allow an authenticated local attacker to access the system files on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5960|2024-08-02T08:14:25.225Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 02:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22915|2024-08-02T10:20:31.467Z -- zyxel -- usg%20flex%20series%20firmware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22915</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow vulnerability in the “fbwifi_forward.cgi” CGI program of Zyxel USG FLEX series firmware versions 4.50 through 5.35, USG FLEX 50(W) firmware versions 4.30 through 5.35, USG20(W)-VPN firmware versions 4.30 through 5.35, and VPN series firmware versions 4.30 through 5.35, which could allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to cause DoS conditions by sending a crafted HTTP request if the Facebook WiFi function were enabled on an affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22915|2024-08-02T10:20:31.467Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
