<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for thehappymonster -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/thehappymonster/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for thehappymonster -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 17:22:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-5347|2024-05-31T09:31:39.273Z -- thehappymonster -- Happy Addons for Elementor
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5347</link><description>The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'arrow' attribute within the plugin's Post Navigation widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.10.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5347|2024-05-31T09:31:39.273Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 09:31:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5041|2024-05-31T09:31:41.018Z -- thehappymonster -- Happy Addons for Elementor
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5041</link><description>The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘ha-ia-content-button’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.10.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5041|2024-05-31T09:31:41.018Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 09:31:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2787|2024-04-09T18:59:31.469Z -- thehappymonster -- Happy Addons for Elementor</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2787</link><description>The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Page Title HTML Tag in all versions up to, and including, 3.10.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2787|2024-04-09T18:59:31.469Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:59:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2786|2024-04-09T18:58:46.911Z -- thehappymonster -- Happy Addons for Elementor</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2786</link><description>The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via several widgets in all versions up to, and including, 3.10.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the title_tag attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2786|2024-04-09T18:58:46.911Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:58:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2789|2024-04-09T18:59:17.679Z -- thehappymonster -- Happy Addons for Elementor</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2789</link><description>The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Calendy widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.10.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2789|2024-04-09T18:59:17.679Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2788|2024-04-09T18:58:56.837Z -- thehappymonster -- Happy Addons for Elementor</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2788</link><description>The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Post Title HTML Tag in all versions up to, and including, 3.10.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2788|2024-04-09T18:58:56.837Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:58:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3724|2024-05-02T16:52:18.348Z -- thehappymonster -- Happy Addons for Elementor</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3724</link><description>The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Image Stack Group, Photo Stack, &amp; Horizontal Timeline widgets in all versions up to, and including, 3.10.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3724|2024-05-02T16:52:18.348Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3891|2024-05-02T16:52:31.149Z -- thehappymonster -- Happy Addons for Elementor</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3891</link><description>The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via HTML tags in widgets in all versions up to, and including, 3.10.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3891|2024-05-02T16:52:31.149Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3890|2024-04-26T07:28:18.173Z -- thehappymonster -- Happy Addons for Elementor</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3890</link><description>The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Calendly widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.10.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3890|2024-04-26T07:28:18.173Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 07:28:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4865|2024-05-18T03:06:58.279Z -- thehappymonster -- Happy Addons for Elementor</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4865</link><description>The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘_id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.10.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4865|2024-05-18T03:06:58.279Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 03:06:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4478|2024-05-16T07:32:42.409Z -- thehappymonster -- Happy Addons for Elementor</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4478</link><description>The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Image Stack Group widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.10.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied 'tooltip_position' attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4478|2024-05-16T07:32:42.409Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 07:32:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4391|2024-05-16T08:32:50.995Z -- thehappymonster -- Happy Addons for Elementor</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4391</link><description>The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Event Calendar widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.10.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4391|2024-05-16T08:32:50.995Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 08:32:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0838|2024-02-20T18:56:48.371Z -- thehappymonster -- Happy Addons for Elementor</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0838</link><description>The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the side image URL parameter in the Age Gate in all versions up to, and including, 3.10.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0838|2024-02-20T18:56:48.371Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0438|2024-02-20T18:56:23.200Z -- thehappymonster -- Happy Addons for Elementor</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0438</link><description>The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the wrapper link parameter in the Age Gate in all versions up to, and including, 3.10.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor access or higher to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0438|2024-02-20T18:56:23.200Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:56:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1387|2024-04-09T18:59:14.618Z -- thehappymonster -- Happy Addons for Elementor</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1387</link><description>The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to insufficient authorization on the duplicate_thing() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.10.4. This makes it possible for attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to clone arbitrary posts (including private and password protected ones) which may lead to information exposure.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1387|2024-04-09T18:59:14.618Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:59:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1498|2024-04-09T18:59:33.337Z -- thehappymonster -- Happy Addons for Elementor</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1498</link><description>The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Photo Stack Widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.10.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1498|2024-04-09T18:59:33.337Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1377|2024-03-07T05:32:40.450Z -- thehappymonster -- Happy Addons for Elementor</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1377</link><description>The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘author_meta_tag’ attribute of the Author Meta widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.10.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1377|2024-03-07T05:32:40.450Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 05:32:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1366|2024-03-07T05:32:38.892Z -- thehappymonster -- Happy Addons for Elementor</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1366</link><description>The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘archive_title_tag’ attribute of the Archive Title widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.10.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1366|2024-03-07T05:32:38.892Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 05:32:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5088|2024-05-18T11:35:59.688Z -- thehappymonster -- Happy Addons for Elementor</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5088</link><description>The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘_id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.10.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5088|2024-05-18T11:35:59.688Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 11:35:59 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>