<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Quest Kace -- K1000 Appliance</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/quest%20kace/k1000%20appliance.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Quest Kace -- K1000 Appliance</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 08:24:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5406|2024-08-05T05:33:44.407Z -- quest%20kace -- k1000%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5406</link>
      <description>The Quest Kace K1000 Appliance, versions prior to 9.0.270, allows a remote attacker to exploit the misconfigured Cross-Origin Resource Sharing (CORS) mechanism. An unauthenticated, remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to perform sensitive actions such as adding a new administrator account or changing the appliance’s settings. A malicious internal user could also gain administrator privileges of this appliance and use it to visit a malicious link that exploits this vulnerability. This could cause the application to perform sensitive actions such as adding a new administrator account or changing the appliance’s settings. An unauthenticated, remote attacker could add an administrator-level account or change the appliance's settings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5406|2024-08-05T05:33:44.407Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 18:23:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5405|2024-08-05T05:33:44.381Z -- quest%20kace -- k1000%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5405</link>
      <description>The Quest Kace K1000 Appliance, versions prior to 9.0.270, allows an authenticated least privileged user with 'User Console Only' rights to potentially inject arbitrary JavaScript code on the tickets page. Script execution could allow a malicious user of the system to steal session cookies of other users including Administrator and take over their session. This can further be exploited to launch other attacks. The software also does not neutralize or incorrectly neutralizes user-controllable input before it is placed in output that is used as a web page that is served to other users. The software does not neutralize or incorrectly neutralizes user-controllable input before it is placed in output that is used as a web page that is served to other user. An authenticated user with 'user console only' rights may inject arbitrary JavaScript, which could result in an attacker taking over a session of others, including an Administrator.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5405|2024-08-05T05:33:44.381Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 18:23:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5404|2024-08-05T05:33:44.447Z -- quest%20kace -- k1000%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5404</link>
      <description>The Quest Kace K1000 Appliance, versions prior to 9.0.270, allows an authenticated, remote attacker with least privileges ('User Console Only' role) to potentially exploit multiple Blind SQL Injection vulnerabilities to retrieve sensitive information from the database or copy the entire database. An authenticated remote attacker could leverage Blind SQL injections to obtain sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5404|2024-08-05T05:33:44.447Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 18:23:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
