<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for lakernote -- EasyAdmin</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/lakernote/easyadmin.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for lakernote -- EasyAdmin</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 20:21:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5383|2024-06-20T19:24:23.438Z -- lakernote -- easyadmin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5383</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in lakernote EasyAdmin up to 20240324. This affects an unknown part of the file /sys/file/upload. The manipulation of the argument file leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The identifier of the patch is 9c8a836ace17a93c45e5ad52a2340788b7795030. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier VDB-266301 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in lakernote EasyAdmin bis 20240324 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei /sys/file/upload. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments file mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Dieses Produkt setzt Rolling Releases ein. Aus diesem Grund sind Details zu betroffenen oder zu aktualisierende Versionen nicht verfügbar. Der Patch wird als 9c8a836ace17a93c45e5ad52a2340788b7795030 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5383|2024-06-20T19:24:23.438Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 23:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2826|2024-03-22T19:00:09.857Z -- lakernote -- easyadmin</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2826</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in lakernote EasyAdmin up to 20240315. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /ureport/designer/saveReportFile. The manipulation leads to xml external entity reference. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257716.
In lakernote EasyAdmin bis 20240315 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei /ureport/designer/saveReportFile. Durch Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine xml external entity reference-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2826|2024-03-22T19:00:09.857Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 19:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2827|2024-03-22T19:00:15.250Z -- lakernote -- easyadmin</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2827</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in lakernote EasyAdmin up to 20240315. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /ureport/designer/saveReportFile. The manipulation leads to server-side request forgery. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-257717 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in lakernote EasyAdmin bis 20240315 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei /ureport/designer/saveReportFile. Durch das Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine server-side request forgery-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2827|2024-03-22T19:00:15.250Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 19:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2828|2024-03-22T19:31:11.240Z -- lakernote -- easyadmin</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2828</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in lakernote EasyAdmin up to 20240315. Affected is the function thumbnail of the file src/main/java/com/laker/admin/module/sys/controller/IndexController.java. The manipulation of the argument url leads to server-side request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The patch is identified as 23165d8cb569048c531150f194fea39f8800b8d5. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. VDB-257718 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in lakernote EasyAdmin bis 20240315 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es die Funktion thumbnail der Datei src/main/java/com/laker/admin/module/sys/controller/IndexController.java. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments url mit unbekannten Daten kann eine server-side request forgery-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Der Patch wird als 23165d8cb569048c531150f194fea39f8800b8d5 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2828|2024-03-22T19:31:11.240Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 19:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2825|2024-03-22T18:31:08.472Z -- lakernote -- easyadmin</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2825</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in lakernote EasyAdmin up to 20240315. This affects an unknown part of the file /ureport/designer/saveReportFile. The manipulation of the argument file leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-257715.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in lakernote EasyAdmin bis 20240315 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei /ureport/designer/saveReportFile. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments file mit unbekannten Daten kann eine path traversal: '../filedir'-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2825|2024-03-22T18:31:08.472Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 18:31:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5383|2024-05-26T23:00:12.726Z -- lakernote -- easyadmin</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5383</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in lakernote EasyAdmin up to 20240324. This affects an unknown part of the file /sys/file/upload. The manipulation of the argument file leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The identifier of the patch is 9c8a836ace17a93c45e5ad52a2340788b7795030. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier VDB-266301 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in lakernote EasyAdmin bis 20240324 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei /sys/file/upload. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments file mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Dieses Produkt setzt Rolling Releases ein. Aus diesem Grund sind Details zu betroffenen oder zu aktualisierende Versionen nicht verfügbar. Der Patch wird als 9c8a836ace17a93c45e5ad52a2340788b7795030 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5383|2024-05-26T23:00:12.726Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 23:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
