<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Weaver -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/weaver/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Weaver -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 22:23:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2647|2024-08-02T06:26:09.776Z -- weaver -- e-office
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2647</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Weaver E-Office 9.5 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /webroot/inc/utility_all.php of the component File Upload Handler. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-228776. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Weaver E-Office 9.5 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei /webroot/inc/utility_all.php der Komponente File Upload Handler. Durch das Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2647|2024-08-02T06:26:09.776Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 07:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2766|2024-08-02T06:33:05.602Z -- weaver -- oa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2766</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Weaver OA 9.5 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /building/backmgr/urlpage/mobileurl/configfile/jx2_config.ini. The manipulation leads to files or directories accessible. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-229271. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in Weaver OA 9.5 gefunden. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei /building/backmgr/urlpage/mobileurl/configfile/jx2_config.ini. Durch das Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine files or directories accessible-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2766|2024-08-02T06:33:05.602Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 16:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3793|2024-08-02T07:08:49.931Z -- weaver -- e-cology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3793</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Weaver e-cology. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file filelFileDownloadForOutDoc.class of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument fileid with the input 1+WAITFOR+DELAY leads to sql injection. Upgrading to version 10.58.0 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-235061 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Weaver e-cology ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei filelFileDownloadForOutDoc.class der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments fileid mit der Eingabe 1+WAITFOR+DELAY mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 10.58.0 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3793|2024-08-02T07:08:49.931Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 19:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2806|2024-08-02T06:33:05.802Z -- weaver -- e-cology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2806</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Weaver e-cology up to 9.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function RequestInfoByXml of the component API. The manipulation leads to xml external entity reference. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-229411. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Weaver e-cology bis 9.0 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Das betrifft die Funktion RequestInfoByXml der Komponente API. Mittels Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine xml external entity reference-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2806|2024-08-02T06:33:05.802Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 08:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2523|2024-08-02T06:26:08.981Z -- weaver -- e-office
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2523</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Weaver E-Office 9.5. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file App/Ajax/ajax.php?action=mobile_upload_save. The manipulation of the argument upload_quwan leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-228014 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Weaver E-Office 9.5 ausgemacht. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei App/Ajax/ajax.php?action=mobile_upload_save. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments upload_quwan mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2523|2024-08-02T06:26:08.981Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 18:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2765|2024-08-02T06:33:05.773Z -- weaver -- oa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2765</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Weaver OA up to 9.5 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /E-mobile/App/System/File/downfile.php. The manipulation of the argument url leads to absolute path traversal. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-229270 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Weaver OA bis 9.5 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle gefunden. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei /E-mobile/App/System/File/downfile.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments url mit unbekannten Daten kann eine absolute path traversal-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2765|2024-08-02T06:33:05.773Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 16:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2648|2024-08-02T06:26:09.905Z -- weaver -- e-office
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2648</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Weaver E-Office 9.5. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /inc/jquery/uploadify/uploadify.php. The manipulation of the argument Filedata leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-228777 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Weaver E-Office 9.5 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei /inc/jquery/uploadify/uploadify.php. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments Filedata mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2648|2024-08-02T06:26:09.905Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 08:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
