<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Weaver -- e-cology</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/weaver/e-cology.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Weaver -- e-cology</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 18:25:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3793|2024-08-02T07:08:49.931Z -- weaver -- e-cology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3793</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Weaver e-cology. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file filelFileDownloadForOutDoc.class of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument fileid with the input 1+WAITFOR+DELAY leads to sql injection. Upgrading to version 10.58.0 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-235061 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Weaver e-cology ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei filelFileDownloadForOutDoc.class der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments fileid mit der Eingabe 1+WAITFOR+DELAY mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 10.58.0 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3793|2024-08-02T07:08:49.931Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 19:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2806|2024-08-02T06:33:05.802Z -- weaver -- e-cology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2806</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Weaver e-cology up to 9.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function RequestInfoByXml of the component API. The manipulation leads to xml external entity reference. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-229411. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Weaver e-cology bis 9.0 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Das betrifft die Funktion RequestInfoByXml der Komponente API. Mittels Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine xml external entity reference-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2806|2024-08-02T06:33:05.802Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 08:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
