<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Weaver -- e-cology</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/weaver/e-cology.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Weaver -- e-cology</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 14:23:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3793|2024-10-21T13:06:18.440Z -- weaver -- e-cology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3793</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Weaver e-cology. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file filelFileDownloadForOutDoc.class of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument fileid with the input 1+WAITFOR+DELAY leads to sql injection. Upgrading to version 10.58.0 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-235061 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Weaver e-cology ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei filelFileDownloadForOutDoc.class der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments fileid mit der Eingabe 1+WAITFOR+DELAY mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 10.58.0 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3793|2024-10-21T13:06:18.440Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 19:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7704|2024-08-12T20:31:03.873Z -- weaver -- e-cology</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7704</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Weaver e-cology 8. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /cloudstore/ecode/setup/ecology_dev.zip of the component Source Code Handler. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in Weaver e-cology 8 ausgemacht. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei /cloudstore/ecode/setup/ecology_dev.zip der Komponente Source Code Handler. Durch das Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine information disclosure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7704|2024-08-12T20:31:03.873Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 20:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7704|2024-08-13T14:08:11.976Z -- weaver -- e-cology</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7704</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Weaver e-cology 8. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /cloudstore/ecode/setup/ecology_dev.zip of the component Source Code Handler. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in Weaver e-cology 8 ausgemacht. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei /cloudstore/ecode/setup/ecology_dev.zip der Komponente Source Code Handler. Durch das Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine information disclosure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7704|2024-08-13T14:08:11.976Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 20:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
