<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for wpeverest -- User Registration – Custom Registration Form, Login Form, and User Profile WordPress Plugin</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/wpeverest/user%20registration%20%E2%80%93%20custom%20registration%20form%2C%20login%20form%2C%20and%20user%20profile%20wordpress%20plugin.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for wpeverest -- User Registration – Custom Registration Form, Login Form, and User Profile WordPress Plugin</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 11:21:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-1720|2024-03-07T05:32:39.478Z -- wpeverest -- User Registration – Custom Registration Form, Login Form, and User Profile WordPress Plugin</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1720</link><description>The User Registration – Custom Registration Form, Login Form, and User Profile WordPress Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'Display Name' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This vulnerability requires social engineering to successfully exploit, and the impact would be very limited due to the attacker requiring a user to login as the user with the injected payload for execution.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1720|2024-03-07T05:32:39.478Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 05:32:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3295|2024-05-02T16:52:21.344Z -- wpeverest -- User Registration – Custom Registration Form, Login Form, and User Profile WordPress Plugin</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3295</link><description>The User Registration – Custom Registration Form, Login Form, and User Profile WordPress Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the profile_pic_remove function in versions up to, and including, 3.1.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete any media file.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3295|2024-05-02T16:52:21.344Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2417|2024-05-02T16:52:41.534Z -- wpeverest -- User Registration – Custom Registration Form, Login Form, and User Profile WordPress Plugin</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2417</link><description>The User Registration – Custom Registration Form, Login Form, and User Profile WordPress Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the form_save_action() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to update the registration form and make the default registration role administrator. This subsequently allows the attacker to register an account as an administrator on the site.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2417|2024-05-02T16:52:41.534Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4958|2024-06-01T07:35:56.868Z -- wpeverest -- User Registration – Custom Registration Form, Login Form, and User Profile WordPress Plugin</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4958</link><description>The User Registration – Custom Registration Form, Login Form, and User Profile WordPress Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'import_form_action' function in versions up to, and including, 3.2.0.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to import a registration form with a default user role of administrator. If an administrator approves or publishes a post or page with the shortcode to the imported form, any user can register as an administrator.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4958|2024-06-01T07:35:56.868Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 07:35:56 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>