<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for gopiplushotmailcom -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/gopiplushotmailcom/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for gopiplushotmailcom -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 18:24:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5432|2024-08-02T07:59:44.625Z -- gopiplushotmailcom -- jquery%20news%20ticker
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5432</link>
      <description>The Jquery news ticker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'jquery-news-ticker' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 3.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5432|2024-08-02T07:59:44.625Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 03:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5430|2024-08-02T07:59:44.719Z -- gopiplushotmailcom -- jquery%20news%20ticker
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5430</link>
      <description>The Jquery news ticker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 3.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5430|2024-08-02T07:59:44.719Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:32:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5436|2024-08-02T07:59:44.623Z -- gopiplushotmailcom -- vertical%20marquee%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5436</link>
      <description>The Vertical marquee plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 7.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5436|2024-08-02T07:59:44.623Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:32:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5465|2024-08-02T07:59:44.709Z -- gopiplushotmailcom -- popup%20with%20fancybox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5465</link>
      <description>The Popup with fancybox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 3.5 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5465|2024-08-02T07:59:44.709Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:33:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
