<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Google Inc. -- Android</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/google%20inc./android.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Google Inc. -- Android</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 02:28:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6771|2024-08-06T01:43:37.906Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6771</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in Telephony could enable a local malicious application to access system functions beyond its access level. This issue is rated as Moderate because it is a local bypass of restrictions on a constrained process. Product: Android. Versions: 6.0, 6.0.1, 7.0. Android ID: A-31566390.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6771|2024-08-06T01:43:37.906Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6716|2024-08-06T01:36:29.532Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6716</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the AOSP Launcher in Android 7.0 before 2016-11-01 could allow a local malicious application to create shortcuts that have elevated privileges without the user's consent. This issue is rated as Moderate because it is a local bypass of user interaction requirements (access to functionality that would normally require either user initiation or user permission). Android ID: A-30778130.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6716|2024-08-06T01:36:29.532Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6777|2024-08-06T01:43:37.764Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6777</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the NVIDIA GPU driver could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of the kernel. This issue is rated as Critical due to the possibility of a local permanent device compromise, which may require reflashing the operating system to repair the device. Product: Android. Versions: Kernel-3.10. Android ID: A-31910462. References: N-CVE-2016-6777.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6777|2024-08-06T01:43:37.764Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6755|2024-08-06T01:43:37.894Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6755</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the Qualcomm camera driver could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of the kernel. This issue is rated as High because it first requires compromising a privileged process. Product: Android. Versions: Kernel-3.10, Kernel-3.18. Android ID: A-30740545. References: QC-CR#1065916.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6755|2024-08-06T01:43:37.894Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6728|2024-08-06T01:36:29.596Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6728</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the kernel ION subsystem in Android before 2016-11-05 could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of the kernel. This issue is rated as Critical due to the possibility of a local permanent device compromise, which may require reflashing the operating system to repair the device. Android ID: A-30400942.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6728|2024-08-06T01:36:29.596Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6705|2024-08-06T01:36:29.476Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6705</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in Mediaserver in Android 5.0.x before 5.0.2, 5.1.x before 5.1.1, 6.x before 2016-11-01, and 7.0 before 2016-11-01 could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of a privileged process. This issue is rated as High because it could be used to gain local access to elevated capabilities, which are not normally accessible to a third-party application. Android ID: A-30907212.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6705|2024-08-06T01:36:29.476Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-3907|2024-08-06T00:10:31.864Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-3907</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability in Qualcomm components including the GPU driver, power driver, SMSM Point-to-Point driver, and sound driver in Android before 2016-11-05 could enable a local malicious application to access data outside of its permission levels. This issue is rated as Moderate because it first requires compromising a privileged process. Android ID: A-30593266. References: Qualcomm QC-CR#1054352.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-3907|2024-08-06T00:10:31.864Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6774|2024-08-06T01:43:37.862Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6774</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability in Package Manager could enable a local malicious application to bypass operating system protections that isolate application data from other applications. This issue is rated as Moderate because it first requires compromising a privileged process. Product: Android. Versions: 7.0. Android ID: A-31251489.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6774|2024-08-06T01:43:37.862Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6766|2024-08-06T01:43:37.790Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6766</link>
      <description>A denial of service vulnerability in libmedia and libstagefright in Mediaserver could enable an attacker to use a specially crafted file to cause a device hang or reboot. This issue is rated as High due to the possibility of remote denial of service. Product: Android. Versions: 4.4.4, 5.0.2, 5.1.1, 6.0, 6.0.1, 7.0. Android ID: A-31318219.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6766|2024-08-06T01:43:37.790Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6736|2024-08-06T01:36:29.633Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6736</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the NVIDIA GPU driver in Android before 2016-11-05 could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of the kernel. This issue is rated as Critical due to the possibility of a local permanent device compromise, which may require reflashing the operating system to repair the device. Android ID: A-30953284. References: NVIDIA N-CVE-2016-6736.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6736|2024-08-06T01:36:29.633Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6745|2024-08-06T01:36:29.574Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6745</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the Synaptics touchscreen driver in Android before 2016-11-05 could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of the kernel. This issue is rated as High because it first requires compromising a privileged process. Android ID: A-31252388.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6745|2024-08-06T01:36:29.574Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6773|2024-08-06T01:43:37.977Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6773</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability in the ih264d decoder in Mediaserver could enable a local malicious application to access data outside of its permission levels. This issue is rated as Moderate because it could be used to access sensitive data without permission. Product: Android. Versions: 6.0, 6.0.1, 7.0. Android ID: A-30481714.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6773|2024-08-06T01:43:37.977Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6757|2024-08-06T01:43:37.985Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6757</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability in Qualcomm components including the camera driver and video driver could enable a local malicious application to access data outside of its permission levels. This issue is rated as Moderate because it first requires compromising a privileged process. Product: Android. Versions: Kernel-3.10, Kernel-3.18. Android ID: A-30148242. References: QC-CR#1052821.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6757|2024-08-06T01:43:37.985Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6698|2024-08-06T01:36:29.594Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6698</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability in Qualcomm components including the GPU driver, power driver, SMSM Point-to-Point driver, and sound driver in Android before 2016-11-05 could enable a local malicious application to access data outside of its permission levels. This issue is rated as Moderate because it first requires compromising a privileged process. Android ID: A-30741851. References: Qualcomm QC-CR#1058826.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6698|2024-08-06T01:36:29.594Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6763|2024-08-06T01:43:37.900Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6763</link>
      <description>A denial of service vulnerability in Telephony could enable a local malicious application to use a specially crafted file to cause a device hang or reboot. This issue is rated as High due to the possibility of local permanent denial of service. Product: Android. Versions: 4.4.4, 5.0.2, 5.1.1, 6.0, 6.0.1, 7.0. Android ID: A-31530456.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6763|2024-08-06T01:43:37.900Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6748|2024-08-06T01:36:29.675Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6748</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability in Qualcomm components including the GPU driver, power driver, SMSM Point-to-Point driver, and sound driver in Android before 2016-11-05 could enable a local malicious application to access data outside of its permission levels. This issue is rated as Moderate because it first requires compromising a privileged process. Android ID: A-30076504. References: Qualcomm QC-CR#987018.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6748|2024-08-06T01:36:29.675Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6750|2024-08-06T01:36:29.545Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6750</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability in Qualcomm components including the GPU driver, power driver, SMSM Point-to-Point driver, and sound driver in Android before 2016-11-05 could enable a local malicious application to access data outside of its permission levels. This issue is rated as Moderate because it first requires compromising a privileged process. Android ID: A-30312054. References: Qualcomm QC-CR#1052825.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6750|2024-08-06T01:36:29.545Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6754|2024-08-06T01:43:37.841Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6754</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability in Webview in Android 5.0.x before 5.0.2, 5.1.x before 5.1.1, and 6.x before 2016-11-05 could enable a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code when the user is navigating to a website. This issue is rated as High due to the possibility of remote code execution in an unprivileged process. Android ID: A-31217937.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6754|2024-08-06T01:43:37.841Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6729|2024-08-06T01:36:29.462Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6729</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the Qualcomm bootloader in Android before 2016-11-05 could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of the kernel. This issue is rated as Critical due to the possibility of a local permanent device compromise, which may require reflashing the operating system to repair the device. Android ID: A-30977990. References: Qualcomm QC-CR#977684.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6729|2024-08-06T01:36:29.462Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6789|2024-08-06T01:43:38.034Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6789</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the NVIDIA libomx library (libnvomx) could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of a privileged process. This issue is rated as High because it could be used to gain local access to elevated capabilities, which are not normally accessible to a third-party application. Product: Android. Versions: Kernel-3.18. Android ID: A-31251973. References: N-CVE-2016-6789.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6789|2024-08-06T01:43:38.034Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6770|2024-08-06T01:43:37.715Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6770</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the Framework API could enable a local malicious application to access system functions beyond its access level. This issue is rated as Moderate because it is a local bypass of restrictions on a constrained process. Product: Android. Versions: 4.4.4, 5.0.2, 5.1.1, 6.0, 6.0.1, 7.0. Android ID: A-30202228.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6770|2024-08-06T01:43:37.715Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-3904|2024-08-06T00:10:31.865Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-3904</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the Qualcomm bus driver in Android before 2016-11-05 could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of the kernel. This issue is rated as High because it first requires compromising a privileged process. Android ID: A-30311977. References: Qualcomm QC-CR#1050455.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-3904|2024-08-06T00:10:31.865Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6731|2024-08-06T01:36:29.571Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6731</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the NVIDIA GPU driver in Android before 2016-11-05 could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of the kernel. This issue is rated as Critical due to the possibility of a local permanent device compromise, which may require reflashing the operating system to repair the device. Android ID: A-30906023. References: NVIDIA N-CVE-2016-6731.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6731|2024-08-06T01:36:29.571Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6738|2024-08-06T01:36:29.543Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6738</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the Qualcomm crypto engine driver in Android before 2016-11-05 could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of the kernel. This issue is rated as High because it first requires compromising a privileged process. Android ID: A-30034511. References: Qualcomm QC-CR#1050538.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6738|2024-08-06T01:36:29.543Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6737|2024-08-06T01:36:29.549Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6737</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the kernel ION subsystem in Android before 2016-11-05 could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of the kernel. This issue is rated as Critical due to the possibility of a local permanent device compromise, which may require reflashing the operating system to repair the device. Android ID: A-30928456.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6737|2024-08-06T01:36:29.549Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6701|2024-08-06T01:36:29.575Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6701</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability in libskia in Android 7.0 before 2016-11-01 could enable an attacker using a specially crafted file to cause memory corruption during media file and data processing. This issue is rated as High due to the possibility of remote code execution within the context of the gallery process. Android ID: A-30190637.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6701|2024-08-06T01:36:29.575Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6708|2024-08-06T01:36:29.475Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6708</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege in the System UI in Android 7.0 before 2016-11-01 could enable a local malicious user to bypass the security prompt of your work profile in Multi-Window mode. This issue is rated as High because it is a local bypass of user interaction requirements for any developer or security setting modifications. Android ID: A-30693465.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6708|2024-08-06T01:36:29.475Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6747|2024-08-06T01:36:29.578Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6747</link>
      <description>A denial of service vulnerability in Mediaserver in Android before 2016-11-05 could enable an attacker to use a specially crafted file to cause a device hang or reboot. This issue is rated as High due to the possibility of remote denial of service. Android ID: A-31244612. References: NVIDIA N-CVE-2016-6747.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6747|2024-08-06T01:36:29.578Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6739|2024-08-06T01:36:29.550Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6739</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the Qualcomm camera driver in Android before 2016-11-05 could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of the kernel. This issue is rated as High because it first requires compromising a privileged process. Android ID: A-30074605. References: Qualcomm QC-CR#1049826.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6739|2024-08-06T01:36:29.550Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6715|2024-08-06T01:36:29.569Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6715</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the Framework APIs in Android 4.x before 4.4.4, 5.0.x before 5.0.2, 5.1.x before 5.1.1, 6.x before 2016-11-01, and 7.0 before 2016-11-01 could allow a local malicious application to record audio without the user's permission. This issue is rated as Moderate because it is a local bypass of user interaction requirements (access to functionality that would normally require either user initiation or user permission.) Android ID: A-29833954.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6715|2024-08-06T01:36:29.569Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6742|2024-08-06T01:36:29.645Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6742</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the Synaptics touchscreen driver in Android before 2016-11-05 could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of the kernel. This issue is rated as High because it first requires compromising a privileged process. Android ID: A-30799828.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6742|2024-08-06T01:36:29.645Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6703|2024-08-06T01:36:29.368Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6703</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability in an Android runtime library in Android 4.x before 4.4.4, 5.0.x before 5.0.2, 5.1.x before 5.1.1, and 6.x before 2016-11-01 could enable an attacker using a specially crafted payload to execute arbitrary code in the context of an unprivileged process. This issue is rated as High due to the possibility of remote code execution in an application that uses the Android runtime. Android ID: A-30765246.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6703|2024-08-06T01:36:29.368Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6730|2024-08-06T01:36:29.568Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6730</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the NVIDIA GPU driver in Android before 2016-11-05 could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of the kernel. This issue is rated as Critical due to the possibility of a local permanent device compromise, which may require reflashing the operating system to repair the device. Android ID: A-30904789. References: NVIDIA N-CVE-2016-6730.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6730|2024-08-06T01:36:29.568Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6733|2024-08-06T01:36:29.578Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6733</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the NVIDIA GPU driver in Android before 2016-11-05 could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of the kernel. This issue is rated as Critical due to the possibility of a local permanent device compromise, which may require reflashing the operating system to repair the device. Android ID: A-30906694. References: NVIDIA N-CVE-2016-6733.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6733|2024-08-06T01:36:29.578Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6756|2024-08-06T01:43:37.868Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6756</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability in Qualcomm components including the camera driver and video driver could enable a local malicious application to access data outside of its permission levels. This issue is rated as Moderate because it first requires compromising a privileged process. Product: Android. Versions: Kernel-3.10, Kernel-3.18. Android ID: A-29464815. References: QC-CR#1042068.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6756|2024-08-06T01:43:37.868Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6713|2024-08-06T01:36:29.528Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6713</link>
      <description>A remote denial of service vulnerability in Mediaserver in Android 6.x before 2016-11-01 and 7.0 before 2016-11-01 could enable an attacker to use a specially crafted file to cause a device hang or reboot. This issue is rated as High due to the possibility of remote denial of service. Android ID: A-30822755.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6713|2024-08-06T01:36:29.528Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6719|2024-08-06T01:36:29.565Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6719</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the Bluetooth component in Android 4.x before 4.4.4, 5.0.x before 5.0.2, 5.1.x before 5.1.1, 6.x before 2016-11-01, and 7.0 before 2016-11-01 could enable a local malicious application to pair with any Bluetooth device without user consent. This issue is rated as Moderate because it is a local bypass of user interaction requirements (access to functionality that would normally require either user initiation or user permission.) Android ID: A-29043989.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6719|2024-08-06T01:36:29.565Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6710|2024-08-06T01:36:29.492Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6710</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability in the download manager in Android 5.0.x before 5.0.2, 5.1.x before 5.1.1, 6.x before 2016-11-01, and 7.0 before 2016-11-01 could enable a local malicious application to bypass operating system protections that isolate application data from other applications. This issue is rated as High because it could be used to gain access to data that the application does not have access to. Android ID: A-30537115.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6710|2024-08-06T01:36:29.492Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6782|2024-08-06T01:43:38.035Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6782</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the MediaTek driver could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of the kernel. This issue is rated as High because it first requires compromising a privileged process. Product: Android. Versions: Kernel-3.10. Android ID: A-31224389. References: MT-ALPS02943506.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6782|2024-08-06T01:43:38.035Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6744|2024-08-06T01:36:29.544Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6744</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the Synaptics touchscreen driver in Android before 2016-11-05 could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of the kernel. This issue is rated as High because it first requires compromising a privileged process. Android ID: A-30970485.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6744|2024-08-06T01:36:29.544Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6740|2024-08-06T01:36:29.578Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6740</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the Qualcomm camera driver in Android before 2016-11-05 could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of the kernel. This issue is rated as High because it first requires compromising a privileged process. Android ID: A-30143904. References: Qualcomm QC-CR#1056307.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6740|2024-08-06T01:36:29.578Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6762|2024-08-06T01:43:37.851Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6762</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the libziparchive library could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of a privileged process. This issue is rated as High because it could be used to gain local access to elevated capabilities, which are not normally accessible to a third-party application. Product: Android. Versions: 5.0.2, 5.1.1, 6.0, 6.0.1, 7.0. Android ID: A-31251826.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6762|2024-08-06T01:43:37.851Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6734|2024-08-06T01:36:29.471Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6734</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the NVIDIA GPU driver in Android before 2016-11-05 could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of the kernel. This issue is rated as Critical due to the possibility of a local permanent device compromise, which may require reflashing the operating system to repair the device. Android ID: A-30907120. References: NVIDIA N-CVE-2016-6734.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6734|2024-08-06T01:36:29.471Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6732|2024-08-06T01:36:29.534Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6732</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the NVIDIA GPU driver in Android before 2016-11-05 could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of the kernel. This issue is rated as Critical due to the possibility of a local permanent device compromise, which may require reflashing the operating system to repair the device. Android ID: A-30906599. References: NVIDIA N-CVE-2016-6732.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6732|2024-08-06T01:36:29.534Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6724|2024-08-06T01:36:29.594Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6724</link>
      <description>A denial of service vulnerability in the Input Manager Service in Android 4.x before 4.4.4, 5.0.x before 5.0.2, 5.1.x before 5.1.1, 6.x before 2016-11-01, and 7.0 before 2016-11-01 could enable a local malicious application to cause the device to continually reboot. This issue is rated as Moderate because it is a temporary denial of service that requires a factory reset to fix. Android ID: A-30568284.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6724|2024-08-06T01:36:29.594Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6707|2024-08-06T01:36:29.542Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6707</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in System Server in Android 6.x before 2016-11-01 and 7.0 before 2016-11-01 could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of a privileged process. This issue is rated as High because it could be used to gain local access to elevated capabilities, which are not normally accessible to a third-party application. Android ID: A-31350622.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6707|2024-08-06T01:36:29.542Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6751|2024-08-06T01:36:29.567Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6751</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability in Qualcomm components including the GPU driver, power driver, SMSM Point-to-Point driver, and sound driver in Android before 2016-11-05 could enable a local malicious application to access data outside of its permission levels. This issue is rated as Moderate because it first requires compromising a privileged process. Android ID: A-30902162. References: Qualcomm QC-CR#1062271.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6751|2024-08-06T01:36:29.567Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6760|2024-08-06T01:43:37.780Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6760</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in Qualcomm media codecs could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of a privileged process. This issue is rated as High because it could be used to gain local access to elevated capabilities, which are not normally accessible to a third-party application. Product: Android. Versions: Kernel-3.10, Kernel-3.18. Android ID: A-29617572. References: QC-CR#1055783.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6760|2024-08-06T01:43:37.780Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6788|2024-08-06T01:43:37.891Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6788</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the MediaTek I2C driver could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of the kernel. This issue is rated as High because it first requires compromising a privileged process. Product: Android. Versions: N/A. Android ID: A-31224428. References: MT-ALPS02943467.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6788|2024-08-06T01:43:37.891Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6723|2024-08-06T01:36:29.564Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6723</link>
      <description>A denial of service vulnerability in Proxy Auto Config in Android 4.x before 4.4.4, 5.0.x before 5.0.2, 5.1.x before 5.1.1, 6.x before 2016-11-01, and 7.0 before 2016-11-01 could enable a remote attacker to use a specially crafted file to cause a device hang or reboot. This issue is rated as Moderate because it requires an uncommon device configuration. Android ID: A-30100884.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6723|2024-08-06T01:36:29.564Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6781|2024-08-06T01:43:37.890Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6781</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the MediaTek driver could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of the kernel. This issue is rated as High because it first requires compromising a privileged process. Product: Android. Versions: Kernel-3.10. Android ID: A-31095175. References: MT-ALPS02943455.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6781|2024-08-06T01:43:37.890Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6714|2024-08-06T01:36:29.563Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6714</link>
      <description>A remote denial of service vulnerability in Mediaserver in Android 6.x before 2016-11-01 and 7.0 before 2016-11-01 could enable an attacker to use a specially crafted file to cause a device hang or reboot. This issue is rated as High due to the possibility of remote denial of service. Android ID: A-31092462.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6714|2024-08-06T01:36:29.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6741|2024-08-06T01:36:29.576Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6741</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the Qualcomm camera driver in Android before 2016-11-05 could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of the kernel. This issue is rated as High because it first requires compromising a privileged process. Android ID: A-30559423. References: Qualcomm QC-CR#1060554.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6741|2024-08-06T01:36:29.576Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6783|2024-08-06T01:43:37.782Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6783</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the MediaTek driver could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of the kernel. This issue is rated as High because it first requires compromising a privileged process. Product: Android. Versions: N/A. Android ID: A-31350044. References: MT-ALPS02943437.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6783|2024-08-06T01:43:37.782Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6772|2024-08-06T01:43:37.891Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6772</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in Wi-Fi could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of a privileged process. This issue is rated as Moderate because it first requires compromising a privileged process. Product: Android. Versions: 5.0.2, 5.1.1, 6.0, 6.0.1, 7.0. Android ID: A-31856351.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6772|2024-08-06T01:43:37.891Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6776|2024-08-06T01:43:37.977Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6776</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the NVIDIA GPU driver could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of the kernel. This issue is rated as Critical due to the possibility of a local permanent device compromise, which may require reflashing the operating system to repair the device. Product: Android. Versions: Kernel-3.10. Android ID: A-31680980. References: N-CVE-2016-6776.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6776|2024-08-06T01:43:37.977Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6700|2024-08-06T01:36:29.425Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6700</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in libzipfile in Android 4.x before 4.4.4, 5.0.x before 5.0.2, and 5.1.x before 5.1.1 could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of a privileged process. This issue is rated as Critical due to the possibility of a local permanent device compromise, which may require reflashing the operating system to repair the device. Android ID: A-30916186.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6700|2024-08-06T01:36:29.425Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6785|2024-08-06T01:43:37.915Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6785</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the MediaTek driver could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of the kernel. This issue is rated as High because it first requires compromising a privileged process. Product: Android. Versions: Kernel-3.10. Android ID: A-31748056. References: MT-ALPS02961400.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6785|2024-08-06T01:43:37.915Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6702|2024-08-06T01:36:29.563Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6702</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability in libjpeg in Android 4.x before 4.4.4, 5.0.x before 5.0.2, and 5.1.x before 5.1.1 could enable an attacker using a specially crafted file to execute arbitrary code in the context of an unprivileged process. This issue is rated as High due to the possibility of remote code execution in an application that uses libjpeg. Android ID: A-30259087.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6702|2024-08-06T01:36:29.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6752|2024-08-06T01:36:29.566Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6752</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability in Qualcomm components including the GPU driver, power driver, SMSM Point-to-Point driver, and sound driver in Android before 2016-11-05 could enable a local malicious application to access data outside of its permission levels. This issue is rated as Moderate because it first requires compromising a privileged process. Android ID: A-31498159. References: Qualcomm QC-CR#987051.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6752|2024-08-06T01:36:29.566Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6721|2024-08-06T01:36:29.566Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6721</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability in Mediaserver in Android 6.x before 2016-11-01 and 7.0 before 2016-11-01 could enable a local malicious application to access data outside of its permission levels. This issue is rated as Moderate because it could be used to access sensitive data without permission. Android ID: A-30875060.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6721|2024-08-06T01:36:29.566Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6768|2024-08-06T01:43:38.167Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6768</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability in the Framesequence library could enable an attacker using a specially crafted file to execute arbitrary code in the context of an unprivileged process. This issue is rated as High due to the possibility of remote code execution in an application that uses the Framesequence library. Product: Android. Versions: 5.0.2, 5.1.1, 6.0, 6.0.1, 7.0. Android ID: A-31631842.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6768|2024-08-06T01:43:38.167Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6791|2024-08-06T01:43:37.928Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6791</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the Qualcomm sound driver could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of the kernel. This issue is rated as High because it first requires compromising a privileged process. Product: Android. Versions: Kernel-3.10, Kernel-3.18. Android ID: A-31252384. References: QC-CR#1071809.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6791|2024-08-06T01:43:37.928Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6725|2024-08-06T01:36:29.614Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6725</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability in the Qualcomm crypto driver in Android before 2016-11-05 could enable a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code within the context of the kernel. This issue is rated as Critical due to the possibility of remote code execution in the context of the kernel. Android ID: A-30515053. References: Qualcomm QC-CR#1050970.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6725|2024-08-06T01:36:29.614Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6749|2024-08-06T01:36:29.557Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6749</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability in Qualcomm components including the GPU driver, power driver, SMSM Point-to-Point driver, and sound driver in Android before 2016-11-05 could enable a local malicious application to access data outside of its permission levels. This issue is rated as Moderate because it first requires compromising a privileged process. Android ID: A-30228438. References: Qualcomm QC-CR#1052818.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6749|2024-08-06T01:36:29.557Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6775|2024-08-06T01:43:37.909Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6775</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the NVIDIA GPU driver could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of the kernel. This issue is rated as Critical due to the possibility of a local permanent device compromise, which may require reflashing the operating system to repair the device. Product: Android. Versions: Kernel-3.10. Android ID: A-31222873. References: N-CVE-2016-6775.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6775|2024-08-06T01:43:37.909Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6767|2024-08-06T01:43:37.641Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6767</link>
      <description>A denial of service vulnerability in Mediaserver could enable an attacker to use a specially crafted file to cause a device hang or reboot. This issue is rated as High due to the possibility of remote denial of service. Product: Android. Versions: 4.4.4. Android ID: A-31833604.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6767|2024-08-06T01:43:37.641Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6764|2024-08-06T01:43:38.141Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6764</link>
      <description>A denial of service vulnerability in Mediaserver could enable an attacker to use a specially crafted file to cause a device hang or reboot. This issue is rated as High due to the possibility of remote denial of service. Product: Android. Versions: 4.4.4, 5.0.2, 5.1.1, 6.0, 6.0.1, 7.0. Android ID: A-31681434.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6764|2024-08-06T01:43:38.141Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6704|2024-08-06T01:36:29.469Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6704</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in Mediaserver in Android 4.x before 4.4.4, 5.0.x before 5.0.2, 5.1.x before 5.1.1, 6.x before 2016-11-01, and 7.0 before 2016-11-01 could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of a privileged process. This issue is rated as High because it could be used to gain local access to elevated capabilities, which are not normally accessible to a third-party application. Android ID: A-30229821.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6704|2024-08-06T01:36:29.469Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6778|2024-08-06T01:43:37.668Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6778</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the HTC sound codec driver could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of the kernel. This issue is rated as High because it first requires compromising a privileged process. Product: Android. Versions: Kernel-3.10. Android ID: A-31384646.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6778|2024-08-06T01:43:37.668Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6765|2024-08-06T01:43:37.779Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6765</link>
      <description>A denial of service vulnerability in libstagefright in Mediaserver could enable an attacker to use a specially crafted file to cause a device hang or reboot. This issue is rated as High due to the possibility of remote denial of service. Product: Android. Versions: 4.4.4, 5.0.2, 5.1.1, 7.0. Android ID: A-31449945.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6765|2024-08-06T01:43:37.779Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6746|2024-08-06T01:36:29.584Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6746</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability in the NVIDIA GPU driver in Android before 2016-11-05 could enable a local malicious application to access data outside of its permission levels. This issue is rated as High because it could be used to access sensitive data without explicit user permission. Android ID: A-30955105. References: NVIDIA N-CVE-2016-6746.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6746|2024-08-06T01:36:29.584Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6761|2024-08-06T01:43:37.868Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6761</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in Qualcomm media codecs could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of a privileged process. This issue is rated as High because it could be used to gain local access to elevated capabilities, which are not normally accessible to a third-party application. Product: Android. Versions: Kernel-3.10, Kernel-3.18. Android ID: A-29421682. References: QC-CR#1055792.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6761|2024-08-06T01:43:37.868Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6759|2024-08-06T01:43:37.880Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6759</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in Qualcomm media codecs could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of a privileged process. This issue is rated as High because it could be used to gain local access to elevated capabilities, which are not normally accessible to a third-party application. Product: Android. Versions: Kernel-3.10, Kernel-3.18. Android ID: A-29982686. References: QC-CR#1055766.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6759|2024-08-06T01:43:37.880Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6780|2024-08-06T01:43:38.320Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6780</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the HTC sound codec driver could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of the kernel. This issue is rated as High because it first requires compromising a privileged process. Product: Android. Versions: Kernel-3.10. Android ID: A-31251496.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6780|2024-08-06T01:43:38.320Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6769|2024-08-06T01:43:37.836Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6769</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in Smart Lock could enable a local malicious user to access Smart Lock settings without a PIN. This issue is rated as Moderate because it first requires physical access to an unlocked device where Smart Lock was the last settings pane accessed by the user. Product: Android. Versions: 5.0.2, 5.1.1, 6.0, 6.0.1. Android ID: A-29055171.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6769|2024-08-06T01:43:37.836Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6753|2024-08-06T01:43:37.658Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6753</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability in kernel components, including the process-grouping subsystem and the networking subsystem, in Android before 2016-11-05 could enable a local malicious application to access data outside of its permission levels. This issue is rated as Moderate because it first requires compromising a privileged process. Android ID: A-30149174.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6753|2024-08-06T01:43:37.658Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6718|2024-08-06T01:36:29.566Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6718</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the Account Manager Service in Android 7.0 before 2016-11-01 could enable a local malicious application to retrieve sensitive information without user interaction. This issue is rated as Moderate because it is a local bypass of user interaction requirements (access to functionality that would normally require either user initiation or user permission.) Android ID: A-30455516.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6718|2024-08-06T01:36:29.566Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6717|2024-08-06T01:36:29.595Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6717</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in Mediaserver in Android 4.x before 4.4.4, 5.0.x before 5.0.2, 5.1.x before 5.1.1, 6.x before 2016-11-01, and 7.0 before 2016-11-01 could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of a privileged process. This issue is rated as Moderate because it first requires exploitation of a separate vulnerability. Android ID: A-31350239.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6717|2024-08-06T01:36:29.595Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6758|2024-08-06T01:43:37.713Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6758</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in Qualcomm media codecs could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of a privileged process. This issue is rated as High because it could be used to gain local access to elevated capabilities, which are not normally accessible to a third-party application. Product: Android. Versions: Kernel-3.10, Kernel-3.18. Android ID: A-30148882. References: QC-CR#1071731.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6758|2024-08-06T01:43:37.713Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6735|2024-08-06T01:36:29.560Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6735</link>
      <description>An elevation of privilege vulnerability in the NVIDIA GPU driver in Android before 2016-11-05 could enable a local malicious application to execute arbitrary code within the context of the kernel. This issue is rated as Critical due to the possibility of a local permanent device compromise, which may require reflashing the operating system to repair the device. Android ID: A-30907701. References: NVIDIA N-CVE-2016-6735.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6735|2024-08-06T01:36:29.560Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-6709|2024-08-06T01:36:29.567Z -- google%20inc. -- android
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-6709</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability in Conscrypt and BoringSSL in Android 6.x before 2016-11-01 and 7.0 before 2016-11-01 could enable a man-in-the-middle attacker to gain access to sensitive information if a non-standard cipher suite is used by an application. This issue is rated as High because it could be used to access data without permission. Android ID: A-31081987.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-6709|2024-08-06T01:36:29.567Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
