<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for oretnom23 -- Fast Food Ordering System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oretnom23/fast%20food%20ordering%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for oretnom23 -- Fast Food Ordering System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 09:23:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2686|2024-08-03T00:46:03.705Z -- oretnom23 -- fast%20food%20ordering%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2686</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in oretnom23 Fast Food Ordering System. This affects an unknown part of the component Menu List Page. The manipulation of the argument Description leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-205725 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2686|2024-08-03T00:46:03.705Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 06:25:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3015|2024-08-03T00:52:59.893Z -- oretnom23 -- fast%20food%20ordering%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3015</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in oretnom23 Fast Food Ordering System. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file admin/?page=reports. The manipulation of the argument date leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The identifier VDB-207425 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3015|2024-08-03T00:52:59.893Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 09:05:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3012|2024-08-03T00:53:00.679Z -- oretnom23 -- fast%20food%20ordering%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3012</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in oretnom23 Fast Food Ordering System. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file ffos/admin/reports/index.php. The manipulation of the argument date leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-207422 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3012|2024-08-03T00:53:00.679Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 09:05:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
