<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for University of Central Florida -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/university%20of%20central%20florida/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for University of Central Florida -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:22:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4564|2024-08-03T01:41:45.598Z -- university%20of%20central%20florida -- materia
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4564</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in University of Central Florida Materia up to 9.0.0. This affects the function before of the file fuel/app/classes/controller/api.php of the component API Controller. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 9.0.1-alpha1 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is af259115d2e8f17068e61902151ee8a9dbac397b. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-215973 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in University of Central Florida Materia bis 9.0.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es die Funktion before der Datei fuel/app/classes/controller/api.php der Komponente API Controller. Durch Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross-site request forgery-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 9.0.1-alpha1 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als af259115d2e8f17068e61902151ee8a9dbac397b bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4564|2024-08-03T01:41:45.598Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
