<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for ISC -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/isc/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for ISC -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:25:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3137|2024-09-17T01:02:07.037Z -- isc -- bind%209
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3137</link>
      <description>Mistaken assumptions about the ordering of records in the answer section of a response containing CNAME or DNAME resource records could lead to a situation in which named would exit with an assertion failure when processing a response in which records occurred in an unusual order. Affects BIND 9.9.9-P6, 9.9.10b1-&gt;9.9.10rc1, 9.10.4-P6, 9.10.5b1-&gt;9.10.5rc1, 9.11.0-P3, 9.11.1b1-&gt;9.11.1rc1, and 9.9.9-S8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3137|2024-09-17T01:02:07.037Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6472|2024-09-17T03:58:54.278Z -- isc -- kea
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6472</link>
      <description>A packet containing a malformed DUID can cause the Kea DHCPv6 server process (kea-dhcp6) to exit due to an assertion failure. Versions affected: 1.4.0 to 1.5.0, 1.6.0-beta1, and 1.6.0-beta2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6472|2024-09-17T03:58:54.278Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 17:22:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6467|2024-09-17T00:11:15.675Z -- isc -- bind%209
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6467</link>
      <description>A programming error in the nxdomain-redirect feature can cause an assertion failure in query.c if the alternate namespace used by nxdomain-redirect is a descendant of a zone that is served locally. The most likely scenario where this might occur is if the server, in addition to performing NXDOMAIN redirection for recursive clients, is also serving a local copy of the root zone or using mirroring to provide the root zone, although other configurations are also possible. Versions affected: BIND 9.12.0-&gt; 9.12.4, 9.14.0. Also affects all releases in the 9.13 development branch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6467|2024-09-17T00:11:15.675Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 14:17:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8620|2024-09-17T01:40:34.573Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8620</link>
      <description>In BIND 9.15.6 -&gt; 9.16.5, 9.17.0 -&gt; 9.17.3, An attacker who can establish a TCP connection with the server and send data on that connection can exploit this to trigger the assertion failure, causing the server to exit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8620|2024-09-17T01:40:34.573Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 20:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5741|2024-09-17T02:26:39.095Z -- isc -- bind%209
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5741</link>
      <description>To provide fine-grained controls over the ability to use Dynamic DNS (DDNS) to update records in a zone, BIND 9 provides a feature called update-policy. Various rules can be configured to limit the types of updates that can be performed by a client, depending on the key used when sending the update request. Unfortunately, some rule types were not initially documented, and when documentation for them was added to the Administrator Reference Manual (ARM) in change #3112, the language that was added to the ARM at that time incorrectly described the behavior of two rule types, krb5-subdomain and ms-subdomain. This incorrect documentation could mislead operators into believing that policies they had configured were more restrictive than they actually were. This affects BIND versions prior to BIND 9.11.5 and BIND 9.12.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5741|2024-09-17T02:26:39.095Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6471|2024-09-17T01:56:17.224Z -- isc -- bind%209
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6471</link>
      <description>A race condition which may occur when discarding malformed packets can result in BIND exiting due to a REQUIRE assertion failure in dispatch.c. Versions affected: BIND 9.11.0 -&gt; 9.11.7, 9.12.0 -&gt; 9.12.4-P1, 9.14.0 -&gt; 9.14.2. Also all releases of the BIND 9.13 development branch and version 9.15.0 of the BIND 9.15 development branch and BIND Supported Preview Edition versions 9.11.3-S1 -&gt; 9.11.7-S1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6471|2024-09-17T01:56:17.224Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 14:17:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5734|2024-09-17T02:31:46.321Z -- isc -- bind%209
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5734</link>
      <description>While handling a particular type of malformed packet BIND erroneously selects a SERVFAIL rcode instead of a FORMERR rcode. If the receiving view has the SERVFAIL cache feature enabled, this can trigger an assertion failure in badcache.c when the request doesn't contain all of the expected information. Affects BIND 9.10.5-S1 to 9.10.5-S4, 9.10.6-S1, 9.10.6-S2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5734|2024-09-17T02:31:46.321Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2906|2024-09-17T03:39:00.585Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2906</link>
      <description>An attacker can leverage this flaw to gradually erode available memory to the point where named crashes for lack of resources. Upon restart the attacker would have to begin again, but nevertheless there is the potential to deny service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2906|2024-09-17T03:39:00.585Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 10:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8623|2024-09-17T03:19:11.433Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8623</link>
      <description>In BIND 9.10.0 -&gt; 9.11.21, 9.12.0 -&gt; 9.16.5, 9.17.0 -&gt; 9.17.3, also affects 9.10.5-S1 -&gt; 9.11.21-S1 of the BIND 9 Supported Preview Edition, An attacker that can reach a vulnerable system with a specially crafted query packet can trigger a crash. To be vulnerable, the system must: * be running BIND that was built with "--enable-native-pkcs11" * be signing one or more zones with an RSA key * be able to receive queries from a possible attacker</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8623|2024-09-17T03:19:11.433Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 20:50:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2881|2024-09-17T03:59:41.045Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2881</link>
      <description>The underlying bug might cause read past end of the buffer and either read memory it should not read, or crash the process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2881|2024-09-17T03:59:41.045Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 10:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3145|2024-09-17T00:10:46.349Z -- isc -- bind%209
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3145</link>
      <description>BIND was improperly sequencing cleanup operations on upstream recursion fetch contexts, leading in some cases to a use-after-free error that can trigger an assertion failure and crash in named. Affects BIND 9.0.0 to 9.8.x, 9.9.0 to 9.9.11, 9.10.0 to 9.10.6, 9.11.0 to 9.11.2, 9.9.3-S1 to 9.9.11-S1, 9.10.5-S1 to 9.10.6-S1, 9.12.0a1 to 9.12.0rc1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3145|2024-09-17T00:10:46.349Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5743|2024-09-17T02:26:38.493Z -- isc -- bind%209
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5743</link>
      <description>By design, BIND is intended to limit the number of TCP clients that can be connected at any given time. The number of allowed connections is a tunable parameter which, if unset, defaults to a conservative value for most servers. Unfortunately, the code which was intended to limit the number of simultaneous connections contained an error which could be exploited to grow the number of simultaneous connections beyond this limit. Versions affected: BIND 9.9.0 -&gt; 9.10.8-P1, 9.11.0 -&gt; 9.11.6, 9.12.0 -&gt; 9.12.4, 9.14.0. BIND 9 Supported Preview Edition versions 9.9.3-S1 -&gt; 9.11.5-S3, and 9.11.5-S5. Versions 9.13.0 -&gt; 9.13.7 of the 9.13 development branch are also affected. Versions prior to BIND 9.9.0 have not been evaluated for vulnerability to CVE-2018-5743.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5743|2024-09-17T02:26:38.493Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 14:17:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38177|2024-09-17T00:06:02.235Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38177</link>
      <description>By spoofing the target resolver with responses that have a malformed ECDSA signature, an attacker can trigger a small memory leak. It is possible to gradually erode available memory to the point where named crashes for lack of resources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38177|2024-09-17T00:06:02.235Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 10:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5733|2024-09-17T04:13:54.977Z -- isc -- isc%20dhcp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5733</link>
      <description>A malicious client which is allowed to send very large amounts of traffic (billions of packets) to a DHCP server can eventually overflow a 32-bit reference counter, potentially causing dhcpd to crash. Affects ISC DHCP 4.1.0 -&gt; 4.1-ESV-R15, 4.2.0 -&gt; 4.2.8, 4.3.0 -&gt; 4.3.6, 4.4.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5733|2024-09-17T04:13:54.977Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3136|2024-09-17T00:51:35.181Z -- isc -- bind%209
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3136</link>
      <description>A query with a specific set of characteristics could cause a server using DNS64 to encounter an assertion failure and terminate. An attacker could deliberately construct a query, enabling denial-of-service against a server if it was configured to use the DNS64 feature and other preconditions were met. Affects BIND 9.8.0 -&gt; 9.8.8-P1, 9.9.0 -&gt; 9.9.9-P6, 9.9.10b1-&gt;9.9.10rc1, 9.10.0 -&gt; 9.10.4-P6, 9.10.5b1-&gt;9.10.5rc1, 9.11.0 -&gt; 9.11.0-P3, 9.11.1b1-&gt;9.11.1rc1, 9.9.3-S1 -&gt; 9.9.9-S8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3136|2024-09-17T00:51:35.181Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-0635|2024-09-17T02:21:44.299Z -- isc -- bind
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-0635</link>
      <description>Versions affected: BIND 9.18.0 When a vulnerable version of named receives a series of specific queries, the named process will eventually terminate due to a failed assertion check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-0635|2024-09-17T02:21:44.299Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 11:55:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2928|2024-09-17T00:21:40.167Z -- isc -- isc%20dhcp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2928</link>
      <description>In ISC DHCP 4.4.0 -&gt; 4.4.3, ISC DHCP 4.1-ESV-R1 -&gt; 4.1-ESV-R16-P1, when the function option_code_hash_lookup() is called from add_option(), it increases the option's refcount field. However, there is not a corresponding call to option_dereference() to decrement the refcount field. The function add_option() is only used in server responses to lease query packets. Each lease query response calls this function for several options, so eventually, the reference counters could overflow and cause the server to abort.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2928|2024-09-17T00:21:40.167Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 04:45:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-1183|2024-09-17T04:00:26.575Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1183</link>
      <description>On vulnerable configurations, the named daemon may, in some circumstances, terminate with an assertion failure. Vulnerable configurations are those that include a reference to http within the listen-on statements in their named.conf. TLS is used by both DNS over TLS (DoT) and DNS over HTTPS (DoH), but configurations using DoT alone are unaffected. Affects BIND 9.18.0 -&gt; 9.18.2 and version 9.19.0 of the BIND 9.19 development branch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-1183|2024-09-17T04:00:26.575Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 09:55:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38178|2024-09-17T02:58:12.991Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38178</link>
      <description>By spoofing the target resolver with responses that have a malformed EdDSA signature, an attacker can trigger a small memory leak. It is possible to gradually erode available memory to the point where named crashes for lack of resources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38178|2024-09-17T02:58:12.991Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 10:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2795|2024-09-17T03:03:19.543Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2795</link>
      <description>By flooding the target resolver with queries exploiting this flaw an attacker can significantly impair the resolver's performance, effectively denying legitimate clients access to the DNS resolution service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2795|2024-09-17T03:03:19.543Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 10:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8619|2024-09-17T03:28:34.772Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8619</link>
      <description>In ISC BIND9 versions BIND 9.11.14 -&gt; 9.11.19, BIND 9.14.9 -&gt; 9.14.12, BIND 9.16.0 -&gt; 9.16.3, BIND Supported Preview Edition 9.11.14-S1 -&gt; 9.11.19-S1: Unless a nameserver is providing authoritative service for one or more zones and at least one zone contains an empty non-terminal entry containing an asterisk ("*") character, this defect cannot be encountered. A would-be attacker who is allowed to change zone content could theoretically introduce such a record in order to exploit this condition to cause denial of service, though we consider the use of this vector unlikely because any such attack would require a significant privilege level and be easily traceable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8619|2024-09-17T03:28:34.772Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 21:20:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3080|2024-09-17T01:56:40.440Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3080</link>
      <description>By sending specific queries to the resolver, an attacker can cause named to crash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3080|2024-09-17T01:56:40.440Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 10:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3140|2024-09-17T04:10:30.985Z -- isc -- bind%209
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3140</link>
      <description>If named is configured to use Response Policy Zones (RPZ) an error processing some rule types can lead to a condition where BIND will endlessly loop while handling a query. Affects BIND 9.9.10, 9.10.5, 9.11.0-&gt;9.11.1, 9.9.10-S1, 9.10.5-S1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3140|2024-09-17T04:10:30.985Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25214|2024-09-17T00:37:21.136Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25214</link>
      <description>In BIND 9.8.5 -&gt; 9.8.8, 9.9.3 -&gt; 9.11.29, 9.12.0 -&gt; 9.16.13, and versions BIND 9.9.3-S1 -&gt; 9.11.29-S1 and 9.16.8-S1 -&gt; 9.16.13-S1 of BIND 9 Supported Preview Edition, as well as release versions 9.17.0 -&gt; 9.17.11 of the BIND 9.17 development branch, when a vulnerable version of named receives a malformed IXFR triggering the flaw described above, the named process will terminate due to a failed assertion the next time the transferred secondary zone is refreshed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25214|2024-09-17T00:37:21.136Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 00:55:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25218|2024-09-17T03:07:43.591Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25218</link>
      <description>In BIND 9.16.19, 9.17.16. Also, version 9.16.19-S1 of BIND Supported Preview Edition When a vulnerable version of named receives a query under the circumstances described above, the named process will terminate due to a failed assertion check. The vulnerability affects only BIND 9 releases 9.16.19, 9.17.16, and release 9.16.19-S1 of the BIND Supported Preview Edition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25218|2024-09-17T03:07:43.591Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 18:20:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6469|2024-09-17T01:30:59.645Z -- isc -- bind%209%20supported%20preview%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6469</link>
      <description>An error in the EDNS Client Subnet (ECS) feature for recursive resolvers can cause BIND to exit with an assertion failure when processing a response that has malformed RRSIGs. Versions affected: BIND 9.10.5-S1 -&gt; 9.11.6-S1 of BIND 9 Supported Preview Edition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6469|2024-09-17T01:30:59.645Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 14:17:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5739|2024-09-17T02:11:49.386Z -- isc -- kea%20dhcp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5739</link>
      <description>An extension to hooks capabilities which debuted in Kea 1.4.0 introduced a memory leak for operators who are using certain hooks library facilities. In order to support multiple requests simultaneously, Kea 1.4 added a callout handle store but unfortunately the initial implementation of this store does not properly free memory in every case. Hooks which make use of query4 or query6 parameters in their callouts can leak memory, resulting in the eventual exhaustion of available memory and subsequent failure of the server process. Affects Kea DHCP 1.4.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5739|2024-09-17T02:11:49.386Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0760|2024-08-13T20:36:51.162Z -- isc -- bind%209</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0760</link>
      <description>A malicious client can send many DNS messages over TCP, potentially causing the server to become unstable while the attack is in progress. The server may recover after the attack ceases. Use of ACLs will not mitigate the attack. 
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.18.1 through 9.18.27, 9.19.0 through 9.19.24, and 9.18.11-S1 through 9.18.27-S1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0760|2024-08-13T20:36:51.162Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 14:26:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4076|2024-08-01T20:33:51.640Z -- isc -- bind%209</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4076</link>
      <description>Client queries that trigger serving stale data and that also require lookups in local authoritative zone data may result in an assertion failure.
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.16.13 through 9.16.50, 9.18.0 through 9.18.27, 9.19.0 through 9.19.24, 9.11.33-S1 through 9.11.37-S1, 9.16.13-S1 through 9.16.50-S1, and 9.18.11-S1 through 9.18.27-S1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4076|2024-08-01T20:33:51.640Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 14:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4076|2024-07-31T20:17:03.288Z -- isc -- bind%209</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4076</link>
      <description>Client queries that trigger serving stale data and that also require lookups in local authoritative zone data may result in an assertion failure.
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.16.13 through 9.16.50, 9.18.0 through 9.18.27, 9.19.0 through 9.19.24, 9.11.33-S1 through 9.11.37-S1, 9.16.13-S1 through 9.16.50-S1, and 9.18.11-S1 through 9.18.27-S1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4076|2024-07-31T20:17:03.288Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 14:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1737|2024-07-31T20:16:55.479Z -- isc -- bind%209</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1737</link>
      <description>Resolver caches and authoritative zone databases that hold significant numbers of RRs for the same hostname (of any RTYPE) can suffer from degraded performance as content is being added or updated, and also when handling client queries for this name.
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.11.0 through 9.11.37, 9.16.0 through 9.16.50, 9.18.0 through 9.18.27, 9.19.0 through 9.19.24, 9.11.4-S1 through 9.11.37-S1, 9.16.8-S1 through 9.16.50-S1, and 9.18.11-S1 through 9.18.27-S1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1737|2024-07-31T20:16:55.479Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 14:34:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1975|2024-07-31T20:16:56.440Z -- isc -- bind%209</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1975</link>
      <description>If a server hosts a zone containing a "KEY" Resource Record, or a resolver DNSSEC-validates a "KEY" Resource Record from a DNSSEC-signed domain in cache, a client can exhaust resolver CPU resources by sending a stream of SIG(0) signed requests.
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.0.0 through 9.11.37, 9.16.0 through 9.16.50, 9.18.0 through 9.18.27, 9.19.0 through 9.19.24, 9.9.3-S1 through 9.11.37-S1, 9.16.8-S1 through 9.16.49-S1, and 9.18.11-S1 through 9.18.27-S1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1975|2024-07-31T20:16:56.440Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 14:38:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0760|2024-07-31T20:16:54.511Z -- isc -- bind%209</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0760</link>
      <description>A malicious client can send many DNS messages over TCP, potentially causing the server to become unstable while the attack is in progress. The server may recover after the attack ceases. Use of ACLs will not mitigate the attack. 
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.18.1 through 9.18.27, 9.19.0 through 9.19.24, and 9.18.11-S1 through 9.18.27-S1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0760|2024-07-31T20:16:54.511Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 14:26:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1975|2024-07-24T20:08:56.485Z -- isc -- bind%209</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1975</link>
      <description>If a server hosts a zone containing a "KEY" Resource Record, or a resolver DNSSEC-validates a "KEY" Resource Record from a DNSSEC-signed domain in cache, a client can exhaust resolver CPU resources by sending a stream of SIG(0) signed requests.
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.0.0 through 9.11.37, 9.16.0 through 9.16.50, 9.18.0 through 9.18.27, 9.19.0 through 9.19.24, 9.9.3-S1 through 9.11.37-S1, 9.16.8-S1 through 9.16.49-S1, and 9.18.11-S1 through 9.18.27-S1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1975|2024-07-24T20:08:56.485Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 14:38:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1737|2024-07-23T20:43:33.244Z -- isc -- bind%209</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1737</link>
      <description>Resolver caches and authoritative zone databases that hold significant numbers of RRs for the same hostname (of any RTYPE) can suffer from degraded performance as content is being added or updated, and also when handling client queries for this name.
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.11.0 through 9.11.37, 9.16.0 through 9.16.50, 9.18.0 through 9.18.27, 9.19.0 through 9.19.24, 9.11.4-S1 through 9.11.37-S1, 9.16.8-S1 through 9.16.50-S1, and 9.18.11-S1 through 9.18.27-S1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1737|2024-07-23T20:43:33.244Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 14:34:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4076|2024-07-23T14:40:57.256Z -- isc -- bind%209</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4076</link>
      <description>Client queries that trigger serving stale data and that also require lookups in local authoritative zone data may result in an assertion failure.
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.16.13 through 9.16.50, 9.18.0 through 9.18.27, 9.19.0 through 9.19.24, 9.11.33-S1 through 9.11.37-S1, 9.16.13-S1 through 9.16.50-S1, and 9.18.11-S1 through 9.18.27-S1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4076|2024-07-23T14:40:57.256Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 14:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0760|2024-07-23T14:26:54.983Z -- isc -- bind%209</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0760</link>
      <description>A malicious client can send many DNS messages over TCP, potentially causing the server to become unstable while the attack is in progress. The server may recover after the attack ceases. Use of ACLs will not mitigate the attack. 
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.18.1 through 9.18.27, 9.19.0 through 9.19.24, and 9.18.11-S1 through 9.18.27-S1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0760|2024-07-23T14:26:54.983Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 14:26:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1737|2024-07-23T14:34:09.750Z -- isc -- bind%209</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1737</link>
      <description>Resolver caches and authoritative zone databases that hold significant numbers of RRs for the same hostname (of any RTYPE) can suffer from degraded performance as content is being added or updated, and also when handling client queries for this name.
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.11.0 through 9.11.37, 9.16.0 through 9.16.50, 9.18.0 through 9.18.27, 9.19.0 through 9.19.24, 9.11.4-S1 through 9.11.37-S1, 9.16.8-S1 through 9.16.50-S1, and 9.18.11-S1 through 9.18.27-S1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1737|2024-07-23T14:34:09.750Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 14:34:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1975|2024-07-23T14:38:57.143Z -- isc -- bind%209</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1975</link>
      <description>If a server hosts a zone containing a "KEY" Resource Record, or a resolver DNSSEC-validates a "KEY" Resource Record from a DNSSEC-signed domain in cache, a client can exhaust resolver CPU resources by sending a stream of SIG(0) signed requests.
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.0.0 through 9.11.37, 9.16.0 through 9.16.50, 9.18.0 through 9.18.27, 9.19.0 through 9.19.24, 9.9.3-S1 through 9.11.37-S1, 9.16.8-S1 through 9.16.49-S1, and 9.18.11-S1 through 9.18.27-S1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1975|2024-07-23T14:38:57.143Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 14:38:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28872|2024-07-11T14:49:12.156Z -- isc -- stork</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28872</link>
      <description>The TLS certificate validation code is flawed. An attacker can obtain a TLS certificate from the Stork server and use it to connect to the Stork agent. Once this connection is established with the valid certificate, the attacker can send malicious commands to a monitored service (Kea or BIND 9), possibly resulting in confidential data loss and/or denial of service. It should be noted that this vulnerability is not related to BIND 9 or Kea directly, and only customers using the Stork management tool are potentially affected.
This issue affects Stork versions 0.15.0 through 1.15.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28872|2024-07-11T14:49:12.156Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 14:49:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28872|2024-07-11T15:17:39.200Z -- isc -- stork</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28872</link>
      <description>The TLS certificate validation code is flawed. An attacker can obtain a TLS certificate from the Stork server and use it to connect to the Stork agent. Once this connection is established with the valid certificate, the attacker can send malicious commands to a monitored service (Kea or BIND 9), possibly resulting in confidential data loss and/or denial of service. It should be noted that this vulnerability is not related to BIND 9 or Kea directly, and only customers using the Stork management tool are potentially affected.
This issue affects Stork versions 0.15.0 through 1.15.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28872|2024-07-11T15:17:39.200Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 14:49:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0760|2024-07-23T16:13:05.915Z -- isc -- bind%209</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0760</link>
      <description>A malicious client can send many DNS messages over TCP, potentially causing the server to become unstable while the attack is in progress. The server may recover after the attack ceases. Use of ACLs will not mitigate the attack. 
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.18.1 through 9.18.27, 9.19.0 through 9.19.24, and 9.18.11-S1 through 9.18.27-S1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0760|2024-07-23T16:13:05.915Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 14:26:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4076|2024-07-24T18:47:06.657Z -- isc -- bind%209</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4076</link>
      <description>Client queries that trigger serving stale data and that also require lookups in local authoritative zone data may result in an assertion failure.
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.16.13 through 9.16.50, 9.18.0 through 9.18.27, 9.19.0 through 9.19.24, 9.11.33-S1 through 9.11.37-S1, 9.16.13-S1 through 9.16.50-S1, and 9.18.11-S1 through 9.18.27-S1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4076|2024-07-24T18:47:06.657Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 14:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1737|2024-07-26T17:35:12.133Z -- isc -- bind%209</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1737</link>
      <description>Resolver caches and authoritative zone databases that hold significant numbers of RRs for the same hostname (of any RTYPE) can suffer from degraded performance as content is being added or updated, and also when handling client queries for this name.
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.11.0 through 9.11.37, 9.16.0 through 9.16.50, 9.18.0 through 9.18.27, 9.19.0 through 9.19.24, 9.11.4-S1 through 9.11.37-S1, 9.16.8-S1 through 9.16.50-S1, and 9.18.11-S1 through 9.18.27-S1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1737|2024-07-26T17:35:12.133Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 14:34:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0760|2024-08-01T18:18:18.515Z -- isc -- bind%209</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0760</link>
      <description>A malicious client can send many DNS messages over TCP, potentially causing the server to become unstable while the attack is in progress. The server may recover after the attack ceases. Use of ACLs will not mitigate the attack. 
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.18.1 through 9.18.27, 9.19.0 through 9.19.24, and 9.18.11-S1 through 9.18.27-S1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0760|2024-08-01T18:18:18.515Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 14:26:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1975|2024-08-01T18:56:22.635Z -- isc -- bind%209</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1975</link>
      <description>If a server hosts a zone containing a "KEY" Resource Record, or a resolver DNSSEC-validates a "KEY" Resource Record from a DNSSEC-signed domain in cache, a client can exhaust resolver CPU resources by sending a stream of SIG(0) signed requests.
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.0.0 through 9.11.37, 9.16.0 through 9.16.50, 9.18.0 through 9.18.27, 9.19.0 through 9.19.24, 9.9.3-S1 through 9.11.37-S1, 9.16.8-S1 through 9.16.49-S1, and 9.18.11-S1 through 9.18.27-S1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1975|2024-08-01T18:56:22.635Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 14:38:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1737|2024-08-01T18:48:21.779Z -- isc -- bind%209</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1737</link>
      <description>Resolver caches and authoritative zone databases that hold significant numbers of RRs for the same hostname (of any RTYPE) can suffer from degraded performance as content is being added or updated, and also when handling client queries for this name.
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.11.0 through 9.11.37, 9.16.0 through 9.16.50, 9.18.0 through 9.18.27, 9.19.0 through 9.19.24, 9.11.4-S1 through 9.11.37-S1, 9.16.8-S1 through 9.16.50-S1, and 9.18.11-S1 through 9.18.27-S1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1737|2024-08-01T18:48:21.779Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 14:34:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28872|2024-08-02T00:56:58.413Z -- isc -- stork</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28872</link>
      <description>The TLS certificate validation code is flawed. An attacker can obtain a TLS certificate from the Stork server and use it to connect to the Stork agent. Once this connection is established with the valid certificate, the attacker can send malicious commands to a monitored service (Kea or BIND 9), possibly resulting in confidential data loss and/or denial of service. It should be noted that this vulnerability is not related to BIND 9 or Kea directly, and only customers using the Stork management tool are potentially affected.
This issue affects Stork versions 0.15.0 through 1.15.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28872|2024-08-02T00:56:58.413Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 14:49:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
