<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for ISC -- BIND9</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/isc/bind9.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for ISC -- BIND9</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 15:22:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8620|2024-08-04T10:03:46.233Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8620</link>
      <description>In BIND 9.15.6 -&gt; 9.16.5, 9.17.0 -&gt; 9.17.3, An attacker who can establish a TCP connection with the server and send data on that connection can exploit this to trigger the assertion failure, causing the server to exit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8620|2024-08-04T10:03:46.233Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8622|2024-08-04T10:03:46.256Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8622</link>
      <description>In BIND 9.0.0 -&gt; 9.11.21, 9.12.0 -&gt; 9.16.5, 9.17.0 -&gt; 9.17.3, also affects 9.9.3-S1 -&gt; 9.11.21-S1 of the BIND 9 Supported Preview Edition, An attacker on the network path for a TSIG-signed request, or operating the server receiving the TSIG-signed request, could send a truncated response to that request, triggering an assertion failure, causing the server to exit. Alternately, an off-path attacker would have to correctly guess when a TSIG-signed request was sent, along with other characteristics of the packet and message, and spoof a truncated response to trigger an assertion failure, causing the server to exit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8622|2024-08-04T10:03:46.256Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8619|2024-08-04T10:03:46.317Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8619</link>
      <description>In ISC BIND9 versions BIND 9.11.14 -&gt; 9.11.19, BIND 9.14.9 -&gt; 9.14.12, BIND 9.16.0 -&gt; 9.16.3, BIND Supported Preview Edition 9.11.14-S1 -&gt; 9.11.19-S1: Unless a nameserver is providing authoritative service for one or more zones and at least one zone contains an empty non-terminal entry containing an asterisk ("*") character, this defect cannot be encountered. A would-be attacker who is allowed to change zone content could theoretically introduce such a record in order to exploit this condition to cause denial of service, though we consider the use of this vector unlikely because any such attack would require a significant privilege level and be easily traceable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8619|2024-08-04T10:03:46.317Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8618|2024-08-04T10:03:46.364Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8618</link>
      <description>An attacker who is permitted to send zone data to a server via zone transfer can exploit this to intentionally trigger the assertion failure with a specially constructed zone, denying service to clients.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8618|2024-08-04T10:03:46.364Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8621|2024-08-04T10:03:46.261Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8621</link>
      <description>In BIND 9.14.0 -&gt; 9.16.5, 9.17.0 -&gt; 9.17.3, If a server is configured with both QNAME minimization and 'forward first' then an attacker who can send queries to it may be able to trigger the condition that will cause the server to crash. Servers that 'forward only' are not affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8621|2024-08-04T10:03:46.261Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8625|2024-08-04T10:03:46.290Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8625</link>
      <description>BIND servers are vulnerable if they are running an affected version and are configured to use GSS-TSIG features. In a configuration which uses BIND's default settings the vulnerable code path is not exposed, but a server can be rendered vulnerable by explicitly setting valid values for the tkey-gssapi-keytab or tkey-gssapi-credentialconfiguration options. Although the default configuration is not vulnerable, GSS-TSIG is frequently used in networks where BIND is integrated with Samba, as well as in mixed-server environments that combine BIND servers with Active Directory domain controllers. The most likely outcome of a successful exploitation of the vulnerability is a crash of the named process. However, remote code execution, while unproven, is theoretically possible. Affects: BIND 9.5.0 -&gt; 9.11.27, 9.12.0 -&gt; 9.16.11, and versions BIND 9.11.3-S1 -&gt; 9.11.27-S1 and 9.16.8-S1 -&gt; 9.16.11-S1 of BIND Supported Preview Edition. Also release versions 9.17.0 -&gt; 9.17.1 of the BIND 9.17 development branch</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8625|2024-08-04T10:03:46.290Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8623|2024-08-04T10:03:46.191Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8623</link>
      <description>In BIND 9.10.0 -&gt; 9.11.21, 9.12.0 -&gt; 9.16.5, 9.17.0 -&gt; 9.17.3, also affects 9.10.5-S1 -&gt; 9.11.21-S1 of the BIND 9 Supported Preview Edition, An attacker that can reach a vulnerable system with a specially crafted query packet can trigger a crash. To be vulnerable, the system must: * be running BIND that was built with "--enable-native-pkcs11" * be signing one or more zones with an RSA key * be able to receive queries from a possible attacker</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8623|2024-08-04T10:03:46.191Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8624|2024-08-04T10:03:46.258Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8624</link>
      <description>In BIND 9.9.12 -&gt; 9.9.13, 9.10.7 -&gt; 9.10.8, 9.11.3 -&gt; 9.11.21, 9.12.1 -&gt; 9.16.5, 9.17.0 -&gt; 9.17.3, also affects 9.9.12-S1 -&gt; 9.9.13-S1, 9.11.3-S1 -&gt; 9.11.21-S1 of the BIND 9 Supported Preview Edition, An attacker who has been granted privileges to change a specific subset of the zone's content could abuse these unintended additional privileges to update other contents of the zone.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8624|2024-08-04T10:03:46.258Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8617|2024-08-04T10:03:46.366Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8617</link>
      <description>Using a specially-crafted message, an attacker may potentially cause a BIND server to reach an inconsistent state if the attacker knows (or successfully guesses) the name of a TSIG key used by the server. Since BIND, by default, configures a local session key even on servers whose configuration does not otherwise make use of it, almost all current BIND servers are vulnerable. In releases of BIND dating from March 2018 and after, an assertion check in tsig.c detects this inconsistent state and deliberately exits. Prior to the introduction of the check the server would continue operating in an inconsistent state, with potentially harmful results.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8617|2024-08-04T10:03:46.366Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8616|2024-08-04T10:03:46.371Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8616</link>
      <description>A malicious actor who intentionally exploits this lack of effective limitation on the number of fetches performed when processing referrals can, through the use of specially crafted referrals, cause a recursing server to issue a very large number of fetches in an attempt to process the referral. This has at least two potential effects: The performance of the recursing server can potentially be degraded by the additional work required to perform these fetches, and The attacker can exploit this behavior to use the recursing server as a reflector in a reflection attack with a high amplification factor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8616|2024-08-04T10:03:46.371Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
