<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for ISC -- BIND9</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/isc/bind9.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for ISC -- BIND9</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 19:20:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6477|2024-09-16T16:47:45.899Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6477</link>
      <description>With pipelining enabled each incoming query on a TCP connection requires a similar resource allocation to a query received via UDP or via TCP without pipelining enabled. A client using a TCP-pipelined connection to a server could consume more resources than the server has been provisioned to handle. When a TCP connection with a large number of pipelined queries is closed, the load on the server releasing these multiple resources can cause it to become unresponsive, even for queries that can be answered authoritatively or from cache. (This is most likely to be perceived as an intermittent server problem).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6477|2024-09-16T16:47:45.899Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 16:11:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8621|2024-09-16T16:18:00.777Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8621</link>
      <description>In BIND 9.14.0 -&gt; 9.16.5, 9.17.0 -&gt; 9.17.3, If a server is configured with both QNAME minimization and 'forward first' then an attacker who can send queries to it may be able to trigger the condition that will cause the server to crash. Servers that 'forward only' are not affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8621|2024-09-16T16:18:00.777Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 20:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8622|2024-09-16T17:14:14.760Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8622</link>
      <description>In BIND 9.0.0 -&gt; 9.11.21, 9.12.0 -&gt; 9.16.5, 9.17.0 -&gt; 9.17.3, also affects 9.9.3-S1 -&gt; 9.11.21-S1 of the BIND 9 Supported Preview Edition, An attacker on the network path for a TSIG-signed request, or operating the server receiving the TSIG-signed request, could send a truncated response to that request, triggering an assertion failure, causing the server to exit. Alternately, an off-path attacker would have to correctly guess when a TSIG-signed request was sent, along with other characteristics of the packet and message, and spoof a truncated response to trigger an assertion failure, causing the server to exit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8622|2024-09-16T17:14:14.760Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 20:50:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25219|2024-09-16T17:33:38.865Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25219</link>
      <description>In BIND 9.3.0 -&gt; 9.11.35, 9.12.0 -&gt; 9.16.21, and versions 9.9.3-S1 -&gt; 9.11.35-S1 and 9.16.8-S1 -&gt; 9.16.21-S1 of BIND Supported Preview Edition, as well as release versions 9.17.0 -&gt; 9.17.18 of the BIND 9.17 development branch, exploitation of broken authoritative servers using a flaw in response processing can cause degradation in BIND resolver performance. The way the lame cache is currently designed makes it possible for its internal data structures to grow almost infinitely, which may cause significant delays in client query processing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25219|2024-09-16T17:33:38.865Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 21:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8624|2024-09-16T17:52:52.920Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8624</link>
      <description>In BIND 9.9.12 -&gt; 9.9.13, 9.10.7 -&gt; 9.10.8, 9.11.3 -&gt; 9.11.21, 9.12.1 -&gt; 9.16.5, 9.17.0 -&gt; 9.17.3, also affects 9.9.12-S1 -&gt; 9.9.13-S1, 9.11.3-S1 -&gt; 9.11.21-S1 of the BIND 9 Supported Preview Edition, An attacker who has been granted privileges to change a specific subset of the zone's content could abuse these unintended additional privileges to update other contents of the zone.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8624|2024-09-16T17:52:52.920Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 20:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
