<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for ISC -- BIND9</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/isc/bind9.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for ISC -- BIND9</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 21:21:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25219|2024-08-03T19:56:11.060Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25219</link>
      <description>In BIND 9.3.0 -&gt; 9.11.35, 9.12.0 -&gt; 9.16.21, and versions 9.9.3-S1 -&gt; 9.11.35-S1 and 9.16.8-S1 -&gt; 9.16.21-S1 of BIND Supported Preview Edition, as well as release versions 9.17.0 -&gt; 9.17.18 of the BIND 9.17 development branch, exploitation of broken authoritative servers using a flaw in response processing can cause degradation in BIND resolver performance. The way the lame cache is currently designed makes it possible for its internal data structures to grow almost infinitely, which may cause significant delays in client query processing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25219|2024-08-03T19:56:11.060Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25214|2024-08-03T19:56:11.064Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25214</link>
      <description>In BIND 9.8.5 -&gt; 9.8.8, 9.9.3 -&gt; 9.11.29, 9.12.0 -&gt; 9.16.13, and versions BIND 9.9.3-S1 -&gt; 9.11.29-S1 and 9.16.8-S1 -&gt; 9.16.13-S1 of BIND 9 Supported Preview Edition, as well as release versions 9.17.0 -&gt; 9.17.11 of the BIND 9.17 development branch, when a vulnerable version of named receives a malformed IXFR triggering the flaw described above, the named process will terminate due to a failed assertion the next time the transferred secondary zone is refreshed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25214|2024-08-03T19:56:11.064Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3080|2024-08-03T01:00:10.486Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3080</link>
      <description>By sending specific queries to the resolver, an attacker can cause named to crash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3080|2024-08-03T01:00:10.486Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38177|2024-08-03T10:45:52.975Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38177</link>
      <description>By spoofing the target resolver with responses that have a malformed ECDSA signature, an attacker can trigger a small memory leak. It is possible to gradually erode available memory to the point where named crashes for lack of resources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38177|2024-08-03T10:45:52.975Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25216|2024-08-03T19:56:11.090Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25216</link>
      <description>In BIND 9.5.0 -&gt; 9.11.29, 9.12.0 -&gt; 9.16.13, and versions BIND 9.11.3-S1 -&gt; 9.11.29-S1 and 9.16.8-S1 -&gt; 9.16.13-S1 of BIND Supported Preview Edition, as well as release versions 9.17.0 -&gt; 9.17.1 of the BIND 9.17 development branch, BIND servers are vulnerable if they are running an affected version and are configured to use GSS-TSIG features. In a configuration which uses BIND's default settings the vulnerable code path is not exposed, but a server can be rendered vulnerable by explicitly setting values for the tkey-gssapi-keytab or tkey-gssapi-credential configuration options. Although the default configuration is not vulnerable, GSS-TSIG is frequently used in networks where BIND is integrated with Samba, as well as in mixed-server environments that combine BIND servers with Active Directory domain controllers. For servers that meet these conditions, the ISC SPNEGO implementation is vulnerable to various attacks, depending on the CPU architecture for which BIND was built: For named binaries compiled for 64-bit platforms, this flaw can be used to trigger a buffer over-read, leading to a server crash. For named binaries compiled for 32-bit platforms, this flaw can be used to trigger a server crash due to a buffer overflow and possibly also to achieve remote code execution. We have determined that standard SPNEGO implementations are available in the MIT and Heimdal Kerberos libraries, which support a broad range of operating systems, rendering the ISC implementation unnecessary and obsolete. Therefore, to reduce the attack surface for BIND users, we will be removing the ISC SPNEGO implementation in the April releases of BIND 9.11 and 9.16 (it had already been dropped from BIND 9.17). We would not normally remove something from a stable ESV (Extended Support Version) of BIND, but since system libraries can replace the ISC SPNEGO implementation, we have made an exception in this case for reasons of stability and security.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25216|2024-08-03T19:56:11.090Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38178|2024-08-03T10:45:52.980Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38178</link>
      <description>By spoofing the target resolver with responses that have a malformed EdDSA signature, an attacker can trigger a small memory leak. It is possible to gradually erode available memory to the point where named crashes for lack of resources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38178|2024-08-03T10:45:52.980Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25215|2024-08-03T19:56:11.110Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25215</link>
      <description>In BIND 9.0.0 -&gt; 9.11.29, 9.12.0 -&gt; 9.16.13, and versions BIND 9.9.3-S1 -&gt; 9.11.29-S1 and 9.16.8-S1 -&gt; 9.16.13-S1 of BIND Supported Preview Edition, as well as release versions 9.17.0 -&gt; 9.17.11 of the BIND 9.17 development branch, when a vulnerable version of named receives a query for a record triggering the flaw described above, the named process will terminate due to a failed assertion check. The vulnerability affects all currently maintained BIND 9 branches (9.11, 9.11-S, 9.16, 9.16-S, 9.17) as well as all other versions of BIND 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25215|2024-08-03T19:56:11.110Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2795|2024-08-03T00:46:04.433Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2795</link>
      <description>By flooding the target resolver with queries exploiting this flaw an attacker can significantly impair the resolver's performance, effectively denying legitimate clients access to the DNS resolution service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2795|2024-08-03T00:46:04.433Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2906|2024-08-03T00:52:59.888Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2906</link>
      <description>An attacker can leverage this flaw to gradually erode available memory to the point where named crashes for lack of resources. Upon restart the attacker would have to begin again, but nevertheless there is the potential to deny service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2906|2024-08-03T00:52:59.888Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2881|2024-08-03T00:53:00.479Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2881</link>
      <description>The underlying bug might cause read past end of the buffer and either read memory it should not read, or crash the process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2881|2024-08-03T00:53:00.479Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25218|2024-08-03T19:56:11.055Z -- isc -- bind9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25218</link>
      <description>In BIND 9.16.19, 9.17.16. Also, version 9.16.19-S1 of BIND Supported Preview Edition When a vulnerable version of named receives a query under the circumstances described above, the named process will terminate due to a failed assertion check. The vulnerability affects only BIND 9 releases 9.16.19, 9.17.16, and release 9.16.19-S1 of the BIND Supported Preview Edition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25218|2024-08-03T19:56:11.055Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
