<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for AiLux -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ailux/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for AiLux -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 17:21:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-45592|2024-07-23T16:13:58.851Z -- ailux -- imx6%20bundle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45592</link>
      <description>A CWE-250 “Execution with Unnecessary Privileges” vulnerability in the embedded Chromium browser (due to the binary being executed with the “--no-sandbox” option and with root privileges) exacerbates the impacts of successful attacks executed against the browser. This issue affects: AiLux imx6 bundle below version imx6_1.0.7-2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-45592|2024-07-23T16:13:58.851Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 11:22:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-45592|2024-03-05T11:22:14.789Z -- ailux -- imx6%20bundle</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-45592</link>
      <description>A CWE-250 “Execution with Unnecessary Privileges” vulnerability in the embedded Chromium browser (due to the binary being executed with the “--no-sandbox” option and with root privileges) exacerbates the impacts of successful attacks executed against the browser. This issue affects: AiLux imx6 bundle below version imx6_1.0.7-2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-45592|2024-03-05T11:22:14.789Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 11:22:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-45593|2024-03-05T11:27:46.837Z -- ailux -- imx6%20bundle</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-45593</link>
      <description>A CWE-693 “Protection Mechanism Failure” vulnerability in the embedded Chromium browser (concerning the handling of alternative URLs, other than “ http://localhost” http://localhost” ) allows a physical attacker to read arbitrary files on the file system, alter the configuration of the embedded browser, and have other unspecified impacts to the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the device. This issue affects: AiLux imx6 bundle below version imx6_1.0.7-2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-45593|2024-03-05T11:27:46.837Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 11:27:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-45598|2024-03-05T11:33:24.233Z -- ailux -- imx6%20bundle</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-45598</link>
      <description>A CWE-862 “Missing Authorization” vulnerability in the “measure” functionality of the web application allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to access confidential measure information. This issue affects: AiLux imx6 bundle below version imx6_1.0.7-2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-45598|2024-03-05T11:33:24.233Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 11:33:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-45594|2024-03-05T11:28:38.333Z -- ailux -- imx6%20bundle</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-45594</link>
      <description>A CWE-552 “Files or Directories Accessible to External Parties” vulnerability in the embedded Chromium browser allows a physical attacker to arbitrarily download/upload files to/from the file system, with unspecified impacts to the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the device. This issue affects: AiLux imx6 bundle below version imx6_1.0.7-2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-45594|2024-03-05T11:28:38.333Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 11:28:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-45595|2024-03-05T11:29:58.832Z -- ailux -- imx6%20bundle</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-45595</link>
      <description>A CWE-434 “Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type” vulnerability in the “file_configuration” functionality of the web application allows a remote authenticated attacker to upload any arbitrary type of file into the device. This issue affects: AiLux imx6 bundle below version imx6_1.0.7-2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-45595|2024-03-05T11:29:58.832Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 11:29:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-45599|2024-03-05T11:34:38.752Z -- ailux -- imx6%20bundle</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-45599</link>
      <description>A CWE-646 “Reliance on File Name or Extension of Externally-Supplied File” vulnerability in the “iec61850” functionality of the web application allows a remote authenticated attacker to upload any arbitrary type of file into the device. This issue affects: AiLux imx6 bundle below version imx6_1.0.7-2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-45599|2024-03-05T11:34:38.752Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 11:34:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-45596|2024-06-04T17:20:00.741Z -- ailux -- imx6%20bundle</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-45596</link>
      <description>A CWE-862 “Missing Authorization” vulnerability in the “file_configuration” functionality of the web application allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to access confidential configuration files. This issue affects: AiLux imx6 bundle below version imx6_1.0.7-2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-45596|2024-06-04T17:20:00.741Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 11:31:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-45597|2024-03-05T11:32:18.971Z -- ailux -- imx6%20bundle</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-45597</link>
      <description>A CWE-1236 “Improper Neutralization of Formula Elements in a CSV File” vulnerability in the “file_configuration” functionality of the web application (concerning the function “export_file”) allows a remote authenticated attacker to inject arbitrary formulas inside generated CSV files. This issue affects: AiLux imx6 bundle below version imx6_1.0.7-2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-45597|2024-03-05T11:32:18.971Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 11:32:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-45591|2024-03-05T11:19:46.198Z -- ailux -- imx6%20bundle</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-45591</link>
      <description>A CWE-122 “Heap-based Buffer Overflow” vulnerability in the “logger_generic” function of the “Ax_rtu” binary allows a remote authenticated attacker to trigger a memory corruption in the context of the binary. This may result in a Denial-of-Service (DoS) condition, possibly in the execution of arbitrary code with the same privileges of the process (root), or have other unspecified impacts on the device. This issue affects: AiLux imx6 bundle below version imx6_1.0.7-2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-45591|2024-03-05T11:19:46.198Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 11:19:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-45600|2024-03-05T11:35:39.567Z -- ailux -- imx6%20bundle</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-45600</link>
      <description>A CWE-613 “Insufficient Session Expiration” vulnerability in the web application, due to the session cookie “sessionid” lasting two weeks, facilitates session hijacking attacks against victims. This issue affects: AiLux imx6 bundle below version imx6_1.0.7-2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-45600|2024-03-05T11:35:39.567Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 11:35:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5456|2024-03-05T11:10:44.986Z -- ailux -- imx6%20bundle</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5456</link>
      <description>A CWE-798 “Use of Hard-coded Credentials” vulnerability in the MariaDB database of the web application allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to access the database service and all included data with the same privileges of the web application. This issue affects: AiLux imx6 bundle below version imx6_1.0.7-2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5456|2024-03-05T11:10:44.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 11:10:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5457|2024-03-05T11:15:01.811Z -- ailux -- imx6%20bundle</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5457</link>
      <description>A CWE-1269 “Product Released in Non-Release Configuration” vulnerability in the Django web framework used by the web application (due to the “debug” configuration parameter set to “True”) allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to access critical information and have other unspecified impacts to the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the application. This issue affects: AiLux imx6 bundle below version imx6_1.0.7-2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5457|2024-03-05T11:15:01.811Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 11:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
