<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Corveda -- PHPSandbox</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/corveda/phpsandbox.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Corveda -- PHPSandbox</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 18:24:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-125107|2024-08-06T14:10:56.666Z -- corveda -- phpsandbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125107</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Corveda PHPSandbox 1.3.4 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component String Handler. The manipulation leads to protection mechanism failure. The attack may be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 1.3.5 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as 48fde5ffa4d76014bad260a3cbab7ada3744a4cc. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-248270 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Corveda PHPSandbox 1.3.4 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Komponente String Handler. Dank der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine protection mechanism failure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 1.3.5 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als 48fde5ffa4d76014bad260a3cbab7ada3744a4cc bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-125107|2024-08-06T14:10:56.666Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 02:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
