<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Kaspersky -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/kaspersky/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Kaspersky -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 08:24:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15684|2024-08-05T00:56:22.379Z -- kaspersky -- kaspersky%20protection%20extension%20for%20google%20chrome
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15684</link>
      <description>Kaspersky Protection extension for web browser Google Chrome prior to 30.112.62.0 was vulnerable to unauthorized access to its features remotely that could lead to removing other installed extensions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15684|2024-08-05T00:56:22.379Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 16:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15685|2024-08-05T00:56:22.456Z -- kaspersky -- kaspersky%20anti-virus%2C%20kaspersky%20internet%20security%2C%20kaspersky%20total%20security%2C%20kaspersky%20free%20anti-virus%2C%20kaspersky%20small%20office%20security%2C%20kaspersky%20security%20cloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15685</link>
      <description>Kaspersky Anti-Virus, Kaspersky Internet Security, Kaspersky Total Security, Kaspersky Free Anti-Virus, Kaspersky Small Office Security, Kaspersky Security Cloud up to 2020, the web protection component allowed an attacker remotely disable such product's security features as private browsing and anti-banner. Bypass.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15685|2024-08-05T00:56:22.456Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 15:44:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15691|2024-08-05T00:56:22.245Z -- kaspersky -- tigervnc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15691</link>
      <description>TigerVNC version prior to 1.10.1 is vulnerable to stack use-after-return, which occurs due to incorrect usage of stack memory in ZRLEDecoder. If decoding routine would throw an exception, ZRLEDecoder may try to access stack variable, which has been already freed during the process of stack unwinding. Exploitation of this vulnerability could potentially result into remote code execution. This attack appear to be exploitable via network connectivity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15691|2024-08-05T00:56:22.245Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 14:52:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15681|2024-08-05T00:56:22.452Z -- kaspersky -- libvnc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15681</link>
      <description>LibVNC commit before d01e1bb4246323ba6fcee3b82ef1faa9b1dac82a contains a memory leak (CWE-655) in VNC server code, which allow an attacker to read stack memory and can be abused for information disclosure. Combined with another vulnerability, it can be used to leak stack memory and bypass ASLR. This attack appear to be exploitable via network connectivity. These vulnerabilities have been fixed in commit d01e1bb4246323ba6fcee3b82ef1faa9b1dac82a.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15681|2024-08-05T00:56:22.452Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 16:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15695|2024-08-05T00:56:22.455Z -- kaspersky -- tigervnc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15695</link>
      <description>TigerVNC version prior to 1.10.1 is vulnerable to stack buffer overflow, which could be triggered from CMsgReader::readSetCursor. This vulnerability occurs due to insufficient sanitization of PixelFormat. Since remote attacker can choose offset from start of the buffer to start writing his values, exploitation of this vulnerability could potentially result into remote code execution. This attack appear to be exploitable via network connectivity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15695|2024-08-05T00:56:22.455Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 15:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15678|2024-08-05T00:56:22.434Z -- kaspersky -- tightvnc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15678</link>
      <description>TightVNC code version 1.3.10 contains heap buffer overflow in rfbServerCutText handler, which can potentially result code execution.. This attack appear to be exploitable via network connectivity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15678|2024-08-05T00:56:22.434Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 16:44:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15688|2024-08-05T00:56:22.438Z -- kaspersky -- kaspersky%20anti-virus%2C%20kaspersky%20internet%20security%2C%20kaspersky%20total%20security%2C%20kaspersky%20free%20anti-virus%2C%20kaspersky%20small%20office%20security%2C%20kaspersky%20security%20cloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15688</link>
      <description>Kaspersky Anti-Virus, Kaspersky Internet Security, Kaspersky Total Security, Kaspersky Free Anti-Virus, Kaspersky Small Office Security, Kaspersky Security Cloud up to 2020, the web protection component did not adequately inform the user about the threat of redirecting to an untrusted site. Bypass.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15688|2024-08-05T00:56:22.438Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 15:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15686|2024-08-05T00:56:22.047Z -- kaspersky -- kaspersky%20anti-virus%2C%20kaspersky%20internet%20security%2C%20kaspersky%20total%20security%2C%20kaspersky%20free%20anti-virus%2C%20kaspersky%20small%20office%20security%2C%20kaspersky%20security%20cloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15686</link>
      <description>Kaspersky Anti-Virus, Kaspersky Internet Security, Kaspersky Total Security, Kaspersky Free Anti-Virus, Kaspersky Small Office Security, Kaspersky Security Cloud up to 2020, the web protection component allowed an attacker remotely disable various anti-virus protection features. DoS, Bypass.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15686|2024-08-05T00:56:22.047Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 15:44:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15692|2024-08-05T00:56:22.409Z -- kaspersky -- tigervnc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15692</link>
      <description>TigerVNC version prior to 1.10.1 is vulnerable to heap buffer overflow. Vulnerability could be triggered from CopyRectDecoder due to incorrect value checks. Exploitation of this vulnerability could potentially result into remote code execution. This attack appear to be exploitable via network connectivity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15692|2024-08-05T00:56:22.409Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 14:55:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15679|2024-08-05T00:56:22.416Z -- kaspersky -- tightvnc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15679</link>
      <description>TightVNC code version 1.3.10 contains heap buffer overflow in InitialiseRFBConnection function, which can potentially result code execution. This attack appear to be exploitable via network connectivity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15679|2024-08-05T00:56:22.416Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 16:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15694|2024-08-05T00:56:22.428Z -- kaspersky -- tigervnc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15694</link>
      <description>TigerVNC version prior to 1.10.1 is vulnerable to heap buffer overflow, which could be triggered from DecodeManager::decodeRect. Vulnerability occurs due to the signdness error in processing MemOutStream. Exploitation of this vulnerability could potentially result into remote code execution. This attack appear to be exploitable via network connectivity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15694|2024-08-05T00:56:22.428Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 14:59:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15689|2024-08-05T00:56:22.341Z -- kaspersky -- kaspersky%20secure%20connection%2C%20kaspersky%20internet%20security%2C%20kaspersky%20total%20security%2C%20kaspersky%20security%20cloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15689</link>
      <description>Kaspersky Secure Connection, Kaspersky Internet Security, Kaspersky Total Security, Kaspersky Security Cloud prior to version 2020 patch E have bug that allows a local user to execute arbitrary code via execution compromised file placed by an attacker with administrator rights. No privilege escalation. Possible whitelisting bypass some of the security products</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15689|2024-08-05T00:56:22.341Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 20:43:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15687|2024-08-05T00:56:22.458Z -- kaspersky -- kaspersky%20anti-virus%2C%20kaspersky%20internet%20security%2C%20kaspersky%20total%20security%2C%20kaspersky%20free%20anti-virus%2C%20kaspersky%20small%20office%20security%2C%20kaspersky%20security%20cloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15687</link>
      <description>Kaspersky Anti-Virus, Kaspersky Internet Security, Kaspersky Total Security, Kaspersky Free Anti-Virus, Kaspersky Small Office Security, Kaspersky Security Cloud up to 2020, the web protection component was vulnerable to remote disclosure of various information about the user's system (like Windows version and version of the product, host unique ID). Information Disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15687|2024-08-05T00:56:22.458Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 15:45:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15680|2024-08-05T00:56:22.088Z -- kaspersky -- tightvnc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15680</link>
      <description>TightVNC code version 1.3.10 contains null pointer dereference in HandleZlibBPP function, which results Denial of System (DoS). This attack appear to be exploitable via network connectivity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15680|2024-08-05T00:56:22.088Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 16:45:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15693|2024-08-05T00:56:22.462Z -- kaspersky -- tigervnc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15693</link>
      <description>TigerVNC version prior to 1.10.1 is vulnerable to heap buffer overflow, which occurs in TightDecoder::FilterGradient. Exploitation of this vulnerability could potentially result into remote code execution. This attack appear to be exploitable via network connectivity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15693|2024-08-05T00:56:22.462Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 14:57:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-15683|2024-08-05T00:56:22.465Z -- kaspersky -- turbovnc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15683</link>
      <description>TurboVNC server code contains stack buffer overflow vulnerability in commit prior to cea98166008301e614e0d36776bf9435a536136e. This could possibly result into remote code execution, since stack frame is not protected with stack canary. This attack appear to be exploitable via network connectivity. To exploit this vulnerability authorization on server is required. These issues have been fixed in commit cea98166008301e614e0d36776bf9435a536136e.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-15683|2024-08-05T00:56:22.465Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 17:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-23349|2024-08-02T10:28:40.854Z -- kaspersky -- kaspersky%20password%20manager%20for%20windows</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23349</link>
      <description>Kaspersky has fixed a security issue in Kaspersky Password Manager (KPM) for Windows that allowed a local user to recover the auto-filled credentials from a memory dump when the KPM extension for Google Chrome is used. To exploit the issue, an attacker must trick a user into visiting a login form of a website with the saved credentials, and the KPM extension must autofill these credentials. The attacker must then launch a malware module to steal those specific credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-23349|2024-08-02T10:28:40.854Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 16:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-23349|2024-06-04T17:22:23.513Z -- kaspersky -- kaspersky%20password%20manager%20for%20windows</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-23349</link>
      <description>Kaspersky has fixed a security issue in Kaspersky Password Manager (KPM) for Windows that allowed a local user to recover the auto-filled credentials from a memory dump when the KPM extension for Google Chrome is used. To exploit the issue, an attacker must trick a user into visiting a login form of a website with the saved credentials, and the KPM extension must autofill these credentials. The attacker must then launch a malware module to steal those specific credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-23349|2024-06-04T17:22:23.513Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 16:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1619|2024-06-04T18:00:28.058Z -- kaspersky -- kaspersky%20security%20for%20linux%20mail%20server%208</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1619</link>
      <description>Kaspersky has fixed a security issue in the Kaspersky Security 8.0 for Linux Mail Server. The issue was that an attacker could potentially force an administrator to click on a malicious link to perform unauthorized actions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1619|2024-06-04T18:00:28.058Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 09:22:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1619|2024-08-01T18:48:20.684Z -- kaspersky -- kaspersky%20security%20for%20linux%20mail%20server%208</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1619</link>
      <description>Kaspersky has fixed a security issue in the Kaspersky Security 8.0 for Linux Mail Server. The issue was that an attacker could potentially force an administrator to click on a malicious link to perform unauthorized actions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1619|2024-08-01T18:48:20.684Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 09:22:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
