<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 06:24:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3506|2024-06-28T03:55:17.955Z -- oracle%20corporation -- weblogic%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3506</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle WebLogic Server component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Web Services). Supported versions that are affected are 10.3.6.0, 12.1.3.0, 12.2.1.0, 12.2.1.1 and 12.2.1.2. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle WebLogic Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle WebLogic Server accessible data as well as unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle WebLogic Server accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3506|2024-06-28T03:55:17.955Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21059|2024-06-18T20:35:26.723Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21059</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Utility).   The supported version that is affected is 11. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle Solaris, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21059|2024-06-18T20:35:26.723Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21113|2024-06-18T20:35:09.485Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21113</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21113|2024-06-18T20:35:09.485Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21019|2024-06-17T15:59:29.656Z -- oracle%20corporation -- complex%20maintenance%2C%20repair%2C%20and%20overhaul</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21019</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21019|2024-06-17T15:59:29.656Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21016|2024-06-17T16:13:53.319Z -- oracle%20corporation -- complex%20maintenance%2C%20repair%2C%20and%20overhaul</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21016</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21016|2024-06-17T16:13:53.319Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-21833|2024-02-17T01:48:16.779Z -- oracle%20corporation -- sun%20zfs%20storage%20appliance%20kit%20%28ak%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-21833</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle ZFS Storage Appliance Kit product of Oracle Systems (component: Object Store).   The supported version that is affected is 8.8. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle ZFS Storage Appliance Kit.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle ZFS Storage Appliance Kit accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.3 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-21833|2024-02-17T01:48:16.779Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:48:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-21901|2024-01-16T21:39:38.605Z -- oracle%20corporation -- financial%20services%20analytical%20applications%20infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-21901</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Financial Services Analytical Applications Infrastructure product of Oracle Financial Services Applications (component: Infrastructure).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.7, 8.0.8, 8.0.9, 8.1.0, 8.1.1 and  8.1.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Financial Services Analytical Applications Infrastructure.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle Financial Services Analytical Applications Infrastructure, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Financial Services Analytical Applications Infrastructure accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Financial Services Analytical Applications Infrastructure accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Financial Services Analytical Applications Infrastructure. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.4 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-21901|2024-01-16T21:39:38.605Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:39:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20926|2024-01-16T21:41:16.336Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20926</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Scripting).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u391, 8u391-perf, 11.0.21; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.9; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.12, 21.3.8 and  22.3.4. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.9 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20926|2024-01-16T21:41:16.336Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20971|2024-01-16T21:41:23.509Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20971</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20971|2024-01-16T21:41:23.509Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20967|2024-01-16T21:41:22.915Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20967</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Replication).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server as well as  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of MySQL Server accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.5 (Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20967|2024-01-16T21:41:22.915Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20930|2024-01-16T21:41:17.071Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20930</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Content Access SDK, Image Export SDK, PDF Export SDK, HTML Export SDK).   The supported version that is affected is 8.5.6. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20930|2024-01-16T21:41:17.071Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20992|2024-06-04T17:40:48.486Z -- oracle%20corporation -- webcenter%20portal</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20992</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle WebCenter Portal product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Content integration).   The supported version that is affected is 12.2.1.4.0. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle WebCenter Portal.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle WebCenter Portal, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle WebCenter Portal accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle WebCenter Portal accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20992|2024-06-04T17:40:48.486Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20984|2024-02-17T01:50:22.747Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20984</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server : Security : Firewall).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.4 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20984|2024-02-17T01:50:22.747Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20947|2024-02-17T01:50:15.825Z -- oracle%20corporation -- common%20applications</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20947</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Common Applications product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: CRM User Management Framework).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Common Applications.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Common Applications, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Common Applications accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Common Applications accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20947|2024-02-17T01:50:15.825Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20910|2024-01-16T21:41:13.662Z -- oracle%20corporation -- audit%20vault%20and%20database%20firewall</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20910</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in Oracle Audit Vault and Database Firewall (component: Firewall).  Supported versions that are affected are 20.1-20.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via Oracle Net to compromise Oracle Audit Vault and Database Firewall.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle Audit Vault and Database Firewall, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Audit Vault and Database Firewall accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.0 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20910|2024-01-16T21:41:13.662Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20906|2024-01-16T21:41:12.976Z -- oracle%20corporation -- ssm%20-%20%28hot-tamale%29%20ilom%3A%20integrated%20lights%20out%20manager</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20906</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Integrated Lights Out Manager (ILOM) product of Oracle Systems (component: System Management).  Supported versions that are affected are 3, 4 and  5. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via ICMP to compromise Integrated Lights Out Manager (ILOM).  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Integrated Lights Out Manager (ILOM), attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Integrated Lights Out Manager (ILOM) accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Integrated Lights Out Manager (ILOM) accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.8 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20906|2024-01-16T21:41:12.976Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20951|2024-02-17T01:50:16.584Z -- oracle%20corporation -- customer%20interaction%20history</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20951</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Customer Interaction History product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: Outcome-Result).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Customer Interaction History.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Customer Interaction History, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Customer Interaction History accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Customer Interaction History accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20951|2024-02-17T01:50:16.584Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20950|2024-01-16T21:41:20.250Z -- oracle%20corporation -- customer%20interaction%20history</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20950</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Customer Interaction History product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: Outcome-Result).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Customer Interaction History.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Customer Interaction History, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Customer Interaction History accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Customer Interaction History accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20950|2024-01-16T21:41:20.250Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20907|2024-06-04T17:40:43.968Z -- oracle%20corporation -- web%20applications%20desktop%20integrator</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20907</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Web Applications Desktop Integrator product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: File download).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Web Applications Desktop Integrator.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Web Applications Desktop Integrator, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Web Applications Desktop Integrator accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Web Applications Desktop Integrator accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20907|2024-06-04T17:40:43.968Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20911|2024-02-17T01:50:08.831Z -- oracle%20corporation -- audit%20vault%20and%20database%20firewall</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20911</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in Oracle Audit Vault and Database Firewall (component: Firewall).  Supported versions that are affected are 20.1-20.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via Oracle Net to compromise Oracle Audit Vault and Database Firewall.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Audit Vault and Database Firewall, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Audit Vault and Database Firewall accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 2.6 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20911|2024-02-17T01:50:08.831Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20946|2024-01-16T21:41:19.641Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20946</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Kernel).   The supported version that is affected is 11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.5 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20946|2024-01-16T21:41:19.641Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20985|2024-01-16T21:41:25.704Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20985</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: UDF).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20985|2024-01-16T21:41:25.704Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20993|2024-04-16T21:25:55.794Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20993</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20993|2024-04-16T21:25:55.794Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20931|2024-02-17T01:50:12.858Z -- oracle%20corporation -- weblogic%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20931</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle WebLogic Server product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.1.4.0 and  14.1.1.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via T3, IIOP to compromise Oracle WebLogic Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle WebLogic Server accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20931|2024-02-17T01:50:12.858Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20966|2024-06-04T17:40:38.223Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20966</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20966|2024-06-04T17:40:38.223Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20989|2024-04-16T21:25:19.882Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20simphony</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20989</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality Simphony product of Oracle Food and Beverage Applications (component: Simphony POS).  Supported versions that are affected are 19.1.0-19.5.4. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Hospitality Simphony.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Hospitality Simphony accessible data as well as  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Hospitality Simphony accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Hospitality Simphony. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.0 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20989|2024-04-16T21:25:19.882Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20970|2024-06-04T17:40:37.317Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20970</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20970|2024-06-04T17:40:37.317Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20927|2024-02-17T01:50:11.937Z -- oracle%20corporation -- weblogic%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20927</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle WebLogic Server product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.1.4.0 and  14.1.1.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle WebLogic Server.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle WebLogic Server, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle WebLogic Server accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.6 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20927|2024-02-17T01:50:11.937Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20994|2024-06-04T17:40:35.225Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20994</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Information Schema).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20994|2024-06-04T17:40:35.225Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20982|2024-06-04T17:40:34.772Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20982</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20982|2024-06-04T17:40:34.772Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20941|2024-02-17T01:50:14.707Z -- oracle%20corporation -- installed%20base</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20941</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Installed Base product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: HTML UI).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Installed Base.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Installed Base, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Installed Base accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Installed Base accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20941|2024-02-17T01:50:14.707Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20916|2024-01-16T21:41:14.656Z -- oracle%20corporation -- enterprise%20manager%20base%20platform</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20916</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Enterprise Manager Base Platform product of Oracle Enterprise Manager (component: Event Management).   The supported version that is affected is 13.5.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with access to the physical communication segment attached to the hardware where the Oracle Enterprise Manager Base Platform executes to compromise Oracle Enterprise Manager Base Platform.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle Enterprise Manager Base Platform, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle Enterprise Manager Base Platform accessible data as well as  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Enterprise Manager Base Platform accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Enterprise Manager Base Platform. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:A/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20916|2024-01-16T21:41:14.656Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20957|2024-01-16T21:41:21.266Z -- oracle%20corporation -- jd%20edwards%20enterpriseone%20tools</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20957</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools product of Oracle JD Edwards (component: Package Build SEC).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 9.2.8.1. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via JDENET to compromise JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 2.7 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20957|2024-01-16T21:41:21.266Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20920|2024-01-16T21:41:15.262Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20920</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Filesystem).   The supported version that is affected is 11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle Solaris, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Solaris accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.8 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20920|2024-01-16T21:41:15.262Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20977|2024-01-16T21:41:24.447Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20977</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20977|2024-01-16T21:41:24.447Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20998|2024-06-04T17:40:30.457Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20998</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20998|2024-06-04T17:40:30.457Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20961|2024-01-16T21:41:21.943Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20961</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20961|2024-01-16T21:41:21.943Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20936|2024-01-16T21:41:18.009Z -- oracle%20corporation -- one-to-one%20fulfillment</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20936</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle One-to-One Fulfillment product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: Documents).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle One-to-One Fulfillment.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle One-to-One Fulfillment, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle One-to-One Fulfillment accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle One-to-One Fulfillment accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20936|2024-01-16T21:41:18.009Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20937|2024-02-17T01:50:13.991Z -- oracle%20corporation -- jd%20edwards%20enterpriseone%20tools</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20937</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools product of Oracle JD Edwards (component: Monitoring and Diagnostics SEC).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 9.2.8.1. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.3 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20937|2024-02-17T01:50:13.991Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20960|2024-06-04T17:40:24.649Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20960</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: RAPID).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20960|2024-06-04T17:40:24.649Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20976|2024-02-17T01:50:21.249Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20976</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20976|2024-02-17T01:50:21.249Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20999|2024-04-16T21:25:57.507Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20999</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Zones).   The supported version that is affected is 11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle Solaris, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.2 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20999|2024-04-16T21:25:57.507Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20921|2024-02-17T01:50:10.681Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20921</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u391, 8u391-perf, 11.0.21, 17.0.9, 21.0.1; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.9, 21.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.12, 21.3.8 and  22.3.4. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.9 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20921|2024-02-17T01:50:10.681Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20956|2024-02-17T01:50:17.379Z -- oracle%20corporation -- agile%20product%20lifecycle%20management%20for%20process</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20956</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Agile Product Lifecycle Management for Process product of Oracle Supply Chain (component: Installation).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 6.2.4.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Agile Product Lifecycle Management for Process.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Agile Product Lifecycle Management for Process accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Agile Product Lifecycle Management for Process accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Agile Product Lifecycle Management for Process. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20956|2024-02-17T01:50:17.379Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20917|2024-02-17T01:50:09.948Z -- oracle%20corporation -- enterprise%20manager%20base%20platform</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20917</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Enterprise Manager Base Platform product of Oracle Enterprise Manager (component: Log Management).   The supported version that is affected is 13.5.0.0. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Enterprise Manager Base Platform.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Enterprise Manager Base Platform, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Enterprise Manager Base Platform accessible data as well as  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Enterprise Manager Base Platform accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Enterprise Manager Base Platform. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:H/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20917|2024-02-17T01:50:09.948Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20940|2024-01-16T21:41:18.642Z -- oracle%20corporation -- knowledge%20management</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20940</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Knowledge Management product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: Create, Update, Authoring Flow).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Knowledge Management.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Knowledge Management, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Knowledge Management accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Knowledge Management accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20940|2024-01-16T21:41:18.642Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20983|2024-01-16T21:41:25.405Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20983</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DML).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.34 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20983|2024-01-16T21:41:25.405Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20995|2024-04-16T21:25:56.479Z -- oracle%20corporation -- database%20-%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20995</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Database Sharding component of Oracle Database Server.  Supported versions that are affected are 19.3-19.22 and  21.3-21.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker having DBA privilege with network access via Oracle Net to compromise Oracle Database Sharding.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Database Sharding. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 2.4 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20995|2024-04-16T21:25:56.479Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20955|2024-01-26T21:59:54.860Z -- oracle%20corporation -- graalvm%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20955</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Compiler).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.9, 21.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.12, 21.3.8 and  22.3.4. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20955|2024-01-26T21:59:54.860Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20914|2024-01-16T21:41:14.356Z -- oracle%20corporation -- sun%20zfs%20storage%20appliance%20kit%20%28ak%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20914</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle ZFS Storage Appliance Kit product of Oracle Systems (component: Core).   The supported version that is affected is 8.8. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle ZFS Storage Appliance Kit executes to compromise Oracle ZFS Storage Appliance Kit.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle ZFS Storage Appliance Kit accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 2.3 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20914|2024-01-16T21:41:14.356Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20943|2024-02-17T01:50:15.073Z -- oracle%20corporation -- knowledge%20management</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20943</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Knowledge Management product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: Internal Operations).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Knowledge Management.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Knowledge Management, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Knowledge Management accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Knowledge Management accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20943|2024-02-17T01:50:15.073Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20938|2024-01-16T21:41:18.340Z -- oracle%20corporation -- istore</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20938</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle iStore product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: ECC).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle iStore.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle iStore, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle iStore accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle iStore accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20938|2024-01-16T21:41:18.340Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20980|2024-02-17T01:50:21.994Z -- oracle%20corporation -- bi%20publisher%20%28formerly%20xml%20publisher%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20980</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle BI Publisher product of Oracle Analytics (component: Web Server).  Supported versions that are affected are 6.4.0.0.0 and  7.0.0.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle BI Publisher.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle BI Publisher, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle BI Publisher accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle BI Publisher accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20980|2024-02-17T01:50:21.994Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20979|2024-01-16T21:41:24.760Z -- oracle%20corporation -- bi%20publisher%20%28formerly%20xml%20publisher%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20979</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle BI Publisher product of Oracle Analytics (component: Web Server).  Supported versions that are affected are 6.4.0.0.0, 7.0.0.0.0 and  12.2.1.4.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle BI Publisher.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle BI Publisher, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle BI Publisher accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle BI Publisher accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20979|2024-01-16T21:41:24.760Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20959|2024-01-16T21:41:21.596Z -- oracle%20corporation -- sun%20zfs%20storage%20appliance%20kit%20%28ak%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20959</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle ZFS Storage Appliance Kit product of Oracle Systems (component: Core).   The supported version that is affected is 8.8. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle ZFS Storage Appliance Kit executes to compromise Oracle ZFS Storage Appliance Kit.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle ZFS Storage Appliance Kit. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.4 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20959|2024-01-16T21:41:21.596Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20918|2024-01-16T21:41:14.954Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20918</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u391, 8u391-perf, 11.0.21, 17.0.9, 21.0.1; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.9, 21.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.12, 21.3.8 and  22.3.4. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data as well as  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20918|2024-01-16T21:41:14.954Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20934|2024-01-16T21:41:17.683Z -- oracle%20corporation -- installed%20base</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20934</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Installed Base product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: Engineering Change Order).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Installed Base.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Installed Base, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Installed Base accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Installed Base accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20934|2024-01-16T21:41:17.683Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20963|2024-01-16T21:41:22.251Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20963</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Security: Encryption).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20963|2024-01-16T21:41:22.251Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20975|2024-01-16T21:41:24.124Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20975</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20975|2024-01-16T21:41:24.124Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20922|2024-01-16T21:41:15.590Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20922</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: JavaFX).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u391; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.12 and  21.3.8. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition executes to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 2.5 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20922|2024-01-16T21:41:15.590Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20923|2024-02-17T01:50:11.127Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20923</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: JavaFX).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u391; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.12 and  21.3.8. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.1 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20923|2024-02-17T01:50:11.127Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20974|2024-02-17T01:50:20.861Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20974</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20974|2024-02-17T01:50:20.861Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20962|2024-06-07T15:57:59.785Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20962</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20962|2024-06-07T15:57:59.785Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20935|2024-02-17T01:50:13.606Z -- oracle%20corporation -- installed%20base</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20935</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Installed Base product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: Engineering Change Order).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Installed Base.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Installed Base, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Installed Base accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Installed Base accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20935|2024-02-17T01:50:13.606Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20919|2024-02-17T01:50:10.320Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20919</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u391, 8u391-perf, 11.0.21, 17.0.9, 21.0.1; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.9, 21.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.12, 21.3.8 and  22.3.4. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can only be exploited by supplying data to APIs in the specified Component without using Untrusted Java Web Start applications or Untrusted Java applets, such as through a web service. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.9 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20919|2024-02-17T01:50:10.320Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20958|2024-02-17T01:50:17.747Z -- oracle%20corporation -- installed%20base</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20958</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Installed Base product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: Engineering Change Order).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Installed Base.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Installed Base, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Installed Base accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Installed Base accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20958|2024-02-17T01:50:17.747Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20997|2024-04-16T21:25:56.839Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20simphony</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20997</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality Simphony product of Oracle Food and Beverage Applications (component: Simphony Enterprise Server).  Supported versions that are affected are 19.1.0-19.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Hospitality Simphony.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle Hospitality Simphony, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle Hospitality Simphony. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 9.9 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20997|2024-04-16T21:25:56.839Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20978|2024-02-17T01:50:21.606Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20978</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20978|2024-02-17T01:50:21.606Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20981|2024-01-16T21:41:25.081Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20981</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DDL).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20981|2024-01-16T21:41:25.081Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20939|2024-02-17T01:50:14.359Z -- oracle%20corporation -- crm%20technical%20foundation</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20939</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle CRM Technical Foundation product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: Admin Console).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle CRM Technical Foundation.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle CRM Technical Foundation. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.3 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20939|2024-02-17T01:50:14.359Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20942|2024-01-16T21:41:18.967Z -- oracle%20corporation -- complex%20maintenance%2C%20repair%2C%20and%20overhaul</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20942</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul product of Oracle Supply Chain (component: LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 11.5, 12.1 and  12.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20942|2024-01-16T21:41:18.967Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20915|2024-02-17T01:50:09.593Z -- oracle%20corporation -- application%20object%20library</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20915</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Application Object Library product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: Login - SSO).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Application Object Library.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Application Object Library. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20915|2024-02-17T01:50:09.593Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20903|2024-02-17T01:49:51.064Z -- oracle%20corporation -- database%20-%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20903</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java VM component of Oracle Database Server.  Supported versions that are affected are 19.3-19.21 and  21.3-21.12. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker having Create Session, Create Procedure privilege with network access via Oracle Net to compromise Java VM.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Java VM accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20903|2024-02-17T01:49:51.064Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:49:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20954|2024-06-04T17:40:07.179Z -- oracle%20corporation -- graalvm</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20954</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Compiler).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.10, 21.0.2, 22; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.13 and  21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20954|2024-06-04T17:40:07.179Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20908|2024-01-16T21:41:13.320Z -- oracle%20corporation -- webcenter%20sites</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20908</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle WebCenter Sites product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Advanced UI).   The supported version that is affected is 12.2.1.4.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle WebCenter Sites.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle WebCenter Sites, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle WebCenter Sites accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle WebCenter Sites accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20908|2024-01-16T21:41:13.320Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20949|2024-06-04T17:40:03.833Z -- oracle%20corporation -- customer%20interaction%20history</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20949</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Customer Interaction History product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: Outcome-Result).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Customer Interaction History.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Customer Interaction History, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Customer Interaction History accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Customer Interaction History accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20949|2024-06-04T17:40:03.833Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20932|2024-01-16T21:41:17.380Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20932</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Security).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 17.0.9; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.9; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 21.3.8 and  22.3.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20932|2024-01-16T21:41:17.380Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20965|2024-01-16T21:41:22.582Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20ndb%20cluster</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20965</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20965|2024-01-16T21:41:22.582Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20973|2024-01-16T21:41:23.811Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20973</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20973|2024-01-16T21:41:23.811Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20924|2024-01-16T21:41:15.905Z -- oracle%20corporation -- audit%20vault%20and%20database%20firewall</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20924</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in Oracle Audit Vault and Database Firewall (component: Firewall).  Supported versions that are affected are 20.1-20.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via Oracle Net to compromise Oracle Audit Vault and Database Firewall.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Audit Vault and Database Firewall, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle Audit Vault and Database Firewall. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.6 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:R/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20924|2024-01-16T21:41:15.905Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20953|2024-02-17T01:50:16.976Z -- oracle%20corporation -- agile%20plm%20framework</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20953</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Agile PLM product of Oracle Supply Chain (component: Export).   The supported version that is affected is 9.3.6. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Agile PLM.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle Agile PLM. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20953|2024-02-17T01:50:16.976Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20904|2024-01-16T21:41:12.622Z -- oracle%20corporation -- business%20intelligence%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20904</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Analytics (component: Pod Admin).  Supported versions that are affected are 6.4.0.0.0 and  12.2.1.4.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.0 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20904|2024-01-16T21:41:12.622Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20912|2024-01-16T21:41:14.033Z -- oracle%20corporation -- audit%20vault%20and%20database%20firewall</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20912</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in Oracle Audit Vault and Database Firewall (component: Firewall).  Supported versions that are affected are 20.1-20.9. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via Oracle Net to compromise Oracle Audit Vault and Database Firewall.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Audit Vault and Database Firewall accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 2.7 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20912|2024-01-16T21:41:14.033Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20945|2024-02-17T01:50:15.446Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20945</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Security).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u391, 8u391-perf, 11.0.21, 17.0.9, 21.0.1; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.9, 21.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.12, 21.3.8 and  22.3.4. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition executes to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.7 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20945|2024-02-17T01:50:15.446Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20986|2024-02-17T01:50:23.116Z -- oracle%20corporation -- weblogic%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20986</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle WebLogic Server product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.1.4.0 and  14.1.1.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle WebLogic Server.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle WebLogic Server, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle WebLogic Server accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle WebLogic Server accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20986|2024-02-17T01:50:23.116Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20969|2024-01-16T21:41:23.217Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20969</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DDL).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server as well as  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of MySQL Server accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.5 (Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20969|2024-01-16T21:41:23.217Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20990|2024-06-04T17:39:57.967Z -- oracle%20corporation -- e-business%20suite%20technology%20stack</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20990</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Applications Technology product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: Templates).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Applications Technology.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Applications Technology accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20990|2024-06-04T17:39:57.967Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20928|2024-01-16T21:41:16.730Z -- oracle%20corporation -- webcenter%20content</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20928</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle WebCenter Content product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Content Server).   The supported version that is affected is 12.2.1.4.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle WebCenter Content.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle WebCenter Content, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle WebCenter Content accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle WebCenter Content accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20928|2024-01-16T21:41:16.730Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20929|2024-06-04T17:39:56.723Z -- oracle%20corporation -- application%20object%20library</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20929</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Application Object Library product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: DB Privileges).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Application Object Library.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Application Object Library accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Application Object Library accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20929|2024-06-04T17:39:56.723Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20991|2024-04-16T21:25:55.089Z -- oracle%20corporation -- http%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20991</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle HTTP Server product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Web Listener).   The supported version that is affected is 12.2.1.4.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle HTTP Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle HTTP Server accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20991|2024-04-16T21:25:55.089Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20987|2024-01-16T21:41:26.007Z -- oracle%20corporation -- bi%20publisher%20%28formerly%20xml%20publisher%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20987</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle BI Publisher product of Oracle Analytics (component: Web Server).   The supported version that is affected is 12.2.1.4.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle BI Publisher.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle BI Publisher, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle BI Publisher accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle BI Publisher accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20987|2024-01-16T21:41:26.007Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20968|2024-02-17T01:50:19.680Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20968</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Options).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.34 and prior and  8.1.0. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.4 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20968|2024-02-17T01:50:19.680Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20944|2024-01-16T21:41:19.302Z -- oracle%20corporation -- isupport</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20944</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle iSupport product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: Internal Operations).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle iSupport.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle iSupport, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle iSupport accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle iSupport accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20944|2024-01-16T21:41:19.302Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20913|2024-02-17T01:50:09.197Z -- oracle%20corporation -- business%20intelligence%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20913</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Analytics (component: BI Platform Security).   The supported version that is affected is 12.2.1.4.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20913|2024-02-17T01:50:09.197Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20905|2024-02-17T01:50:07.693Z -- oracle%20corporation -- jd%20edwards%20enterpriseone%20tools</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20905</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools product of Oracle JD Edwards (component: Enterprise Infrastructure SEC).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 9.2.8.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via JDENET to compromise JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 2.7 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20905|2024-02-17T01:50:07.693Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20952|2024-01-16T21:41:20.593Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20952</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Security).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u391, 8u391-perf, 11.0.21, 17.0.9, 21.0.1; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.9, 21.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.12, 21.3.8 and  22.3.4. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data as well as  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20952|2024-01-16T21:41:20.593Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20925|2024-02-17T01:50:11.500Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20925</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: JavaFX).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u391; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.12 and  21.3.8. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.1 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20925|2024-02-17T01:50:11.500Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20972|2024-02-17T01:50:20.471Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20972</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20972|2024-02-17T01:50:20.471Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20964|2024-02-17T01:50:18.930Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20964</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Security: Privileges).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20964|2024-02-17T01:50:18.930Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20933|2024-02-17T01:50:13.253Z -- oracle%20corporation -- installed%20base</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20933</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Installed Base product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: Engineering Change Order).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Installed Base.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Installed Base, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Installed Base accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Installed Base accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20933|2024-02-17T01:50:13.253Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20948|2024-01-16T21:41:19.946Z -- oracle%20corporation -- knowledge%20management</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20948</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Knowledge Management product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: Setup, Admin).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Knowledge Management.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Knowledge Management, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Knowledge Management accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Knowledge Management accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20948|2024-01-16T21:41:19.946Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20909|2024-02-17T01:50:08.455Z -- oracle%20corporation -- audit%20vault%20and%20database%20firewall</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20909</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in Oracle Audit Vault and Database Firewall (component: Firewall).  Supported versions that are affected are 20.1-20.9. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via Oracle Net to compromise Oracle Audit Vault and Database Firewall.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle Audit Vault and Database Firewall accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20909|2024-02-17T01:50:08.455Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21008|2024-06-04T17:38:18.945Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21008</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.4 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21008|2024-06-04T17:38:18.945Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21049|2024-04-16T21:26:14.785Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21049</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DML).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.34 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21049|2024-04-16T21:26:14.785Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21120|2024-04-16T21:26:38.818Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21120</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Core).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.6 and  8.5.7. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Outside In Technology executes to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21120|2024-04-16T21:26:38.818Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21065|2024-04-16T21:26:20.238Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21065</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools product of Oracle PeopleSoft (component: Workflow).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.59, 8.60 and  8.61. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21065|2024-04-16T21:26:20.238Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21032|2024-04-16T21:26:08.979Z -- oracle%20corporation -- complex%20maintenance%2C%20repair%2C%20and%20overhaul</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21032</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21032|2024-04-16T21:26:08.979Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21024|2024-04-16T21:26:06.304Z -- oracle%20corporation -- complex%20maintenance%2C%20repair%2C%20and%20overhaul</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21024</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21024|2024-04-16T21:26:06.304Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21073|2024-06-04T17:38:17.307Z -- oracle%20corporation -- trade%20management</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21073</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Trade Management product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: Claim LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Trade Management.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Trade Management accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21073|2024-06-04T17:38:17.307Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21004|2024-06-04T17:38:16.533Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21004</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: JavaFX).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u401; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.13 and  21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition executes to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 2.5 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21004|2024-06-04T17:38:16.533Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21053|2024-06-04T17:38:15.735Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21053</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DML).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.34 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21053|2024-06-04T17:38:15.735Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21116|2024-04-16T21:26:37.525Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21116</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. Note: This vulnerability applies to Linux hosts only. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21116|2024-04-16T21:26:37.525Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21045|2024-06-04T17:38:14.934Z -- oracle%20corporation -- complex%20maintenance%2C%20repair%2C%20and%20overhaul</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21045</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21045|2024-06-04T17:38:14.934Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21100|2024-04-16T21:26:32.274Z -- oracle%20corporation -- commerce%20platform</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21100</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Commerce Platform product of Oracle Commerce (component: Platform).  Supported versions that are affected are 11.3.0, 11.3.1 and  11.3.2. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Commerce Platform.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle Commerce Platform, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Commerce Platform accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.0 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21100|2024-04-16T21:26:32.274Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21012|2024-04-16T21:26:02.245Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21012</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Networking).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 11.0.22, 17.0.10, 21.0.2, 22; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.10, 21.0.2, 22; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.13 and  21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21012|2024-04-16T21:26:02.245Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21086|2024-06-04T17:38:14.534Z -- oracle%20corporation -- crm%20technical%20foundation</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21086</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle CRM Technical Foundation product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: Preferences).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle CRM Technical Foundation.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle CRM Technical Foundation accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.3 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21086|2024-06-04T17:38:14.534Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21069|2024-04-16T21:26:21.750Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21069</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DDL).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21069|2024-04-16T21:26:21.750Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21028|2024-06-04T17:38:13.056Z -- oracle%20corporation -- complex%20maintenance%2C%20repair%2C%20and%20overhaul</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21028</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21028|2024-06-04T17:38:13.056Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21090|2024-06-04T17:38:12.660Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20connectors</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21090</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Connectors product of Oracle MySQL (component: Connector/Python).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Connectors.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Connectors. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21090|2024-06-04T17:38:12.660Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21091|2024-06-04T17:38:12.256Z -- oracle%20corporation -- agile%20product%20lifecycle%20management%20for%20process</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21091</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Agile Product Lifecycle Management for Process product of Oracle Supply Chain (component: Data Import).   The supported version that is affected is 6.2.4.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Agile Product Lifecycle Management for Process.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Agile Product Lifecycle Management for Process accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21091|2024-06-04T17:38:12.256Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21029|2024-04-16T21:26:07.959Z -- oracle%20corporation -- complex%20maintenance%2C%20repair%2C%20and%20overhaul</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21029</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21029|2024-04-16T21:26:07.959Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21087|2024-04-16T21:26:27.815Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21087</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Group Replication Plugin).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21087|2024-04-16T21:26:27.815Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21068|2024-04-16T21:26:21.424Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21068</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u401-perf, 11.0.22, 17.0.10, 21.0.2, 22; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.10, 21.0.2 and  22; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21068|2024-04-16T21:26:21.424Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21013|2024-06-04T17:38:09.373Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21013</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.4 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21013|2024-06-04T17:38:09.373Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21044|2024-04-16T21:26:13.091Z -- oracle%20corporation -- complex%20maintenance%2C%20repair%2C%20and%20overhaul</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21044</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21044|2024-04-16T21:26:13.091Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21101|2024-04-16T21:26:32.608Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20ndb%20cluster</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21101</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Cluster product of Oracle MySQL (component: Cluster: General).  Supported versions that are affected are 7.5.33 and prior, 7.6.29 and prior, 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Cluster.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of MySQL Cluster accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 2.2 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21101|2024-04-16T21:26:32.608Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21052|2024-04-16T21:26:15.734Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21052</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DML).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.34 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21052|2024-04-16T21:26:15.734Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21117|2024-04-16T21:26:37.832Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21117</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Core).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.6 and  8.5.7. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Outside In Technology executes to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21117|2024-04-16T21:26:37.832Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21005|2024-04-16T21:25:59.621Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21005</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: JavaFX).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u401; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.13 and  21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.1 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21005|2024-04-16T21:25:59.621Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21072|2024-06-04T17:38:06.135Z -- oracle%20corporation -- installed%20base</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21072</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Installed Base product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: Data Provider UI).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Installed Base.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Installed Base, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Installed Base accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Installed Base accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21072|2024-06-04T17:38:06.135Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21025|2024-04-16T21:26:06.626Z -- oracle%20corporation -- complex%20maintenance%2C%20repair%2C%20and%20overhaul</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21025</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21025|2024-04-16T21:26:06.626Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21033|2024-04-16T21:26:09.344Z -- oracle%20corporation -- complex%20maintenance%2C%20repair%2C%20and%20overhaul</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21033</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21033|2024-04-16T21:26:09.344Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21121|2024-06-04T17:38:05.209Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21121</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21121|2024-06-04T17:38:05.209Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21064|2024-06-04T17:38:04.816Z -- oracle%20corporation -- business%20intelligence%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21064</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Analytics (component: Analytics Web Answers).  Supported versions that are affected are 7.0.0.0.0 and  12.2.1.4.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21064|2024-06-04T17:38:04.816Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21048|2024-04-16T21:26:14.451Z -- oracle%20corporation -- web%20applications%20desktop%20integrator</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21048</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Web Applications Desktop Integrator product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: XML input).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Web Applications Desktop Integrator.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Web Applications Desktop Integrator accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.3 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21048|2024-04-16T21:26:14.451Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21009|2024-04-16T21:26:01.082Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21009</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21009|2024-04-16T21:26:01.082Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21002|2024-06-04T17:38:03.601Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21002</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: JavaFX).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u401; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.13 and  21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition executes to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 2.5 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21002|2024-06-04T17:38:03.601Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21055|2024-04-16T21:26:16.694Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21055</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21055|2024-04-16T21:26:16.694Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21110|2024-04-16T21:26:35.598Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21110</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21110|2024-04-16T21:26:35.598Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21043|2024-04-16T21:26:12.707Z -- oracle%20corporation -- complex%20maintenance%2C%20repair%2C%20and%20overhaul</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21043</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21043|2024-04-16T21:26:12.707Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21106|2024-06-04T17:38:02.363Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21106</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21106|2024-06-04T17:38:02.363Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21014|2024-04-16T21:26:02.932Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20simphony</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21014</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality Simphony product of Oracle Food and Beverage Applications (component: Simphony Enterprise Server).  Supported versions that are affected are 19.1.0-19.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Hospitality Simphony.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle Hospitality Simphony. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 9.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21014|2024-04-16T21:26:02.932Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21080|2024-04-16T21:26:25.378Z -- oracle%20corporation -- applications%20framework</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21080</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Applications Framework product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: REST Services).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.9-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Applications Framework.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Applications Framework accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21080|2024-04-16T21:26:25.378Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21038|2024-04-16T21:26:11.084Z -- oracle%20corporation -- complex%20maintenance%2C%20repair%2C%20and%20overhaul</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21038</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21038|2024-04-16T21:26:11.084Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21096|2024-04-16T21:26:30.986Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21096</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Client: mysqldump).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with logon to the infrastructure where MySQL Server executes to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of MySQL Server accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of MySQL Server accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21096|2024-04-16T21:26:30.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21079|2024-06-04T17:38:01.117Z -- oracle%20corporation -- marketing</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21079</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Marketing product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: Campaign LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Marketing.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Marketing accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21079|2024-06-04T17:38:01.117Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21059|2024-04-16T21:26:18.102Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21059</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Utility).   The supported version that is affected is 11. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle Solaris, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21059|2024-04-16T21:26:18.102Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21018|2024-04-16T21:26:04.270Z -- oracle%20corporation -- complex%20maintenance%2C%20repair%2C%20and%20overhaul</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21018</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21018|2024-04-16T21:26:04.270Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21063|2024-04-16T21:26:19.470Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20hcm%20benefits%20administration</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21063</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise HCM Benefits Administration product of Oracle PeopleSoft (component: Benefits Administration).   The supported version that is affected is 9.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where PeopleSoft Enterprise HCM Benefits Administration executes to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise HCM Benefits Administration.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all PeopleSoft Enterprise HCM Benefits Administration accessible data as well as  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of PeopleSoft Enterprise HCM Benefits Administration accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of PeopleSoft Enterprise HCM Benefits Administration. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:U/C:H/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21063|2024-04-16T21:26:19.470Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21034|2024-04-16T21:26:09.690Z -- oracle%20corporation -- complex%20maintenance%2C%20repair%2C%20and%20overhaul</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21034</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21034|2024-04-16T21:26:09.690Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21022|2024-04-16T21:26:05.597Z -- oracle%20corporation -- complex%20maintenance%2C%20repair%2C%20and%20overhaul</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21022</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21022|2024-04-16T21:26:05.597Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21075|2024-06-04T17:37:58.706Z -- oracle%20corporation -- trade%20management</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21075</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Trade Management product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: Claim Line LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Trade Management.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Trade Management accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21075|2024-06-04T17:37:58.706Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21074|2024-04-16T21:26:23.463Z -- oracle%20corporation -- trade%20management</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21074</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Trade Management product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: Finance LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Trade Management.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Trade Management accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21074|2024-04-16T21:26:23.463Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21023|2024-06-04T17:37:58.300Z -- oracle%20corporation -- complex%20maintenance%2C%20repair%2C%20and%20overhaul</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21023</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21023|2024-06-04T17:37:58.300Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21035|2024-06-04T17:37:57.420Z -- oracle%20corporation -- complex%20maintenance%2C%20repair%2C%20and%20overhaul</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21035</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21035|2024-06-04T17:37:57.420Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21062|2024-06-06T20:19:04.844Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21062</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21062|2024-06-06T20:19:04.844Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21019|2024-04-16T21:26:04.617Z -- oracle%20corporation -- complex%20maintenance%2C%20repair%2C%20and%20overhaul</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21019</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21019|2024-04-16T21:26:04.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21058|2024-04-16T21:26:17.684Z -- oracle%20corporation -- database%20-%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21058</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Unified Audit component of Oracle Database Server.  Supported versions that are affected are 19.3-19.22 and  21.3-21.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker having SYSDBA privilege with network access via Oracle Net to compromise Unified Audit.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Unified Audit accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21058|2024-04-16T21:26:17.684Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21097|2024-04-16T21:26:31.307Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21097</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools product of Oracle PeopleSoft (component: Security).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.59, 8.60 and  8.61. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21097|2024-04-16T21:26:31.307Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21078|2024-06-04T17:37:55.684Z -- oracle%20corporation -- marketing</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21078</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Marketing product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: Campaign LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Marketing.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Marketing accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21078|2024-06-04T17:37:55.684Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21039|2024-06-04T17:37:54.508Z -- oracle%20corporation -- complex%20maintenance%2C%20repair%2C%20and%20overhaul</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21039</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21039|2024-06-04T17:37:54.508Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21081|2024-04-16T21:26:25.720Z -- oracle%20corporation -- partner%20management</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21081</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Partner Management product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: Attribute Admin Setup).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Partner Management.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Partner Management, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Partner Management accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.7 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21081|2024-04-16T21:26:25.720Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21015|2024-04-16T21:26:03.248Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21015</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DML).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.34 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server as well as  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of MySQL Server accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.5 (Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21015|2024-04-16T21:26:03.248Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21042|2024-04-16T21:26:12.392Z -- oracle%20corporation -- complex%20maintenance%2C%20repair%2C%20and%20overhaul</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21042</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21042|2024-04-16T21:26:12.392Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21107|2024-04-16T21:26:34.607Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21107</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. Note: This vulnerability applies to Windows hosts only. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.7 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21107|2024-04-16T21:26:34.607Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21054|2024-06-04T17:37:52.860Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21054</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21054|2024-06-04T17:37:52.860Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21111|2024-04-16T21:26:35.907Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21111</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. Note: This vulnerability applies to Windows hosts only. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21111|2024-04-16T21:26:35.907Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21003|2024-06-04T17:37:52.453Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21003</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: JavaFX).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u401; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.13 and  21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.1 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21003|2024-06-04T17:37:52.453Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21094|2024-06-04T17:37:51.570Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21094</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u401, 8u401-perf, 11.0.22, 17.0.10, 21.0.2, 22; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.10, 21.0.2, 22; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.13 and  21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21094|2024-06-04T17:37:51.570Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21082|2024-06-04T17:37:50.333Z -- oracle%20corporation -- bi%20publisher%20%28formerly%20xml%20publisher%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21082</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle BI Publisher product of Oracle Analytics (component: XML Services).  Supported versions that are affected are 7.0.0.0.0 and  12.2.1.4.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle BI Publisher.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle BI Publisher. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 9.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21082|2024-06-04T17:37:50.333Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21016|2024-04-16T21:26:03.601Z -- oracle%20corporation -- complex%20maintenance%2C%20repair%2C%20and%20overhaul</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21016</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21016|2024-04-16T21:26:03.601Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21104|2024-04-16T21:26:33.597Z -- oracle%20corporation -- sun%20zfs%20storage%20appliance%20kit%20%28ak%29%20software</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21104</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle ZFS Storage Appliance Kit product of Oracle Systems (component: Core).   The supported version that is affected is 8.8. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle ZFS Storage Appliance Kit executes to compromise Oracle ZFS Storage Appliance Kit.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle ZFS Storage Appliance Kit. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:R/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21104|2024-04-16T21:26:33.597Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21041|2024-06-04T17:37:49.934Z -- oracle%20corporation -- complex%20maintenance%2C%20repair%2C%20and%20overhaul</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21041</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21041|2024-06-04T17:37:49.934Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21112|2024-04-16T21:26:36.221Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21112</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21112|2024-04-16T21:26:36.221Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21057|2024-06-04T17:37:49.526Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21057</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21057|2024-06-04T17:37:49.526Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21000|2024-04-16T21:25:57.876Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21000</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Security: Privileges).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of MySQL Server accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of MySQL Server accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.8 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21000|2024-04-16T21:25:57.876Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21077|2024-06-04T17:37:48.730Z -- oracle%20corporation -- trade%20management</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21077</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Trade Management product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: GL Accounts LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Trade Management.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Trade Management accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21077|2024-06-04T17:37:48.730Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21098|2024-04-16T21:26:31.636Z -- oracle%20corporation -- graalvm</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21098</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Compiler).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.10, 21.0.2, 22; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.13 and  21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21098|2024-04-16T21:26:31.636Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21020|2024-06-04T17:37:47.939Z -- oracle%20corporation -- complex%20maintenance%2C%20repair%2C%20and%20overhaul</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21020</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21020|2024-06-04T17:37:47.939Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21036|2024-04-16T21:26:10.429Z -- oracle%20corporation -- complex%20maintenance%2C%20repair%2C%20and%20overhaul</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21036</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21036|2024-04-16T21:26:10.429Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21061|2024-04-16T21:26:18.783Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21061</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Audit Plug-in).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21061|2024-04-16T21:26:18.783Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21108|2024-04-16T21:26:34.967Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21108</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.3 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21108|2024-04-16T21:26:34.967Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21109|2024-04-16T21:26:35.292Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21109</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.9 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21109|2024-04-16T21:26:35.292Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21060|2024-06-04T17:37:44.979Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21060</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Data Dictionary).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21060|2024-06-04T17:37:44.979Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21037|2024-06-04T17:37:43.771Z -- oracle%20corporation -- complex%20maintenance%2C%20repair%2C%20and%20overhaul</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21037</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21037|2024-06-04T17:37:43.771Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21021|2024-06-04T17:37:43.381Z -- oracle%20corporation -- complex%20maintenance%2C%20repair%2C%20and%20overhaul</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21021</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21021|2024-06-04T17:37:43.381Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21076|2024-04-16T21:26:24.099Z -- oracle%20corporation -- trade%20management</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21076</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Trade Management product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: Offer LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Trade Management.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Trade Management accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21076|2024-04-16T21:26:24.099Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21099|2024-04-16T21:26:31.973Z -- oracle%20corporation -- business%20intelligence%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21099</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Analytics (component: Data Visualization).   The supported version that is affected is 7.0.0.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.3 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21099|2024-04-16T21:26:31.973Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21001|2024-06-04T17:37:42.554Z -- oracle%20corporation -- business%20intelligence%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21001</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Analytics (component: BI Platform Security).   The supported version that is affected is 7.0.0.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21001|2024-06-04T17:37:42.554Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21113|2024-04-16T21:26:36.530Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21113</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21113|2024-04-16T21:26:36.530Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21056|2024-04-16T21:26:17.004Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21056</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DML).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.34 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21056|2024-04-16T21:26:17.004Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21105|2024-04-16T21:26:33.939Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21105</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Utility).   The supported version that is affected is 11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Solaris accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 2.0 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21105|2024-04-16T21:26:33.939Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21040|2024-06-04T17:37:42.146Z -- oracle%20corporation -- complex%20maintenance%2C%20repair%2C%20and%20overhaul</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21040</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21040|2024-06-04T17:37:42.146Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21017|2024-04-16T21:26:03.927Z -- oracle%20corporation -- complex%20maintenance%2C%20repair%2C%20and%20overhaul</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21017</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21017|2024-04-16T21:26:03.927Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21083|2024-04-16T21:26:26.424Z -- oracle%20corporation -- bi%20publisher%20%28formerly%20xml%20publisher%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21083</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle BI Publisher product of Oracle Analytics (component: Script Engine).  Supported versions that are affected are 7.0.0.0.0 and  12.2.1.4.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle BI Publisher.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle BI Publisher. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.2 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21083|2024-04-16T21:26:26.424Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21095|2024-06-04T17:37:40.121Z -- oracle%20corporation -- primavera%20p6%20enterprise%20project%20portfolio%20management</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21095</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Primavera P6 Enterprise Project Portfolio Management product of Oracle Construction and Engineering (component: Web Access).  Supported versions that are affected are 19.12.0-19.12.22, 20.12.0-20.12.21, 21.12.0-21.12.18, 22.12.0-22.12.12 and  23.12.0-23.12.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Primavera P6 Enterprise Project Portfolio Management.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Primavera P6 Enterprise Project Portfolio Management accessible data as well as  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Primavera P6 Enterprise Project Portfolio Management accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.2 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21095|2024-06-04T17:37:40.121Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21071|2024-04-16T21:26:22.479Z -- oracle%20corporation -- workflow</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21071</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Workflow product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: Admin Screens and Grants UI).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Workflow.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle Workflow, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle Workflow. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 9.1 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21071|2024-04-16T21:26:22.479Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21026|2024-04-16T21:26:06.948Z -- oracle%20corporation -- complex%20maintenance%2C%20repair%2C%20and%20overhaul</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21026</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21026|2024-04-16T21:26:06.948Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21030|2024-06-04T17:37:38.498Z -- oracle%20corporation -- complex%20maintenance%2C%20repair%2C%20and%20overhaul</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21030</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21030|2024-06-04T17:37:38.498Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21067|2024-04-16T21:26:21.067Z -- oracle%20corporation -- enterprise%20manager%20base%20platform</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21067</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Enterprise Manager Base Platform product of Oracle Enterprise Manager (component: Host Management).   The supported version that is affected is 13.5.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Enterprise Manager Base Platform executes to compromise Oracle Enterprise Manager Base Platform.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle Enterprise Manager Base Platform, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle Enterprise Manager Base Platform. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21067|2024-04-16T21:26:21.067Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21088|2024-04-16T21:26:28.130Z -- oracle%20corporation -- production%20scheduling</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21088</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Production Scheduling product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: Import Utility).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.4-12.2.12. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Production Scheduling.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle Production Scheduling accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21088|2024-04-16T21:26:28.130Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21118|2024-04-16T21:26:38.176Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21118</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Core).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.6 and  8.5.7. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Outside In Technology executes to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21118|2024-04-16T21:26:38.176Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21092|2024-04-16T21:26:29.408Z -- oracle%20corporation -- agile%20product%20lifecycle%20management%20for%20process</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21092</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Agile Product Lifecycle Management for Process product of Oracle Supply Chain (component: Product Quality Management).   The supported version that is affected is 6.2.4.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Agile Product Lifecycle Management for Process.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle Agile Product Lifecycle Management for Process accessible data as well as  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Agile Product Lifecycle Management for Process accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21092|2024-04-16T21:26:29.408Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21084|2024-06-04T17:37:36.857Z -- oracle%20corporation -- bi%20publisher%20%28formerly%20xml%20publisher%29</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21084</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle BI Publisher product of Oracle Analytics (component: Service Gateway).  Supported versions that are affected are 7.0.0.0.0 and  12.2.1.4.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle BI Publisher.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle BI Publisher, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle BI Publisher accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.8 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21084|2024-06-04T17:37:36.857Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21010|2024-04-16T21:26:01.542Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20simphony</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21010</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality Simphony product of Oracle Food and Beverage Applications (component: Simphony Enterprise Server).  Supported versions that are affected are 19.1.0-19.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Hospitality Simphony.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle Hospitality Simphony, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle Hospitality Simphony. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 9.9 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21010|2024-04-16T21:26:01.542Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21102|2024-06-04T17:37:36.436Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20ndb%20cluster</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21102</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Thread Pooling).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21102|2024-06-04T17:37:36.436Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21047|2024-04-16T21:26:14.113Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21047</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21047|2024-04-16T21:26:14.113Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21114|2024-04-16T21:26:36.879Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21114</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21114|2024-04-16T21:26:36.879Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21051|2024-06-04T17:37:36.010Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21051</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DML).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.34 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21051|2024-06-04T17:37:36.010Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21006|2024-06-04T17:37:35.590Z -- oracle%20corporation -- weblogic%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21006</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle WebLogic Server product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.1.4.0 and  14.1.1.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via T3, IIOP to compromise Oracle WebLogic Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle WebLogic Server accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21006|2024-06-04T17:37:35.590Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21007|2024-04-16T21:26:00.320Z -- oracle%20corporation -- weblogic%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21007</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle WebLogic Server product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.1.4.0 and  14.1.1.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via T3, IIOP to compromise Oracle WebLogic Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle WebLogic Server accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21007|2024-04-16T21:26:00.320Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21115|2024-04-16T21:26:37.191Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21115</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21115|2024-04-16T21:26:37.191Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21050|2024-06-04T17:37:32.693Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21050</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DML).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.34 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21050|2024-06-04T17:37:32.693Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21103|2024-04-16T21:26:33.292Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21103</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. Note: This vulnerability applies to Linux hosts only. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21103|2024-04-16T21:26:33.292Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21046|2024-06-04T17:37:32.302Z -- oracle%20corporation -- complex%20maintenance%2C%20repair%2C%20and%20overhaul</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21046</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21046|2024-06-04T17:37:32.302Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21011|2024-04-16T21:26:01.896Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21011</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u401, 8u401-perf, 11.0.22, 17.0.10, 21.0.2, 22; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.10, 21.0.2, 22;   Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.13 and  21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21011|2024-04-16T21:26:01.896Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21085|2024-04-16T21:26:27.090Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21085</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Concurrency).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u401, 8u401-perf, 11.0.22; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.13 and  21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21085|2024-04-16T21:26:27.090Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21093|2024-06-04T17:37:30.191Z -- oracle%20corporation -- database%20-%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21093</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java VM component of Oracle Database Server.  Supported versions that are affected are 19.3-19.22 and  21.3-21.13. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker having Create Session, Create Procedure privilege with network access via Oracle Net to compromise Java VM.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Java VM accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21093|2024-06-04T17:37:30.191Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21119|2024-04-16T21:26:38.497Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21119</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Core).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.6 and  8.5.7. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Outside In Technology executes to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21119|2024-04-16T21:26:38.497Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21066|2024-06-04T17:37:28.548Z -- oracle%20corporation -- database%20-%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21066</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the RDBMS component of Oracle Database Server.  Supported versions that are affected are 19.3-19.22 and  21.3-21.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker having Authenticated User privilege with logon to the infrastructure where RDBMS executes to compromise RDBMS.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all RDBMS accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.2 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:R/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21066|2024-06-04T17:37:28.548Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21089|2024-06-04T17:37:28.142Z -- oracle%20corporation -- concurrent%20processing</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21089</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Concurrent Processing product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: Request Submission and Scheduling).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Concurrent Processing.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Concurrent Processing accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21089|2024-06-04T17:37:28.142Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21031|2024-06-04T17:37:27.739Z -- oracle%20corporation -- complex%20maintenance%2C%20repair%2C%20and%20overhaul</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21031</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21031|2024-06-04T17:37:27.739Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21027|2024-04-16T21:26:07.262Z -- oracle%20corporation -- complex%20maintenance%2C%20repair%2C%20and%20overhaul</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21027</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21027|2024-04-16T21:26:07.262Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21070|2024-04-16T21:26:22.131Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21070</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools product of Oracle PeopleSoft (component: Search Framework).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.59, 8.60 and  8.61. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21070|2024-04-16T21:26:22.131Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21025|2024-06-13T20:46:28.565Z -- oracle%20corporation -- complex%20maintenance%2C%20repair%2C%20and%20overhaul</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21025</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21025|2024-06-13T20:46:28.565Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21108|2024-06-13T20:14:08.699Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21108</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.3 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21108|2024-06-13T20:14:08.699Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21085|2024-06-13T20:36:00.856Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21085</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Concurrency).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u401, 8u401-perf, 11.0.22; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.13 and  21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21085|2024-06-13T20:36:00.856Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21026|2024-06-13T20:45:10.225Z -- oracle%20corporation -- complex%20maintenance%2C%20repair%2C%20and%20overhaul</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21026</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: LOV).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.3-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Complex Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21026|2024-06-13T20:45:10.225Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21056|2024-06-13T20:44:04.573Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21056</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DML).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.34 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21056|2024-06-13T20:44:04.573Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21080|2024-06-13T20:37:51.548Z -- oracle%20corporation -- applications%20framework</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21080</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Applications Framework product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: REST Services).  Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.9-12.2.13. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Applications Framework.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Applications Framework accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21080|2024-06-13T20:37:51.548Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21061|2024-06-13T20:41:03.231Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21061</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Audit Plug-in).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21061|2024-06-13T20:41:03.231Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21099|2024-06-13T20:26:14.788Z -- oracle%20corporation -- business%20intelligence%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21099</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Analytics (component: Data Visualization).   The supported version that is affected is 7.0.0.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.3 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21099|2024-06-13T20:26:14.788Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20993|2024-06-17T18:08:46.736Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20993</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20993|2024-06-17T18:08:46.736Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21005|2024-06-17T18:07:05.474Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21005</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: JavaFX).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u401; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.13 and  21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.1 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21005|2024-06-17T18:07:05.474Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21121|2024-06-26T03:55:33.081Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21121</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21121|2024-06-26T03:55:33.081Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
