<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- Banking Digital Experience</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/banking%20digital%20experience.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- Banking Digital Experience</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 20:23:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3019|2024-10-01T16:21:35.079Z -- oracle%20corporation -- banking%20digital%20experience
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3019</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Banking Digital Experience product of Oracle Financial Services Applications (component: Loan Calculator). Supported versions that are affected are 18.1, 18.2, 18.3 and 19.1. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Banking Digital Experience. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Banking Digital Experience, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Banking Digital Experience accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Banking Digital Experience accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3019|2024-10-01T16:21:35.079Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 17:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
