<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- BI Publisher (formerly XML Publisher)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/bi%20publisher%20%28formerly%20xml%20publisher%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- BI Publisher (formerly XML Publisher)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 20:24:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2768|2024-10-15T18:58:28.895Z -- oracle%20corporation -- bi%20publisher%20%28formerly%20xml%20publisher%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2768</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the BI Publisher (formerly XML Publisher) component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: BI Publisher Security). The supported version that is affected is 11.1.1.9.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise BI Publisher (formerly XML Publisher). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all BI Publisher (formerly XML Publisher) accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2768|2024-10-15T18:58:28.895Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 22:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2742|2024-10-15T19:00:20.341Z -- oracle%20corporation -- bi%20publisher%20%28formerly%20xml%20publisher%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2742</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle BI Publisher component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Web Service API). The supported version that is affected is 11.1.1.9.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle BI Publisher. While the vulnerability is in Oracle BI Publisher, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle BI Publisher accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle BI Publisher accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.2 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2742|2024-10-15T19:00:20.341Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 22:31:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2767|2024-10-15T18:58:41.433Z -- oracle%20corporation -- bi%20publisher%20%28formerly%20xml%20publisher%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2767</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the BI Publisher (formerly XML Publisher) component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: BI Publisher Security). The supported version that is affected are 11.1.1.9.0, 12.2.1.3.0 and 12.2.1.4.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise BI Publisher (formerly XML Publisher). While the vulnerability is in BI Publisher (formerly XML Publisher), attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of BI Publisher (formerly XML Publisher) accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of BI Publisher (formerly XML Publisher) accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.2 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2767|2024-10-15T18:58:41.433Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 22:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
