<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/business%20intelligence%20enterprise%20edition.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 16:24:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22082|2024-08-02T09:59:29.144Z -- oracle%20corporation -- business%20intelligence%20enterprise%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22082</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Analytics (component: Pod Admin).  Supported versions that are affected are 6.4.0.0.0 and  7.0.0.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22082|2024-08-02T09:59:29.144Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 21:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-21965|2024-08-02T09:59:28.698Z -- oracle%20corporation -- business%20intelligence%20enterprise%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21965</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Analytics (component: Analytics Server).   The supported version that is affected is 6.4.0.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.7 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-21965|2024-08-02T09:59:28.698Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 19:54:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-21861|2024-08-02T09:51:51.301Z -- oracle%20corporation -- business%20intelligence%20enterprise%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21861</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Visual Analyzer).  Supported versions that are affected are 5.9.0.0.0 and  6.4.0.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-21861|2024-08-02T09:51:51.301Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 23:35:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-21910|2024-08-02T09:51:51.408Z -- oracle%20corporation -- business%20intelligence%20enterprise%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21910</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Analytics (component: Analytics Web General).  Supported versions that are affected are 6.4.0.0.0 and  12.2.1.4.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-21910|2024-08-02T09:51:51.408Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 19:54:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22012|2024-08-02T09:59:28.713Z -- oracle%20corporation -- business%20intelligence%20enterprise%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22012</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Analytics (component: Analytics Server).   The supported version that is affected is 7.0.0.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.3 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22012|2024-08-02T09:59:28.713Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 20:18:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22013|2024-08-02T09:59:28.793Z -- oracle%20corporation -- business%20intelligence%20enterprise%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22013</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Analytics (component: Analytics Server).  Supported versions that are affected are 6.4.0.0.0 and  7.0.0.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.3 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22013|2024-08-02T09:59:28.793Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 20:18:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-21892|2024-08-02T09:51:51.428Z -- oracle%20corporation -- business%20intelligence%20enterprise%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21892</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Visual Analyzer).  Supported versions that are affected are 5.9.0.0.0 and  6.4.0.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-21892|2024-08-02T09:51:51.428Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 23:35:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22011|2024-08-02T09:59:28.684Z -- oracle%20corporation -- business%20intelligence%20enterprise%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22011</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Analytics (component: Analytics Server).  Supported versions that are affected are 6.4.0.0.0 and  7.0.0.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22011|2024-08-02T09:59:28.684Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 20:18:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-21952|2024-08-02T09:59:28.623Z -- oracle%20corporation -- business%20intelligence%20enterprise%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21952</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Analytics (component: Analytics Server).   The supported version that is affected is 6.4.0.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.7 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-21952|2024-08-02T09:59:28.623Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 19:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22021|2024-08-02T09:59:28.895Z -- oracle%20corporation -- business%20intelligence%20enterprise%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22021</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Analytics (component: Analytics Server).  Supported versions that are affected are 6.4.0.0.0 and  7.0.0.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.3 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22021|2024-08-02T09:59:28.895Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 20:18:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22020|2024-08-02T09:59:28.617Z -- oracle%20corporation -- business%20intelligence%20enterprise%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22020</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Analytics (component: Analytics Server).  Supported versions that are affected are 6.4.0.0.0 and  7.0.0.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22020|2024-08-02T09:59:28.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 20:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22027|2024-08-02T09:59:28.706Z -- oracle%20corporation -- business%20intelligence%20enterprise%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22027</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Analytics (component: Analytics Server).   The supported version that is affected is 7.0.0.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.3 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22027|2024-08-02T09:59:28.706Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 20:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22109|2024-08-02T09:59:29.121Z -- oracle%20corporation -- business%20intelligence%20enterprise%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22109</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Analytics (component: Analytics Web Dashboards).  Supported versions that are affected are 6.4.0.0.0, 7.0.0.0.0 and  12.2.1.4.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.6 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22109|2024-08-02T09:59:29.121Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 21:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-21891|2024-08-02T09:51:51.212Z -- oracle%20corporation -- business%20intelligence%20enterprise%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21891</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Visual Analyzer).  Supported versions that are affected are 5.9.0.0.0 and  6.4.0.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-21891|2024-08-02T09:51:51.212Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 23:35:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22061|2024-08-02T09:59:29.027Z -- oracle%20corporation -- business%20intelligence%20enterprise%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22061</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Analytics (component: Visual Analyzer).   The supported version that is affected is 6.4.0.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22061|2024-08-02T09:59:29.027Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 20:18:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21139|2024-07-22T14:39:18.042Z -- oracle%20corporation -- business%20intelligence%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21139</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Analytics (component: Analytics Web Answers).  Supported versions that are affected are 7.0.0.0.0, 7.6.0.0.0 and  12.2.1.4.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21139|2024-07-22T14:39:18.042Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20913|2024-07-05T17:20:57.944Z -- oracle%20corporation -- business%20intelligence%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20913</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Analytics (component: BI Platform Security).   The supported version that is affected is 12.2.1.4.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20913|2024-07-05T17:20:57.944Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20913|2024-02-17T01:50:09.197Z -- oracle%20corporation -- business%20intelligence%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20913</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Analytics (component: BI Platform Security).   The supported version that is affected is 12.2.1.4.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20913|2024-02-17T01:50:09.197Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21064|2024-06-04T17:38:04.816Z -- oracle%20corporation -- business%20intelligence%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21064</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Analytics (component: Analytics Web Answers).  Supported versions that are affected are 7.0.0.0.0 and  12.2.1.4.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21064|2024-06-04T17:38:04.816Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21099|2024-04-16T21:26:31.973Z -- oracle%20corporation -- business%20intelligence%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21099</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Analytics (component: Data Visualization).   The supported version that is affected is 7.0.0.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.3 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21099|2024-04-16T21:26:31.973Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21001|2024-06-04T17:37:42.554Z -- oracle%20corporation -- business%20intelligence%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21001</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Analytics (component: BI Platform Security).   The supported version that is affected is 7.0.0.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21001|2024-06-04T17:37:42.554Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21099|2024-06-13T20:26:14.788Z -- oracle%20corporation -- business%20intelligence%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21099</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Analytics (component: Data Visualization).   The supported version that is affected is 7.0.0.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.3 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21099|2024-06-13T20:26:14.788Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21139|2024-07-16T22:39:56.549Z -- oracle%20corporation -- business%20intelligence%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21139</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Analytics (component: Analytics Web Answers).  Supported versions that are affected are 7.0.0.0.0, 7.6.0.0.0 and  12.2.1.4.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21139|2024-07-16T22:39:56.549Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21064|2024-08-01T22:13:42.363Z -- oracle%20corporation -- business%20intelligence%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21064</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Analytics (component: Analytics Web Answers).  Supported versions that are affected are 7.0.0.0.0 and  12.2.1.4.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21064|2024-08-01T22:13:42.363Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21099|2024-08-01T22:13:42.655Z -- oracle%20corporation -- business%20intelligence%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21099</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Analytics (component: Data Visualization).   The supported version that is affected is 7.0.0.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.3 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21099|2024-08-01T22:13:42.655Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21001|2024-08-01T22:13:41.459Z -- oracle%20corporation -- business%20intelligence%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21001</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Analytics (component: BI Platform Security).   The supported version that is affected is 7.0.0.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21001|2024-08-01T22:13:41.459Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21139|2024-08-01T22:13:42.886Z -- oracle%20corporation -- business%20intelligence%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21139</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Analytics (component: Analytics Web Answers).  Supported versions that are affected are 7.0.0.0.0, 7.6.0.0.0 and  12.2.1.4.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21139|2024-08-01T22:13:42.886Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20913|2024-08-01T22:06:37.345Z -- oracle%20corporation -- business%20intelligence%20enterprise%20edition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20913</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Analytics (component: BI Platform Security).   The supported version that is affected is 12.2.1.4.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Business Intelligence Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20913|2024-08-01T22:06:37.345Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
