<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- Commerce Platform</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/commerce%20platform.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- Commerce Platform</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 20:23:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2659|2024-08-04T18:56:45.487Z -- oracle%20corporation -- commerce%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2659</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Commerce Platform component of Oracle Commerce (subcomponent: Dynamo Application Framework). The supported version that is affected is 11.2.0.3. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Commerce Platform. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Commerce Platform, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Commerce Platform accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Commerce Platform accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2659|2024-08-04T18:56:45.487Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 18:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2712|2024-08-04T18:56:45.638Z -- oracle%20corporation -- commerce%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2712</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Commerce Platform component of Oracle Commerce (subcomponent: Dynamo Application Framework). Supported versions that are affected are 11.2.0.3 and 11.3.1. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Commerce Platform. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Commerce Platform, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Commerce Platform accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Commerce Platform accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2712|2024-08-04T18:56:45.638Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 18:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14533|2024-08-04T12:46:34.788Z -- oracle%20corporation -- commerce%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14533</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Commerce Platform product of Oracle Commerce (component: Dynamo Application Framework). Supported versions that are affected are 11.1, 11.2 and prior to 11.3.1. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Commerce Platform. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Commerce Platform accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Commerce Platform accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.5 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14533|2024-08-04T12:46:34.788Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14532|2024-08-04T12:46:34.689Z -- oracle%20corporation -- commerce%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14532</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Commerce Platform product of Oracle Commerce (component: Dynamo Application Framework). Supported versions that are affected are 11.1, 11.2 and prior to 11.3.1. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Commerce Platform. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Commerce Platform, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Commerce Platform accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.7 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14532|2024-08-04T12:46:34.689Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14535|2024-08-04T12:46:34.654Z -- oracle%20corporation -- commerce%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14535</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Commerce Service Center product of Oracle Commerce (component: Commerce Service Center). Supported versions that are affected are 11.1, 11.2 and prior to 11.3.1. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Commerce Service Center. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle Commerce Service Center accessible data as well as unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Commerce Service Center accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14535|2024-08-04T12:46:34.654Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21100|2024-07-15T20:03:35.359Z -- oracle%20corporation -- commerce%20platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21100</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Commerce Platform product of Oracle Commerce (component: Platform).  Supported versions that are affected are 11.3.0, 11.3.1 and  11.3.2. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Commerce Platform.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle Commerce Platform, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Commerce Platform accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.0 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21100|2024-07-15T20:03:35.359Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21100|2024-04-16T21:26:32.274Z -- oracle%20corporation -- commerce%20platform</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21100</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Commerce Platform product of Oracle Commerce (component: Platform).  Supported versions that are affected are 11.3.0, 11.3.1 and  11.3.2. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Commerce Platform.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle Commerce Platform, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Commerce Platform accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.0 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21100|2024-04-16T21:26:32.274Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21100|2024-08-01T22:13:42.367Z -- oracle%20corporation -- commerce%20platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21100</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Commerce Platform product of Oracle Commerce (component: Platform).  Supported versions that are affected are 11.3.0, 11.3.1 and  11.3.2. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Commerce Platform.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle Commerce Platform, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Commerce Platform accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.0 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21100|2024-08-01T22:13:42.367Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
