<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- Enterprise Manager Ops Center</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/enterprise%20manager%20ops%20center.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- Enterprise Manager Ops Center</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 23:22:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2728|2024-10-01T16:46:03.929Z -- oracle%20corporation -- enterprise%20manager%20ops%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2728</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Enterprise Manager Ops Center component of Oracle Enterprise Manager Products Suite (subcomponent: Networking). Supported versions that are affected are 12.3.3 and 12.4.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Enterprise Manager Ops Center. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Enterprise Manager Ops Center accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.3 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2728|2024-10-01T16:46:03.929Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 22:31:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2726|2024-10-01T16:47:11.757Z -- oracle%20corporation -- enterprise%20manager%20ops%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2726</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Enterprise Manager Ops Center component of Oracle Enterprise Manager Products Suite (subcomponent: Services Integration). The supported version that is affected is 12.3.3. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Enterprise Manager Ops Center. While the vulnerability is in Enterprise Manager Ops Center, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Enterprise Manager Ops Center. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.3 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2726|2024-10-01T16:47:11.757Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 16:24:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
