<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- Financial Services Crime and Compliance Investigation Hub</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/financial%20services%20crime%20and%20compliance%20investigation%20hub.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- Financial Services Crime and Compliance Investigation Hub</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:22:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-2448|2024-08-03T16:45:50.463Z -- oracle%20corporation -- financial%20services%20crime%20and%20compliance%20investigation%20hub
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-2448</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Financial Services Crime and Compliance Investigation Hub product of Oracle Financial Services Applications (component: Reports). The supported version that is affected is 20.1.2. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Financial Services Crime and Compliance Investigation Hub executes to compromise Oracle Financial Services Crime and Compliance Investigation Hub. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Financial Services Crime and Compliance Investigation Hub, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Financial Services Crime and Compliance Investigation Hub accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Financial Services Crime and Compliance Investigation Hub accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:H/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-2448|2024-08-03T16:45:50.463Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 22:44:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
