<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- Financial Services Analytical Applications Infrastructure</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/financial%20services%20analytical%20applications%20infrastructure.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- Financial Services Analytical Applications Infrastructure</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 17:22:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-2140|2024-08-03T16:32:03.180Z -- oracle%20corporation -- financial%20services%20analytical%20applications%20infrastructure
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-2140</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Financial Services Analytical Applications Infrastructure product of Oracle Financial Services Applications (component: Rules Framework). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.6-8.1.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Financial Services Analytical Applications Infrastructure. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Financial Services Analytical Applications Infrastructure, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Financial Services Analytical Applications Infrastructure accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Financial Services Analytical Applications Infrastructure accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-2140|2024-08-03T16:32:03.180Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 21:53:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
