<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- FLEXCUBE Direct Banking</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/flexcube%20direct%20banking.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- FLEXCUBE Direct Banking</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:22:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2979|2024-08-04T19:12:08.479Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20direct%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2979</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Direct Banking product of Oracle Financial Services Applications (component: Payments). Supported versions that are affected are 12.0.2 and 12.0.3. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Direct Banking. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle FLEXCUBE Direct Banking accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.7 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2979|2024-08-04T19:12:08.479Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 17:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2980|2024-08-04T19:12:08.417Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20direct%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2980</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Direct Banking product of Oracle Financial Services Applications (component: eMail). Supported versions that are affected are 12.0.2 and 12.0.3. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Direct Banking. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle FLEXCUBE Direct Banking accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2980|2024-08-04T19:12:08.417Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 17:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2550|2024-08-04T18:56:44.003Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20direct%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2550</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Direct Banking component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Logoff Page). The supported version that is affected is 12.0.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Direct Banking. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle FLEXCUBE Direct Banking accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.3 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2550|2024-08-04T18:56:44.003Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14890|2024-08-04T13:00:51.660Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20direct%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14890</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Direct Banking product of Oracle Financial Services Applications (component: Pre Login). Supported versions that are affected are 12.0.1, 12.0.2 and 12.0.3. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Direct Banking. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle FLEXCUBE Direct Banking accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14890|2024-08-04T13:00:51.660Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 14:04:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2549|2024-08-04T18:49:48.340Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20direct%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2549</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Direct Banking component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Logoff Page). The supported version that is affected is 12.0.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Direct Banking. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle FLEXCUBE Direct Banking, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle FLEXCUBE Direct Banking accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle FLEXCUBE Direct Banking accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2549|2024-08-04T18:49:48.340Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14897|2024-08-04T13:00:51.537Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20direct%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14897</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Direct Banking product of Oracle Financial Services Applications (component: Pre Login). Supported versions that are affected are 12.0.1, 12.0.2 and 12.0.3. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Direct Banking. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle FLEXCUBE Direct Banking accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14897|2024-08-04T13:00:51.537Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 14:04:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
