<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- FLEXCUBE Universal Banking</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/flexcube%20universal%20banking.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- FLEXCUBE Universal Banking</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 20:22:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10098|2024-08-05T17:33:15.131Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20universal%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10098</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Infrastructure). Supported versions that are affected are 11.3.0, 11.4.0, 12.0.1, 12.0.2, 12.0.3, 12.1.0, 12.2.0 and 12.3.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10098|2024-08-05T17:33:15.131Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2749|2024-08-05T04:29:44.077Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20universal%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2749</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Banking Corporate Lending component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Core module). Supported versions that are affected are 12.3.0, 12.4.0, 12.5.0 and 14.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Banking Corporate Lending. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Banking Corporate Lending, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Banking Corporate Lending accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Banking Corporate Lending accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2749|2024-08-05T04:29:44.077Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3482|2024-08-05T14:30:57.518Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20universal%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3482</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Infrastructure). Supported versions that are affected are 12.0.0, 12.0.1, 12.0.2, 12.0.3, 12.1.0, 12.2.0 and 12.3.0. Easily "exploitable" vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3482|2024-08-05T14:30:57.518Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3485|2024-08-05T14:30:57.506Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20universal%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3485</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Infrastructure). Supported versions that are affected are 11.3.0, 11.4.0, 12.0.0, 12.0.1, 12.0.2, 12.0.3, 12.1.0 and 12.2.0. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.8 (Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3485|2024-08-05T14:30:57.506Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3015|2024-08-05T04:36:39.505Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20universal%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3015</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Infrastructure). Supported versions that are affected are 11.3.0, 11.4.0, 12.0.1, 12.0.2, 12.0.3, 12.1.0, 12.2.0, 12.3.0, 12.4.0, 14.0.0 and 14.1.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data as well as unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3015|2024-08-05T04:36:39.505Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2982|2024-08-05T04:36:39.559Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20universal%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2982</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Infrastructure). Supported versions that are affected are 11.3.0, 11.4.0, 12.0.1, 12.0.2, 12.0.3, 12.1.0, 12.2.0, 12.3.0, 12.4.0, 14.0.0 and 14.1.0. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2982|2024-08-05T04:36:39.559Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3481|2024-08-05T14:30:57.621Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20universal%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3481</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Infrastructure). Supported versions that are affected are 11.3.0, 11.4.0 and 12.0.1. Easily "exploitable" vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.3 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3481|2024-08-05T14:30:57.621Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2748|2024-08-05T04:29:44.083Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20universal%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2748</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Banking Corporate Lending component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Core module). Supported versions that are affected are 12.3.0, 12.4.0, 12.5.0 and 14.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Banking Corporate Lending. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Banking Corporate Lending, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Banking Corporate Lending accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Banking Corporate Lending accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2748|2024-08-05T04:29:44.083Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2746|2024-08-05T04:29:44.412Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20universal%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2746</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Banking Corporate Lending component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Core module). Supported versions that are affected are 12.3.0, 12.4.0, 12.5.0 and 14.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Banking Corporate Lending. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Banking Corporate Lending accessible data as well as unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Banking Corporate Lending accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2746|2024-08-05T04:29:44.412Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10073|2024-08-05T17:25:00.873Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20universal%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10073</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Infrastructure). Supported versions that are affected are 11.3.0, 11.4.0, 12.0.1, 12.0.2, 12.0.3, 12.1.0, 12.2.0 and 12.3.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10073|2024-08-05T17:25:00.873Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3534|2024-08-05T14:30:58.150Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20universal%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3534</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Infrastructure). Supported versions that are affected are 12.0.1, 12.0.2, 12.0.3, 12.1.0, 12.2.0 and 12.3.0. Easily "exploitable" vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3534|2024-08-05T14:30:58.150Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10085|2024-08-05T17:25:00.911Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20universal%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10085</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Infrastructure). Supported versions that are affected are 11.3.0, 11.4.0, 12.0.1, 12.0.2, 12.0.3, 12.1.0, 12.2.0 and 12.3.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data as well as unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10085|2024-08-05T17:25:00.911Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2979|2024-08-05T04:36:39.128Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20universal%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2979</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Infrastructure). Supported versions that are affected are 11.3.0, 11.4.0, 12.0.1, 12.0.2, 12.0.3, 12.1.0, 12.2.0, 12.3.0, 12.4.0, 14.0.0 and 14.1.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2979|2024-08-05T04:36:39.128Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2981|2024-08-05T04:36:39.528Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20universal%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2981</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Infrastructure). Supported versions that are affected are 11.3.0, 11.4.0, 12.0.1, 12.0.2, 12.0.3, 12.1.0, 12.2.0, 12.3.0, 12.4.0, 14.0.0 and 14.1.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2981|2024-08-05T04:36:39.528Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2648|2024-08-05T04:21:34.590Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20universal%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2648</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Infrastructure). Supported versions that are affected are 11.3.0, 11.4.0, 12.0.1, 12.0.2, 12.0.3, 12.1.0, 12.2.0, 12.3.0 and 12.4.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2648|2024-08-05T04:21:34.590Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2975|2024-08-05T04:36:39.191Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20universal%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2975</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Infrastructure). Supported versions that are affected are 11.3.0, 11.4.0, 12.0.1, 12.0.2, 12.0.3, 12.1.0, 12.2.0, 12.3.0, 12.4.0, 14.0.0 and 14.1.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2975|2024-08-05T04:36:39.191Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10083|2024-08-05T17:25:00.662Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20universal%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10083</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Infrastructure). Supported versions that are affected are 11.3.0, 11.4.0, 12.0.1, 12.0.2, 12.0.3, 12.1.0, 12.2.0 and 12.3.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10083|2024-08-05T17:25:00.662Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2974|2024-08-05T04:36:39.177Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20universal%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2974</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Infrastructure). Supported versions that are affected are 11.3.0, 11.4.0, 12.0.1, 12.0.2, 12.0.3, 12.1.0, 12.2.0, 12.3.0, 12.4.0, 14.0.0 and 14.1.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2974|2024-08-05T04:36:39.177Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3494|2024-08-05T14:30:57.561Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20universal%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3494</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Retail Teller). Supported versions that are affected are 11.3.0, 11.4.0, 12.0.1, 12.0.2 and 12.0.3. Easily "exploitable" vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.7 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3494|2024-08-05T14:30:57.561Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10363|2024-08-05T17:41:55.271Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20universal%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10363</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Security). Supported versions that are affected are 11.3, 11.4.0, 12.0.1, 12.0.2, 12.0.3, 12.1.0, 12.2.0, 12.3.0 and 12.4.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data as well as unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data. Note: Contact Support for fixes. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10363|2024-08-05T17:41:55.271Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3019|2024-08-05T04:36:39.570Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20universal%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3019</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Infrastructure). Supported versions that are affected are 11.3.0, 11.4.0, 12.0.1, 12.0.2, 12.0.3, 12.1.0, 12.2.0, 12.3.0, 12.4.0, 14.0.0 and 14.1.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3019|2024-08-05T04:36:39.570Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2630|2024-08-05T04:21:34.412Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20universal%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2630</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Security Management System). Supported versions that are affected are 11.5.0, 11.6.0 and 11.7.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2630|2024-08-05T04:21:34.412Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2980|2024-08-05T04:36:39.561Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20universal%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2980</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Infrastructure). Supported versions that are affected are 11.3.0, 11.4.0, 12.0.1, 12.0.2, 12.0.3, 12.1.0, 12.2.0, 12.3.0, 12.4.0, 14.0.0 and 14.1.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.4 (Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2980|2024-08-05T04:36:39.561Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2747|2024-08-05T04:29:44.446Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20universal%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2747</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Banking Corporate Lending component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Core module). Supported versions that are affected are 12.3.0, 12.4.0, 12.5.0 and 14.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Banking Corporate Lending. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Banking Corporate Lending accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2747|2024-08-05T04:29:44.446Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10084|2024-08-05T17:25:00.754Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20universal%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10084</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Report Generator). Supported versions that are affected are 11.3.0, 11.4.0, 12.0.1, 12.0.2, 12.0.3, 12.1.0, 12.2.0 and 12.3.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10084|2024-08-05T17:25:00.754Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10072|2024-08-05T17:25:00.957Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20universal%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10072</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: All Modules). Supported versions that are affected are 11.3.0, 11.4.0, 12.0.1, 12.0.2, 12.0.3, 12.1.0, 12.2.0 and 12.3.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10072|2024-08-05T17:25:00.957Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2614|2024-08-05T04:21:34.591Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20universal%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2614</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Infrastructure). Supported versions that are affected are 11.3.0, 11.4.0, 12.0.1, 12.0.2, 12.0.3, 12.1.0, 12.2.0, 12.3.0 and 12.4.0. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2614|2024-08-05T04:21:34.591Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3480|2024-08-05T14:30:57.474Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20universal%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3480</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Infrastructure). Supported versions that are affected are 11.3.0, 11.4.0 and 12.0.1. Easily "exploitable" vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.7 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3480|2024-08-05T14:30:57.474Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2649|2024-08-05T04:21:34.424Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20universal%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2649</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Infrastructure). Supported versions that are affected are 11.3.0, 11.4.0, 12.0.1, 12.0.2, 12.0.3, 12.1.0, 12.2.0, 12.3.0 and 12.4.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.1 (Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2649|2024-08-05T04:21:34.424Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3535|2024-08-05T14:30:58.122Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20universal%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3535</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Infrastructure). Supported versions that are affected are 11.3.0, 11.4.0, 12.0.1, 12.0.2 and 12.0.3. Easily "exploitable" vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.7 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3535|2024-08-05T14:30:58.122Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10071|2024-08-05T17:25:00.869Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20universal%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10071</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: All Modules). Supported versions that are affected are 11.3.0, 11.4.0, 12.0.1, 12.0.2, 12.0.3, 12.1.0, 12.2.0 and 12.3.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.3 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10071|2024-08-05T17:25:00.869Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2899|2024-08-05T04:36:38.991Z -- oracle%20corporation -- flexcube%20universal%20banking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2899</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking component of Oracle Financial Services Applications (subcomponent: Infrastructure). Supported versions that are affected are 11.3.0, 11.4.0, 12.0.1, 12.0.2, 12.0.3, 12.1.0, 12.2.0, 12.3.0, 12.4.0, 14.0.0 and 14.1.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle FLEXCUBE Universal Banking accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2899|2024-08-05T04:36:38.991Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
