<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- GraalVM</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/graalvm.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- GraalVM</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 22:02:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-20954|2024-04-16T21:25:05.152Z -- Oracle Corporation -- GraalVM
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20954</link><description>Vulnerability in the Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Compiler).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.10, 21.0.2, 22; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.13 and  21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20954|2024-04-16T21:25:05.152Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21098|2024-04-16T21:26:31.636Z -- Oracle Corporation -- GraalVM
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21098</link><description>Vulnerability in the Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Compiler).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.10, 21.0.2, 22; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.13 and  21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21098|2024-04-16T21:26:31.636Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:31 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>