<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- GraalVM Enterprise Edition</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/graalvm%20enterprise%20edition.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- GraalVM Enterprise Edition</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 21:21:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21634|2024-08-03T02:46:39.382Z -- oracle%20corporation -- graalvm%20enterprise%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21634</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: LLVM Interpreter). Supported versions that are affected are Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.7, 21.3.3 and 22.2.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21634|2024-08-03T02:46:39.382Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21597|2024-08-03T02:46:38.585Z -- oracle%20corporation -- graalvm%20enterprise%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21597</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: JavaScript). Supported versions that are affected are Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.7, 21.3.3 and 22.2.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21597|2024-08-03T02:46:38.585Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
