<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- GraalVM Enterprise Edition</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/graalvm%20enterprise%20edition.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- GraalVM Enterprise Edition</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 15:22:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2900|2024-08-04T07:23:59.865Z -- oracle%20corporation -- graalvm%20enterprise%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2900</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle GraalVM (component: Tools). Supported versions that are affected are 19.3.1 and 20.0.0. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 3.7 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:L/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2900|2024-08-04T07:23:59.865Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2799|2024-08-04T07:17:02.892Z -- oracle%20corporation -- graalvm%20enterprise%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2799</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle GraalVM (component: GraalVM Compiler). Supported versions that are affected are 19.3.1 and 20.0.0. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition. While the vulnerability is in Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.3 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2799|2024-08-04T07:17:02.892Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2581|2024-08-04T07:09:54.759Z -- oracle%20corporation -- graalvm%20enterprise%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2581</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle GraalVM (component: LLVM Interpreter). The supported version that is affected is 19.3.0.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition executes to compromise Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.0 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2581|2024-08-04T07:09:54.759Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2802|2024-08-04T07:17:02.633Z -- oracle%20corporation -- graalvm%20enterprise%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2802</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle GraalVM (component: GraalVM Compiler). Supported versions that are affected are 19.3.1 and 20.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition. While the vulnerability is in Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.7 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2802|2024-08-04T07:17:02.633Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2595|2024-08-04T07:09:54.888Z -- oracle%20corporation -- graalvm%20enterprise%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2595</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle GraalVM (component: GraalVM Compiler). The supported version that is affected is 19.3.0.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition. While the vulnerability is in Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.8 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2595|2024-08-04T07:09:54.888Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14718|2024-08-04T12:53:43.234Z -- oracle%20corporation -- graalvm%20enterprise%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14718</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle GraalVM (component: JVMCI). Supported versions that are affected are 19.3.2 and 20.1.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.2 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14718|2024-08-04T12:53:43.234Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
