<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- Hospitality Guest Access</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/hospitality%20guest%20access.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- Hospitality Guest Access</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:23:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10219|2024-08-05T17:33:16.919Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20guest%20access
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10219</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality Guest Access component of Oracle Hospitality Applications (subcomponent: Base). Supported versions that are affected are 4.2.0.0 and 4.2.1.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Hospitality Guest Access executes to compromise Oracle Hospitality Guest Access. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Hospitality Guest Access accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10219|2024-08-05T17:33:16.919Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10383|2024-08-05T17:41:54.761Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20guest%20access
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10383</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality Guest Access component of Oracle Hospitality Applications (subcomponent: Interface). Supported versions that are affected are 4.2.0 and 4.2.1. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Hospitality Guest Access. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Hospitality Guest Access accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10383|2024-08-05T17:41:54.761Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2607|2024-08-05T04:21:34.584Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20guest%20access
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2607</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality Guest Access component of Oracle Hospitality Applications (subcomponent: Base). The supported version that is affected is 4.2.1. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Hospitality Guest Access. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Hospitality Guest Access. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2607|2024-08-05T04:21:34.584Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10218|2024-08-05T17:33:16.989Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20guest%20access
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10218</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality Guest Access component of Oracle Hospitality Applications (subcomponent: Base). Supported versions that are affected are 4.2.0.0 and 4.2.1.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Hospitality Guest Access. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Hospitality Guest Access accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.3 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10218|2024-08-05T17:33:16.989Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2604|2024-08-05T04:21:34.580Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20guest%20access
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2604</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality Guest Access component of Oracle Hospitality Applications (subcomponent: Base). The supported version that is affected is 4.2.1. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Hospitality Guest Access. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Hospitality Guest Access accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2604|2024-08-05T04:21:34.580Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10370|2024-08-05T17:41:55.396Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20guest%20access
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10370</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality Guest Access component of Oracle Hospitality Applications (subcomponent: Base). Supported versions that are affected are 4.2.0 and 4.2.1. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Hospitality Guest Access. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Hospitality Guest Access, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Hospitality Guest Access accessible data as well as unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Hospitality Guest Access accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.9 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:R/S:C/C:H/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10370|2024-08-05T17:41:55.396Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10375|2024-08-05T17:41:55.496Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20guest%20access
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10375</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality Guest Access component of Oracle Hospitality Applications (subcomponent: Base). Supported versions that are affected are 4.2.0 and 4.2.1. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Hospitality Guest Access. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Hospitality Guest Access accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Hospitality Guest Access accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.6 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10375|2024-08-05T17:41:55.496Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10372|2024-08-05T17:41:55.548Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20guest%20access
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10372</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality Guest Access component of Oracle Hospitality Applications (subcomponent: Base). Supported versions that are affected are 4.2.0 and 4.2.1. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Hospitality Guest Access. While the vulnerability is in Oracle Hospitality Guest Access, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle Hospitality Guest Access accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Hospitality Guest Access. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.7 (Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10372|2024-08-05T17:41:55.548Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2606|2024-08-05T04:21:34.581Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20guest%20access
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2606</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality Guest Access component of Oracle Hospitality Applications (subcomponent: Base). Supported versions that are affected are 4.2.0 and 4.2.1. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Hospitality Guest Access executes to compromise Oracle Hospitality Guest Access. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Hospitality Guest Access accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.2 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2606|2024-08-05T04:21:34.581Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2852|2024-08-05T04:29:44.933Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20guest%20access
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2852</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality Guest Access component of Oracle Hospitality Applications (subcomponent: Base). Supported versions that are affected are 4.2.0 and 4.2.1. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Hospitality Guest Access. While the vulnerability is in Oracle Hospitality Guest Access, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Hospitality Guest Access accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Hospitality Guest Access accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2852|2024-08-05T04:29:44.933Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10217|2024-08-05T17:33:16.949Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20guest%20access
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10217</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality Guest Access component of Oracle Hospitality Applications (subcomponent: Base). Supported versions that are affected are 4.2.0.0 and 4.2.1.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Hospitality Guest Access. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Hospitality Guest Access accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.3 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10217|2024-08-05T17:33:16.949Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
