<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/hospitality%20cruise%20shipboard%20property%20management%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 19:21:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10361|2024-10-04T16:47:46.937Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20cruise%20shipboard%20property%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10361</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System component of Oracle Hospitality Applications (subcomponent: OHC DRS). The supported version that is affected is 8.0.2.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System. While the vulnerability is in Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.4 (Confidentiality and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10361|2024-10-04T16:47:46.937Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10228|2024-10-04T17:07:03.142Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20cruise%20shipboard%20property%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10228</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System component of Oracle Hospitality Applications (subcomponent: Module). The supported version that is affected is 8.0.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10228|2024-10-04T17:07:03.142Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
