<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- Hospitality Hotel Mobile</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/hospitality%20hotel%20mobile.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- Hospitality Hotel Mobile</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 21:23:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10353|2024-08-05T17:41:54.647Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20hotel%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10353</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality Hotel Mobile component of Oracle Hospitality Applications (subcomponent: Suite8/RESTAPI). The supported version that is affected is 1.1. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Hospitality Hotel Mobile. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Hospitality Hotel Mobile accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Hospitality Hotel Mobile. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.1 (Confidentiality and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10353|2024-08-05T17:41:54.647Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10133|2024-08-05T17:33:16.687Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20hotel%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10133</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Hospitality Hotel Mobile component of Oracle Hospitality Applications (subcomponent: Suite8/RestAPI). The supported version that is affected is 1.1. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Hospitality Hotel Mobile. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Hospitality Hotel Mobile accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.3 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10133|2024-08-05T17:33:16.687Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10014|2024-08-05T17:25:00.679Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20hotel%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10014</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality Hotel Mobile component of Oracle Hospitality Applications (subcomponent: Suite8/RESTAPI). The supported version that is affected is 1.1. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Hospitality Hotel Mobile. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Hospitality Hotel Mobile accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 3.5 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10014|2024-08-05T17:25:00.679Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10188|2024-08-05T17:33:16.606Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20hotel%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10188</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Hospitality Hotel Mobile component of Oracle Hospitality Applications (subcomponent: Suite 8/Android). The supported version that is affected is 1.01. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Hospitality Hotel Mobile executes to compromise Hospitality Hotel Mobile. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Hospitality Hotel Mobile accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10188|2024-08-05T17:33:16.606Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10168|2024-08-05T17:33:16.600Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20hotel%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10168</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Hospitality Hotel Mobile component of Oracle Hospitality Applications (subcomponent: Suite 8/Windows). The supported version that is affected is 1.1. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows physical access to compromise Hospitality Hotel Mobile. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Hospitality Hotel Mobile accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Hospitality Hotel Mobile. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.6 (Confidentiality and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:P/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10168|2024-08-05T17:33:16.600Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10132|2024-08-05T17:33:16.061Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20hotel%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10132</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Hospitality Hotel Mobile component of Oracle Hospitality Applications (subcomponent: Suite8/iOS). The supported version that is affected is 1.05. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Hospitality Hotel Mobile. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Hospitality Hotel Mobile accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.3 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10132|2024-08-05T17:33:16.061Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
