<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/hospitality%20cruise%20shipboard%20property%20management%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 21:23:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3000|2024-10-02T20:08:04.520Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20cruise%20shipboard%20property%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3000</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System component of Oracle Hospitality Applications (subcomponent: SPMS Suite). The supported version that is affected is 8.x. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System executes to compromise Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System. While the vulnerability is in Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.1 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3000|2024-10-02T20:08:04.520Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3001|2024-10-02T20:07:50.260Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20cruise%20shipboard%20property%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3001</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System component of Oracle Hospitality Applications (subcomponent: SPMS Suite). The supported version that is affected is 8.x. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System executes to compromise Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.2 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3001|2024-10-02T20:07:50.260Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2410|2024-10-02T16:22:01.842Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20cruise%20shipboard%20property%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2410</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System component of Oracle Hospitality Applications (subcomponent: DGS RES Online, FMS Sender, FMS Receiver, OHC WPF Security). The supported version that is affected is 8.0.8. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System executes to compromise Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2410|2024-10-02T16:22:01.842Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3160|2024-10-02T19:41:40.065Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20cruise%20shipboard%20property%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3160</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System component of Oracle Hospitality Applications (subcomponent: OHC Admin, OHC Management). The supported version that is affected is 8.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System executes to compromise Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.7 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:R/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3160|2024-10-02T19:41:40.065Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2411|2024-10-02T16:21:55.323Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20cruise%20shipboard%20property%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2411</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System component of Oracle Hospitality Applications (subcomponent: SPMS Suite). The supported version that is affected is 8.0.8. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via TCP to compromise Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System as well as unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.6 (Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:N/I:L/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2411|2024-10-02T16:21:55.323Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2409|2024-10-02T16:22:09.876Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20cruise%20shipboard%20property%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2409</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System component of Oracle Hospitality Applications (subcomponent: SPMS Suite). The supported version that is affected is 8.0.8. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System executes to compromise Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System as well as unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System accessible data and unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2409|2024-10-02T16:22:09.876Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3181|2024-10-02T19:39:13.501Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20cruise%20shipboard%20property%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3181</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System component of Oracle Hospitality Applications (subcomponent: OHC ENOAD). The supported version that is affected is 8.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System executes to compromise Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Hospitality Cruise Shipboard Property Management System accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3181|2024-10-02T19:39:13.501Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
