<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- Hospitality Reporting and Analytics</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/hospitality%20reporting%20and%20analytics.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- Hospitality Reporting and Analytics</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 19:20:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2401|2024-10-02T16:23:37.356Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20reporting%20and%20analytics
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2401</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality Reporting and Analytics component of Oracle Food and Beverage Applications. The supported version that is affected is 9.1.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker having Admin privilege with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Hospitality Reporting and Analytics. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle Hospitality Reporting and Analytics accessible data as well as unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Hospitality Reporting and Analytics accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2401|2024-10-02T16:23:37.356Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2397|2024-10-02T16:24:28.982Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20reporting%20and%20analytics
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2397</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality Reporting and Analytics component of Oracle Food and Beverage Applications. The supported version that is affected is 9.1.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker having Report privilege with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Hospitality Reporting and Analytics executes to compromise Oracle Hospitality Reporting and Analytics. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Hospitality Reporting and Analytics accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Hospitality Reporting and Analytics accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2397|2024-10-02T16:24:28.982Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2425|2024-10-02T16:19:57.155Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20reporting%20and%20analytics
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2425</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality Reporting and Analytics component of Oracle Food and Beverage Applications. The supported version that is affected is 9.1.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Hospitality Reporting and Analytics. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Hospitality Reporting and Analytics accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Hospitality Reporting and Analytics accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2425|2024-10-02T16:19:57.155Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2407|2024-10-02T16:22:27.268Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20reporting%20and%20analytics
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2407</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality Reporting and Analytics component of Oracle Food and Beverage Applications. The supported version that is affected is 9.1.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker having Report privilege with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Hospitality Reporting and Analytics executes to compromise Oracle Hospitality Reporting and Analytics. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Hospitality Reporting and Analytics accessible data as well as unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Hospitality Reporting and Analytics accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2407|2024-10-02T16:22:27.268Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
