<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/hospitality%20opera%205%20property%20services.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 20:24:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3573|2024-10-07T16:10:53.128Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20opera%205%20property%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3573</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services component of Oracle Hospitality Applications (subcomponent: OPERA Printing). Supported versions that are affected are 5.4.0.x, 5.4.1.x, 5.4.2.x, 5.4.3.x, 5.5.0.x and 5.5.1.x. Easily "exploitable" vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3573|2024-10-07T16:10:53.128Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3552|2024-10-07T16:11:51.344Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20opera%205%20property%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3552</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services component of Oracle Hospitality Applications (subcomponent: OPERA Room Image/Picture Setup). Supported versions that are affected are 5.4.0.x, 5.4.1.x, 5.4.2.x, 5.4.3.x, 5.5.0.x and 5.5.1.x. Easily "exploitable" vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.3 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3552|2024-10-07T16:11:51.344Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3569|2024-10-07T16:11:01.960Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20opera%205%20property%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3569</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services component of Oracle Hospitality Applications (subcomponent: OPERA Business Events). Supported versions that are affected are 5.4.0.x, 5.4.1.x, 5.4.2.x, 5.4.3.x, 5.5.0.x and 5.5.1.x. Easily "exploitable" vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3569|2024-10-07T16:11:01.960Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3574|2024-10-07T16:10:44.812Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20opera%205%20property%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3574</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services component of Oracle Hospitality Applications (subcomponent: OPERA License code configuration). Supported versions that are affected are 5.4.0.x, 5.4.1.x, 5.4.2.x, 5.4.3.x, 5.5.0.x and 5.5.1.x. Easily "exploitable" vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services accessible data as well as unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3574|2024-10-07T16:10:44.812Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3560|2024-10-07T16:11:17.912Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20opera%205%20property%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3560</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services component of Oracle Hospitality Applications (subcomponent: OXI Interface). Supported versions that are affected are 5.4.0.x, 5.4.1.x, 5.4.2.x, 5.4.3.x, 5.5.0.x and 5.5.1.x. Easily "exploitable" vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.3 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3560|2024-10-07T16:11:17.912Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
