<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/hospitality%20opera%205%20property%20services.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 19:21:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10197|2024-10-04T16:57:35.827Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20opera%205%20property%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10197</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services component of Oracle Hospitality Applications (subcomponent: Folios). The supported version that is affected is 5.4.2.x through 5.5.1.x. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows physical access to compromise Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.6 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:P/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10197|2024-10-04T16:57:35.827Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10182|2024-10-04T17:11:36.766Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20opera%205%20property%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10182</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services component of Oracle Hospitality Applications (subcomponent: OPERA Export Functionality). Supported versions that are affected are 5.4.0.x, 5.4.1.x and 5.4.3.x. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.4 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10182|2024-10-04T17:11:36.766Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
