<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/hospitality%20opera%205%20property%20services.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 16:23:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2677|2024-08-04T07:17:01.011Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20opera%205%20property%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2677</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 product of Oracle Hospitality Applications (component: Login). Supported versions that are affected are 5.5 and 5.6. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.7 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2677|2024-08-04T07:17:01.011Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14877|2024-08-04T13:00:51.534Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20opera%205%20property%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14877</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services product of Oracle Hospitality Applications (component: Logging). Supported versions that are affected are 5.5 and 5.6. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services accessible data as well as unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14877|2024-08-04T13:00:51.534Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 14:04:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14858|2024-08-04T13:00:51.506Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20opera%205%20property%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14858</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services product of Oracle Hospitality Applications (component: Logging). Supported versions that are affected are 5.5 and 5.6. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 Property Services. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:R/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14858|2024-08-04T13:00:51.506Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 14:04:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2676|2024-08-04T07:17:01.830Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20opera%205%20property%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2676</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 product of Oracle Hospitality Applications (component: Printing). The supported version that is affected is 5.5. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2676|2024-08-04T07:17:01.830Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2675|2024-08-04T07:17:01.917Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hospitality%20opera%205%20property%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2675</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 product of Oracle Hospitality Applications (component: Login). The supported version that is affected is 5.5. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 accessible data as well as unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Hospitality OPERA 5 accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2675|2024-08-04T07:17:01.917Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
