<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- Hyperion Essbase Administration Services</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/hyperion%20essbase%20administration%20services.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- Hyperion Essbase Administration Services</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 14:23:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35654|2024-08-04T00:40:47.443Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hyperion%20essbase%20administration%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35654</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Essbase Administration Services product of Oracle Essbase (component: EAS Console). The supported versions that are affected are Prior to 11.1.2.4.046 and Prior to 21.3. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Essbase Administration Services. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Essbase Administration Services. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35654|2024-08-04T00:40:47.443Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35651|2024-08-04T00:40:47.539Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hyperion%20essbase%20administration%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35651</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Essbase Administration Services product of Oracle Essbase (component: EAS Console). The supported versions that are affected are Prior to 11.1.2.4.046 and Prior to 21.3. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Essbase Administration Services. While the vulnerability is in Essbase Administration Services, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Essbase Administration Services accessible data as well as unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Essbase Administration Services accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.5 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35651|2024-08-04T00:40:47.539Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35683|2024-08-04T00:40:47.369Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hyperion%20essbase%20administration%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35683</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Essbase Administration Services product of Oracle Essbase (component: EAS Console). The supported version that is affected is Prior to 11.1.2.4.047. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Essbase Administration Services. While the vulnerability is in Oracle Essbase Administration Services, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle Essbase Administration Services. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 9.9 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35683|2024-08-04T00:40:47.369Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 11:21:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35653|2024-08-04T00:40:47.361Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hyperion%20essbase%20administration%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35653</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Essbase Administration Services product of Oracle Essbase (component: EAS Console). The supported versions that are affected are Prior to 11.1.2.4.046 and Prior to 21.3. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Essbase Administration Services. While the vulnerability is in Essbase Administration Services, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Essbase Administration Services accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.7 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35653|2024-08-04T00:40:47.361Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35652|2024-08-04T00:40:47.456Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hyperion%20essbase%20administration%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35652</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Essbase Administration Services product of Oracle Essbase (component: EAS Console). The supported versions that are affected are Prior to 11.1.2.4.046 and Prior to 21.3. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Essbase Administration Services. While the vulnerability is in Essbase Administration Services, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Essbase Administration Services. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 10.0 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35652|2024-08-04T00:40:47.456Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35655|2024-08-04T00:40:47.461Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hyperion%20essbase%20administration%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35655</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Essbase Administration Services product of Oracle Essbase (component: EAS Console). The supported versions that are affected are Prior to 11.1.2.4.046 and Prior to 21.3. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Essbase Administration Services. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Essbase Administration Services accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35655|2024-08-04T00:40:47.461Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
