<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- Hyperion Essbase Administration Services</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/hyperion%20essbase%20administration%20services.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- Hyperion Essbase Administration Services</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 15:23:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-2350|2024-09-26T14:03:32.255Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hyperion%20essbase%20administration%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-2350</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Hyperion Essbase Administration Services product of Oracle Essbase (component: EAS Console). Supported versions that are affected are 11.1.2.4 and 21.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Hyperion Essbase Administration Services. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Hyperion Essbase Administration Services accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-2350|2024-09-26T14:03:32.255Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 22:43:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-2349|2024-09-26T14:03:43.162Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hyperion%20essbase%20administration%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-2349</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Hyperion Essbase Administration Services product of Oracle Essbase (component: EAS Console). Supported versions that are affected are 11.1.2.4 and 21.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Hyperion Essbase Administration Services. While the vulnerability is in Hyperion Essbase Administration Services, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Hyperion Essbase Administration Services accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.6 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-2349|2024-09-26T14:03:43.162Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 22:43:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
