<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- Hyperion Financial Reporting</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/hyperion%20financial%20reporting.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- Hyperion Financial Reporting</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 18:24:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2769|2024-08-04T07:17:02.534Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hyperion%20financial%20reporting
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2769</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Hyperion Financial Reporting product of Oracle Hyperion (component: Web Based Report Designer). The supported version that is affected is 11.1.2.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Hyperion Financial Reporting. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Hyperion Financial Reporting accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 2.4 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2769|2024-08-04T07:17:02.534Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35665|2024-08-04T00:40:47.437Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hyperion%20financial%20reporting
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35665</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Hyperion Financial Reporting product of Oracle Hyperion (component: Repository). The supported version that is affected is 11.2.6.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Hyperion Financial Reporting. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Hyperion Financial Reporting, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Hyperion Financial Reporting accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Hyperion Financial Reporting accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35665|2024-08-04T00:40:47.437Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
