<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- Hyperion Financial Reporting</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/hyperion%20financial%20reporting.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- Hyperion Financial Reporting</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 18:25:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10358|2024-08-05T17:41:55.021Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hyperion%20financial%20reporting
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10358</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hyperion Financial Reporting component of Oracle Hyperion (subcomponent: Workspace). The supported version that is affected is 11.1.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Hyperion Financial Reporting. While the vulnerability is in Oracle Hyperion Financial Reporting, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Hyperion Financial Reporting accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Hyperion Financial Reporting accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10358|2024-08-05T17:41:55.021Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10310|2024-08-05T17:41:54.043Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hyperion%20financial%20reporting
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10310</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Hyperion Financial Reporting component of Oracle Hyperion (subcomponent: Security Models). The supported version that is affected is 11.1.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Hyperion Financial Reporting. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Hyperion Financial Reporting accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10310|2024-08-05T17:41:54.043Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2907|2024-08-05T04:36:38.549Z -- oracle%20corporation -- hyperion%20financial%20reporting
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2907</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Hyperion Financial Reporting component of Oracle Hyperion (subcomponent: Security Models). The supported version that is affected is 11.1.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Hyperion Financial Reporting. While the vulnerability is in Hyperion Financial Reporting, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Hyperion Financial Reporting accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.6 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2907|2024-08-05T04:36:38.549Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
