<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- Identity Manager</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/identity%20manager.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- Identity Manager</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:22:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2858|2024-08-04T19:03:43.137Z -- oracle%20corporation -- identity%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2858</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Identity Manager component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Advanced Console). Supported versions that are affected are 11.1.2.3.0 and 12.2.1.3.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Identity Manager. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Identity Manager accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.3 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2858|2024-08-04T19:03:43.137Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 22:31:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2728|2024-08-04T07:17:02.197Z -- oracle%20corporation -- identity%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2728</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Identity Manager product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: OIM - LDAP user and role Synch). The supported version that is affected is 12.2.1.3.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Identity Manager. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Identity Manager accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2728|2024-08-04T07:17:02.197Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2729|2024-08-04T07:17:02.239Z -- oracle%20corporation -- identity%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2729</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Identity Manager product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Advanced Console). Supported versions that are affected are 11.1.2.3.0 and 12.2.1.3.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Identity Manager. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Identity Manager accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Identity Manager accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2729|2024-08-04T07:17:02.239Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
