<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- Internet Expenses</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/internet%20expenses.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- Internet Expenses</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 16:24:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14719|2024-08-04T12:53:43.274Z -- oracle%20corporation -- internet%20expenses
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14719</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Internet Expenses product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: Mobile Expenses Admin Utilities). Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.4-12.2.9. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Internet Expenses. While the vulnerability is in Oracle Internet Expenses, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle Internet Expenses accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.7 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14719|2024-08-04T12:53:43.274Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14720|2024-08-04T12:53:43.256Z -- oracle%20corporation -- internet%20expenses
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14720</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Internet Expenses product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: Mobile Expenses Admin Utilities). Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.4-12.2.9. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Internet Expenses. While the vulnerability is in Oracle Internet Expenses, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Internet Expenses accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.7 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14720|2024-08-04T12:53:43.256Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
