<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- Java</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/java.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- Java</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 17:22:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10345|2024-10-04T16:49:38.245Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10345</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, Java SE Embedded, JRockit component of Oracle Java SE (subcomponent: Serialization). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 6u161, 7u151, 8u144 and 9; Java SE Embedded: 8u144; JRockit: R28.3.15. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE, Java SE Embedded, JRockit. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Java SE, Java SE Embedded, JRockit. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited through sandboxed Java Web Start applications and sandboxed Java applets. It can also be exploited by supplying data to APIs in the specified Component without using sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, such as through a web service. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 3.1 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10345|2024-10-04T16:49:38.245Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10285|2024-10-04T16:55:14.846Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10285</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, Java SE Embedded component of Oracle Java SE (subcomponent: RMI). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 6u161, 7u151, 8u144 and 9; Java SE Embedded: 8u144. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Java SE, Java SE Embedded, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.0 Base Score 9.6 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10285|2024-10-04T16:55:14.846Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10347|2024-10-04T16:49:25.137Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10347</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, JRockit component of Oracle Java SE (subcomponent: Serialization). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 6u161, 7u151, 8u144 and 9; Java SE Embedded: 8u144. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE, JRockit. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Java SE, JRockit. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.3 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10347|2024-10-04T16:49:25.137Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10386|2024-10-04T16:45:17.567Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10386</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java Advanced Management Console component of Oracle Java SE (subcomponent: Server). The supported version that is affected is Java Advanced Management Console: 2.7. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Java Advanced Management Console. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Java Advanced Management Console, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Java Advanced Management Console accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Java Advanced Management Console accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.8 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10386|2024-10-04T16:45:17.567Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10357|2024-10-04T16:48:18.092Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10357</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, Java SE Embedded component of Oracle Java SE (subcomponent: Serialization). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 6u161, 7u151, 8u144 and 9; Java SE Embedded: 8u144. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.3 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10357|2024-10-04T16:48:18.092Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10350|2024-10-04T16:49:05.882Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10350</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, Java SE Embedded component of Oracle Java SE (subcomponent: JAX-WS). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 7u151, 8u144 and 9; Java SE Embedded: 8u144. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.3 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10350|2024-10-04T16:49:05.882Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10342|2024-10-04T16:49:58.033Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10342</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java Advanced Management Console component of Oracle Java SE (subcomponent: Server). The supported version that is affected is Java Advanced Management Console: 2.7. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java Advanced Management Console. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Java Advanced Management Console. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.3 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10342|2024-10-04T16:49:58.033Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10348|2024-10-04T16:49:18.786Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10348</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, Java SE Embedded component of Oracle Java SE (subcomponent: Libraries). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 6u161, 7u151, 8u144 and 9; Java SE Embedded: 8u144. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.3 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10348|2024-10-04T16:49:18.786Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10349|2024-10-04T16:49:11.928Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10349</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, Java SE Embedded component of Oracle Java SE (subcomponent: JAXP). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 6u161, 7u151, 8u144 and 9; Java SE Embedded: 8u144. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.3 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10349|2024-10-04T16:49:11.928Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10346|2024-10-04T16:49:31.398Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10346</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, Java SE Embedded component of Oracle Java SE (subcomponent: Hotspot). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 6u161, 7u151, 8u144 and 9; Java SE Embedded: 8u144. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Java SE, Java SE Embedded, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.0 Base Score 9.6 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10346|2024-10-04T16:49:31.398Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10295|2024-10-04T16:54:34.588Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10295</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, Java SE Embedded, JRockit component of Oracle Java SE (subcomponent: Networking). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 6u161, 7u151, 8u144 and 9; Java SE Embedded: 8u144; JRockit: R28.3.15. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Java SE, Java SE Embedded, JRockit. While the vulnerability is in Java SE, Java SE Embedded, JRockit, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Java SE, Java SE Embedded, JRockit accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited through sandboxed Java Web Start applications and sandboxed Java applets. It can also be exploited by supplying data to APIs in the specified Component without using sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, such as through a web service. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.0 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10295|2024-10-04T16:54:34.588Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10355|2024-10-04T16:48:32.115Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10355</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, Java SE Embedded, JRockit component of Oracle Java SE (subcomponent: Networking). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 6u161, 7u151, 8u144 and 9; Java SE Embedded: 8u144; JRockit: R28.3.15. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE, Java SE Embedded, JRockit. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Java SE, Java SE Embedded, JRockit. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited through sandboxed Java Web Start applications and sandboxed Java applets. It can also be exploited by supplying data to APIs in the specified Component without using sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, such as through a web service. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.3 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10355|2024-10-04T16:48:32.115Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10341|2024-10-04T16:50:05.510Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10341</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java Advanced Management Console component of Oracle Java SE (subcomponent: Server). The supported version that is affected is Java Advanced Management Console: 2.7. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java Advanced Management Console. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Java Advanced Management Console accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.0 Base Score 3.7 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10341|2024-10-04T16:50:05.510Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10309|2024-10-04T16:53:38.783Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10309</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE component of Oracle Java SE (subcomponent: Deployment). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 8u144 and 9. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Java SE, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Java SE accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Java SE accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Java SE. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.1 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10309|2024-10-04T16:53:38.783Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10293|2024-10-04T16:54:48.511Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10293</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE component of Oracle Java SE (subcomponent: Javadoc). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 6u161, 7u151, 8u144 and 9. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Java SE. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Java SE, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Java SE accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Java SE accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10293|2024-10-04T16:54:48.511Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10380|2024-10-04T16:46:06.128Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10380</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java Advanced Management Console component of Oracle Java SE (subcomponent: Server). The supported version that is affected is Java Advanced Management Console: 2.7. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Java Advanced Management Console. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Java Advanced Management Console, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Java Advanced Management Console accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Java Advanced Management Console accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.7 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10380|2024-10-04T16:46:06.128Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10356|2024-10-04T16:48:24.887Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10356</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, Java SE Embedded, JRockit component of Oracle Java SE (subcomponent: Security). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 6u161, 7u151, 8u144 and 9; Java SE Embedded: 8u144; JRockit: R28.3.15. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Java SE, Java SE Embedded, JRockit executes to compromise Java SE, Java SE Embedded, JRockit. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Java SE, Java SE Embedded, JRockit accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited through sandboxed Java Web Start applications and sandboxed Java applets. It can also be exploited by supplying data to APIs in the specified Component without using sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, such as through a web service. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.2 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10356|2024-10-04T16:48:24.887Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10388|2024-10-04T16:44:59.766Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10388</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, Java SE Embedded component of Oracle Java SE (subcomponent: Libraries). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 6u161, 7u151, 8u144 and 9; Java SE Embedded: 8u144. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via Kerberos to compromise Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Note: Applies to the Java SE Kerberos client. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10388|2024-10-04T16:44:59.766Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10274|2024-10-04T16:56:12.072Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10274</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE component of Oracle Java SE (subcomponent: Smart Card IO). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 6u161, 7u151, 8u144 and 9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Java SE accessible data as well as unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Java SE accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.8 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10274|2024-10-04T16:56:12.072Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10281|2024-10-04T16:55:34.292Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10281</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, Java SE Embedded, JRockit component of Oracle Java SE (subcomponent: Serialization). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 6u161, 7u151, 8u144 and 9; Java SE Embedded: 8u144; JRockit: R28.3.15. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE, Java SE Embedded, JRockit. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Java SE, Java SE Embedded, JRockit. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited through sandboxed Java Web Start applications and sandboxed Java applets. It can also be exploited by supplying data to APIs in the specified Component without using sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, such as through a web service. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.3 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10281|2024-10-04T16:55:34.292Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
