<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- Java SE JDK and JRE</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- Java SE JDK and JRE</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 16:24:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22044|2024-08-02T09:59:28.778Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22044</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition, Oracle GraalVM for JDK product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u371-perf, 17.0.7, 20.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 21.3.6, 22.3.2; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.7 and  20.0.1. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition, Oracle GraalVM for JDK.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition, Oracle GraalVM for JDK accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22044|2024-08-02T09:59:28.778Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 20:18:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-21843|2024-08-02T09:51:51.130Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21843</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Sound).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u351, 8u351-perf, 11.0.17, 17.0.5, 19.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.8, 21.3.4 and  22.3.0. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-21843|2024-08-02T09:51:51.130Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 23:35:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22006|2024-08-02T09:59:28.529Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22006</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition, Oracle GraalVM for JDK product of Oracle Java SE (component: Networking).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 11.0.19, 17.0.7, 20.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.10, 21.3.6, 22.3.2; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.7 and  20.0.1. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition, Oracle GraalVM for JDK.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition, Oracle GraalVM for JDK accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.1 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22006|2024-08-02T09:59:28.529Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 20:18:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22043|2024-08-02T09:59:28.669Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22043</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in Oracle Java SE (component: JavaFX).   The supported version that is affected is Oracle Java SE: 8u371. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle Java SE accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.9 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22043|2024-08-02T09:59:28.669Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 20:18:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-21968|2024-08-02T09:59:28.370Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21968</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Libraries).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u361, 8u361-perf, 11.0.18, 17.0.6, 20; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.9, 21.3.5 and  22.3.1. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability can also be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-21968|2024-08-02T09:59:28.370Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 19:54:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22049|2024-08-02T09:59:28.682Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22049</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition, Oracle GraalVM for JDK product of Oracle Java SE (component: Libraries).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u371, 8u371-perf, 11.0.19, 17.0.7, 20.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.10, 21.3.6, 22.3.2; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.7 and  20.0.1. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition, Oracle GraalVM for JDK.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition, Oracle GraalVM for JDK accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22049|2024-08-02T09:59:28.682Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 20:18:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22036|2024-08-02T09:59:28.789Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22036</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition, Oracle GraalVM for JDK product of Oracle Java SE (component: Utility).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 11.0.19, 17.0.7, 20.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.10, 21.3.6, 22.3.2; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.7 and  20.0.1. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition, Oracle GraalVM for JDK.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition, Oracle GraalVM for JDK. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22036|2024-08-02T09:59:28.789Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 20:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-21930|2024-08-02T09:59:27.250Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21930</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: JSSE).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u361, 8u361-perf, 11.0.18, 17.0.6, 20; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.9, 21.3.5 and  22.3.1. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via TLS to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data as well as  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability can also be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-21930|2024-08-02T09:59:27.250Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 19:54:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22041|2024-08-02T09:59:28.638Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22041</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition, Oracle GraalVM for JDK product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u371-perf, 11.0.19, 17.0.7, 20.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.10, 21.3.6, 22.3.2; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.7 and  20.0.1. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition, Oracle GraalVM for JDK executes to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition, Oracle GraalVM for JDK.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition, Oracle GraalVM for JDK accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.1 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22041|2024-08-02T09:59:28.638Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 20:18:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-21937|2024-08-02T09:59:28.528Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21937</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Networking).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u361, 8u361-perf, 11.0.18, 17.0.6, 20; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.9, 21.3.5 and  22.3.1. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability can also be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-21937|2024-08-02T09:59:28.528Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 19:54:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-21830|2024-08-02T09:51:51.152Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21830</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Serialization).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u351, 8u351-perf; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.8 and  21.3.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-21830|2024-08-02T09:51:51.152Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 23:35:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-21967|2024-08-02T09:59:28.383Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21967</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: JSSE).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u361, 8u361-perf, 11.0.18, 17.0.6, 20; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.9, 21.3.5 and  22.3.1. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTPS to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability can also be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-21967|2024-08-02T09:59:28.383Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 19:54:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-21835|2024-08-02T09:51:50.877Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21835</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: JSSE).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 11.0.17, 17.0.5, 19.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.8, 21.3.4 and  22.3.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via DTLS to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-21835|2024-08-02T09:51:50.877Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 23:35:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-21954|2024-08-02T09:59:28.530Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21954</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u361, 8u361-perf, 11.0.18, 17.0.6; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.9, 21.3.5 and  22.3.1. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability can also be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.9 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-21954|2024-08-02T09:59:28.530Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 19:54:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-21939|2024-08-02T09:59:27.929Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21939</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Swing).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u361, 8u361-perf, 11.0.18, 17.0.6, 20; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.9, 21.3.5 and  22.3.1. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability can also be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-21939|2024-08-02T09:59:27.929Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 19:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22045|2024-08-02T09:59:28.912Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22045</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition, Oracle GraalVM for JDK product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u371, 8u371-perf, 11.0.19, 17.0.7, 20.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.10, 21.3.6, 22.3.2; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.7 and  20.0.1. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition, Oracle GraalVM for JDK.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition, Oracle GraalVM for JDK accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22045|2024-08-02T09:59:28.912Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 20:18:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22081|2024-08-02T09:59:29.109Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22081</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: JSSE).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u381, 8u381-perf, 11.0.20, 17.0.8, 21; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.8, 21; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.11, 21.3.7 and  22.3.3. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTPS to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22081|2024-08-02T09:59:29.109Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 21:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22025|2024-08-02T09:59:28.998Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22025</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition, product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u381-perf, 17.0.8, 21; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.8, 21; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 21.3.7 and  22.3.3. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition,.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition, accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22025|2024-08-02T09:59:28.998Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 21:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-21938|2024-08-02T09:59:27.256Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21938</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Libraries).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u361, 8u361-perf, 11.0.18, 17.0.6, 20; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.8, 21.3.4 and  22.3.0. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-21938|2024-08-02T09:59:27.256Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 19:54:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22067|2024-08-02T09:59:28.818Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22067</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: CORBA).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u381, 8u381-perf; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.11 and  21.3.7. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via CORBA to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can only be exploited by supplying data to APIs in the specified Component without using Untrusted Java Web Start applications or Untrusted Java applets, such as through a web service. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22067|2024-08-02T09:59:28.818Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 21:02:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20919|2024-07-29T16:45:08.145Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20919</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u391, 8u391-perf, 11.0.21, 17.0.9, 21.0.1; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.9, 21.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.12, 21.3.8 and  22.3.4. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can only be exploited by supplying data to APIs in the specified Component without using Untrusted Java Web Start applications or Untrusted Java applets, such as through a web service. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.9 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20919|2024-07-29T16:45:08.145Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21147|2024-07-17T14:28:02.911Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21147</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u411, 8u411-perf, 11.0.23, 17.0.11, 21.0.3, 22.0.1; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.11, 21.0.3, 22.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.14 and  21.3.10. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data as well as  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21147|2024-07-17T14:28:02.911Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21144|2024-07-17T14:20:35.722Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21144</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Concurrency).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u411, 8u411-perf, 11.0.23; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.14 and  21.3.10. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21144|2024-07-17T14:20:35.722Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21140|2024-07-16T22:39:56.895Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21140</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u411, 8u411-perf, 11.0.23, 17.0.11, 21.0.3, 22.0.1; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.11, 21.0.3, 22.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.14 and  21.3.10. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.8 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21140|2024-07-16T22:39:56.895Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21147|2024-07-16T22:39:59.298Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21147</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u411, 8u411-perf, 11.0.23, 17.0.11, 21.0.3, 22.0.1; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.11, 21.0.3, 22.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.14 and  21.3.10. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data as well as  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21147|2024-07-16T22:39:59.298Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21138|2024-07-16T22:39:56.205Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21138</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u411, 8u411-perf, 11.0.23, 17.0.11, 21.0.3, 22.0.1; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.11, 21.0.3, 22.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.14 and  21.3.10. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21138|2024-07-16T22:39:56.205Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21145|2024-07-16T22:39:58.658Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21145</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: 2D).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u411, 8u411-perf, 11.0.23, 17.0.11, 21.0.3, 22.0.1; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.11, 21.0.3, 22.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.14 and  21.3.10. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.8 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21145|2024-07-16T22:39:58.658Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21131|2024-07-16T22:39:53.849Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21131</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u411, 8u411-perf, 11.0.23, 17.0.11, 21.0.3, 22.0.1; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.11, 21.0.3, 22.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.14 and  21.3.10. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21131|2024-07-16T22:39:53.849Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21144|2024-07-16T22:39:58.306Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21144</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Concurrency).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u411, 8u411-perf, 11.0.23; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.14 and  21.3.10. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21144|2024-07-16T22:39:58.306Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21068|2024-07-05T12:44:00.522Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21068</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u401-perf, 11.0.22, 17.0.10, 21.0.2, 22; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.10, 21.0.2 and  22; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21068|2024-07-05T12:44:00.522Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21085|2024-06-13T20:36:00.856Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21085</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Concurrency).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u401, 8u401-perf, 11.0.22; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.13 and  21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21085|2024-06-13T20:36:00.856Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21085|2024-04-16T21:26:27.090Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21085</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Concurrency).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u401, 8u401-perf, 11.0.22; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.13 and  21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21085|2024-04-16T21:26:27.090Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21011|2024-04-16T21:26:01.896Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21011</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u401, 8u401-perf, 11.0.22, 17.0.10, 21.0.2, 22; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.10, 21.0.2, 22;   Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.13 and  21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21011|2024-04-16T21:26:01.896Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21094|2024-06-04T17:37:51.570Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21094</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u401, 8u401-perf, 11.0.22, 17.0.10, 21.0.2, 22; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.10, 21.0.2, 22; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.13 and  21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21094|2024-06-04T17:37:51.570Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21003|2024-06-04T17:37:52.453Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21003</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: JavaFX).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u401; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.13 and  21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.1 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21003|2024-06-04T17:37:52.453Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21002|2024-06-04T17:38:03.601Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21002</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: JavaFX).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u401; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.13 and  21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition executes to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 2.5 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21002|2024-06-04T17:38:03.601Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21005|2024-04-16T21:25:59.621Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21005</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: JavaFX).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u401; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.13 and  21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.1 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21005|2024-04-16T21:25:59.621Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21068|2024-04-16T21:26:21.424Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21068</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u401-perf, 11.0.22, 17.0.10, 21.0.2, 22; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.10, 21.0.2 and  22; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21068|2024-04-16T21:26:21.424Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21012|2024-04-16T21:26:02.245Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21012</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Networking).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 11.0.22, 17.0.10, 21.0.2, 22; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.10, 21.0.2, 22; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.13 and  21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21012|2024-04-16T21:26:02.245Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21004|2024-06-04T17:38:16.533Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21004</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: JavaFX).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u401; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.13 and  21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition executes to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 2.5 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21004|2024-06-04T17:38:16.533Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20925|2024-02-17T01:50:11.500Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20925</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: JavaFX).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u391; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.12 and  21.3.8. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.1 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20925|2024-02-17T01:50:11.500Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20945|2024-02-17T01:50:15.446Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20945</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Security).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u391, 8u391-perf, 11.0.21, 17.0.9, 21.0.1; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.9, 21.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.12, 21.3.8 and  22.3.4. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition executes to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.7 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20945|2024-02-17T01:50:15.446Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20919|2024-02-17T01:50:10.320Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20919</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u391, 8u391-perf, 11.0.21, 17.0.9, 21.0.1; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.9, 21.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.12, 21.3.8 and  22.3.4. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can only be exploited by supplying data to APIs in the specified Component without using Untrusted Java Web Start applications or Untrusted Java applets, such as through a web service. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.9 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20919|2024-02-17T01:50:10.320Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20923|2024-02-17T01:50:11.127Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20923</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: JavaFX).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u391; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.12 and  21.3.8. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.1 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20923|2024-02-17T01:50:11.127Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20921|2024-02-17T01:50:10.681Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20921</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u391, 8u391-perf, 11.0.21, 17.0.9, 21.0.1; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.9, 21.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.12, 21.3.8 and  22.3.4. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.9 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20921|2024-02-17T01:50:10.681Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21005|2024-06-17T18:07:05.474Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21005</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: JavaFX).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u401; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.13 and  21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.1 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21005|2024-06-17T18:07:05.474Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20923|2024-07-05T17:21:45.654Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20923</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: JavaFX).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u391; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.12 and  21.3.8. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.1 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20923|2024-07-05T17:21:45.654Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20921|2024-07-05T17:20:57.149Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20921</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u391, 8u391-perf, 11.0.21, 17.0.9, 21.0.1; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.9, 21.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.12, 21.3.8 and  22.3.4. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.9 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20921|2024-07-05T17:20:57.149Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21131|2024-07-17T13:34:23.233Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21131</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u411, 8u411-perf, 11.0.23, 17.0.11, 21.0.3, 22.0.1; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.11, 21.0.3, 22.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.14 and  21.3.10. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21131|2024-07-17T13:34:23.233Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21145|2024-07-17T13:58:17.726Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21145</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: 2D).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u411, 8u411-perf, 11.0.23, 17.0.11, 21.0.3, 22.0.1; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.11, 21.0.3, 22.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.14 and  21.3.10. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.8 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21145|2024-07-17T13:58:17.726Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21138|2024-07-17T13:32:48.327Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21138</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u411, 8u411-perf, 11.0.23, 17.0.11, 21.0.3, 22.0.1; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.11, 21.0.3, 22.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.14 and  21.3.10. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21138|2024-07-17T13:32:48.327Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21140|2024-07-18T15:24:58.364Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21140</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u411, 8u411-perf, 11.0.23, 17.0.11, 21.0.3, 22.0.1; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.11, 21.0.3, 22.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.14 and  21.3.10. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.8 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21140|2024-07-18T15:24:58.364Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21147|2024-07-19T03:55:25.572Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21147</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u411, 8u411-perf, 11.0.23, 17.0.11, 21.0.3, 22.0.1; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.11, 21.0.3, 22.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.14 and  21.3.10. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data as well as  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21147|2024-07-19T03:55:25.572Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21011|2024-07-26T15:16:22.341Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21011</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u401, 8u401-perf, 11.0.22, 17.0.10, 21.0.2, 22; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.10, 21.0.2, 22;   Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.13 and  21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21011|2024-07-26T15:16:22.341Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21012|2024-07-26T15:15:57.519Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21012</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Networking).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 11.0.22, 17.0.10, 21.0.2, 22; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.10, 21.0.2, 22; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.13 and  21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21012|2024-07-26T15:15:57.519Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20945|2024-08-01T22:06:37.386Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20945</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Security).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u391, 8u391-perf, 11.0.21, 17.0.9, 21.0.1; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.9, 21.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.12, 21.3.8 and  22.3.4. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition executes to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.7 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20945|2024-08-01T22:06:37.386Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20921|2024-08-01T22:06:37.324Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20921</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u391, 8u391-perf, 11.0.21, 17.0.9, 21.0.1; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.9, 21.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.12, 21.3.8 and  22.3.4. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.9 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20921|2024-08-01T22:06:37.324Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21144|2024-08-01T22:13:42.672Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21144</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Concurrency).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u411, 8u411-perf, 11.0.23; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.14 and  21.3.10. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21144|2024-08-01T22:13:42.672Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21094|2024-08-01T22:13:42.604Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21094</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u401, 8u401-perf, 11.0.22, 17.0.10, 21.0.2, 22; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.10, 21.0.2, 22; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.13 and  21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21094|2024-08-01T22:13:42.604Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21147|2024-08-01T22:13:42.691Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21147</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u411, 8u411-perf, 11.0.23, 17.0.11, 21.0.3, 22.0.1; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.11, 21.0.3, 22.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.14 and  21.3.10. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data as well as  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21147|2024-08-01T22:13:42.691Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21003|2024-08-01T22:13:42.193Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21003</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: JavaFX).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u401; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.13 and  21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.1 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21003|2024-08-01T22:13:42.193Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21085|2024-08-01T22:13:42.673Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21085</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Concurrency).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u401, 8u401-perf, 11.0.22; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.13 and  21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21085|2024-08-01T22:13:42.673Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21011|2024-08-01T22:13:42.278Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21011</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u401, 8u401-perf, 11.0.22, 17.0.10, 21.0.2, 22; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.10, 21.0.2, 22;   Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.13 and  21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21011|2024-08-01T22:13:42.278Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21068|2024-08-01T22:13:42.375Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21068</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u401-perf, 11.0.22, 17.0.10, 21.0.2, 22; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.10, 21.0.2 and  22; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21068|2024-08-01T22:13:42.375Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21005|2024-08-01T22:13:41.483Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21005</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: JavaFX).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u401; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.13 and  21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.1 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21005|2024-08-01T22:13:41.483Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20919|2024-08-01T22:06:37.337Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20919</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u391, 8u391-perf, 11.0.21, 17.0.9, 21.0.1; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.9, 21.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.12, 21.3.8 and  22.3.4. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can only be exploited by supplying data to APIs in the specified Component without using Untrusted Java Web Start applications or Untrusted Java applets, such as through a web service. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.9 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20919|2024-08-01T22:06:37.337Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20923|2024-08-01T22:06:37.360Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20923</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: JavaFX).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u391; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.12 and  21.3.8. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.1 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20923|2024-08-01T22:06:37.360Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20925|2024-08-01T22:06:37.329Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20925</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: JavaFX).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u391; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.12 and  21.3.8. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.1 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20925|2024-08-01T22:06:37.329Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21145|2024-08-01T22:13:42.684Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21145</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: 2D).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u411, 8u411-perf, 11.0.23, 17.0.11, 21.0.3, 22.0.1; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.11, 21.0.3, 22.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.14 and  21.3.10. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.8 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21145|2024-08-01T22:13:42.684Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21012|2024-08-01T22:13:42.060Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21012</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Networking).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 11.0.22, 17.0.10, 21.0.2, 22; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.10, 21.0.2, 22; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.13 and  21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21012|2024-08-01T22:13:42.060Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21140|2024-08-01T22:13:42.666Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21140</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u411, 8u411-perf, 11.0.23, 17.0.11, 21.0.3, 22.0.1; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.11, 21.0.3, 22.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.14 and  21.3.10. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.8 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21140|2024-08-01T22:13:42.666Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21004|2024-08-01T22:13:42.435Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21004</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: JavaFX).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u401; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.13 and  21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition executes to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 2.5 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21004|2024-08-01T22:13:42.435Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21138|2024-08-01T22:13:42.697Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21138</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u411, 8u411-perf, 11.0.23, 17.0.11, 21.0.3, 22.0.1; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.11, 21.0.3, 22.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.14 and  21.3.10. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21138|2024-08-01T22:13:42.697Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21002|2024-08-01T22:13:42.041Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21002</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: JavaFX).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u401; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.13 and  21.3.9. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition executes to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 2.5 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21002|2024-08-01T22:13:42.041Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21131|2024-08-01T22:13:42.680Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java%20se%20jdk%20and%20jre</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21131</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot).  Supported versions that are affected are Oracle Java SE: 8u411, 8u411-perf, 11.0.23, 17.0.11, 21.0.3, 22.0.1; Oracle GraalVM for JDK: 17.0.11, 21.0.3, 22.0.1; Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition: 20.3.14 and  21.3.10. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Java SE, Oracle GraalVM for JDK, Oracle GraalVM Enterprise Edition accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. This vulnerability also applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21131|2024-08-01T22:13:42.680Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
