<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- Java</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/java.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- Java</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 17:21:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2754|2024-08-04T07:17:02.636Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2754</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, Java SE Embedded product of Oracle Java SE (component: Scripting). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 8u241, 11.0.6 and 14; Java SE Embedded: 8u241. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Note: Applies to client and server deployment of Java. This vulnerability can be exploited through sandboxed Java Web Start applications and sandboxed Java applets. It can also be exploited by supplying data to APIs in the specified Component without using sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, such as through a web service. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 3.7 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2754|2024-08-04T07:17:02.636Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14583|2024-08-04T12:53:41.875Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14583</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, Java SE Embedded product of Oracle Java SE (component: Libraries). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 7u261, 8u251, 11.0.7 and 14.0.1; Java SE Embedded: 8u251. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Java SE, Java SE Embedded, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14583|2024-08-04T12:53:41.875Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2816|2024-08-04T07:17:02.771Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2816</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE product of Oracle Java SE (component: JSSE). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 11.0.6 and 14. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTPS to compromise Java SE. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Java SE accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can only be exploited by supplying data to APIs in the specified Component without using Untrusted Java Web Start applications or Untrusted Java applets, such as through a web service. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.5 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2816|2024-08-04T07:17:02.771Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2655|2024-08-04T07:09:54.844Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2655</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE product of Oracle Java SE (component: JSSE). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 11.0.5 and 13.0.1. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTPS to compromise Java SE. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Java SE accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Java SE accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets (in Java SE 8), that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability can also be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.8 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2655|2024-08-04T07:09:54.844Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14621|2024-08-04T12:53:42.540Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14621</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, Java SE Embedded product of Oracle Java SE (component: JAXP). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 7u261, 8u251, 11.0.7 and 14.0.1; Java SE Embedded: 8u251. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Java SE, Java SE Embedded accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can only be exploited by supplying data to APIs in the specified Component without using Untrusted Java Web Start applications or Untrusted Java applets, such as through a web service. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14621|2024-08-04T12:53:42.540Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2830|2024-08-04T07:17:02.823Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2830</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, Java SE Embedded product of Oracle Java SE (component: Concurrency). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 7u251, 8u241, 11.0.6 and 14; Java SE Embedded: 8u241. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Note: Applies to client and server deployment of Java. This vulnerability can be exploited through sandboxed Java Web Start applications and sandboxed Java applets. It can also be exploited by supplying data to APIs in the specified Component without using sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, such as through a web service. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.3 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2830|2024-08-04T07:17:02.823Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14578|2024-08-04T12:46:34.793Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14578</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, Java SE Embedded product of Oracle Java SE (component: Libraries). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 7u261 and 8u251; Java SE Embedded: 8u251. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Note: Applies to client and server deployment of Java. This vulnerability can be exploited through sandboxed Java Web Start applications and sandboxed Java applets. It can also be exploited by supplying data to APIs in the specified Component without using sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, such as through a web service. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14578|2024-08-04T12:46:34.793Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2585|2024-08-04T07:09:54.833Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2585</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE product of Oracle Java SE (component: JavaFX). The supported version that is affected is Java SE: 8u231. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Java SE accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets (in Java SE 8), that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability can also be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.9 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2585|2024-08-04T07:09:54.833Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14562|2024-08-04T12:46:34.833Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14562</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE product of Oracle Java SE (component: ImageIO). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 11.0.7 and 14.0.1. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Java SE. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14562|2024-08-04T12:46:34.833Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14593|2024-08-04T12:53:42.576Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14593</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, Java SE Embedded product of Oracle Java SE (component: 2D). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 7u261, 8u251, 11.0.7 and 14.0.1; Java SE Embedded: 8u251. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Java SE, Java SE Embedded, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Java SE, Java SE Embedded accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.4 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:N/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14593|2024-08-04T12:53:42.576Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2805|2024-08-04T07:17:02.632Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2805</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, Java SE Embedded product of Oracle Java SE (component: Libraries). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 7u251, 8u241, 11.0.6 and 14; Java SE Embedded: 8u241. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Java SE, Java SE Embedded, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2805|2024-08-04T07:17:02.632Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2659|2024-08-04T07:09:54.920Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2659</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, Java SE Embedded product of Oracle Java SE (component: Networking). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 7u241 and 8u231; Java SE Embedded: 8u231. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets (in Java SE 8), that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability can also be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 3.7 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2659|2024-08-04T07:09:54.920Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14581|2024-08-04T12:53:41.868Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14581</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, Java SE Embedded product of Oracle Java SE (component: 2D). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 8u251, 11.0.7 and 14.0.1; Java SE Embedded: 8u251. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Java SE, Java SE Embedded accessible data. Note: Applies to client and server deployment of Java. This vulnerability can be exploited through sandboxed Java Web Start applications and sandboxed Java applets. It can also be exploited by supplying data to APIs in the specified Component without using sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, such as through a web service. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14581|2024-08-04T12:53:41.868Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2583|2024-08-04T07:09:54.723Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2583</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, Java SE Embedded product of Oracle Java SE (component: Serialization). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 7u241, 8u231, 11.0.5 and 13.0.1; Java SE Embedded: 8u231. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets (in Java SE 8), that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability can also be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 3.7 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2583|2024-08-04T07:09:54.723Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2604|2024-08-04T07:09:54.972Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2604</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, Java SE Embedded product of Oracle Java SE (component: Serialization). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 7u241, 8u231, 11.0.5 and 13.0.1; Java SE Embedded: 8u231. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets (in Java SE 8), that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability can also be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. CVSS v3.0 Base Score 8.1 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2604|2024-08-04T07:09:54.972Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2601|2024-08-04T07:09:54.842Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2601</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, Java SE Embedded product of Oracle Java SE (component: Security). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 7u241, 8u231, 11.0.5 and 13.0.1; Java SE Embedded: 8u231. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via Kerberos to compromise Java SE, Java SE Embedded. While the vulnerability is in Java SE, Java SE Embedded, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Java SE, Java SE Embedded accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets (in Java SE 8), that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability can also be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.8 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2601|2024-08-04T07:09:54.842Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2654|2024-08-04T07:09:55.025Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2654</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE product of Oracle Java SE (component: Libraries). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 7u241, 8u231, 11.0.5 and 13.0.1. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Java SE. Note: This vulnerability can only be exploited by supplying data to APIs in the specified Component without using Untrusted Java Web Start applications or Untrusted Java applets, such as through a web service. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 3.7 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2654|2024-08-04T07:09:55.025Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2781|2024-08-04T07:17:02.849Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2781</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, Java SE Embedded product of Oracle Java SE (component: JSSE). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 7u251, 8u241, 11.0.6 and 14; Java SE Embedded: 8u241. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTPS to compromise Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Note: Applies to client and server deployment of Java. This vulnerability can be exploited through sandboxed Java Web Start applications and sandboxed Java applets. It can also be exploited by supplying data to APIs in the specified Component without using sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, such as through a web service. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.3 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2781|2024-08-04T07:17:02.849Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2778|2024-08-04T07:17:02.621Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2778</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE product of Oracle Java SE (component: JSSE). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 11.0.6 and 14. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTPS to compromise Java SE. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Java SE accessible data. Note: Applies to client and server deployment of Java. This vulnerability can be exploited through sandboxed Java Web Start applications and sandboxed Java applets. It can also be exploited by supplying data to APIs in the specified Component without using sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, such as through a web service. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 3.7 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2778|2024-08-04T07:17:02.621Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2764|2024-08-04T07:17:02.496Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2764</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE product of Oracle Java SE (component: Advanced Management Console). The supported version that is affected is Java Advanced Management Console: 2.16. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Java SE accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can only be exploited by supplying data to APIs in the specified Component without using Untrusted Java Web Start applications or Untrusted Java applets, such as through a web service. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 3.7 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2764|2024-08-04T07:17:02.496Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2590|2024-08-04T07:09:54.836Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2590</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, Java SE Embedded product of Oracle Java SE (component: Security). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 7u241, 8u231, 11.0.5 and 13.0.1; Java SE Embedded: 8u231. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via Kerberos to compromise Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Java SE, Java SE Embedded accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets (in Java SE 8), that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability can also be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 3.7 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2590|2024-08-04T07:09:54.836Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14579|2024-08-04T12:46:35.006Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14579</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, Java SE Embedded product of Oracle Java SE (component: Libraries). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 7u261 and 8u251; Java SE Embedded: 8u251. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Note: Applies to client and server deployment of Java. This vulnerability can be exploited through sandboxed Java Web Start applications and sandboxed Java applets. It can also be exploited by supplying data to APIs in the specified Component without using sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, such as through a web service. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14579|2024-08-04T12:46:35.006Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2773|2024-08-04T07:17:02.372Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2773</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, Java SE Embedded product of Oracle Java SE (component: Security). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 7u251, 8u241, 11.0.6 and 14; Java SE Embedded: 8u241. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Note: Applies to client and server deployment of Java. This vulnerability can be exploited through sandboxed Java Web Start applications and sandboxed Java applets. It can also be exploited by supplying data to APIs in the specified Component without using sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, such as through a web service. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 3.7 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2773|2024-08-04T07:17:02.372Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2755|2024-08-04T07:17:02.660Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2755</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, Java SE Embedded product of Oracle Java SE (component: Scripting). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 8u241, 11.0.6 and 14; Java SE Embedded: 8u241. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Note: Applies to client and server deployment of Java. This vulnerability can be exploited through sandboxed Java Web Start applications and sandboxed Java applets. It can also be exploited by supplying data to APIs in the specified Component without using sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, such as through a web service. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 3.7 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2755|2024-08-04T07:17:02.660Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2593|2024-08-04T07:09:54.836Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2593</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, Java SE Embedded product of Oracle Java SE (component: Networking). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 7u241, 8u231, 11.0.5 and 13.0.1; Java SE Embedded: 8u231. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Java SE, Java SE Embedded accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Java SE, Java SE Embedded accessible data. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets (in Java SE 8), that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability can also be exploited by using APIs in the specified Component, e.g., through a web service which supplies data to the APIs. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.8 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2593|2024-08-04T07:09:54.836Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14577|2024-08-04T12:46:34.986Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14577</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, Java SE Embedded product of Oracle Java SE (component: JSSE). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 7u261, 8u251, 11.0.7 and 14.0.1; Java SE Embedded: 8u251. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via TLS to compromise Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Java SE, Java SE Embedded accessible data. Note: Applies to client and server deployment of Java. This vulnerability can be exploited through sandboxed Java Web Start applications and sandboxed Java applets. It can also be exploited by supplying data to APIs in the specified Component without using sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, such as through a web service. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14577|2024-08-04T12:46:34.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14573|2024-08-04T12:46:34.936Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14573</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE product of Oracle Java SE (component: Hotspot). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 11.0.7 and 14.0.1. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Java SE accessible data. Note: Applies to client and server deployment of Java. This vulnerability can be exploited through sandboxed Java Web Start applications and sandboxed Java applets. It can also be exploited by supplying data to APIs in the specified Component without using sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, such as through a web service. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.7 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14573|2024-08-04T12:46:34.936Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2757|2024-08-04T07:17:02.624Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2757</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, Java SE Embedded product of Oracle Java SE (component: Serialization). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 7u251, 8u241, 11.0.6 and 14; Java SE Embedded: 8u241. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Note: Applies to client and server deployment of Java. This vulnerability can be exploited through sandboxed Java Web Start applications and sandboxed Java applets. It can also be exploited by supplying data to APIs in the specified Component without using sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, such as through a web service. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 3.7 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2757|2024-08-04T07:17:02.624Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14556|2024-08-04T12:46:34.700Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14556</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, Java SE Embedded product of Oracle Java SE (component: Libraries). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 8u251, 11.0.7 and 14.0.1; Java SE Embedded: 8u251. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Java SE, Java SE Embedded accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Java SE, Java SE Embedded accessible data. Note: Applies to client and server deployment of Java. This vulnerability can be exploited through sandboxed Java Web Start applications and sandboxed Java applets. It can also be exploited by supplying data to APIs in the specified Component without using sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, such as through a web service. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.8 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14556|2024-08-04T12:46:34.700Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14664|2024-08-04T12:53:42.545Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14664</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE product of Oracle Java SE (component: JavaFX). The supported version that is affected is Java SE: 8u251. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Java SE, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Java SE. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14664|2024-08-04T12:53:42.545Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2767|2024-08-04T07:17:02.632Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2767</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE product of Oracle Java SE (component: JSSE). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 11.0.6 and 14. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTPS to compromise Java SE. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Java SE accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Java SE accessible data. Note: Applies to client and server deployment of Java. This vulnerability can be exploited through sandboxed Java Web Start applications and sandboxed Java applets. It can also be exploited by supplying data to APIs in the specified Component without using sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, such as through a web service. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.8 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2767|2024-08-04T07:17:02.632Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2803|2024-08-04T07:17:02.732Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2803</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, Java SE Embedded product of Oracle Java SE (component: Libraries). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 7u251, 8u241, 11.0.6 and 14; Java SE Embedded: 8u241. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Java SE, Java SE Embedded, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Note: This vulnerability applies to Java deployments, typically in clients running sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, that load and run untrusted code (e.g., code that comes from the internet) and rely on the Java sandbox for security. This vulnerability does not apply to Java deployments, typically in servers, that load and run only trusted code (e.g., code installed by an administrator). CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2803|2024-08-04T07:17:02.732Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2756|2024-08-04T07:17:02.285Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2756</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, Java SE Embedded product of Oracle Java SE (component: Serialization). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 7u251, 8u241, 11.0.6 and 14; Java SE Embedded: 8u241. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Note: Applies to client and server deployment of Java. This vulnerability can be exploited through sandboxed Java Web Start applications and sandboxed Java applets. It can also be exploited by supplying data to APIs in the specified Component without using sandboxed Java Web Start applications or sandboxed Java applets, such as through a web service. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 3.7 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2756|2024-08-04T07:17:02.285Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2800|2024-08-04T07:17:02.727Z -- oracle%20corporation -- java
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2800</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java SE, Java SE Embedded product of Oracle Java SE (component: Lightweight HTTP Server). Supported versions that are affected are Java SE: 7u251, 8u241, 11.0.6 and 14; Java SE Embedded: 8u241. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java SE, Java SE Embedded. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Java SE, Java SE Embedded accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Java SE, Java SE Embedded accessible data. Note: This vulnerability can only be exploited by supplying data to APIs in the specified Component without using Untrusted Java Web Start applications or Untrusted Java applets, such as through a web service. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.8 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2800|2024-08-04T07:17:02.727Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
