<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/jd%20edwards%20enterpriseone%20tools.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 23:23:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21409|2024-08-03T02:38:56.197Z -- oracle%20corporation -- jd%20edwards%20enterpriseone%20tools
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21409</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools product of Oracle JD Edwards (component: Web Runtime). The supported version that is affected is Prior to 9.2.6.3. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21409|2024-08-03T02:38:56.197Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 20:36:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-2375|2024-08-03T16:38:57.695Z -- oracle%20corporation -- jd%20edwards%20enterpriseone%20tools
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-2375</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools product of Oracle JD Edwards (component: Web Runtime). Supported versions that are affected are 9.2.5.3 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-2375|2024-08-03T16:38:57.695Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 22:43:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-2373|2024-08-03T16:38:57.563Z -- oracle%20corporation -- jd%20edwards%20enterpriseone%20tools
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-2373</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools product of Oracle JD Edwards (component: Web Runtime). Supported versions that are affected are 9.2.5.3 and Prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-2373|2024-08-03T16:38:57.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 22:43:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21629|2024-08-03T02:46:39.448Z -- oracle%20corporation -- jd%20edwards%20enterpriseone%20tools
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21629</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools product of Oracle JD Edwards (component: Web Runtime SEC). Supported versions that are affected are 9.2.6.4 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21629|2024-08-03T02:46:39.448Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21561|2024-08-03T02:46:38.624Z -- oracle%20corporation -- jd%20edwards%20enterpriseone%20tools
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21561</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools product of Oracle JD Edwards (component: Web Runtime). Supported versions that are affected are 9.2.6.3 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21561|2024-08-03T02:46:38.624Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 21:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21630|2024-08-03T02:46:39.086Z -- oracle%20corporation -- jd%20edwards%20enterpriseone%20tools
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21630</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools product of Oracle JD Edwards (component: Web Runtime SEC). Supported versions that are affected are 9.2.6.4 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21630|2024-08-03T02:46:39.086Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21542|2024-08-03T02:46:38.495Z -- oracle%20corporation -- jd%20edwards%20enterpriseone%20tools
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21542</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools product of Oracle JD Edwards (component: Web Runtime). Supported versions that are affected are 9.2.6.3 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools. While the vulnerability is in JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.4 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21542|2024-08-03T02:46:38.495Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 21:07:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21631|2024-08-03T02:46:39.079Z -- oracle%20corporation -- jd%20edwards%20enterpriseone%20tools
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21631</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools product of Oracle JD Edwards (component: Design Tools SEC). Supported versions that are affected are 9.2.6.4 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21631|2024-08-03T02:46:39.079Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21464|2024-08-03T02:38:56.488Z -- oracle%20corporation -- jd%20edwards%20enterpriseone%20tools
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21464</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools product of Oracle JD Edwards (component: Business Logic Infra SEC). The supported version that is affected is Prior to 9.2.6.3. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools and unauthorized read access to a subset of JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.2 (Confidentiality and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21464|2024-08-03T02:38:56.488Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 20:38:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21150|2024-07-22T14:38:59.393Z -- oracle%20corporation -- jd%20edwards%20enterpriseone%20tools</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21150</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools product of Oracle JD Edwards (component: Web Runtime SEC).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 9.2.8.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21150|2024-07-22T14:38:59.393Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20937|2024-07-05T17:21:43.335Z -- oracle%20corporation -- jd%20edwards%20enterpriseone%20tools</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20937</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools product of Oracle JD Edwards (component: Monitoring and Diagnostics SEC).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 9.2.8.1. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.3 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20937|2024-07-05T17:21:43.335Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20905|2024-02-17T01:50:07.693Z -- oracle%20corporation -- jd%20edwards%20enterpriseone%20tools</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20905</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools product of Oracle JD Edwards (component: Enterprise Infrastructure SEC).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 9.2.8.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via JDENET to compromise JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 2.7 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20905|2024-02-17T01:50:07.693Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20937|2024-02-17T01:50:13.991Z -- oracle%20corporation -- jd%20edwards%20enterpriseone%20tools</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20937</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools product of Oracle JD Edwards (component: Monitoring and Diagnostics SEC).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 9.2.8.1. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.3 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20937|2024-02-17T01:50:13.991Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21150|2024-07-16T22:40:00.257Z -- oracle%20corporation -- jd%20edwards%20enterpriseone%20tools</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21150</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools product of Oracle JD Edwards (component: Web Runtime SEC).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 9.2.8.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21150|2024-07-16T22:40:00.257Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20905|2024-08-01T22:06:37.329Z -- oracle%20corporation -- jd%20edwards%20enterpriseone%20tools</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20905</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools product of Oracle JD Edwards (component: Enterprise Infrastructure SEC).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 9.2.8.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via JDENET to compromise JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 2.7 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20905|2024-08-01T22:06:37.329Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20937|2024-08-01T22:06:37.385Z -- oracle%20corporation -- jd%20edwards%20enterpriseone%20tools</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20937</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools product of Oracle JD Edwards (component: Monitoring and Diagnostics SEC).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 9.2.8.1. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.3 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20937|2024-08-01T22:06:37.385Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21150|2024-08-01T22:13:42.704Z -- oracle%20corporation -- jd%20edwards%20enterpriseone%20tools</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21150</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools product of Oracle JD Edwards (component: Web Runtime SEC).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 9.2.8.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of JD Edwards EnterpriseOne Tools accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21150|2024-08-01T22:13:42.704Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
