<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- Marketing Encyclopedia System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/marketing%20encyclopedia%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- Marketing Encyclopedia System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 08:23:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2807|2024-08-04T07:17:02.672Z -- oracle%20corporation -- marketing%20encyclopedia%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2807</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Marketing Encyclopedia System product of Oracle E-Business Suite (component: Administration). Supported versions that are affected are 12.1.1-12.1.3. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Marketing Encyclopedia System. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Marketing Encyclopedia System, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Marketing Encyclopedia System accessible data as well as unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Marketing Encyclopedia System accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.2 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:H/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2807|2024-08-04T07:17:02.672Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
