<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- MICROS Relate CRM Software</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/micros%20relate%20crm%20software.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- MICROS Relate CRM Software</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 15:23:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3052|2024-08-05T04:36:39.674Z -- oracle%20corporation -- micros%20relate%20crm%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3052</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MICROS Relate CRM Software component of Oracle Retail Applications (subcomponent: Internal Operations). Supported versions that are affected are 10.8.x and 11.4.x. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise MICROS Relate CRM Software. While the vulnerability is in MICROS Relate CRM Software, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of MICROS Relate CRM Software accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of MICROS Relate CRM Software. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.4 (Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3052|2024-08-05T04:36:39.674Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3314|2024-08-05T04:50:30.433Z -- oracle%20corporation -- micros%20relate%20crm%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3314</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MICROS Relate CRM Software component of Oracle Retail Applications (subcomponent: Customer). The supported version that is affected is 11.4. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise MICROS Relate CRM Software. While the vulnerability is in MICROS Relate CRM Software, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all MICROS Relate CRM Software accessible data as well as unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all MICROS Relate CRM Software accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.2 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3314|2024-08-05T04:50:30.433Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 18:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
