<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- MySQL Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/mysql%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- MySQL Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 11:20:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2761|2024-08-04T07:17:02.625Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2761</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Security: Privileges). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.18 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2761|2024-08-04T07:17:02.625Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2806|2024-08-04T07:17:02.791Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2806</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Compiling). Supported versions that are affected are 5.7.28 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.3 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2806|2024-08-04T07:17:02.791Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2892|2024-08-04T07:23:58.786Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2892</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.19 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2892|2024-08-04T07:23:58.786Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2765|2024-08-04T07:17:02.544Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2765</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer). Supported versions that are affected are 5.7.29 and prior and 8.0.19 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2765|2024-08-04T07:17:02.544Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2574|2024-08-04T07:09:54.709Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2574</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Client product of Oracle MySQL (component: C API). Supported versions that are affected are 5.6.46 and prior, 5.7.28 and prior and 8.0.18 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Client. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Client. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2574|2024-08-04T07:09:54.709Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35575|2024-08-04T00:40:46.993Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35575</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.26 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35575|2024-08-04T00:40:46.993Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:50:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35636|2024-08-04T00:40:47.449Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35636</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.26 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35636|2024-08-04T00:40:47.449Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35622|2024-08-04T00:40:47.455Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35622</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Security: Encryption). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.26 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35622|2024-08-04T00:40:47.455Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:50:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2925|2024-08-04T07:23:59.619Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2925</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: PS). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.19 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2925|2024-08-04T07:23:59.619Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35610|2024-08-04T00:40:47.575Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35610</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.26 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server as well as unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of MySQL Server accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.1 (Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35610|2024-08-04T00:40:47.575Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:50:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2579|2024-08-04T07:09:54.773Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2579</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer). Supported versions that are affected are 5.6.46 and prior, 5.7.28 and prior and 8.0.18 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2579|2024-08-04T07:09:54.773Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35612|2024-08-04T00:40:47.293Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35612</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.26 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server as well as unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of MySQL Server accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.5 (Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35612|2024-08-04T00:40:47.293Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:50:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2760|2024-08-04T07:17:02.443Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2760</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB). Supported versions that are affected are 5.7.29 and prior and 8.0.19 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server as well as unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of MySQL Server accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.5 (Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2760|2024-08-04T07:17:02.443Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2893|2024-08-04T07:23:58.813Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2893</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.19 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2893|2024-08-04T07:23:58.813Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2570|2024-08-04T07:09:54.675Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2570</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Client product of Oracle MySQL (component: C API). Supported versions that are affected are 5.7.28 and prior and 8.0.18 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Client. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Client. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2570|2024-08-04T07:09:54.675Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2853|2024-08-04T07:17:03.068Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2853</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Security: Privileges). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.18 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2853|2024-08-04T07:17:03.068Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2896|2024-08-04T07:23:58.854Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2896</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Information Schema). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.19 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2896|2024-08-04T07:23:58.854Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2679|2024-08-04T07:17:01.066Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2679</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.18 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2679|2024-08-04T07:17:01.066Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35608|2024-08-04T00:40:47.376Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35608</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Group Replication Plugin). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.26 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35608|2024-08-04T00:40:47.376Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:50:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2627|2024-08-04T07:09:54.843Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2627</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Parser). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.18 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2627|2024-08-04T07:09:54.843Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2686|2024-08-04T07:17:01.374Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2686</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.18 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2686|2024-08-04T07:17:01.374Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2804|2024-08-04T07:17:02.646Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2804</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Memcached). Supported versions that are affected are 5.6.47 and prior, 5.7.29 and prior and 8.0.19 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2804|2024-08-04T07:17:02.646Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2770|2024-08-04T07:17:02.679Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2770</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Logging). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.18 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2770|2024-08-04T07:17:02.679Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2926|2024-08-04T07:24:00.579Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2926</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Group Replication GCS). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.19 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.4 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2926|2024-08-04T07:24:00.579Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35623|2024-08-04T00:40:47.529Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35623</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Security: Roles). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.26 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of MySQL Server accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 2.7 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35623|2024-08-04T00:40:47.529Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:50:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2779|2024-08-04T07:17:02.681Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2779</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Security: Privileges). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.18 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2779|2024-08-04T07:17:02.681Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2921|2024-08-04T07:24:00.410Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2921</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Group Replication Plugin). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.19 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.4 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2921|2024-08-04T07:24:00.410Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35635|2024-08-04T00:40:47.611Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35635</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.26 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35635|2024-08-04T00:40:47.611Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35629|2024-08-04T00:40:47.442Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35629</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.25 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35629|2024-08-04T00:40:47.442Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35597|2024-08-04T00:40:47.442Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35597</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Client product of Oracle MySQL (component: C API). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.26 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Client. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Client. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35597|2024-08-04T00:40:47.442Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:50:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35631|2024-08-04T00:40:47.342Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35631</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: GIS). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.26 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35631|2024-08-04T00:40:47.342Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35630|2024-08-04T00:40:47.457Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35630</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Options). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.26 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all MySQL Server accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35630|2024-08-04T00:40:47.457Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35648|2024-08-04T00:40:47.455Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35648</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: FTS). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.26 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35648|2024-08-04T00:40:47.455Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35583|2024-08-04T00:40:47.379Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35583</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Windows). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.25 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35583|2024-08-04T00:40:47.379Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:50:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35633|2024-08-04T00:40:47.441Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35633</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Logging). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.26 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 2.7 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35633|2024-08-04T00:40:47.441Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35577|2024-08-04T00:40:47.385Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35577</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.26 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via MySQL Protcol to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35577|2024-08-04T00:40:47.385Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:50:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2762|2024-08-04T07:17:02.472Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2762</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.19 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2762|2024-08-04T07:17:02.472Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2694|2024-08-04T07:17:01.987Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2694</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Information Schema). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.18 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of MySQL Server accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 3.1 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2694|2024-08-04T07:17:01.987Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2774|2024-08-04T07:17:02.610Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2774</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Security: Privileges). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.18 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2774|2024-08-04T07:17:02.610Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2903|2024-08-04T07:23:59.303Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2903</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Connection Handling). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.19 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2903|2024-08-04T07:23:59.303Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2584|2024-08-04T07:09:54.795Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2584</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Options). Supported versions that are affected are 5.7.28 and prior and 8.0.18 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all MySQL Server accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.4 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2584|2024-08-04T07:09:54.795Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35604|2024-08-04T00:40:47.385Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35604</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB). Supported versions that are affected are 5.7.35 and prior and 8.0.26 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server as well as unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of MySQL Server accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.5 (Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35604|2024-08-04T00:40:47.385Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:50:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35625|2024-08-04T00:40:47.535Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35625</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Security: Privileges). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.26 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of MySQL Server accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 2.7 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35625|2024-08-04T00:40:47.535Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2924|2024-08-04T07:24:00.684Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2924</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.19 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2924|2024-08-04T07:24:00.684Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35627|2024-08-04T00:40:47.371Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35627</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.26 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35627|2024-08-04T00:40:47.371Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35624|2024-08-04T00:40:47.428Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35624</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Security: Privileges). Supported versions that are affected are 5.7.35 and prior and 8.0.26 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all MySQL Server accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35624|2024-08-04T00:40:47.428Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:50:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35602|2024-08-04T00:40:47.303Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35602</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Options). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.26 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server as well as unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of MySQL Server accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.0 (Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35602|2024-08-04T00:40:47.303Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:50:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35642|2024-08-04T00:40:47.341Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35642</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.26 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35642|2024-08-04T00:40:47.341Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35628|2024-08-04T00:40:47.371Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35628</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.26 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35628|2024-08-04T00:40:47.371Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2580|2024-08-04T07:09:54.861Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2580</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DDL). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.17 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2580|2024-08-04T07:09:54.861Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2897|2024-08-04T07:23:58.752Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2897</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.19 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2897|2024-08-04T07:23:58.752Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2812|2024-08-04T07:17:02.664Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2812</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Stored Procedure). Supported versions that are affected are 5.6.47 and prior, 5.7.29 and prior and 8.0.19 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2812|2024-08-04T07:17:02.664Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2588|2024-08-04T07:09:54.846Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2588</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DML). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.18 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2588|2024-08-04T07:09:54.846Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2814|2024-08-04T07:17:02.780Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2814</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB). Supported versions that are affected are 5.6.47 and prior, 5.7.28 and prior and 8.0.18 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2814|2024-08-04T07:17:02.780Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35644|2024-08-04T00:40:47.587Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35644</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.26 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35644|2024-08-04T00:40:47.587Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35638|2024-08-04T00:40:47.434Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35638</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.26 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35638|2024-08-04T00:40:47.434Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35607|2024-08-04T00:40:47.313Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35607</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DML). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.26 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35607|2024-08-04T00:40:47.313Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:50:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35634|2024-08-04T00:40:47.531Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35634</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.26 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35634|2024-08-04T00:40:47.531Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35640|2024-08-04T00:40:47.331Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35640</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DDL). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.26 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of MySQL Server accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 2.7 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35640|2024-08-04T00:40:47.331Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35646|2024-08-04T00:40:47.431Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35646</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.26 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35646|2024-08-04T00:40:47.431Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2759|2024-08-04T07:17:02.455Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2759</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Replication). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.19 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2759|2024-08-04T07:17:02.455Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2780|2024-08-04T07:17:02.564Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2780</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DML). Supported versions that are affected are 5.6.47 and prior, 5.7.29 and prior and 8.0.19 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2780|2024-08-04T07:17:02.564Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2589|2024-08-04T07:09:54.764Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2589</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB). Supported versions that are affected are 5.7.28 and prior and 8.0.17 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2589|2024-08-04T07:09:54.764Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2752|2024-08-04T07:17:02.406Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2752</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Client product of Oracle MySQL (component: C API). Supported versions that are affected are 5.6.47 and prior, 5.7.27 and prior and 8.0.17 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Client. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Client. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.3 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2752|2024-08-04T07:17:02.406Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35637|2024-08-04T00:40:47.360Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35637</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: PS). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.26 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35637|2024-08-04T00:40:47.360Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2930|2024-08-04T07:24:00.579Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2930</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Parser). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.19 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.4 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2930|2024-08-04T07:24:00.579Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35647|2024-08-04T00:40:47.344Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35647</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.26 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35647|2024-08-04T00:40:47.344Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35596|2024-08-04T00:40:47.324Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35596</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Error Handling). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.26 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35596|2024-08-04T00:40:47.324Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:50:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2928|2024-08-04T07:23:59.971Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2928</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.19 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2928|2024-08-04T07:23:59.971Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2904|2024-08-04T07:24:00.568Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2904</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.19 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2904|2024-08-04T07:24:00.568Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2898|2024-08-04T07:23:59.337Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2898</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Charsets). The supported version that is affected is 8.0.19. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2898|2024-08-04T07:23:59.337Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2660|2024-08-04T07:09:54.900Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2660</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer). Supported versions that are affected are 5.7.28 and prior and 8.0.18 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2660|2024-08-04T07:09:54.900Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35626|2024-08-04T00:40:47.441Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35626</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.26 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35626|2024-08-04T00:40:47.441Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2572|2024-08-04T07:09:54.807Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2572</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Audit Plugin). Supported versions that are affected are 5.7.28 and prior and 8.0.18 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of MySQL Server accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 2.7 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2572|2024-08-04T07:09:54.807Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2895|2024-08-04T07:23:59.276Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2895</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.19 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2895|2024-08-04T07:23:59.276Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2901|2024-08-04T07:23:59.372Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2901</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.19 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2901|2024-08-04T07:23:59.372Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2577|2024-08-04T07:09:54.722Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2577</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB). Supported versions that are affected are 5.7.28 and prior and 8.0.18 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2577|2024-08-04T07:09:54.722Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35641|2024-08-04T00:40:47.537Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35641</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.26 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35641|2024-08-04T00:40:47.537Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2923|2024-08-04T07:23:59.774Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2923</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.19 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2923|2024-08-04T07:23:59.774Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2573|2024-08-04T07:09:54.558Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2573</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Client product of Oracle MySQL (component: C API). Supported versions that are affected are 5.7.28 and prior and 8.0.18 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Client. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Client. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2573|2024-08-04T07:09:54.558Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35645|2024-08-04T00:40:47.332Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35645</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.26 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35645|2024-08-04T00:40:47.332Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35537|2024-08-04T00:40:47.235Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35537</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DML). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.25 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35537|2024-08-04T00:40:47.235Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:49:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35639|2024-08-04T00:40:47.456Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35639</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Stored Procedure). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.26 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35639|2024-08-04T00:40:47.456Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35632|2024-08-04T00:40:47.431Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35632</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Data Dictionary). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.26 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where MySQL Server executes to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.4 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35632|2024-08-04T00:40:47.431Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35546|2024-08-04T00:40:46.458Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35546</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Replication). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.26 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35546|2024-08-04T00:40:46.458Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:49:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35591|2024-08-04T00:40:47.305Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35591</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DML). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.26 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35591|2024-08-04T00:40:47.305Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:50:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2763|2024-08-04T07:17:03.015Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2763</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Replication). Supported versions that are affected are 5.6.47 and prior, 5.7.29 and prior and 8.0.19 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2763|2024-08-04T07:17:03.015Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2922|2024-08-04T07:23:59.715Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2922</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Client product of Oracle MySQL (component: C API). Supported versions that are affected are 5.6.47 and prior, 5.7.29 and prior and 8.0.18 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Client. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of MySQL Client accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 3.7 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2922|2024-08-04T07:23:59.715Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35643|2024-08-04T00:40:47.369Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35643</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer). Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.26 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35643|2024-08-04T00:40:47.369Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2790|2024-08-04T07:17:02.710Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2790</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Pluggable Auth). Supported versions that are affected are 5.7.28 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2790|2024-08-04T07:17:02.710Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21051|2024-08-01T22:13:42.397Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21051</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DML).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.34 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21051|2024-08-01T22:13:42.397Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21160|2024-08-01T22:13:42.724Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21160</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21160|2024-08-01T22:13:42.724Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21135|2024-08-01T22:13:42.690Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21135</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21135|2024-08-01T22:13:42.690Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21162|2024-08-01T22:13:42.699Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21162</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21162|2024-08-01T22:13:42.699Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21163|2024-08-01T22:13:42.773Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21163</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server as well as  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of MySQL Server accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.5 (Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21163|2024-08-01T22:13:42.773Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20970|2024-08-01T22:06:37.371Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20970</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20970|2024-08-01T22:06:37.371Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20964|2024-08-01T22:06:37.351Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20964</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Security: Privileges).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20964|2024-08-01T22:06:37.351Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21053|2024-08-01T22:13:42.575Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21053</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DML).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.34 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21053|2024-08-01T22:13:42.575Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21129|2024-08-01T22:13:42.683Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21129</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DDL).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21129|2024-08-01T22:13:42.683Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20994|2024-08-01T22:13:41.476Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20994</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Information Schema).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20994|2024-08-01T22:13:41.476Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20978|2024-08-01T22:06:37.387Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20978</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20978|2024-08-01T22:06:37.387Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20998|2024-08-01T22:13:42.213Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20998</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20998|2024-08-01T22:13:42.213Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20982|2024-08-01T22:06:37.373Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20982</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20982|2024-08-01T22:06:37.373Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21179|2024-08-01T22:13:42.795Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21179</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21179|2024-08-01T22:13:42.795Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21000|2024-08-01T22:13:41.392Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21000</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Security: Privileges).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of MySQL Server accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of MySQL Server accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.8 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21000|2024-08-01T22:13:41.392Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21127|2024-08-01T22:13:42.668Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21127</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DDL).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21127|2024-08-01T22:13:42.668Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21087|2024-08-01T22:13:42.484Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21087</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Group Replication Plugin).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21087|2024-08-01T22:13:42.484Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20974|2024-08-01T22:06:37.415Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20974</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20974|2024-08-01T22:06:37.415Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20993|2024-08-01T22:13:41.490Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20993</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20993|2024-08-01T22:13:41.490Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21013|2024-08-01T22:13:41.770Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21013</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.4 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21013|2024-08-01T22:13:41.770Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21176|2024-08-01T22:13:42.798Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21176</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Thread Pooling).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.4.0 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21176|2024-08-01T22:13:42.798Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20968|2024-08-01T22:06:37.385Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20968</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Options).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.34 and prior and  8.1.0. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.4 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20968|2024-08-01T22:06:37.385Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21157|2024-08-01T22:13:42.693Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21157</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21157|2024-08-01T22:13:42.693Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21055|2024-08-01T22:13:42.365Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21055</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21055|2024-08-01T22:13:42.365Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21185|2024-08-01T22:13:42.683Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21185</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.38, 8.4.1 and  9.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21185|2024-08-01T22:13:42.683Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21062|2024-08-01T22:13:42.343Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21062</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21062|2024-08-01T22:13:42.343Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21142|2024-08-01T22:13:42.779Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21142</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Security: Privileges).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21142|2024-08-01T22:13:42.779Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21008|2024-08-01T22:13:42.660Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21008</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.4 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21008|2024-08-01T22:13:42.660Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21137|2024-08-01T22:13:42.684Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21137</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21137|2024-08-01T22:13:42.684Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21049|2024-08-01T22:13:42.425Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21049</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DML).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.34 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21049|2024-08-01T22:13:42.425Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21052|2024-08-01T22:13:42.349Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21052</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DML).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.34 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21052|2024-08-01T22:13:42.349Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21171|2024-08-01T22:13:42.696Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21171</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21171|2024-08-01T22:13:42.696Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21159|2024-08-01T22:13:42.703Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21159</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21159|2024-08-01T22:13:42.703Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21130|2024-08-01T22:13:42.677Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21130</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21130|2024-08-01T22:13:42.677Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20996|2024-08-01T22:13:42.032Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20996</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20996|2024-08-01T22:13:42.032Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21056|2024-08-01T22:13:42.338Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21056</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DML).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.34 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21056|2024-08-01T22:13:42.338Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21050|2024-08-01T22:13:42.169Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21050</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DML).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.34 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21050|2024-08-01T22:13:42.169Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21047|2024-08-01T22:13:42.238Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21047</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21047|2024-08-01T22:13:42.238Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21060|2024-08-01T22:13:42.287Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21060</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Data Dictionary).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21060|2024-08-01T22:13:42.287Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20960|2024-08-01T22:06:37.384Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20960</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: RAPID).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20960|2024-08-01T22:06:37.384Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21057|2024-08-01T22:13:42.513Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21057</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21057|2024-08-01T22:13:42.513Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21173|2024-08-01T22:13:42.794Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21173</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21173|2024-08-01T22:13:42.794Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21096|2024-08-01T22:13:42.455Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21096</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Client: mysqldump).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with logon to the infrastructure where MySQL Server executes to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of MySQL Server accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of MySQL Server accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21096|2024-08-01T22:13:42.455Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20972|2024-08-01T22:06:37.507Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20972</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20972|2024-08-01T22:06:37.507Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20966|2024-08-01T22:06:37.368Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20966</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20966|2024-08-01T22:06:37.368Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21134|2024-08-01T22:13:42.651Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21134</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Connection Handling).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.3 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21134|2024-08-01T22:13:42.651Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21015|2024-08-01T22:13:41.481Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21015</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DML).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.34 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server as well as  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of MySQL Server accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.5 (Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21015|2024-08-01T22:13:41.481Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21061|2024-08-01T22:13:42.367Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21061</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Audit Plug-in).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21061|2024-08-01T22:13:42.367Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21165|2024-08-01T22:13:42.696Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21165</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Pluggable Auth).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21165|2024-08-01T22:13:42.696Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21009|2024-08-01T22:13:42.323Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21009</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21009|2024-08-01T22:13:42.323Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21054|2024-08-01T22:13:42.351Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21054</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21054|2024-08-01T22:13:42.351Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21166|2024-08-01T22:13:42.784Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21166</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all MySQL Server accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.9 (Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21166|2024-08-01T22:13:42.784Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20984|2024-08-01T22:06:37.451Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20984</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server : Security : Firewall).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.4 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20984|2024-08-01T22:06:37.451Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21069|2024-08-01T22:13:42.360Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21069</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DDL).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21069|2024-08-01T22:13:42.360Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20962|2024-08-01T22:06:37.396Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20962</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20962|2024-08-01T22:06:37.396Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20976|2024-08-01T22:06:37.403Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20976</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20976|2024-08-01T22:06:37.403Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21176|2024-07-31T20:17:00.355Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21176</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Thread Pooling).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.4.0 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21176|2024-07-31T20:17:00.355Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21157|2024-07-31T20:16:58.418Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21157</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21157|2024-07-31T20:16:58.418Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21185|2024-07-31T20:17:01.311Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21185</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.38, 8.4.1 and  9.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21185|2024-07-31T20:17:01.311Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21137|2024-07-31T20:16:57.394Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21137</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21137|2024-07-31T20:16:57.394Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21165|2024-07-31T20:16:59.395Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21165</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Pluggable Auth).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21165|2024-07-31T20:16:59.395Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21130|2024-07-23T16:33:30.444Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21130</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21130|2024-07-23T16:33:30.444Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21127|2024-07-19T17:29:16.955Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21127</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DDL).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21127|2024-07-19T17:29:16.955Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21163|2024-07-17T19:03:59.255Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21163</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server as well as  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of MySQL Server accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.5 (Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21163|2024-07-17T19:03:59.255Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21142|2024-07-17T19:09:55.936Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21142</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Security: Privileges).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21142|2024-07-17T19:09:55.936Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21185|2024-07-17T19:03:04.043Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21185</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.38, 8.4.1 and  9.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21185|2024-07-17T19:03:04.043Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21157|2024-07-17T13:58:37.282Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21157</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21157|2024-07-17T13:58:37.282Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21087|2024-07-17T13:57:08.337Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21087</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Group Replication Plugin).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21087|2024-07-17T13:57:08.337Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21049|2024-07-17T13:45:18.639Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21049</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DML).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.34 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21049|2024-07-17T13:45:18.639Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21179|2024-07-17T13:46:24.341Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21179</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21179|2024-07-17T13:46:24.341Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21162|2024-07-17T13:33:58.044Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21162</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21162|2024-07-17T13:33:58.044Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21129|2024-07-17T13:33:14.881Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21129</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DDL).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21129|2024-07-17T13:33:14.881Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21009|2024-07-17T13:44:18.775Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21009</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21009|2024-07-17T13:44:18.775Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21135|2024-07-17T13:57:29.839Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21135</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21135|2024-07-17T13:57:29.839Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21160|2024-07-17T13:32:14.553Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21160</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21160|2024-07-17T13:32:14.553Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21159|2024-07-17T13:48:58.875Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21159</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21159|2024-07-17T13:48:58.875Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21047|2024-07-15T18:26:41.907Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21047</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21047|2024-07-15T18:26:41.907Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20964|2024-07-05T17:21:45.916Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20964</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Security: Privileges).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20964|2024-07-05T17:21:45.916Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20972|2024-07-05T17:21:48.101Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20972</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20972|2024-07-05T17:21:48.101Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20976|2024-07-05T17:20:57.609Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20976</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20976|2024-07-05T17:20:57.609Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20984|2024-07-05T17:20:55.879Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20984</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server : Security : Firewall).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.4 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20984|2024-07-05T17:20:55.879Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20974|2024-07-05T17:20:55.983Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20974</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20974|2024-07-05T17:20:55.983Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20978|2024-07-05T17:21:44.162Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20978</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20978|2024-07-05T17:21:44.162Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20993|2024-06-17T18:08:46.736Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20993</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20993|2024-06-17T18:08:46.736Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20984|2024-02-17T01:50:22.747Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20984</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server : Security : Firewall).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.4 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20984|2024-02-17T01:50:22.747Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20993|2024-04-16T21:25:55.794Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20993</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20993|2024-04-16T21:25:55.794Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20966|2024-06-04T17:40:38.223Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20966</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20966|2024-06-04T17:40:38.223Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20970|2024-06-04T17:40:37.317Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20970</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20970|2024-06-04T17:40:37.317Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20994|2024-06-04T17:40:35.225Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20994</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Information Schema).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20994|2024-06-04T17:40:35.225Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20982|2024-06-04T17:40:34.772Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20982</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20982|2024-06-04T17:40:34.772Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20998|2024-06-04T17:40:30.457Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20998</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20998|2024-06-04T17:40:30.457Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20960|2024-06-04T17:40:24.649Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20960</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: RAPID).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20960|2024-06-04T17:40:24.649Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20976|2024-02-17T01:50:21.249Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20976</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20976|2024-02-17T01:50:21.249Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20974|2024-02-17T01:50:20.861Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20974</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20974|2024-02-17T01:50:20.861Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20962|2024-06-07T15:57:59.785Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20962</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20962|2024-06-07T15:57:59.785Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20978|2024-02-17T01:50:21.606Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20978</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20978|2024-02-17T01:50:21.606Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20968|2024-02-17T01:50:19.680Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20968</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Options).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.34 and prior and  8.1.0. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.4 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20968|2024-02-17T01:50:19.680Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20972|2024-02-17T01:50:20.471Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20972</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20972|2024-02-17T01:50:20.471Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20964|2024-02-17T01:50:18.930Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20964</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Security: Privileges).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20964|2024-02-17T01:50:18.930Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21008|2024-06-04T17:38:18.945Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21008</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.4 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21008|2024-06-04T17:38:18.945Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21049|2024-04-16T21:26:14.785Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21049</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DML).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.34 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21049|2024-04-16T21:26:14.785Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21053|2024-06-04T17:38:15.735Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21053</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DML).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.34 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21053|2024-06-04T17:38:15.735Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21069|2024-04-16T21:26:21.750Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21069</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DDL).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21069|2024-04-16T21:26:21.750Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21087|2024-04-16T21:26:27.815Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21087</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Group Replication Plugin).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21087|2024-04-16T21:26:27.815Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21013|2024-06-04T17:38:09.373Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21013</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.4 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21013|2024-06-04T17:38:09.373Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21052|2024-04-16T21:26:15.734Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21052</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DML).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.34 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21052|2024-04-16T21:26:15.734Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21009|2024-04-16T21:26:01.082Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21009</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21009|2024-04-16T21:26:01.082Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21055|2024-04-16T21:26:16.694Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21055</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21055|2024-04-16T21:26:16.694Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21096|2024-04-16T21:26:30.986Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21096</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Client: mysqldump).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with logon to the infrastructure where MySQL Server executes to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of MySQL Server accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of MySQL Server accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21096|2024-04-16T21:26:30.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21062|2024-06-06T20:19:04.844Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21062</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21062|2024-06-06T20:19:04.844Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21015|2024-04-16T21:26:03.248Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21015</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DML).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.34 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server as well as  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of MySQL Server accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.5 (Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21015|2024-04-16T21:26:03.248Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21054|2024-06-04T17:37:52.860Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21054</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21054|2024-06-04T17:37:52.860Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21057|2024-06-04T17:37:49.526Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21057</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21057|2024-06-04T17:37:49.526Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21000|2024-04-16T21:25:57.876Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21000</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Security: Privileges).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of MySQL Server accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of MySQL Server accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.8 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21000|2024-04-16T21:25:57.876Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21061|2024-04-16T21:26:18.783Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21061</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Audit Plug-in).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21061|2024-04-16T21:26:18.783Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21060|2024-06-04T17:37:44.979Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21060</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Data Dictionary).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21060|2024-06-04T17:37:44.979Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21056|2024-04-16T21:26:17.004Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21056</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DML).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.34 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21056|2024-04-16T21:26:17.004Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21047|2024-04-16T21:26:14.113Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21047</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21047|2024-04-16T21:26:14.113Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21051|2024-06-04T17:37:36.010Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21051</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DML).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.34 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21051|2024-06-04T17:37:36.010Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21050|2024-06-04T17:37:32.693Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21050</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DML).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.34 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21050|2024-06-04T17:37:32.693Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21056|2024-06-13T20:44:04.573Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21056</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DML).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.34 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21056|2024-06-13T20:44:04.573Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21061|2024-06-13T20:41:03.231Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21061</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Audit Plug-in).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21061|2024-06-13T20:41:03.231Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21000|2024-07-05T12:45:54.132Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21000</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Security: Privileges).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of MySQL Server accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of MySQL Server accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.8 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21000|2024-07-05T12:45:54.132Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21015|2024-07-15T15:58:56.819Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21015</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DML).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.34 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server as well as  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of MySQL Server accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.5 (Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21015|2024-07-15T15:58:56.819Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21159|2024-07-16T22:40:02.964Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21159</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21159|2024-07-16T22:40:02.964Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21166|2024-07-16T22:40:05.491Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21166</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all MySQL Server accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.9 (Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21166|2024-07-16T22:40:05.491Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21185|2024-07-16T22:40:11.998Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21185</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.38, 8.4.1 and  9.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21185|2024-07-16T22:40:11.998Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21160|2024-07-16T22:40:03.314Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21160</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21160|2024-07-16T22:40:03.314Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21171|2024-07-16T22:40:07.647Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21171</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21171|2024-07-16T22:40:07.647Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21142|2024-07-16T22:39:57.590Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21142</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Security: Privileges).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21142|2024-07-16T22:39:57.590Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20996|2024-07-16T22:39:19.199Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20996</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20996|2024-07-16T22:39:19.199Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21135|2024-07-16T22:39:55.199Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21135</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21135|2024-07-16T22:39:55.199Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21137|2024-07-16T22:39:55.864Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21137</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21137|2024-07-16T22:39:55.864Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21176|2024-07-16T22:40:09.035Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21176</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Thread Pooling).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.4.0 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21176|2024-07-16T22:40:09.035Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21163|2024-07-16T22:40:04.314Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21163</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server as well as  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of MySQL Server accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.5 (Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21163|2024-07-16T22:40:04.314Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21129|2024-07-16T22:39:53.186Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21129</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DDL).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21129|2024-07-16T22:39:53.186Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21130|2024-07-16T22:39:53.514Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21130</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21130|2024-07-16T22:39:53.514Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21162|2024-07-16T22:40:03.984Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21162</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21162|2024-07-16T22:40:03.984Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21173|2024-07-16T22:40:07.976Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21173</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21173|2024-07-16T22:40:07.976Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21179|2024-07-16T22:40:10.021Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21179</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21179|2024-07-16T22:40:10.021Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21127|2024-07-16T22:39:52.506Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21127</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DDL).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21127|2024-07-16T22:39:52.506Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21134|2024-07-16T22:39:54.868Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21134</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Connection Handling).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.3 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21134|2024-07-16T22:39:54.868Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21165|2024-07-16T22:40:04.994Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21165</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Pluggable Auth).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21165|2024-07-16T22:40:04.994Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21157|2024-07-16T22:40:02.278Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21157</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21157|2024-07-16T22:40:02.278Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21166|2024-07-17T14:08:36.127Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21166</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all MySQL Server accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.9 (Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21166|2024-07-17T14:08:36.127Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21137|2024-07-17T14:29:36.469Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21137</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21137|2024-07-17T14:29:36.469Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21176|2024-07-17T14:24:19.739Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21176</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Thread Pooling).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.4.0 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21176|2024-07-17T14:24:19.739Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21134|2024-07-17T14:41:15.404Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21134</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Connection Handling).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.3 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21134|2024-07-17T14:41:15.404Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21165|2024-07-17T14:22:53.443Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21165</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Pluggable Auth).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21165|2024-07-17T14:22:53.443Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21171|2024-07-18T15:08:09.215Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21171</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21171|2024-07-18T15:08:09.215Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20996|2024-07-18T15:11:07.185Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20996</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20996|2024-07-18T15:11:07.185Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21173|2024-07-23T15:36:48.895Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21173</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: InnoDB).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.37 and prior and  8.4.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21173|2024-07-23T15:36:48.895Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21052|2024-07-26T15:13:50.618Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21052</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: DML).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.34 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21052|2024-07-26T15:13:50.618Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
