<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- MySQL NDB Cluster</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/mysql%20ndb%20cluster.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- MySQL NDB Cluster</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20965|2024-01-16T21:41:22.582Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20ndb%20cluster
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20965</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Optimizer).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.35 and prior and  8.2.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20965|2024-01-16T21:41:22.582Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21101|2024-04-16T21:26:32.608Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20ndb%20cluster
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21101</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Cluster product of Oracle MySQL (component: Cluster: General).  Supported versions that are affected are 7.5.33 and prior, 7.6.29 and prior, 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Cluster.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of MySQL Cluster accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 2.2 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21101|2024-04-16T21:26:32.608Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21102|2024-06-04T17:37:36.436Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20ndb%20cluster
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21102</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Server product of Oracle MySQL (component: Server: Thread Pooling).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.0.36 and prior and  8.3.0 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise MySQL Server.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Server. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21102|2024-06-04T17:37:36.436Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
