<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- MySQL Installer</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/mysql%20installer.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- MySQL Installer</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 21:22:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22094|2024-09-13T15:58:50.428Z -- oracle%20corporation -- mysql%20installer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22094</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the MySQL Installer product of Oracle MySQL (component: Installer: General).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 1.6.8. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where MySQL Installer executes to compromise MySQL Installer.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in MySQL Installer, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all MySQL Installer accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of MySQL Installer. Note: This patch is used in MySQL Server bundled version 8.0.35 and 5.7.44. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.9 (Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:N/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22094|2024-09-13T15:58:50.428Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 21:03:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
