<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- Oracle VM VirtualBox</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/oracle%20vm%20virtualbox.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- Oracle VM VirtualBox</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 23:22:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3559|2024-10-07T16:11:26.350Z -- oracle%20corporation -- oracle%20vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3559</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.0.38 and Prior to 5.1.20. Easily "exploitable" vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox as well as unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data and unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.9 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3559|2024-10-07T16:11:26.350Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3575|2024-10-07T16:10:37.055Z -- oracle%20corporation -- oracle%20vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3575</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.0.38 and Prior to 5.1.20. Easily "exploitable" vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.9 (Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3575|2024-10-07T16:10:37.055Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3587|2024-10-07T16:10:12.246Z -- oracle%20corporation -- oracle%20vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3587</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Shared Folder). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.0.38 and Prior to 5.1.20. Easily "exploitable" vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.4 (Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3587|2024-10-07T16:10:12.246Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3558|2024-10-07T16:11:32.939Z -- oracle%20corporation -- oracle%20vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3558</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.0.38 and Prior to 5.1.20. Easily "exploitable" vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox as well as unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data and unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.5 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3558|2024-10-07T16:11:32.939Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3513|2024-10-07T16:13:53.608Z -- oracle%20corporation -- oracle%20vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3513</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.0.38 and Prior to 5.1.20. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 2.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3513|2024-10-07T16:13:53.608Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
