<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- Oracle Database</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/oracle%20database.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- Oracle Database</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 10:23:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3259|2024-08-05T04:43:35.172Z -- oracle%20corporation -- oracle%20database
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3259</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java VM component of Oracle Database Server. Supported versions that are affected are 11.2.0.4, 12.1.0.2, 12.2.0.1 and 18c. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java VM. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Java VM. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 9.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3259|2024-08-05T04:43:35.172Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2875|2024-08-05T04:36:38.438Z -- oracle%20corporation -- oracle%20database
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2875</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Core RDBMS component of Oracle Database Server. Supported versions that are affected are 12.2.0.1, 18c and 19c. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker having Create Session privilege with network access via OracleNet to compromise Core RDBMS. While the vulnerability is in Core RDBMS, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Core RDBMS accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.0 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2875|2024-08-05T04:36:38.438Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 17:40:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3004|2024-08-05T04:36:39.491Z -- oracle%20corporation -- oracle%20database
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3004</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java VM component of Oracle Database Server. Supported versions that are affected are 11.2.0.4, 12.1.0.2,12.2.0.1 and 18.2. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker having Create Session, Create Procedure privilege with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java VM. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Java VM accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3004|2024-08-05T04:36:39.491Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2939|2024-08-05T04:36:38.970Z -- oracle%20corporation -- oracle%20database
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2939</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Core RDBMS component of Oracle Database Server. Supported versions that are affected are 11.2.0.4, 12.1.0.2, 12.2.0.1, 18.1 and 18.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker having Local Logon privilege with logon to the infrastructure where Core RDBMS executes to compromise Core RDBMS. While the vulnerability is in Core RDBMS, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Core RDBMS accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Core RDBMS. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.4 (Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2939|2024-08-05T04:36:38.970Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2841|2024-08-05T04:29:45.172Z -- oracle%20corporation -- oracle%20database
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2841</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java VM component of Oracle Database Server. Supported versions that are affected are 11.2.0.4, 12.1.0.2 and 12.2.0.1. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker having Create Session, Create Procedure privilege with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java VM. While the vulnerability is in Java VM, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Java VM. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.5 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2841|2024-08-05T04:29:45.172Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2680|2024-08-05T04:29:43.029Z -- oracle%20corporation -- oracle%20database
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2680</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java VM component of Oracle Database Server. Supported versions that are affected are 11.2.0.4, 12.1.0.2 and 12.2.0.1. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Java VM. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Java VM, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Java VM. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2680|2024-08-05T04:29:43.029Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3110|2024-08-05T04:43:34.542Z -- oracle%20corporation -- oracle%20database
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3110</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was discovered in the Java VM component of Oracle Database Server. Supported versions that are affected are 11.2.0.4, 12.1.0.2, 12.2.0.1 and 18. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker having Create Session privilege with network access via Oracle Net to compromise Java VM. While the vulnerability is in Java VM, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Java VM. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 9.9 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3110|2024-08-05T04:43:34.542Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2575|2024-08-05T04:21:34.583Z -- oracle%20corporation -- oracle%20database
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2575</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Core RDBMS component of Oracle Database Server. Supported versions that are affected are 11.2.0.4, 12.1.0.2, and 12.2.0.1. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker having Local Logon privilege with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Core RDBMS. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Core RDBMS accessible data. Note: Applicable only to Windows platform. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 2.0 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2575|2024-08-05T04:21:34.583Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
