<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- Oracle Database</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/oracle%20database.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- Oracle Database</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 22:23:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10190|2024-10-04T16:57:48.840Z -- oracle%20corporation -- oracle%20database
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10190</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Java VM component of Oracle Database Server. Supported versions that are affected are 11.2.0.4, 12.1.0.2 and 12.2.0.1. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker having Create Session, Create Procedure privilege with logon to the infrastructure where Java VM executes to compromise Java VM. While the vulnerability is in Java VM, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Java VM. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.2 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10190|2024-10-04T16:57:48.840Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10282|2024-10-04T16:38:43.793Z -- oracle%20corporation -- oracle%20database
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10282</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Core RDBMS component of Oracle Database Server. Supported versions that are affected are 12.1.0.2 and 12.2.0.1. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker having Create Session, Execute Catalog Role privilege with network access via Oracle Net to compromise Core RDBMS. While the vulnerability is in Core RDBMS, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Core RDBMS. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 9.1 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10282|2024-10-04T16:38:43.793Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10261|2024-10-04T16:57:03.674Z -- oracle%20corporation -- oracle%20database
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10261</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the XML Database component of Oracle Database Server. Supported versions that are affected are 11.2.0.4 and 12.1.0.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker having Create Session privilege with logon to the infrastructure where XML Database executes to compromise XML Database. While the vulnerability is in XML Database, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all XML Database accessible data. Note: This score is for Windows platform version 11.2.0.4 of Database. For Windows platform version 12.1.0.2 and Linux, the score is 5.5 with scope Unchanged. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10261|2024-10-04T16:57:03.674Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10202|2024-10-04T17:09:47.593Z -- oracle%20corporation -- oracle%20database
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10202</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the OJVM component of Oracle Database Server. Supported versions that are affected are 11.2.0.4, 12.1.0.2 and 12.2.0.1. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker having Create Session, Create Procedure privilege with network access via multiple protocols to compromise OJVM. While the vulnerability is in OJVM, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of OJVM. Note: This score is for Windows platforms. On non-Windows platforms Scope is Unchanged, giving a CVSS Base Score of 8.8. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 9.9 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10202|2024-10-04T17:09:47.593Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10120|2024-10-04T19:01:54.110Z -- oracle%20corporation -- oracle%20database
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10120</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the RDBMS Security component of Oracle Database Server. The supported version that is affected is 12.1.0.2. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker having Create Session, Select Any Dictionary privilege with logon to the infrastructure where RDBMS Security executes to compromise RDBMS Security. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of RDBMS Security accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 1.9 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10120|2024-10-04T19:01:54.110Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10292|2024-10-04T16:54:55.476Z -- oracle%20corporation -- oracle%20database
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10292</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the RDBMS Security component of Oracle Database Server. Supported versions that are affected are 11.2.0.4, 12.1.0.2 and 12.2.0.1. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker having Create User privilege with logon to the infrastructure where RDBMS Security executes to compromise RDBMS Security. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of RDBMS Security accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 2.3 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10292|2024-10-04T16:54:55.476Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10321|2024-10-04T16:52:21.172Z -- oracle%20corporation -- oracle%20database
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10321</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Core RDBMS component of Oracle Database Server. Supported versions that are affected are 11.2.0.4, 12.1.0.2 and 12.2.0.1. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker having Create session privilege with logon to the infrastructure where Core RDBMS executes to compromise Core RDBMS. While the vulnerability is in Core RDBMS, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Core RDBMS. Note: This score is for Windows platform version 11.2.0.4 of Database. For Windows platform version 12.1.0.2 and Linux, the score is 7.8 with scope Unchanged. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10321|2024-10-04T16:52:21.172Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
