<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- Outside In Technology</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/outside%20in%20technology.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- Outside In Technology</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 21:21:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2540|2024-08-04T07:09:54.192Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2540</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Filters). The supported version that is affected is 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2540|2024-08-04T07:09:54.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:33:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2792|2024-08-04T19:03:42.703Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2792</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). The supported version that is affected is 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2792|2024-08-04T19:03:42.703Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 22:31:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35574|2024-08-04T00:40:47.346Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35574</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Filters). The supported version that is affected is 8.5.5. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS Base Score depend on the software that uses Outside In Technology. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35574|2024-08-04T00:40:47.346Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2458|2024-08-04T18:49:47.910Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2458</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.3 and 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.3 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2458|2024-08-04T18:49:47.910Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2972|2024-08-04T19:03:43.622Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2972</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Filters). The supported version that is affected is 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2972|2024-08-04T19:03:43.622Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 17:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2608|2024-08-04T18:56:45.360Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2608</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.3 and 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2608|2024-08-04T18:56:45.360Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 18:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35661|2024-08-04T00:40:47.343Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35661</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Filters). The supported version that is affected is 8.5.5. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS Base Score depend on the software that uses Outside In Technology. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35661|2024-08-04T00:40:47.343Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2784|2024-08-04T07:17:02.662Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2784</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Filters). The supported version that is affected is 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2784|2024-08-04T07:17:02.662Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2542|2024-08-04T07:09:54.470Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2542</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Filters). The supported version that is affected is 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2542|2024-08-04T07:09:54.470Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2613|2024-08-04T18:56:45.249Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2613</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.3 and 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2613|2024-08-04T18:56:45.249Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 18:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2476|2024-08-04T18:49:47.954Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2476</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.3 and 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2476|2024-08-04T18:49:47.954Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2576|2024-08-04T07:09:54.631Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2576</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Filters). The supported version that is affected is 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2576|2024-08-04T07:09:54.631Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2756|2024-08-04T18:56:45.661Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2756</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). The supported version that is affected is 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2756|2024-08-04T18:56:45.661Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 22:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35657|2024-08-04T00:40:47.365Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35657</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Filters). The supported version that is affected is 8.5.5. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS Base Score depend on the software that uses Outside In Technology. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35657|2024-08-04T00:40:47.365Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2459|2024-08-04T18:49:47.906Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2459</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.3 and 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.3 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2459|2024-08-04T18:49:47.906Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2705|2024-08-04T18:56:45.651Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2705</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.3 and 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology as well as unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.2 (Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2705|2024-08-04T18:56:45.651Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 18:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2469|2024-08-04T18:49:48.044Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2469</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.3 and 8.5.4. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology and unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2469|2024-08-04T18:49:48.044Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35662|2024-08-04T00:40:47.378Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35662</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Filters). The supported version that is affected is 8.5.5. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS Base Score depend on the software that uses Outside In Technology. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35662|2024-08-04T00:40:47.378Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35658|2024-08-04T00:40:47.533Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35658</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Filters). The supported version that is affected is 8.5.5. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS Base Score depend on the software that uses Outside In Technology. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35658|2024-08-04T00:40:47.533Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2536|2024-08-04T07:09:54.637Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2536</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Filters). The supported version that is affected is 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2536|2024-08-04T07:09:54.637Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:33:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2610|2024-08-04T18:56:44.497Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2610</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.3 and 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2610|2024-08-04T18:56:44.497Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 18:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2783|2024-08-04T07:17:02.857Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2783</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Filters). Supported versions that is affected is 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.3 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2783|2024-08-04T07:17:02.857Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2609|2024-08-04T18:56:44.805Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2609</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.3 and 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2609|2024-08-04T18:56:44.805Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 18:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2764|2024-08-04T19:03:41.887Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2764</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). The supported version that is affected is 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2764|2024-08-04T19:03:41.887Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 22:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2970|2024-08-04T19:03:43.471Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2970</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Filters). The supported version that is affected is 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2970|2024-08-04T19:03:43.471Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 17:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2855|2024-08-04T19:03:43.169Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2855</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). The supported version that is affected is 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2855|2024-08-04T19:03:43.169Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 22:31:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2786|2024-08-04T07:17:02.725Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2786</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Filters). Supported versions that is affected is 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2786|2024-08-04T07:17:02.725Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2474|2024-08-04T18:49:47.991Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2474</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.3 and 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2474|2024-08-04T18:49:47.991Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2541|2024-08-04T07:09:54.477Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2541</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Filters). The supported version that is affected is 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2541|2024-08-04T07:09:54.477Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2854|2024-08-04T19:03:43.164Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2854</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). The supported version that is affected is 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2854|2024-08-04T19:03:43.164Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 22:31:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2463|2024-08-04T18:49:47.908Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2463</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.3 and 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2463|2024-08-04T18:49:47.908Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2465|2024-08-04T18:49:48.019Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2465</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.3 and 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2465|2024-08-04T18:49:48.019Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2903|2024-08-04T19:03:43.413Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2903</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Filters). The supported version that is affected is 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2903|2024-08-04T19:03:43.413Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 17:40:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2429|2024-08-04T18:49:48.008Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2429</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.3 and 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology and unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.1 (Confidentiality and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2429|2024-08-04T18:49:48.008Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2477|2024-08-04T18:49:47.900Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2477</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.3 and 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2477|2024-08-04T18:49:47.900Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2479|2024-08-04T18:49:47.956Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2479</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.3 and 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2479|2024-08-04T18:49:47.956Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2971|2024-08-04T19:03:43.539Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2971</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Filters). The supported version that is affected is 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2971|2024-08-04T19:03:43.539Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 17:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2460|2024-08-04T18:49:47.935Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2460</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). The supported version that is affected is 8.5.3. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.3 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2460|2024-08-04T18:49:47.935Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2902|2024-08-04T19:03:43.506Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2902</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Filters). The supported version that is affected is 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2902|2024-08-04T19:03:43.506Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 17:40:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35572|2024-08-04T00:40:46.882Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35572</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Filters). The supported version that is affected is 8.5.5. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS Base Score depend on the software that uses Outside In Technology. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35572|2024-08-04T00:40:46.882Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2480|2024-08-04T18:49:47.878Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2480</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.3 and 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.3 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2480|2024-08-04T18:49:47.878Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35659|2024-08-04T00:40:47.533Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35659</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Filters). The supported version that is affected is 8.5.5. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS Base Score depend on the software that uses Outside In Technology. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35659|2024-08-04T00:40:47.533Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2901|2024-08-04T19:03:43.464Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2901</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Filters). The supported version that is affected is 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2901|2024-08-04T19:03:43.464Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 17:40:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2478|2024-08-04T18:49:48.008Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2478</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.3 and 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.3 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2478|2024-08-04T18:49:48.008Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2467|2024-08-04T18:49:47.859Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2467</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.3 and 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2467|2024-08-04T18:49:47.859Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2457|2024-08-04T18:49:47.898Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2457</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.3 and 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.3 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2457|2024-08-04T18:49:47.898Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2787|2024-08-04T07:17:02.624Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2787</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Filters). Supported versions that is affected is 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2787|2024-08-04T07:17:02.624Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2759|2024-08-04T18:56:45.585Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2759</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). The supported version that is affected is 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2759|2024-08-04T18:56:45.585Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 22:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2468|2024-08-04T18:49:47.952Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2468</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.3 and 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2468|2024-08-04T18:49:47.952Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2466|2024-08-04T18:49:47.945Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2466</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.3 and 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2466|2024-08-04T18:49:47.945Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35656|2024-08-04T00:40:47.453Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35656</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Filters). The supported version that is affected is 8.5.5. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS Base Score depend on the software that uses Outside In Technology. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35656|2024-08-04T00:40:47.453Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2473|2024-08-04T18:49:48.153Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2473</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.3 and 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2473|2024-08-04T18:49:48.153Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2456|2024-08-04T18:49:47.900Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2456</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.3 and 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2456|2024-08-04T18:49:47.900Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35573|2024-08-04T00:40:47.259Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35573</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Filters). The supported version that is affected is 8.5.5. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS Base Score depend on the software that uses Outside In Technology. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35573|2024-08-04T00:40:47.259Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:50:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2785|2024-08-04T07:17:02.712Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2785</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Filters). Supported versions that is affected is 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2785|2024-08-04T07:17:02.712Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2461|2024-08-04T18:49:47.894Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2461</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.3 and 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.3 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2461|2024-08-04T18:49:47.894Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2475|2024-08-04T18:49:47.872Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2475</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.3 and 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2475|2024-08-04T18:49:47.872Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2835|2024-08-04T19:03:42.911Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2835</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). The supported version that is affected is 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2835|2024-08-04T19:03:42.911Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 22:31:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35660|2024-08-04T00:40:47.427Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35660</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Filters). The supported version that is affected is 8.5.5. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS Base Score depend on the software that uses Outside In Technology. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35660|2024-08-04T00:40:47.427Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:51:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2612|2024-08-04T18:56:45.394Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2612</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.3 and 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2612|2024-08-04T18:56:45.394Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 18:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2611|2024-08-04T18:56:45.648Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2611</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.3 and 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2611|2024-08-04T18:56:45.648Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 18:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2852|2024-08-04T19:03:43.138Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2852</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). The supported version that is affected is 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2852|2024-08-04T19:03:43.138Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 22:31:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2462|2024-08-04T18:49:48.114Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2462</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.3 and 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. While the vulnerability is in Oracle Outside In Technology, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.2 (Confidentiality and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2462|2024-08-04T18:49:48.114Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2543|2024-08-04T07:09:54.442Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2543</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Filters). The supported version that is affected is 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2543|2024-08-04T07:09:54.442Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2464|2024-08-04T18:49:48.073Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2464</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.3 and 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2464|2024-08-04T18:49:48.073Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2472|2024-08-04T18:49:47.883Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2472</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology component of Oracle Fusion Middleware (subcomponent: Outside In Filters). Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.3 and 8.5.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. Note: Outside In Technology is a suite of software development kits (SDKs). The protocol and CVSS score depend on the software that uses the Outside In Technology code. The CVSS score assumes that the software passes data received over a network directly to Outside In Technology code, but if data is not received over a network the CVSS score may be lower. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.3 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2472|2024-08-04T18:49:47.883Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21119|2024-08-01T22:13:42.689Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21119</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Core).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.6 and  8.5.7. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Outside In Technology executes to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21119|2024-08-01T22:13:42.689Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21117|2024-08-01T22:13:42.670Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21117</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Core).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.6 and  8.5.7. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Outside In Technology executes to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21117|2024-08-01T22:13:42.670Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21118|2024-08-01T22:13:42.658Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21118</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Core).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.6 and  8.5.7. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Outside In Technology executes to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21118|2024-08-01T22:13:42.658Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21120|2024-08-01T22:13:42.660Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21120</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Core).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.6 and  8.5.7. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Outside In Technology executes to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21120|2024-08-01T22:13:42.660Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21120|2024-07-05T13:06:48.074Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21120</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Core).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.6 and  8.5.7. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Outside In Technology executes to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21120|2024-07-05T13:06:48.074Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21119|2024-04-16T21:26:38.497Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21119</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Core).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.6 and  8.5.7. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Outside In Technology executes to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21119|2024-04-16T21:26:38.497Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21118|2024-04-16T21:26:38.176Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21118</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Core).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.6 and  8.5.7. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Outside In Technology executes to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21118|2024-04-16T21:26:38.176Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21117|2024-04-16T21:26:37.832Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21117</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Core).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.6 and  8.5.7. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Outside In Technology executes to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21117|2024-04-16T21:26:37.832Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21120|2024-04-16T21:26:38.818Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21120</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Core).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.6 and  8.5.7. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Outside In Technology executes to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21120|2024-04-16T21:26:38.818Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21117|2024-07-26T15:11:43.167Z -- oracle%20corporation -- outside%20in%20technology</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21117</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Outside In Technology product of Oracle Fusion Middleware (component: Outside In Core).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.5.6 and  8.5.7. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Outside In Technology executes to compromise Oracle Outside In Technology.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Outside In Technology accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Outside In Technology. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21117|2024-07-26T15:11:43.167Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
