<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- PeopleSoft Enterprise ELM Enterprise Learning Management</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/peoplesoft%20enterprise%20elm%20enterprise%20learning%20management.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- PeopleSoft Enterprise ELM Enterprise Learning Management</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 18:25:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2700|2024-10-02T15:39:12.104Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20elm%20enterprise%20learning%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2700</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise ELM component of Oracle PeopleSoft Products (subcomponent: Enterprise Learning Mgmt). The supported version that is affected is 9.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise ELM. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of PeopleSoft Enterprise ELM accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.3 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2700|2024-10-02T15:39:12.104Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 18:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2707|2024-10-02T15:38:48.779Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20elm%20enterprise%20learning%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2707</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise ELM Enterprise Learning Management component of Oracle PeopleSoft Products (subcomponent: Application Search). The supported version that is affected is 9.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise ELM Enterprise Learning Management. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in PeopleSoft Enterprise ELM Enterprise Learning Management, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of PeopleSoft Enterprise ELM Enterprise Learning Management accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of PeopleSoft Enterprise ELM Enterprise Learning Management accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2707|2024-10-02T15:38:48.779Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 18:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
