<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- PeopleSoft Enterprise PT PeopleTools</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- PeopleSoft Enterprise PT PeopleTools</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 23:23:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2695|2024-10-03T20:31:47.180Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2695</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools component of Oracle PeopleSoft Products (subcomponent: Query). Supported versions that are affected are 8.54, 8.55 and 8.56. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2695|2024-10-03T20:31:47.180Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2785|2024-10-03T20:19:08.818Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2785</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools component of Oracle PeopleSoft Products (subcomponent: Stylesheet). Supported versions that are affected are 8.54, 8.55 and 8.56. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.7 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2785|2024-10-03T20:19:08.818Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2772|2024-10-03T20:20:35.862Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2772</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools component of Oracle PeopleSoft Products (subcomponent: Rich Text Editor). Supported versions that are affected are 8.54, 8.55 and 8.56. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2772|2024-10-03T20:20:35.862Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2651|2024-10-03T20:37:07.172Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2651</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools component of Oracle PeopleSoft Products (subcomponent: XML Publisher). Supported versions that are affected are 8.54, 8.55 and 8.56. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2651|2024-10-03T20:37:07.172Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2774|2024-10-03T20:20:22.538Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2774</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise PT PeopleTools component of Oracle PeopleSoft Products (subcomponent: SQR). Supported versions that are affected are 8.54, 8.55 and 8.56. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise PT PeopleTools. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of PeopleSoft Enterprise PT PeopleTools accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of PeopleSoft Enterprise PT PeopleTools accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of PeopleSoft Enterprise PT PeopleTools. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2774|2024-10-03T20:20:22.538Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2653|2024-10-03T20:36:53.473Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2653</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools component of Oracle PeopleSoft Products (subcomponent: Connected Query). Supported versions that are affected are 8.54, 8.55 and 8.56. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2653|2024-10-03T20:36:53.473Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2652|2024-10-03T20:37:00.227Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2652</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools component of Oracle PeopleSoft Products (subcomponent: Integration Broker). Supported versions that are affected are 8.54, 8.55 and 8.56. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2652|2024-10-03T20:37:00.227Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2752|2024-10-03T20:22:34.525Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2752</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise HCM component of Oracle PeopleSoft Products (subcomponent: Security). The supported version that is affected is 9.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise HCM. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in PeopleSoft Enterprise HCM, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of PeopleSoft Enterprise HCM accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of PeopleSoft Enterprise HCM accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2752|2024-10-03T20:22:34.525Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2820|2024-10-03T20:15:55.565Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2820</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools component of Oracle PeopleSoft Products (subcomponent: Fluid Core). Supported versions that are affected are 8.54, 8.55 and 8.56. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.3 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2820|2024-10-03T20:15:55.565Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2821|2024-10-03T20:15:50.131Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2821</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools component of Oracle PeopleSoft Products (subcomponent: Rich Text Editor). Supported versions that are affected are 8.54, 8.55 and 8.56. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2821|2024-10-03T20:15:50.131Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2793|2024-10-03T20:18:25.870Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2793</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise PT PeopleTools component of Oracle PeopleSoft Products (subcomponent: PsAdmin). Supported versions that are affected are 8.54, 8.55 and 8.56. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with logon to the infrastructure where PeopleSoft Enterprise PT PeopleTools executes to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise PT PeopleTools. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all PeopleSoft Enterprise PT PeopleTools accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.2 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2793|2024-10-03T20:18:25.870Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2788|2024-10-03T20:18:51.262Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2788</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools component of Oracle PeopleSoft Products (subcomponent: Fluid Core). Supported versions that are affected are 8.55 and 8.56. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2788|2024-10-03T20:18:51.262Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2593|2024-10-03T20:43:35.956Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2593</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools component of Oracle PeopleSoft Products (subcomponent: PIA Core Technology). Supported versions that are affected are 8.54, 8.55 and 8.56. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2593|2024-10-03T20:43:35.956Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2605|2024-10-03T20:42:18.803Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2605</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools component of Oracle PeopleSoft Products (subcomponent: Integration Broker). Supported versions that are affected are 8.54, 8.55 and 8.56. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2605|2024-10-03T20:42:18.803Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2809|2024-10-03T20:16:51.230Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2809</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools component of Oracle PeopleSoft Products (subcomponent: Fluid Homepage &amp; Navigation). Supported versions that are affected are 8.54, 8.55 and 8.56. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.3 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2809|2024-10-03T20:16:51.230Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21158|2024-08-01T22:13:42.656Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21158</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools product of Oracle PeopleSoft (component: Portal).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.59, 8.60 and  8.61. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools.  While the vulnerability is in PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21158|2024-08-01T22:13:42.656Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21070|2024-08-01T22:13:42.215Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21070</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools product of Oracle PeopleSoft (component: Search Framework).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.59, 8.60 and  8.61. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21070|2024-08-01T22:13:42.215Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21065|2024-08-01T22:13:42.395Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21065</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools product of Oracle PeopleSoft (component: Workflow).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.59, 8.60 and  8.61. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21065|2024-08-01T22:13:42.395Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21097|2024-08-01T22:13:42.625Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21097</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools product of Oracle PeopleSoft (component: Security).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.59, 8.60 and  8.61. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21097|2024-08-01T22:13:42.625Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21180|2024-08-01T22:13:42.709Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21180</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools product of Oracle PeopleSoft (component: OpenSearch Dashboards).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.59, 8.60 and  8.61. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.1 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21180|2024-08-01T22:13:42.709Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21178|2024-08-01T22:13:42.823Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21178</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools product of Oracle PeopleSoft (component: Portal).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.59, 8.60 and  8.61. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21178|2024-08-01T22:13:42.823Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21158|2024-07-17T20:02:06.399Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21158</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools product of Oracle PeopleSoft (component: Portal).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.59, 8.60 and  8.61. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools.  While the vulnerability is in PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21158|2024-07-17T20:02:06.399Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21180|2024-07-17T13:30:38.757Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21180</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools product of Oracle PeopleSoft (component: OpenSearch Dashboards).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.59, 8.60 and  8.61. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.1 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21180|2024-07-17T13:30:38.757Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21097|2024-07-15T19:10:55.688Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21097</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools product of Oracle PeopleSoft (component: Security).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.59, 8.60 and  8.61. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21097|2024-07-15T19:10:55.688Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21065|2024-04-16T21:26:20.238Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21065</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools product of Oracle PeopleSoft (component: Workflow).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.59, 8.60 and  8.61. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21065|2024-04-16T21:26:20.238Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21097|2024-04-16T21:26:31.307Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21097</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools product of Oracle PeopleSoft (component: Security).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.59, 8.60 and  8.61. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.9 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21097|2024-04-16T21:26:31.307Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21070|2024-04-16T21:26:22.131Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21070</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools product of Oracle PeopleSoft (component: Search Framework).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.59, 8.60 and  8.61. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21070|2024-04-16T21:26:22.131Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21070|2024-07-15T18:53:59.272Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21070</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools product of Oracle PeopleSoft (component: Search Framework).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.59, 8.60 and  8.61. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21070|2024-07-15T18:53:59.272Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21180|2024-07-16T22:40:10.386Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21180</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools product of Oracle PeopleSoft (component: OpenSearch Dashboards).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.59, 8.60 and  8.61. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.1 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21180|2024-07-16T22:40:10.386Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21158|2024-07-16T22:40:02.588Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21158</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools product of Oracle PeopleSoft (component: Portal).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.59, 8.60 and  8.61. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools.  While the vulnerability is in PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21158|2024-07-16T22:40:02.588Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21178|2024-07-16T22:40:09.661Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21178</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools product of Oracle PeopleSoft (component: Portal).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.59, 8.60 and  8.61. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21178|2024-07-16T22:40:09.661Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21178|2024-07-17T19:55:44.254Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21178</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools product of Oracle PeopleSoft (component: Portal).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.59, 8.60 and  8.61. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21178|2024-07-17T19:55:44.254Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21065|2024-07-26T15:12:56.964Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20pt%20peopletools</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21065</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools product of Oracle PeopleSoft (component: Workflow).  Supported versions that are affected are 8.59, 8.60 and  8.61. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of PeopleSoft Enterprise PeopleTools accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21065|2024-07-26T15:12:56.964Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
