<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- PeopleSoft Enterprise HCM Talent Acquisition Manager</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/peoplesoft%20enterprise%20hcm%20talent%20acquisition%20manager.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- PeopleSoft Enterprise HCM Talent Acquisition Manager</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 19:19:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2590|2024-08-04T18:56:44.835Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20hcm%20talent%20acquisition%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2590</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise HCM Talent Acquisition Manager component of Oracle PeopleSoft Products (subcomponent: Job Opening). The supported version that is affected is 9.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise HCM Talent Acquisition Manager. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in PeopleSoft Enterprise HCM Talent Acquisition Manager, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all PeopleSoft Enterprise HCM Talent Acquisition Manager accessible data as well as unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of PeopleSoft Enterprise HCM Talent Acquisition Manager accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.2 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:H/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2590|2024-08-04T18:56:44.835Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 18:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
