<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- PeopleSoft Enterprise SCM Purchasing</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/peoplesoft%20enterprise%20scm%20purchasing.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- PeopleSoft Enterprise SCM Purchasing</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 21:22:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2906|2024-08-04T07:23:59.356Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20scm%20purchasing
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2906</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise SCM Purchasing product of Oracle PeopleSoft (component: Supplier Change). The supported version that is affected is 9.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise SCM Purchasing. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all PeopleSoft Enterprise SCM Purchasing accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2906|2024-08-04T07:23:59.356Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2899|2024-08-04T07:23:59.313Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20scm%20purchasing
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2899</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise SCM Purchasing product of Oracle PeopleSoft (component: Purchasing). The supported version that is affected is 9.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise SCM Purchasing. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in PeopleSoft Enterprise SCM Purchasing, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of PeopleSoft Enterprise SCM Purchasing accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of PeopleSoft Enterprise SCM Purchasing accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.8 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2899|2024-08-04T07:23:59.313Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35541|2024-08-04T00:40:47.328Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20scm%20purchasing
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35541</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise SCM product of Oracle PeopleSoft (component: Supplier Portal). The supported version that is affected is 9.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise SCM. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in PeopleSoft Enterprise SCM, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of PeopleSoft Enterprise SCM accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of PeopleSoft Enterprise SCM accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35541|2024-08-04T00:40:47.328Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:49:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
