<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- PeopleSoft Enterprise HCM Shared Components</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/peoplesoft%20enterprise%20hcm%20shared%20components.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- PeopleSoft Enterprise HCM Shared Components</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 23:23:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21122|2024-07-16T22:39:43.118Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20hcm%20shared%20components
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21122</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise HCM Shared Components product of Oracle PeopleSoft (component: Text Catalog).   The supported version that is affected is 9.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise HCM Shared Components.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in PeopleSoft Enterprise HCM Shared Components, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of PeopleSoft Enterprise HCM Shared Components accessible data as well as  unauthorized read access to a subset of PeopleSoft Enterprise HCM Shared Components accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21122|2024-07-16T22:39:43.118Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
