<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- PeopleSoft Enterprise PRTL Interaction Hub</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/peoplesoft%20enterprise%20prtl%20interaction%20hub.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- PeopleSoft Enterprise PRTL Interaction Hub</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 10:23:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21450|2024-08-03T02:38:56.388Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20prtl%20interaction%20hub
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21450</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise PRTL Interaction Hub product of Oracle PeopleSoft (component: My Links). The supported version that is affected is 9.1. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise PRTL Interaction Hub. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in PeopleSoft Enterprise PRTL Interaction Hub, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of PeopleSoft Enterprise PRTL Interaction Hub accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of PeopleSoft Enterprise PRTL Interaction Hub accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21450|2024-08-03T02:38:56.388Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 20:37:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
