<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- PeopleSoft Enterprise CC Common Application Objects</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/peoplesoft%20enterprise%20cc%20common%20application%20objects.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- PeopleSoft Enterprise CC Common Application Objects</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 20:23:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2419|2024-08-04T18:49:48.073Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20cc%20common%20application%20objects
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2419</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise CC Common Application Objects component of Oracle PeopleSoft Products (subcomponent: Form and Approval Builder). The supported version that is affected is 9.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise CC Common Application Objects. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in PeopleSoft Enterprise CC Common Application Objects, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of PeopleSoft Enterprise CC Common Application Objects accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of PeopleSoft Enterprise CC Common Application Objects accessible data. Note: This Enterprise Common Component is used by all PeopleSoft Application products. Please refer to the &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://support.oracle.com/rs?type=doc&amp;id=2487756.1"&gt;MOS Note Doc ID 2493366.1 for patch information. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2419|2024-08-04T18:49:48.073Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35543|2024-08-04T00:40:47.172Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20cc%20common%20application%20objects
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35543</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise CC Common Application Objects product of Oracle PeopleSoft (component: Activity Guide Composer). The supported version that is affected is 9.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise CC Common Application Objects. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all PeopleSoft Enterprise CC Common Application Objects accessible data as well as unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all PeopleSoft Enterprise CC Common Application Objects accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35543|2024-08-04T00:40:47.172Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:49:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2695|2024-08-04T07:17:01.895Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20cc%20common%20application%20objects
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2695</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise CC Common Application Objects product of Oracle PeopleSoft (component: Approval Framework). Supported versions that are affected are 9.1 and 9.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise CC Common Application Objects. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of PeopleSoft Enterprise CC Common Application Objects accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2695|2024-08-04T07:17:01.895Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
