<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- PeopleSoft Enterprise SCM Strategic Sourcing</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/peoplesoft%20enterprise%20scm%20strategic%20sourcing.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- PeopleSoft Enterprise SCM Strategic Sourcing</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 21:24:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3524|2024-08-05T14:30:57.816Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20scm%20strategic%20sourcing
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3524</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise SCM Strategic Sourcing component of Oracle PeopleSoft Products (subcomponent: Bidder Registration). The supported version that is affected is 9.2. Easily "exploitable" vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise SCM Strategic Sourcing. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all PeopleSoft Enterprise SCM Strategic Sourcing accessible data as well as unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all PeopleSoft Enterprise SCM Strategic Sourcing accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3524|2024-08-05T14:30:57.816Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2702|2024-08-05T04:29:43.940Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20scm%20strategic%20sourcing
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2702</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise FSCM component of Oracle PeopleSoft Products (subcomponent: Strategic Sourcing). The supported version that is affected is 9.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise FSCM. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all PeopleSoft Enterprise FSCM accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2702|2024-08-05T04:29:43.940Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10018|2024-08-05T17:25:00.636Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20scm%20strategic%20sourcing
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10018</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise FSCM component of Oracle PeopleSoft Products (subcomponent: Strategic Sourcing). The supported version that is affected is 9.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise FSCM. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of PeopleSoft Enterprise FSCM accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.3 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10018|2024-08-05T17:25:00.636Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-10287|2024-08-05T17:33:17.035Z -- oracle%20corporation -- peoplesoft%20enterprise%20scm%20strategic%20sourcing
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-10287</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the PeopleSoft Enterprise FSCM component of Oracle PeopleSoft Products (subcomponent: Strategic Sourcing). The supported version that is affected is 9.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise PeopleSoft Enterprise FSCM. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of PeopleSoft Enterprise FSCM accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.3 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-10287|2024-08-05T17:33:17.035Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
