<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- Primavera Portfolio Management</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/primavera%20portfolio%20management.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- Primavera Portfolio Management</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 21:21:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21243|2024-08-03T02:31:59.884Z -- oracle%20corporation -- primavera%20portfolio%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21243</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Primavera Portfolio Management product of Oracle Construction and Engineering (component: Web Access). Supported versions that are affected are 18.0.0.0-18.0.3.0, 19.0.0.0-19.0.1.2, 20.0.0.0 and 20.0.0.1. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Primavera Portfolio Management. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Primavera Portfolio Management. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.3 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21243|2024-08-03T02:31:59.884Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 11:21:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21376|2024-08-03T02:38:55.920Z -- oracle%20corporation -- primavera%20portfolio%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21376</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Primavera Portfolio Management product of Oracle Construction and Engineering (component: Web Access). Supported versions that are affected are 18.0.0.0-18.0.3.0, 19.0.0.0-19.0.1.2 and 20.0.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Primavera Portfolio Management. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Primavera Portfolio Management accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Primavera Portfolio Management accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21376|2024-08-03T02:38:55.920Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 11:26:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21281|2024-08-03T02:38:55.126Z -- oracle%20corporation -- primavera%20portfolio%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21281</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Primavera Portfolio Management product of Oracle Construction and Engineering (component: Web Access). Supported versions that are affected are 18.0.0.0-18.0.3.0, 19.0.0.0-19.0.1.2, 20.0.0.0 and 20.0.0.1. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Primavera Portfolio Management. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Primavera Portfolio Management, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Primavera Portfolio Management accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Primavera Portfolio Management accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.8 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21281|2024-08-03T02:38:55.126Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 11:23:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21269|2024-08-03T02:31:59.316Z -- oracle%20corporation -- primavera%20portfolio%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21269</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Primavera Portfolio Management product of Oracle Construction and Engineering (component: Web Access). Supported versions that are affected are 18.0.0.0-18.0.3.0, 19.0.0.0-19.0.1.2, 20.0.0.0 and 20.0.0.1. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Primavera Portfolio Management. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Primavera Portfolio Management, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Primavera Portfolio Management accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Primavera Portfolio Management accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.1 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21269|2024-08-03T02:31:59.316Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 11:22:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21242|2024-08-03T02:31:59.873Z -- oracle%20corporation -- primavera%20portfolio%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21242</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Primavera Portfolio Management product of Oracle Construction and Engineering (component: Web Access). Supported versions that are affected are 18.0.0.0-18.0.3.0, 19.0.0.0-19.0.1.2, 20.0.0.0 and 20.0.0.1. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Primavera Portfolio Management. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Primavera Portfolio Management, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Primavera Portfolio Management accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Primavera Portfolio Management accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21242|2024-08-03T02:31:59.873Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 11:21:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21244|2024-08-03T02:31:59.343Z -- oracle%20corporation -- primavera%20portfolio%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21244</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Primavera Portfolio Management product of Oracle Construction and Engineering (component: Web Access). Supported versions that are affected are 18.0.0.0-18.0.3.0, 19.0.0.0-19.0.1.2, 20.0.0.0 and 20.0.0.1. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Primavera Portfolio Management. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Primavera Portfolio Management accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.3 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21244|2024-08-03T02:31:59.343Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 11:21:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21377|2024-08-03T02:38:55.835Z -- oracle%20corporation -- primavera%20portfolio%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21377</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Primavera Portfolio Management product of Oracle Construction and Engineering (component: Web API). Supported versions that are affected are 18.0.0.0-18.0.3.0, 19.0.0.0-19.0.1.2 and 20.0.0.0. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Primavera Portfolio Management. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Primavera Portfolio Management accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Primavera Portfolio Management accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21377|2024-08-03T02:38:55.835Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 11:26:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
