<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- Primavera Unifier</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/primavera%20unifier.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- Primavera Unifier</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:22:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14617|2024-08-04T12:53:42.563Z -- oracle%20corporation -- primavera%20unifier
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14617</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Primavera Unifier product of Oracle Construction and Engineering (component: Platform, Mobile App). Supported versions that are affected are 16.1, 16.2, 17.7-17.12, 18.8 and 19.12; Mobile App: Prior to 20.6. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTPS to compromise Primavera Unifier. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Primavera Unifier accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.7 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14617|2024-08-04T12:53:42.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14618|2024-08-04T12:53:42.477Z -- oracle%20corporation -- primavera%20unifier
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14618</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Primavera Unifier product of Oracle Construction and Engineering (component: Mobile App). The supported version that is affected is Prior to 20.6. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTPS to compromise Primavera Unifier. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Primavera Unifier accessible data as well as unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Primavera Unifier accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.9 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:H/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14618|2024-08-04T12:53:42.477Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
