<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- Siebel Core - Server Framework</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/siebel%20core%20-%20server%20framework.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- Siebel Core - Server Framework</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:22:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-2004|2024-08-03T16:32:01.619Z -- oracle%20corporation -- siebel%20core%20-%20server%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-2004</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Siebel Core - Server BizLogic Script product of Oracle Siebel CRM (component: Integration - Scripting). Supported versions that are affected are 20.12 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Siebel Core - Server BizLogic Script. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Siebel Core - Server BizLogic Script accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.3 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-2004|2024-08-03T16:32:01.619Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 14:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-2039|2024-08-03T16:32:01.527Z -- oracle%20corporation -- siebel%20core%20-%20server%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-2039</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Siebel Core - Server Framework product of Oracle Siebel CRM (component: Search). Supported versions that are affected are 20.12 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Siebel Core - Server Framework. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Siebel Core - Server Framework, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Siebel Core - Server Framework accessible data as well as unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Siebel Core - Server Framework accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.6 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:H/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-2039|2024-08-03T16:32:01.527Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 14:50:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-2368|2024-08-03T16:38:57.571Z -- oracle%20corporation -- siebel%20core%20-%20server%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-2368</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Siebel CRM product of Oracle Siebel CRM (component: Siebel Core - Server Infrastructure). Supported versions that are affected are 21.5 and Prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTPS to compromise Siebel CRM. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Siebel CRM accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.9 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-2368|2024-08-03T16:38:57.571Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 22:43:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-2353|2024-08-03T16:38:57.560Z -- oracle%20corporation -- siebel%20core%20-%20server%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-2353</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Siebel Core - Server Framework product of Oracle Siebel CRM (component: Loging). Supported versions that are affected are 21.5 and Prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Siebel Core - Server Framework executes to compromise Siebel Core - Server Framework. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Siebel Core - Server Framework accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.4 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-2353|2024-08-03T16:38:57.560Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 22:43:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
