<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- Siebel UI Framework</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/siebel%20ui%20framework.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- Siebel UI Framework</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 17:21:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2738|2024-08-04T07:17:02.683Z -- oracle%20corporation -- siebel%20ui%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2738</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Siebel UI Framework product of Oracle Siebel CRM (component: EAI, SWSE). Supported versions that are affected are 20.2 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Siebel UI Framework. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Siebel UI Framework accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.3 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2738|2024-08-04T07:17:02.683Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2564|2024-08-04T07:09:54.524Z -- oracle%20corporation -- siebel%20ui%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2564</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Siebel UI Framework product of Oracle Siebel CRM (component: EAI). Supported versions that are affected are 19.10 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Siebel UI Framework. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Siebel UI Framework accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2564|2024-08-04T07:09:54.524Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2560|2024-08-04T07:09:54.709Z -- oracle%20corporation -- siebel%20ui%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2560</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Siebel UI Framework product of Oracle Siebel CRM (component: SWSE Server). Supported versions that are affected are 19.10 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Siebel UI Framework. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Siebel UI Framework, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Siebel UI Framework accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.7 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2560|2024-08-04T07:09:54.709Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2559|2024-08-04T07:09:54.654Z -- oracle%20corporation -- siebel%20ui%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2559</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Siebel UI Framework product of Oracle Siebel CRM (component: UIF Open UI). Supported versions that are affected are 19.7 and prior. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Siebel UI Framework. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Siebel UI Framework accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2559|2024-08-04T07:09:54.654Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14531|2024-08-04T12:46:34.694Z -- oracle%20corporation -- siebel%20ui%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14531</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Siebel UI Framework product of Oracle Siebel CRM (component: SWSE Server). Supported versions that are affected are 20.6 and prior. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Siebel UI Framework. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Siebel UI Framework accessible data as well as unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Siebel UI Framework accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.9 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:H/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14531|2024-08-04T12:46:34.694Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
