<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- Solaris Operating System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/solaris%20operating%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- Solaris Operating System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 17:21:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2771|2024-08-04T07:17:02.480Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2771</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Whodo). Supported versions that are affected are 10 and 11. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Solaris, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Solaris accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 2.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:H/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2771|2024-08-04T07:17:02.480Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14724|2024-08-04T12:53:43.261Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14724</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Device Driver Utility). The supported version that is affected is 11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14724|2024-08-04T12:53:43.261Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14537|2024-08-04T12:46:34.624Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14537</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Packaging Scripts). The supported version that is affected is 11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Solaris, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:R/S:C/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14537|2024-08-04T12:46:34.624Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14818|2024-08-04T13:00:50.885Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14818</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Utility). The supported version that is affected is 11. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via SSH to compromise Oracle Solaris. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Solaris, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Solaris accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.0 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14818|2024-08-04T13:00:50.885Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 14:04:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35539|2024-08-04T00:40:46.998Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35539</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Filesystem). The supported version that is affected is 11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris. While the vulnerability is in Oracle Solaris, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35539|2024-08-04T00:40:46.998Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:49:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2680|2024-08-04T07:17:02.616Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2680</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Filesystem). The supported version that is affected is 11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris. While the vulnerability is in Oracle Solaris, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.0 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2680|2024-08-04T07:17:02.616Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2851|2024-08-04T07:17:02.816Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2851</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Common Desktop Environment). Supported versions that are affected are 10 and 11. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris. While the vulnerability is in Oracle Solaris, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2851|2024-08-04T07:17:02.816Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35549|2024-08-04T00:40:46.941Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35549</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Utility). The supported version that is affected is 11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Solaris accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.9 (Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35549|2024-08-04T00:40:46.941Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:49:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2647|2024-08-04T07:09:54.868Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2647</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Kernel). Supported versions that are affected are 10 and 11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.0 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2647|2024-08-04T07:09:54.868Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14545|2024-08-04T12:46:34.681Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14545</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Device Driver Utility). The supported version that is affected is 11. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle Solaris accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.0 (Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:L/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:H/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14545|2024-08-04T12:46:34.681Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14871|2024-08-04T13:00:51.576Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14871</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Pluggable authentication module). Supported versions that are affected are 10 and 11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Solaris. While the vulnerability is in Oracle Solaris, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle Solaris. Note: This CVE is not exploitable for Solaris 11.1 and later releases, and ZFSSA 8.7 and later releases, thus the CVSS Base Score is 0.0. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 10.0 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14871|2024-08-04T13:00:51.576Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 14:04:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14759|2024-08-04T12:53:43.412Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14759</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Kernel). The supported version that is affected is 11. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Solaris, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Solaris accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 2.5 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14759|2024-08-04T12:53:43.412Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 14:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35589|2024-08-04T00:40:47.329Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35589</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Device drivers). The supported version that is affected is 11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris. While the vulnerability is in Oracle Solaris, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.0 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35589|2024-08-04T00:40:47.329Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:50:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2749|2024-08-04T07:17:02.185Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2749</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: SMF command svcbundle). The supported version that is affected is 11. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Solaris, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Solaris accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 2.5 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:H/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2749|2024-08-04T07:17:02.185Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14754|2024-08-04T12:53:43.412Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14754</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Filesystem). The supported version that is affected is 11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14754|2024-08-04T12:53:43.412Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 14:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14758|2024-08-04T12:53:43.284Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14758</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Kernel). The supported version that is affected is 11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle Solaris accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.6 (Confidentiality and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14758|2024-08-04T12:53:43.284Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 14:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2565|2024-08-04T07:09:54.644Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2565</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Consolidation Infrastructure). The supported version that is affected is 11. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Solaris, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:H/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2565|2024-08-04T07:09:54.644Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2605|2024-08-04T07:09:54.841Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2605</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Filesystem). The supported version that is affected is 11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle Solaris accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.1 (Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2605|2024-08-04T07:09:54.841Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2696|2024-08-04T07:17:01.595Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2696</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Common Desktop Environment). The supported version that is affected is 10. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris. While the vulnerability is in Oracle Solaris, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2696|2024-08-04T07:17:01.595Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14542|2024-08-04T12:46:34.804Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14542</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: libsuri). The supported version that is affected is 11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Solaris accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.3 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14542|2024-08-04T12:46:34.804Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2558|2024-08-04T07:09:54.594Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2558</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Kernel). The supported version that is affected is 11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via SMB to compromise Oracle Solaris. While the vulnerability is in Oracle Solaris, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.8 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2558|2024-08-04T07:09:54.594Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2578|2024-08-04T07:09:54.777Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2578</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Kernel). The supported version that is affected is 11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via SMB to compromise Oracle Solaris. While the vulnerability is in Oracle Solaris, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.8 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2578|2024-08-04T07:09:54.777Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2927|2024-08-04T07:23:59.457Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2927</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Common Desktop Environment). Supported versions that are affected are 10 and 11. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris. While the vulnerability is in Oracle Solaris, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2927|2024-08-04T07:23:59.457Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2944|2024-08-04T07:23:59.550Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2944</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Common Desktop Environment). Supported versions that are affected are 10 and 11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris. While the vulnerability is in Oracle Solaris, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2944|2024-08-04T07:23:59.550Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2664|2024-08-04T07:09:54.854Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2664</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Filesystem). The supported version that is affected is 11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Solaris, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Solaris accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Solaris accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.6 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2664|2024-08-04T07:09:54.854Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2656|2024-08-04T07:09:54.898Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2656</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: X Window System). Supported versions that are affected are 10 and 11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Solaris accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Solaris accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 4.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2656|2024-08-04T07:09:54.898Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21151|2024-08-01T22:13:42.712Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21151</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Filesystem).   The supported version that is affected is 11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.3 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21151|2024-08-01T22:13:42.712Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21105|2024-08-01T22:13:42.679Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21105</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Utility).   The supported version that is affected is 11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Solaris accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 2.0 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21105|2024-08-01T22:13:42.679Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20999|2024-08-01T22:13:42.183Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20999</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Zones).   The supported version that is affected is 11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle Solaris, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.2 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20999|2024-08-01T22:13:42.183Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21059|2024-08-01T22:13:42.311Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21059</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Utility).   The supported version that is affected is 11. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle Solaris, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21059|2024-08-01T22:13:42.311Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21151|2024-07-23T16:26:30.829Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21151</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Filesystem).   The supported version that is affected is 11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.3 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21151|2024-07-23T16:26:30.829Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21059|2024-06-18T20:35:26.723Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21059</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Utility).   The supported version that is affected is 11. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle Solaris, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21059|2024-06-18T20:35:26.723Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21105|2024-04-16T21:26:33.939Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21105</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Utility).   The supported version that is affected is 11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Solaris accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 2.0 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21105|2024-04-16T21:26:33.939Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21059|2024-04-16T21:26:18.102Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21059</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Utility).   The supported version that is affected is 11. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle Solaris, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21059|2024-04-16T21:26:18.102Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20999|2024-04-16T21:25:57.507Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20999</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Zones).   The supported version that is affected is 11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle Solaris, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.2 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20999|2024-04-16T21:25:57.507Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21151|2024-07-16T22:40:00.596Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21151</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Filesystem).   The supported version that is affected is 11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.3 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21151|2024-07-16T22:40:00.596Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21105|2024-07-26T15:12:31.784Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21105</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Utility).   The supported version that is affected is 11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Solaris accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 2.0 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21105|2024-07-26T15:12:31.784Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
