<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- Solaris Operating System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/solaris%20operating%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- Solaris Operating System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22023|2023-07-18T20:18:16.785Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-22023</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Device Driver Interface).   The supported version that is affected is 11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle Solaris. Note: CVE-2023-22023 is equivalent to CVE-2023-31284. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22023|2023-07-18T20:18:16.785Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 20:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22003|2023-04-18T19:54:46.472Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-22003</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Utility).  Supported versions that are affected are 10 and  11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Solaris accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.3 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22003|2023-04-18T19:54:46.472Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 19:54:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22129|2023-10-17T21:03:14.842Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-22129</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Kernel).   The supported version that is affected is 11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Solaris. Note: This vunlerability only affects SPARC Systems. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.5 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22129|2023-10-17T21:03:14.842Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 21:03:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22128|2023-10-17T21:03:14.486Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-22128</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Filesystem).  Supported versions that are affected are 10 and  11. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via rquota to compromise Oracle Solaris.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Solaris accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.1 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22128|2023-10-17T21:03:14.486Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 21:03:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-21900|2023-03-23T23:37:50.567Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-21900</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: NSSwitch).  Supported versions that are affected are 10 and  11. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with network access via multiple protocols to compromise Oracle Solaris.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Solaris, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Solaris accessible data and unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.0 (Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:H/UI:R/S:C/C:N/I:L/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-21900|2023-03-23T23:37:50.567Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 23:35:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-21896|2023-04-18T19:54:00.359Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-21896</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: NSSwitch).  Supported versions that are affected are 10 and  11. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.0 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-21896|2023-04-18T19:54:00.359Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 19:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-21984|2023-04-18T19:54:40.319Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-21984</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Libraries).   The supported version that is affected is 11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle Solaris.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-21984|2023-04-18T19:54:40.319Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 19:54:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-21985|2023-04-18T19:54:40.659Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-21985</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Utility).  Supported versions that are affected are 10 and  11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker and while the vulnerability is in Oracle Solaris, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change). Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.7 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:R/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-21985|2023-04-18T19:54:40.659Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 19:54:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-21928|2023-04-18T19:54:22.502Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-21928</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: IPS repository daemon).   The supported version that is affected is 11. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle Solaris accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 1.8 (Integrity impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:H/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:L/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-21928|2023-04-18T19:54:22.502Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 19:54:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-21948|2023-04-18T19:54:29.607Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-21948</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Core).   The supported version that is affected is 10. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-21948|2023-04-18T19:54:29.607Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 19:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20946|2024-01-16T21:41:19.641Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20946</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Kernel).   The supported version that is affected is 11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.5 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20946|2024-01-16T21:41:19.641Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20920|2024-01-16T21:41:15.262Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20920</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Filesystem).   The supported version that is affected is 11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle Solaris, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Solaris accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.8 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20920|2024-01-16T21:41:15.262Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 21:41:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-20999|2024-04-16T21:25:57.507Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-20999</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Zones).   The supported version that is affected is 11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle Solaris, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.2 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-20999|2024-04-16T21:25:57.507Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21059|2024-04-16T21:26:18.102Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21059</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Utility).   The supported version that is affected is 11. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle Solaris, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle Solaris. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21059|2024-04-16T21:26:18.102Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21105|2024-04-16T21:26:33.939Z -- oracle%20corporation -- solaris%20operating%20system
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21105</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle Solaris product of Oracle Systems (component: Utility).   The supported version that is affected is 11. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle Solaris executes to compromise Oracle Solaris.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle Solaris accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 2.0 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:R/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21105|2024-04-16T21:26:33.939Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
