<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Oracle Corporation -- VM VirtualBox</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/oracle%20corporation/vm%20virtualbox.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Oracle Corporation -- VM VirtualBox</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:23:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2913|2024-08-04T07:23:59.292Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2913</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 6.0.20 and prior to 6.1.6. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.0 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2913|2024-08-04T07:23:59.292Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14889|2024-08-04T13:00:51.539Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14889</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). The supported version that is affected is Prior to 6.1.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.0 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14889|2024-08-04T13:00:51.539Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 14:04:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2894|2024-08-04T07:23:58.896Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2894</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.40, prior to 6.0.20 and prior to 6.1.6. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.0 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2894|2024-08-04T07:23:58.896Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2680|2024-08-04T18:56:45.651Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2680</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.28 and prior to 6.0.6. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2680|2024-08-04T18:56:45.651Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 18:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14713|2024-08-04T12:53:43.345Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14713</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.44, prior to 6.0.24 and prior to 6.1.12. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14713|2024-08-04T12:53:43.345Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2944|2024-08-04T19:03:43.479Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2944</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.34 and prior to 6.0.14. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox as well as unauthorized update, insert or delete access to some of Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data and unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:L/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2944|2024-08-04T19:03:43.479Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 17:40:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14647|2024-08-04T12:53:42.524Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14647</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.44, prior to 6.0.24 and prior to 6.1.12. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14647|2024-08-04T12:53:42.524Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14892|2024-08-04T13:00:51.640Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14892</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). The supported version that is affected is Prior to 6.1.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14892|2024-08-04T13:00:51.640Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 14:04:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2690|2024-08-04T18:56:45.646Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2690</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.28 and prior to 6.0.6. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2690|2024-08-04T18:56:45.646Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 18:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2859|2024-08-04T19:03:43.243Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2859</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.32 and prior to 6.0.10. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2859|2024-08-04T19:03:43.243Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 22:31:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2929|2024-08-04T07:23:59.428Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2929</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.40, prior to 6.0.20 and prior to 6.1.6. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2929|2024-08-04T07:23:59.428Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2520|2024-08-04T18:49:48.279Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2520</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are prior to 5.2.24 and prior to 6.0.2. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2520|2024-08-04T18:49:48.279Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2555|2024-08-04T18:56:44.071Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2555</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are prior to 5.2.24 and prior to 6.0.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2555|2024-08-04T18:56:44.071Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2524|2024-08-04T18:49:48.266Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2524</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are prior to 5.2.24 and prior to 6.0.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2524|2024-08-04T18:49:48.266Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2702|2024-08-04T07:17:02.194Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2702</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.36, prior to 6.0.16 and prior to 6.1.2. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2702|2024-08-04T07:17:02.194Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2696|2024-08-04T18:56:45.649Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2696</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.28 and prior to 6.0.6. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2696|2024-08-04T18:56:45.649Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 18:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2848|2024-08-04T19:03:43.080Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2848</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.32 and prior to 6.0.10. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2848|2024-08-04T19:03:43.080Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 22:31:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2741|2024-08-04T07:17:02.436Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2741</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.40, prior to 6.0.20 and prior to 6.1.6. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.0 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2741|2024-08-04T07:17:02.436Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2958|2024-08-04T07:23:59.954Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2958</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.40, prior to 6.0.20 and prior to 6.1.6. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2958|2024-08-04T07:23:59.954Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14711|2024-08-04T12:53:43.285Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14711</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.44, prior to 6.0.24 and prior to 6.1.12. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. Note: The CVE-2020-14711 is applicable to macOS host only. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:R/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14711|2024-08-04T12:53:43.285Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14886|2024-08-04T13:00:51.507Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14886</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). The supported version that is affected is Prior to 6.1.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.0 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14886|2024-08-04T13:00:51.507Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 14:04:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35538|2024-08-04T00:40:47.438Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35538</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). The supported version that is affected is Prior to 6.1.28. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. Note: This vulnerability does not apply to Windows systems. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35538|2024-08-04T00:40:47.438Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:49:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2521|2024-08-04T18:49:48.082Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2521</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are prior to 5.2.24 and prior to 6.0.2. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2521|2024-08-04T18:49:48.082Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2506|2024-08-04T18:49:48.212Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2506</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are prior to 5.2.24 and prior to 6.0.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 3.8 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2506|2024-08-04T18:49:48.212Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2951|2024-08-04T07:23:59.509Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2951</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.40, prior to 6.0.20 and prior to 6.1.6. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2951|2024-08-04T07:23:59.509Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14648|2024-08-04T12:53:42.753Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14648</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.44, prior to 6.0.24 and prior to 6.1.12. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14648|2024-08-04T12:53:42.753Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2509|2024-08-04T18:49:48.198Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2509</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are prior to 5.2.24 and prior to 6.0.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2509|2024-08-04T18:49:48.198Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14694|2024-08-04T12:53:42.833Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14694</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.44, prior to 6.0.24 and prior to 6.1.12. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14694|2024-08-04T12:53:42.833Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14675|2024-08-04T12:53:42.603Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14675</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.44, prior to 6.0.24 and prior to 6.1.12. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14675|2024-08-04T12:53:42.603Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14712|2024-08-04T12:53:43.294Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14712</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.44, prior to 6.0.24 and prior to 6.1.12. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.0 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14712|2024-08-04T12:53:43.294Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2908|2024-08-04T07:23:59.284Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2908</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.40, prior to 6.0.20 and prior to 6.1.6. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.2 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2908|2024-08-04T07:23:59.284Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2726|2024-08-04T07:17:02.456Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2726</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.36, prior to 6.0.16 and prior to 6.1.2. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2726|2024-08-04T07:17:02.456Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2554|2024-08-04T18:56:44.042Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2554</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are prior to 5.2.24 and prior to 6.0.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2554|2024-08-04T18:56:44.042Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2553|2024-08-04T18:56:44.001Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2553</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are prior to 5.2.24 and prior to 6.0.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 3.8 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2553|2024-08-04T18:56:44.001Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14699|2024-08-04T12:53:43.277Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14699</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.44, prior to 6.0.24 and prior to 6.1.12. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14699|2024-08-04T12:53:43.277Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2678|2024-08-04T18:56:45.568Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2678</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.28 and prior to 6.0.6. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2678|2024-08-04T18:56:45.568Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 18:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2748|2024-08-04T07:17:02.578Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2748</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.40, prior to 6.0.20 and prior to 6.1.6. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 3.2 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2748|2024-08-04T07:17:02.578Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2500|2024-08-04T18:49:48.200Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2500</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are prior to 5.2.24 and prior to 6.0.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2500|2024-08-04T18:49:48.200Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2703|2024-08-04T07:17:01.547Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2703</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.36 and prior to 6.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2703|2024-08-04T07:17:01.547Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14673|2024-08-04T12:53:42.808Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14673</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.44, prior to 6.0.24 and prior to 6.1.12. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14673|2024-08-04T12:53:42.808Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2681|2024-08-04T07:17:01.540Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2681</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.36, prior to 6.0.16 and prior to 6.1.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2681|2024-08-04T07:17:01.540Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14676|2024-08-04T12:53:42.742Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14676</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.44, prior to 6.0.24 and prior to 6.1.12. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14676|2024-08-04T12:53:42.742Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14628|2024-08-04T12:53:41.965Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14628</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.44, prior to 6.0.24 and prior to 6.1.12. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. Note: The CVE-2020-14628 is applicable to Windows VM only. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.2 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14628|2024-08-04T12:53:41.965Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2905|2024-08-04T07:23:59.283Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2905</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.40, prior to 6.0.20 and prior to 6.1.6. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.2 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2905|2024-08-04T07:23:59.283Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2907|2024-08-04T07:23:59.560Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2907</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.40, prior to 6.0.20 and prior to 6.1.6. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2907|2024-08-04T07:23:59.560Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2574|2024-08-04T18:56:44.172Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2574</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.28 and prior to 6.0.6. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2574|2024-08-04T18:56:44.172Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 18:16:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14872|2024-08-04T13:00:51.663Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14872</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). The supported version that is affected is Prior to 6.1.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.2 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14872|2024-08-04T13:00:51.663Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 14:04:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14650|2024-08-04T12:53:42.690Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14650</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.44, prior to 6.0.24 and prior to 6.1.12. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14650|2024-08-04T12:53:42.690Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2865|2024-08-04T19:03:43.233Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2865</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.32 and prior to 6.0.10. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2865|2024-08-04T19:03:43.233Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 22:31:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2874|2024-08-04T19:03:43.307Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2874</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.32 and prior to 6.0.10. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 3.3 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2874|2024-08-04T19:03:43.307Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 22:31:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14715|2024-08-04T12:53:43.219Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14715</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.44, prior to 6.0.24 and prior to 6.1.12. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.4 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14715|2024-08-04T12:53:43.219Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14700|2024-08-04T12:53:43.160Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14700</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.44, prior to 6.0.24 and prior to 6.1.12. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14700|2024-08-04T12:53:43.160Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2721|2024-08-04T18:56:45.586Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2721</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.28 and prior to 6.0.6. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2721|2024-08-04T18:56:45.586Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 18:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35545|2024-08-04T00:40:47.322Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35545</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). The supported version that is affected is Prior to 6.1.28. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox and unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.7 (Confidentiality and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35545|2024-08-04T00:40:47.322Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:49:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2723|2024-08-04T18:56:45.653Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2723</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.28 and prior to 6.0.6. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2723|2024-08-04T18:56:45.653Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 18:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2682|2024-08-04T07:17:01.962Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2682</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.36, prior to 6.0.16 and prior to 6.1.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.2 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2682|2024-08-04T07:17:01.962Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2656|2024-08-04T18:56:45.495Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2656</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.28 and prior to 6.0.6. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2656|2024-08-04T18:56:45.495Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 18:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2679|2024-08-04T18:56:45.632Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2679</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.28 and prior to 6.0.6. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox and unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.3 (Confidentiality and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2679|2024-08-04T18:56:45.632Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 18:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2505|2024-08-04T18:49:48.294Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2505</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are prior to 5.2.24 and prior to 6.0.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 3.8 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2505|2024-08-04T18:49:48.294Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14698|2024-08-04T12:53:43.154Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14698</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.44, prior to 6.0.24 and prior to 6.1.12. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14698|2024-08-04T12:53:43.154Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3021|2024-08-04T19:12:09.380Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3021</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.34 and prior to 6.0.14. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3021|2024-08-04T19:12:09.380Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 17:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3031|2024-08-04T19:12:09.027Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3031</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.34 and prior to 6.0.14. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.0 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3031|2024-08-04T19:12:09.027Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 17:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2867|2024-08-04T19:03:43.134Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2867</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.32 and prior to 6.0.10. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.2 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2867|2024-08-04T19:03:43.134Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 22:31:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14649|2024-08-04T12:53:42.837Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14649</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.44, prior to 6.0.24 and prior to 6.1.12. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14649|2024-08-04T12:53:42.837Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2508|2024-08-04T18:49:48.065Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2508</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are prior to 5.2.24 and prior to 6.0.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2508|2024-08-04T18:49:48.065Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2911|2024-08-04T07:24:00.558Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2911</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.40, prior to 6.0.20 and prior to 6.1.6. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2911|2024-08-04T07:24:00.558Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2909|2024-08-04T07:24:00.642Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2909</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.40, prior to 6.0.20 and prior to 6.1.6. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 2.8 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2909|2024-08-04T07:24:00.642Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3028|2024-08-04T19:12:09.290Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3028</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.34 and prior to 6.0.14. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3028|2024-08-04T19:12:09.290Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 17:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2575|2024-08-04T07:09:54.639Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2575</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.40, prior to 6.0.20 and prior to 6.1.6. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2575|2024-08-04T07:09:54.639Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 14:40:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14881|2024-08-04T13:00:51.523Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14881</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). The supported version that is affected is Prior to 6.1.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.0 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14881|2024-08-04T13:00:51.523Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 14:04:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2902|2024-08-04T07:23:59.387Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2902</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.40, prior to 6.0.20 and prior to 6.1.6. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2902|2024-08-04T07:23:59.387Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14885|2024-08-04T13:00:51.502Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14885</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). The supported version that is affected is Prior to 6.1.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.0 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14885|2024-08-04T13:00:51.502Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 14:04:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2873|2024-08-04T19:03:43.144Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2873</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.32 and prior to 6.0.10. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 3.3 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2873|2024-08-04T19:03:43.144Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 22:31:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2864|2024-08-04T19:03:43.139Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2864</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.32 and prior to 6.0.10. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2864|2024-08-04T19:03:43.139Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 22:31:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2501|2024-08-04T18:49:47.959Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2501</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are prior to 5.2.24 and prior to 6.0.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 3.8 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2501|2024-08-04T18:49:47.959Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2722|2024-08-04T18:56:45.649Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2722</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.28 and prior to 6.0.6. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2722|2024-08-04T18:56:45.649Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 18:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2552|2024-08-04T18:56:43.844Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2552</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are prior to 5.2.24 and prior to 6.0.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2552|2024-08-04T18:56:43.844Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2526|2024-08-04T18:49:48.279Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2526</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are prior to 5.2.24 and prior to 6.0.2. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2526|2024-08-04T18:49:48.279Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2910|2024-08-04T07:24:00.502Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2910</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 6.0.20 and prior to 6.1.6. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2910|2024-08-04T07:24:00.502Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2522|2024-08-04T18:49:48.103Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2522</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are prior to 5.2.24 and prior to 6.0.2. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2522|2024-08-04T18:49:48.103Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2984|2024-08-04T19:12:08.398Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2984</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.34 and prior to 6.0.14. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.0 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2984|2024-08-04T19:12:08.398Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 17:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2511|2024-08-04T18:49:48.265Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2511</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are prior to 5.2.24 and prior to 6.0.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via SOAP to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2511|2024-08-04T18:49:48.265Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3017|2024-08-04T19:12:09.591Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3017</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.34 and prior to 6.0.14. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.2 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3017|2024-08-04T19:12:09.591Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 17:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14646|2024-08-04T12:53:42.357Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14646</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.44, prior to 6.0.24 and prior to 6.1.12. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14646|2024-08-04T12:53:42.357Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3026|2024-08-04T19:12:09.510Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3026</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.34 and prior to 6.0.14. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3026|2024-08-04T19:12:09.510Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 17:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2725|2024-08-04T07:17:01.893Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2725</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.36, prior to 6.0.16 and prior to 6.1.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2725|2024-08-04T07:17:01.893Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2926|2024-08-04T19:03:43.460Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2926</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.34 and prior to 6.0.14. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 2.3 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2926|2024-08-04T19:03:43.460Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 17:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3005|2024-08-04T19:12:09.149Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3005</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.34 and prior to 6.0.14. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.0 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3005|2024-08-04T19:12:09.149Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 17:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2692|2024-08-04T07:17:01.805Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2692</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.36, prior to 6.0.16 and prior to 6.1.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2692|2024-08-04T07:17:01.805Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14704|2024-08-04T12:53:43.206Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14704</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.44, prior to 6.0.24 and prior to 6.1.12. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.0 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14704|2024-08-04T12:53:43.206Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2866|2024-08-04T19:03:43.143Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2866</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.32 and prior to 6.0.10. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.2 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2866|2024-08-04T19:03:43.143Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 22:31:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14884|2024-08-04T13:00:51.547Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14884</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). The supported version that is affected is Prior to 6.1.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.0 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14884|2024-08-04T13:00:51.547Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 14:04:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14629|2024-08-04T12:53:42.601Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14629</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.44, prior to 6.0.24 and prior to 6.1.12. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.0 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14629|2024-08-04T12:53:42.601Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2527|2024-08-04T18:49:48.237Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2527</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are prior to 5.2.26 and prior to 6.0.4. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2527|2024-08-04T18:49:48.237Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2451|2024-08-04T18:49:47.930Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2451</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are prior to 5.2.24 and prior to 6.0.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2451|2024-08-04T18:49:47.930Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2689|2024-08-04T07:17:01.778Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2689</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.36, prior to 6.0.16 and prior to 6.1.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2689|2024-08-04T07:17:01.778Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35542|2024-08-04T00:40:47.191Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35542</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). The supported version that is affected is Prior to 6.1.28. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.4 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35542|2024-08-04T00:40:47.191Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:49:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2850|2024-08-04T19:03:43.066Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2850</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.32 and prior to 6.0.10. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 2.8 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2850|2024-08-04T19:03:43.066Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 22:31:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2548|2024-08-04T18:49:48.163Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2548</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are prior to 5.2.24 and prior to 6.0.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2548|2024-08-04T18:49:48.163Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2863|2024-08-04T19:03:43.378Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2863</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.32 and prior to 6.0.10. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2863|2024-08-04T19:03:43.378Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 22:31:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2758|2024-08-04T07:17:02.562Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2758</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.40, prior to 6.0.20 and prior to 6.1.6. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.2 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2758|2024-08-04T07:17:02.562Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2877|2024-08-04T19:03:43.149Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2877</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.32 and prior to 6.0.10. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2877|2024-08-04T19:03:43.149Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 22:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35540|2024-08-04T00:40:47.263Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35540</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). The supported version that is affected is Prior to 6.1.28. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.5 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35540|2024-08-04T00:40:47.263Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 10:49:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2704|2024-08-04T07:17:01.197Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2704</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.36, prior to 6.0.16 and prior to 6.1.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2704|2024-08-04T07:17:01.197Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2914|2024-08-04T07:23:59.337Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2914</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 6.0.20 and prior to 6.1.6. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.0 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2914|2024-08-04T07:23:59.337Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2446|2024-08-04T18:49:47.821Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2446</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are prior to 5.2.24 and prior to 6.0.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2446|2024-08-04T18:49:47.821Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14695|2024-08-04T12:53:42.815Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14695</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.44, prior to 6.0.24 and prior to 6.1.12. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14695|2024-08-04T12:53:42.815Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2690|2024-08-04T07:17:01.065Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2690</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.36, prior to 6.0.16 and prior to 6.1.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2690|2024-08-04T07:17:01.065Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14677|2024-08-04T12:53:42.690Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14677</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.44, prior to 6.0.24 and prior to 6.1.12. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14677|2024-08-04T12:53:42.690Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2742|2024-08-04T07:17:02.129Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2742</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.36, prior to 6.0.16 and prior to 6.1.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.2 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2742|2024-08-04T07:17:02.129Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14703|2024-08-04T12:53:43.265Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14703</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.44, prior to 6.0.24 and prior to 6.1.12. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.0 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14703|2024-08-04T12:53:43.265Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3002|2024-08-04T19:12:09.231Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3002</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.34 and prior to 6.0.14. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.0 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3002|2024-08-04T19:12:09.231Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 17:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2504|2024-08-04T18:49:48.008Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2504</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are prior to 5.2.24 and prior to 6.0.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 3.8 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2504|2024-08-04T18:49:48.008Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2875|2024-08-04T19:03:43.377Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2875</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.32 and prior to 6.0.10. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 3.3 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2875|2024-08-04T19:03:43.377Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 22:31:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2701|2024-08-04T07:17:01.067Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2701</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.36, prior to 6.0.16 and prior to 6.1.2. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2701|2024-08-04T07:17:01.067Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14714|2024-08-04T12:53:43.229Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14714</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.44, prior to 6.0.24 and prior to 6.1.12. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 4.4 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14714|2024-08-04T12:53:43.229Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2674|2024-08-04T07:17:02.131Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2674</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.36, prior to 6.0.16 and prior to 6.1.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.2 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2674|2024-08-04T07:17:02.131Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2691|2024-08-04T07:17:01.065Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2691</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.36, prior to 6.0.16 and prior to 6.1.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2691|2024-08-04T07:17:01.065Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2705|2024-08-04T07:17:01.971Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2705</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.36, prior to 6.0.16 and prior to 6.1.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2705|2024-08-04T07:17:01.971Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2743|2024-08-04T07:17:02.169Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2743</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.36, prior to 6.0.16 and prior to 6.1.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.0 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2743|2024-08-04T07:17:02.169Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2703|2024-08-04T18:56:45.586Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2703</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.28 and prior to 6.0.6. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2703|2024-08-04T18:56:45.586Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 18:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2448|2024-08-04T18:49:48.099Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2448</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are prior to 5.2.24 and prior to 6.0.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2448|2024-08-04T18:49:48.099Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14674|2024-08-04T12:53:42.674Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14674</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.44, prior to 6.0.24 and prior to 6.1.12. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14674|2024-08-04T12:53:42.674Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2693|2024-08-04T07:17:01.030Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2693</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.36, prior to 6.0.16 and prior to 6.1.2. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.3 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2693|2024-08-04T07:17:01.030Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2727|2024-08-04T07:17:02.351Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2727</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.36, prior to 6.0.16 and prior to 6.1.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.0 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2727|2024-08-04T07:17:02.351Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2657|2024-08-04T18:56:45.413Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2657</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.28 and prior to 6.0.6. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2657|2024-08-04T18:56:45.413Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 18:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2698|2024-08-04T07:17:02.097Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2698</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.36, prior to 6.0.16 and prior to 6.1.2. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.5 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2698|2024-08-04T07:17:02.097Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2678|2024-08-04T07:17:02.184Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2678</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.36, prior to 6.0.16 and prior to 6.1.2. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized creation, deletion or modification access to critical data or all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data as well as unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.4 (Confidentiality and Integrity impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:H/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2678|2024-08-04T07:17:02.184Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:34:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2959|2024-08-04T07:24:00.483Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2959</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.40, prior to 6.0.20 and prior to 6.1.6. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via MLD to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 8.6 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2959|2024-08-04T07:24:00.483Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 13:29:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2876|2024-08-04T19:03:43.126Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2876</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.32 and prior to 6.0.10. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a partial denial of service (partial DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 3.3 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:L).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2876|2024-08-04T19:03:43.126Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 22:31:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2450|2024-08-04T18:49:47.976Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2450</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are prior to 5.2.24 and prior to 6.0.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2450|2024-08-04T18:49:47.976Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2525|2024-08-04T18:49:48.201Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2525</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are prior to 5.2.24 and prior to 6.0.2. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 5.6 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2525|2024-08-04T18:49:48.201Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-14707|2024-08-04T12:53:43.238Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-14707</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core). Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 5.2.44, prior to 6.0.24 and prior to 6.1.12. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.0 (Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-14707|2024-08-04T12:53:43.238Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:34:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2556|2024-08-04T18:56:44.173Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2556</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are prior to 5.2.24 and prior to 6.0.2. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2556|2024-08-04T18:56:44.173Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-2523|2024-08-04T18:49:48.198Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2523</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox component of Oracle Virtualization (subcomponent: Core). Supported versions that are affected are prior to 5.2.24 and prior to 6.0.2. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox. While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.0 Base Score 7.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.0/AV:L/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-2523|2024-08-04T18:49:48.198Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21110|2024-08-01T22:13:42.631Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21110</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21110|2024-08-01T22:13:42.631Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21121|2024-08-01T22:13:42.685Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21121</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21121|2024-08-01T22:13:42.685Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21161|2024-08-01T22:13:42.706Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21161</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.20. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. Note: This vulnerability applies to Linux hosts only. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.5 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21161|2024-08-01T22:13:42.706Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21164|2024-08-01T22:13:42.689Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21164</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.20. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 2.5 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21164|2024-08-01T22:13:42.689Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21141|2024-08-01T22:13:42.678Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21141</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.20. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.2 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21141|2024-08-01T22:13:42.678Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21103|2024-08-01T22:13:42.653Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21103</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. Note: This vulnerability applies to Linux hosts only. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21103|2024-08-01T22:13:42.653Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21111|2024-08-01T22:13:42.688Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21111</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. Note: This vulnerability applies to Windows hosts only. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21111|2024-08-01T22:13:42.688Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21106|2024-08-01T22:13:42.666Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21106</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21106|2024-08-01T22:13:42.666Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21112|2024-08-01T22:13:42.684Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21112</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21112|2024-08-01T22:13:42.684Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21108|2024-08-01T22:13:42.674Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21108</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.3 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21108|2024-08-01T22:13:42.674Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21116|2024-08-01T22:13:42.678Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21116</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. Note: This vulnerability applies to Linux hosts only. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21116|2024-08-01T22:13:42.678Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21114|2024-08-01T22:13:42.690Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21114</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21114|2024-08-01T22:13:42.690Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21109|2024-08-01T22:13:42.681Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21109</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.9 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21109|2024-08-01T22:13:42.681Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21107|2024-08-01T22:13:42.636Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21107</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. Note: This vulnerability applies to Windows hosts only. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.7 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21107|2024-08-01T22:13:42.636Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21115|2024-08-01T22:13:42.665Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21115</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21115|2024-08-01T22:13:42.665Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21113|2024-08-01T22:13:42.659Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21113</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21113|2024-08-01T22:13:42.659Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21115|2024-07-25T15:36:45.255Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21115</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21115|2024-07-25T15:36:45.255Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21141|2024-07-19T15:59:53.841Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21141</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.20. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.2 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21141|2024-07-19T15:59:53.841Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21164|2024-07-17T14:45:16.961Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21164</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.20. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 2.5 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21164|2024-07-17T14:45:16.961Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21109|2024-07-15T20:04:59.810Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21109</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.9 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21109|2024-07-15T20:04:59.810Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21121|2024-06-26T03:55:33.081Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21121</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21121|2024-06-26T03:55:33.081Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21108|2024-06-13T20:14:08.699Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21108</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.3 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21108|2024-06-13T20:14:08.699Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21103|2024-04-16T21:26:33.292Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21103</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. Note: This vulnerability applies to Linux hosts only. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21103|2024-04-16T21:26:33.292Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21115|2024-04-16T21:26:37.191Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21115</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21115|2024-04-16T21:26:37.191Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21114|2024-04-16T21:26:36.879Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21114</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21114|2024-04-16T21:26:36.879Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21113|2024-04-16T21:26:36.530Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21113</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21113|2024-04-16T21:26:36.530Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21109|2024-04-16T21:26:35.292Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21109</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows unauthenticated attacker with network access via HTTP to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.9 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:H/PR:N/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21109|2024-04-16T21:26:35.292Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21108|2024-04-16T21:26:34.967Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21108</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 3.3 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21108|2024-04-16T21:26:34.967Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21112|2024-04-16T21:26:36.221Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21112</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21112|2024-04-16T21:26:36.221Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21111|2024-04-16T21:26:35.907Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21111</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. Note: This vulnerability applies to Windows hosts only. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21111|2024-04-16T21:26:35.907Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21107|2024-04-16T21:26:34.607Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21107</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. Note: This vulnerability applies to Windows hosts only. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.7 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21107|2024-04-16T21:26:34.607Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21106|2024-06-04T17:38:02.363Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21106</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21106|2024-06-04T17:38:02.363Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21110|2024-04-16T21:26:35.598Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21110</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  Successful attacks require human interaction from a person other than the attacker. Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.3 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:R/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21110|2024-04-16T21:26:35.598Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21121|2024-06-04T17:38:05.209Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21121</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized access to critical data or complete access to all Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.5 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21121|2024-06-04T17:38:05.209Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21116|2024-04-16T21:26:37.525Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21116</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. Note: This vulnerability applies to Linux hosts only. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21116|2024-04-16T21:26:37.525Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21113|2024-06-18T20:35:09.485Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21113</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21113|2024-06-18T20:35:09.485Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21116|2024-07-08T14:55:19.938Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21116</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. Note: This vulnerability applies to Linux hosts only. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21116|2024-07-08T14:55:19.938Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21161|2024-07-16T22:40:03.629Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21161</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.20. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. Note: This vulnerability applies to Linux hosts only. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.5 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21161|2024-07-16T22:40:03.629Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21164|2024-07-16T22:40:04.641Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21164</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.20. Difficult to exploit vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in  unauthorized read access to a subset of Oracle VM VirtualBox accessible data. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 2.5 (Confidentiality impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:H/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:N).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21164|2024-07-16T22:40:04.641Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21141|2024-07-16T22:39:57.271Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21141</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.20. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.2 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21141|2024-07-16T22:39:57.271Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21141|2024-07-19T03:55:26.292Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21141</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.20. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  While the vulnerability is in Oracle VM VirtualBox, attacks may significantly impact additional products (scope change).  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 8.2 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21141|2024-07-19T03:55:26.292Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:39:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21161|2024-07-23T16:26:01.551Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21161</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.20. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in unauthorized ability to cause a hang or frequently repeatable crash (complete DOS) of Oracle VM VirtualBox. Note: This vulnerability applies to Linux hosts only. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 5.5 (Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21161|2024-07-23T16:26:01.551Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21103|2024-07-26T20:35:45.512Z -- oracle%20corporation -- vm%20virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21103</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in the Oracle VM VirtualBox product of Oracle Virtualization (component: Core).  Supported versions that are affected are Prior to 7.0.16. Easily exploitable vulnerability allows low privileged attacker with logon to the infrastructure where Oracle VM VirtualBox executes to compromise Oracle VM VirtualBox.  Successful attacks of this vulnerability can result in takeover of Oracle VM VirtualBox. Note: This vulnerability applies to Linux hosts only. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 7.8 (Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability impacts).  CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21103|2024-07-26T20:35:45.512Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:26:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
