<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for arduino -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/arduino/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for arduino -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-49296|2023-12-13T19:54:34.638Z -- arduino -- arduino-create-agent
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-49296</link>
      <description>The Arduino Create Agent allows users to use the Arduino Create applications to upload code to any USB connected Arduino board directly from the browser. A vulnerability in versions prior to 1.3.6 affects the endpoint `/certificate.crt` and the way the web interface of the ArduinoCreateAgent handles custom error messages. An attacker that is able to persuade a victim into clicking on a malicious link can perform a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting attack on the web interface of the create agent, which would allow the attacker to execute arbitrary browser client side code. Version 1.3.6 contains a fix for the issue.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-49296|2023-12-13T19:54:34.638Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 19:54:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43802|2023-11-02T17:33:19.918Z -- arduino -- arduino-create-agent
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43802</link>
      <description>Arduino Create Agent is a package to help manage Arduino development. This vulnerability affects the endpoint `/upload` which handles request with the `filename` parameter. A user who has the ability to perform HTTP requests to the localhost interface, or is able to bypass the CORS configuration, can escalate their privileges to those of the user running the Arduino Create Agent service via a crafted HTTP POST request. This issue has been addressed in version `1.3.3`. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43802|2023-11-02T17:33:19.918Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 20:39:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43803|2023-11-02T17:34:57.874Z -- arduino -- arduino-create-agent
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43803</link>
      <description>Arduino Create Agent is a package to help manage Arduino development. This vulnerability affects the endpoint `/v2/pkgs/tools/installed` and the way it handles plugin names supplied as user input. A user who has the ability to perform HTTP requests to the localhost interface, or is able to bypass the CORS configuration, can delete arbitrary files or folders belonging to the user that runs the Arduino Create Agent via a crafted HTTP POST request. This issue has been addressed in version `1.3.3`. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43803|2023-11-02T17:34:57.874Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 20:36:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43800|2023-11-02T17:32:18.720Z -- arduino -- arduino-create-agent
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43800</link>
      <description>Arduino Create Agent is a package to help manage Arduino development. The vulnerability affects the endpoint `/v2/pkgs/tools/installed`. A user who has the ability to perform HTTP requests to the localhost interface, or is able to bypass the CORS configuration, can escalate his privileges to those of the user running the Arduino Create Agent service via a crafted HTTP POST request. This issue has been addressed in version `1.3.3`. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43800|2023-11-02T17:32:18.720Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 21:07:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43801|2023-11-02T17:34:18.109Z -- arduino -- arduino-create-agent
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-43801</link>
      <description>Arduino Create Agent is a package to help manage Arduino development. This vulnerability affects the endpoint `/v2/pkgs/tools/installed` and the way it handles plugin names supplied as user input. A user who has the ability to perform HTTP requests to the localhost interface, or is able to bypass the CORS configuration, can delete arbitrary files or folders belonging to the user that runs the Arduino Create Agent via a crafted HTTP DELETE request. This issue has been addressed in version `1.3.3`. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this issue.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43801|2023-11-02T17:34:18.109Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 21:06:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
