<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for arduino -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/arduino/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for arduino -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 22:23:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43802|2024-09-12T20:04:49.780Z -- arduino -- arduino-create-agent
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43802</link>
      <description>Arduino Create Agent is a package to help manage Arduino development. This vulnerability affects the endpoint `/upload` which handles request with the `filename` parameter. A user who has the ability to perform HTTP requests to the localhost interface, or is able to bypass the CORS configuration, can escalate their privileges to those of the user running the Arduino Create Agent service via a crafted HTTP POST request. This issue has been addressed in version `1.3.3`. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43802|2024-09-12T20:04:49.780Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 20:39:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43801|2024-09-12T20:04:35.655Z -- arduino -- arduino-create-agent
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43801</link>
      <description>Arduino Create Agent is a package to help manage Arduino development. This vulnerability affects the endpoint `/v2/pkgs/tools/installed` and the way it handles plugin names supplied as user input. A user who has the ability to perform HTTP requests to the localhost interface, or is able to bypass the CORS configuration, can delete arbitrary files or folders belonging to the user that runs the Arduino Create Agent via a crafted HTTP DELETE request. This issue has been addressed in version `1.3.3`. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this issue.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43801|2024-09-12T20:04:35.655Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 21:06:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43803|2024-09-12T20:05:16.159Z -- arduino -- arduino-create-agent
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43803</link>
      <description>Arduino Create Agent is a package to help manage Arduino development. This vulnerability affects the endpoint `/v2/pkgs/tools/installed` and the way it handles plugin names supplied as user input. A user who has the ability to perform HTTP requests to the localhost interface, or is able to bypass the CORS configuration, can delete arbitrary files or folders belonging to the user that runs the Arduino Create Agent via a crafted HTTP POST request. This issue has been addressed in version `1.3.3`. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43803|2024-09-12T20:05:16.159Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 20:36:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43800|2024-09-12T20:04:21.852Z -- arduino -- arduino-create-agent
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43800</link>
      <description>Arduino Create Agent is a package to help manage Arduino development. The vulnerability affects the endpoint `/v2/pkgs/tools/installed`. A user who has the ability to perform HTTP requests to the localhost interface, or is able to bypass the CORS configuration, can escalate his privileges to those of the user running the Arduino Create Agent service via a crafted HTTP POST request. This issue has been addressed in version `1.3.3`. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43800|2024-09-12T20:04:21.852Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 21:07:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
