<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for shannah -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/shannah/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for shannah -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:22:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-4303|2024-08-03T17:23:10.457Z -- shannah -- xataface
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4303</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in shannah Xataface up to 2.x. Affected by this issue is the function testftp of the file install/install_form.js.php of the component Installer. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. Upgrading to version 3.0.0 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as 94143a4299e386f33bf582139cd4702571d93bde. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-217442 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: Installer is disabled by default.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in shannah Xataface bis 2.x entdeckt. Dies betrifft die Funktion testftp der Datei install/install_form.js.php der Komponente Installer. Mittels dem Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Sie ist schwierig ausnutzbar. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 3.0.0 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als 94143a4299e386f33bf582139cd4702571d93bde bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-4303|2024-08-03T17:23:10.457Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 08:44:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
