<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for unspecified -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/unspecified/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for unspecified -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:23:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2591|2024-08-05T14:02:06.992Z -- unspecified -- 389-ds-base
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2591</link>
      <description>389-ds-base before version 1.3.6 is vulnerable to an improperly NULL terminated array in the uniqueness_entry_to_config() function in the "attribute uniqueness" plugin of 389 Directory Server. An authenticated, or possibly unauthenticated, attacker could use this flaw to force an out-of-bound heap memory read, possibly triggering a crash of the LDAP service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2591|2024-08-05T14:02:06.992Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1115|2024-08-05T03:51:48.772Z -- unspecified -- postgresql
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1115</link>
      <description>postgresql before versions 10.4, 9.6.9 is vulnerable in the adminpack extension, the pg_catalog.pg_logfile_rotate() function doesn't follow the same ACLs than pg_rorate_logfile. If the adminpack is added to a database, an attacker able to connect to it could exploit this to force log rotation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1115|2024-08-05T03:51:48.772Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-25065|2024-08-05T03:00:19.086Z -- unspecified -- opennetadmin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25065</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in OpenNetAdmin 18.1.1. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to privilege escalation. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-25065|2024-08-05T03:00:19.086Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 13:10:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2606|2024-08-05T14:02:06.482Z -- unspecified -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2606</link>
      <description>Jenkins before versions 2.44, 2.32.2 is vulnerable to an information exposure in the internal API that allows access to item names that should not be visible (SECURITY-380). This only affects anonymous users (other users legitimately have access) that were able to get a list of items via an UnprotectedRootAction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2606|2024-08-05T14:02:06.482Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20095|2024-08-05T21:45:25.431Z -- unspecified -- simple%20ads%20manager%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20095</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Simple Ads Manager Plugin. This vulnerability affects unknown code. The manipulation leads to code injection. The attack can be initiated remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20095|2024-08-05T21:45:25.431Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 06:45:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-25041|2024-08-05T12:26:39.614Z -- unspecified -- utorrent
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25041</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in uTorrent. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component JSON RPC Server. The manipulation leads to privilege escalation. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-25041|2024-08-05T12:26:39.614Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 04:45:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20099|2024-08-05T21:45:25.446Z -- unspecified -- analytics%20stats%20counter%20statistics%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20099</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Analytics Stats Counter Statistics Plugin 1.2.2.5 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing. The manipulation leads to code injection. The attack may be initiated remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20099|2024-08-05T21:45:25.446Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 18:11:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-25042|2024-08-05T12:26:39.588Z -- unspecified -- utorrent
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25042</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in uTorrent. This affects an unknown part. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-25042|2024-08-05T12:26:39.588Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 04:45:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20052|2024-08-05T21:45:25.243Z -- unspecified -- python
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20052</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Python 2.7.13. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component pgAdmin4. The manipulation leads to uncontrolled search path. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20052|2024-08-05T21:45:25.243Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 06:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20129|2024-08-05T21:45:25.971Z -- unspecified -- logostore
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20129</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in LogoStore. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /LogoStore/search.php. The manipulation of the argument query with the input test' UNION ALL SELECT CONCAT(CONCAT('qqkkq','VnPVWVaYxljWqGpLLbEIyPIHBjjjjASQTnaqfKaV'),'qvvpq'),NULL,NULL,NULL,NULL,NULL,NULL,NULL,NULL,NULL,NULL,NULL,NULL-- oCrh&amp;search= leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20129|2024-08-05T21:45:25.971Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 06:55:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20032|2024-08-05T21:45:25.092Z -- unspecified -- phplist
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20032</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPList 3.2.6. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Subscription. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 3.3.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20032|2024-08-05T21:45:25.092Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 09:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12196|2024-08-05T18:28:16.713Z -- unspecified -- undertow
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12196</link>
      <description>undertow before versions 1.4.18.SP1, 2.0.2.Final, 1.4.24.Final was found vulnerable when using Digest authentication, the server does not ensure that the value of URI in the Authorization header matches the URI in HTTP request line. This allows the attacker to cause a MITM attack and access the desired content on the server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12196|2024-08-05T18:28:16.713Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20075|2024-08-05T21:45:25.279Z -- unspecified -- hindu%20matrimonial%20script
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20075</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Hindu Matrimonial Script. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/payment.php. The manipulation leads to improper privilege management. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20075|2024-08-05T21:45:25.279Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 06:05:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20090|2024-08-05T21:45:25.259Z -- unspecified -- global%20content%20blocks%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20090</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Global Content Blocks Plugin 2.1.5. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20090|2024-08-05T21:45:25.259Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 04:20:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20100|2024-08-05T21:45:25.647Z -- unspecified -- air%20transfer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20100</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Air Transfer 1.0.14/1.2.1. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to basic cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20100|2024-08-05T21:45:25.647Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 13:25:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20091|2024-08-05T21:45:25.449Z -- unspecified -- file%20manager%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20091</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in File Manager Plugin 3.0.1. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20091|2024-08-05T21:45:25.449Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 04:20:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20078|2024-08-05T21:45:25.423Z -- unspecified -- hindu%20matrimonial%20script
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20078</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Hindu Matrimonial Script. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/featured.php. The manipulation leads to improper privilege management. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20078|2024-08-05T21:45:25.423Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 06:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20125|2024-08-05T21:45:25.974Z -- unspecified -- online%20hotel%20booking%20system%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20125</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Online Hotel Booking System Pro 1.2. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /roomtype-details.php. The manipulation of the argument tid leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20125|2024-08-05T21:45:25.974Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 05:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20124|2024-08-05T21:45:26.154Z -- unspecified -- online%20hotel%20booking%20system%20pro%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20124</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Online Hotel Booking System Pro Plugin 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /front/roomtype-details.php. The manipulation of the argument tid leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20124|2024-08-05T21:45:26.154Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 05:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-25066|2024-08-05T03:00:18.931Z -- unspecified -- ajenti
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25066</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in ajenti 2.1.31 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component API. The manipulation leads to privilege escalation. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 2.1.32 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is 7aa146b724e0e20cfee2c71ca78fafbf53a8767c. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-25066|2024-08-05T03:00:18.931Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 13:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20089|2024-08-05T21:45:25.272Z -- unspecified -- gwolle%20guestbook%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20089</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Gwolle Guestbook Plugin 1.7.4. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing. The manipulation leads to basic cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20089|2024-08-05T21:45:25.272Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 04:20:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20126|2024-08-05T21:45:25.980Z -- unspecified -- kb%20affiliate%20referral%20script
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20126</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in KB Affiliate Referral Script 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument username/password with the input 'or''=' leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20126|2024-08-05T21:45:25.980Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 17:55:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20018|2024-08-05T21:45:24.555Z -- unspecified -- xampp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20018</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in XAMPP 7.1.1-0-VC14. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the component Installer. The manipulation leads to privilege escalation. It is possible to launch the attack remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20018|2024-08-05T21:45:24.555Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 22:35:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1079|2024-08-05T03:51:48.682Z -- unspecified -- pcs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1079</link>
      <description>pcs before version 0.9.164 and 0.10 is vulnerable to a privilege escalation via authorized user malicious REST call. The REST interface of the pcsd service did not properly sanitize the file name from the /remote/put_file query. If the /etc/booth directory exists, an authenticated attacker with write permissions could create or overwrite arbitrary files with arbitrary data outside of the /etc/booth directory, in the context of the pcsd process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1079|2024-08-05T03:51:48.682Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20029|2024-08-05T21:45:24.944Z -- unspecified -- phplist
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20029</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPList 3.2.6 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /lists/index.php of the component Edit Subscription. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 3.3.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20029|2024-08-05T21:45:24.944Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 09:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20087|2024-08-05T21:45:25.448Z -- unspecified -- alpine%20phototile%20for%20instagram%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20087</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Alpine PhotoTile for Instagram Plugin 1.2.7.7. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to basic cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20087|2024-08-05T21:45:25.448Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 04:20:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20092|2024-08-05T21:45:25.629Z -- unspecified -- google%20analytics%20dashboard%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20092</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Google Analytics Dashboard Plugin 2.1.1. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to basic cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20092|2024-08-05T21:45:25.629Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 06:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20108|2024-08-05T21:45:26.018Z -- unspecified -- easy%20table%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20108</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Easy Table Plugin 1.6. This affects an unknown part of the file /wordpress/wp-admin/options-general.php. The manipulation with the input "&gt;&lt;script&gt;alert(1)&lt;/script&gt; leads to basic cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20108|2024-08-05T21:45:26.018Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 06:55:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20067|2024-08-05T21:45:25.392Z -- unspecified -- hindu%20matrimonial%20script
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20067</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Hindu Matrimonial Script. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/. The manipulation of the argument username/password with the input 'or''=' leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20067|2024-08-05T21:45:25.392Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 06:05:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20080|2024-08-05T21:45:25.196Z -- unspecified -- hindu%20matrimonial%20script
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20080</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Hindu Matrimonial Script. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/googleads.php. The manipulation leads to improper privilege management. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20080|2024-08-05T21:45:25.196Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 06:06:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2601|2024-08-05T14:02:06.982Z -- unspecified -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2601</link>
      <description>Jenkins before versions 2.44, 2.32.2 is vulnerable to a persisted cross-site scripting in parameter names and descriptions (SECURITY-353). Users with the permission to configure jobs were able to inject JavaScript into parameter names and descriptions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2601|2024-08-05T14:02:06.982Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20031|2024-08-05T21:45:24.994Z -- unspecified -- phplist
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20031</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPList 3.2.6. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality. The manipulation of the argument sortby with the input password leads to information disclosure. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 3.3.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20031|2024-08-05T21:45:24.994Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 09:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20072|2024-08-05T21:45:25.247Z -- unspecified -- hindu%20matrimonial%20script
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20072</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Hindu Matrimonial Script. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/generalsettings.php. The manipulation leads to improper privilege management. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20072|2024-08-05T21:45:25.247Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 06:05:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20094|2024-08-05T21:45:25.433Z -- unspecified -- newstatpress%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20094</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in NewStatPress Plugin 1.2.4. This issue affects some unknown processing. The manipulation leads to basic cross site scripting (Persistent). The attack may be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 1.2.5 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20094|2024-08-05T21:45:25.433Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 06:45:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20097|2024-08-05T21:45:25.407Z -- unspecified -- wp-filebase%20download%20manager%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20097</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in WP-Filebase Download Manager Plugin 3.4.4. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to basic cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20097|2024-08-05T21:45:25.407Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 06:45:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1130|2024-08-05T03:51:48.970Z -- unspecified -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1130</link>
      <description>Linux kernel before version 4.16-rc7 is vulnerable to a null pointer dereference in dccp_write_xmit() function in net/dccp/output.c in that allows a local user to cause a denial of service by a number of certain crafted system calls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1130|2024-08-05T03:51:48.970Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20026|2024-08-05T21:45:25.353Z -- unspecified -- humhub
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20026</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in HumHub up to 1.0.1 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting (Reflected). The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 1.1.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20026|2024-08-05T21:45:25.353Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 22:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20128|2024-08-05T21:45:26.204Z -- unspecified -- kb%20messages%20php%20script
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20128</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in KB Messages PHP Script 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality. The manipulation of the argument username/password with the input 'or''=' leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20128|2024-08-05T21:45:26.204Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 17:55:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20073|2024-08-05T21:45:25.233Z -- unspecified -- hindu%20matrimonial%20script
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20073</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Hindu Matrimonial Script and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/cms.php. The manipulation leads to improper privilege management. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20073|2024-08-05T21:45:25.233Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 06:05:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20098|2024-08-05T21:45:25.704Z -- unspecified -- admin%20custom%20login%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20098</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Admin Custom Login Plugin 2.4.5.2. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function. The manipulation leads to basic cross site scripting (Persistent). It is possible to launch the attack remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20098|2024-08-05T21:45:25.704Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 18:11:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-8021|2024-08-05T06:46:11.477Z -- unspecified -- superset
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-8021</link>
      <description>Versions of Superset prior to 0.23 used an unsafe load method from the pickle library to deserialize data leading to possible remote code execution. Note Superset 0.23 was released prior to any Superset release under the Apache Software Foundation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-8021|2024-08-05T06:46:11.477Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1089|2024-08-05T03:51:48.500Z -- unspecified -- 389-ds-base
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1089</link>
      <description>389-ds-base before versions 1.4.0.9, 1.3.8.1, 1.3.6.15 did not properly handle long search filters with characters needing escapes, possibly leading to buffer overflows. A remote, unauthenticated attacker could potentially use this flaw to make ns-slapd crash via a specially crafted LDAP request, thus resulting in denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1089|2024-08-05T03:51:48.500Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20027|2024-08-05T21:45:25.262Z -- unspecified -- humhub
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20027</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in HumHub up to 1.0.1 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting (DOM). The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 1.1.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20027|2024-08-05T21:45:25.262Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 22:36:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20079|2024-08-05T21:45:25.219Z -- unspecified -- hindu%20matrimonial%20script
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20079</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Hindu Matrimonial Script. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/photo.php. The manipulation leads to improper privilege management. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20079|2024-08-05T21:45:25.219Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 06:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20101|2024-08-05T21:45:25.985Z -- unspecified -- projectsend
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20101</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in ProjectSend r754. This affects an unknown part of the file process.php?do=zip_download. The manipulation of the argument client/file leads to information disclosure. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20101|2024-08-05T21:45:25.985Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 13:25:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2592|2024-08-05T14:02:06.483Z -- unspecified -- python-oslo-middleware
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2592</link>
      <description>python-oslo-middleware before versions 3.8.1, 3.19.1, 3.23.1 is vulnerable to an information disclosure. Software using the CatchError class could include sensitive values in a traceback's error message. System users could exploit this flaw to obtain sensitive information from OpenStack component error logs (for example, keystone tokens).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2592|2024-08-05T14:02:06.483Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20077|2024-08-05T21:45:25.661Z -- unspecified -- hindu%20matrimonial%20script
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20077</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Hindu Matrimonial Script. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/success_story.php. The manipulation leads to improper privilege management. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20077|2024-08-05T21:45:25.661Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 06:05:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20066|2024-08-05T21:45:25.226Z -- unspecified -- adminer%20login
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20066</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Adminer Login 1.4.4 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20066|2024-08-05T21:45:25.226Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 20:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20070|2024-08-05T21:45:24.960Z -- unspecified -- hindu%20matrimonial%20script
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20070</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Hindu Matrimonial Script. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/communitymanagement.php. The manipulation leads to improper privilege management. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20070|2024-08-05T21:45:24.960Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 06:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20088|2024-08-05T21:45:25.760Z -- unspecified -- atahualpa%20theme
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20088</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Atahualpa Theme. Affected is an unknown function. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20088|2024-08-05T21:45:25.760Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 04:20:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20085|2024-08-05T21:45:25.511Z -- unspecified -- atahualpa%20theme
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20085</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Atahualpa Theme and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to basic cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20085|2024-08-05T21:45:25.511Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 04:20:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20127|2024-08-05T21:45:25.951Z -- unspecified -- kb%20login%20authentication%20script
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20127</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in KB Login Authentication Script 1.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality. The manipulation of the argument username/password with the input 'or''=' leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20127|2024-08-05T21:45:25.951Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 17:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20105|2024-08-05T21:45:25.909Z -- unspecified -- simplessus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20105</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Simplessus 3.7.7. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing. The manipulation of the argument path with the input ..%2f..%2f..%2f..%2f..%2f..%2f..%2f..%2f..%2f..%2f..%2f..%2f..%2f..%2f..%2f..%2fetc%2fpasswd leads to path traversal. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 3.8.3 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20105|2024-08-05T21:45:25.909Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 06:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20069|2024-08-05T21:45:25.176Z -- unspecified -- hindu%20matrimonial%20script
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20069</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Hindu Matrimonial Script. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/countrymanagement.php. The manipulation leads to improper privilege management. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20069|2024-08-05T21:45:25.176Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 06:05:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-25044|2024-08-05T12:26:39.665Z -- unspecified -- utorrent
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25044</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in uTorrent. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Guest Account. The manipulation leads to privilege escalation. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-25044|2024-08-05T12:26:39.665Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 04:45:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20103|2024-08-05T21:45:25.774Z -- unspecified -- kama%20click%20counter%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20103</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Kama Click Counter Plugin up to 3.4.8. This affects an unknown part of the file wp-admin/admin.php. The manipulation of the argument order_by/order with the input ASC%2c(select*from(select(sleep(2)))a) leads to sql injection (Blind). It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 3.4.9 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20103|2024-08-05T21:45:25.774Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 21:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1112|2024-08-05T03:51:48.898Z -- unspecified -- glusterfs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1112</link>
      <description>glusterfs server before versions 3.10.12, 4.0.2 is vulnerable when using 'auth.allow' option which allows any unauthenticated gluster client to connect from any network to mount gluster storage volumes. NOTE: this vulnerability exists because of a CVE-2018-1088 regression.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1112|2024-08-05T03:51:48.898Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2594|2024-08-05T14:02:06.485Z -- unspecified -- hawtio
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2594</link>
      <description>hawtio before versions 2.0-beta-1, 2.0-beta-2 2.0-m1, 2.0-m2, 2.0-m3, and 1.5 is vulnerable to a path traversal that leads to a NullPointerException with a full stacktrace. An attacker could use this flaw to gather undisclosed information from within hawtio's root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2594|2024-08-05T14:02:06.485Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-25078|2024-08-05T03:00:18.888Z -- unspecified -- pacparser
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25078</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in pacparser up to 1.3.x. Affected by this vulnerability is the function pacparser_find_proxy of the file src/pacparser.c. The manipulation of the argument url leads to buffer overflow. Attacking locally is a requirement. Upgrading to version 1.4.0 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is 853e8f45607cb07b877ffd270c63dbcdd5201ad9. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-215443.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-25078|2024-08-05T03:00:18.888Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20096|2024-08-05T21:45:25.450Z -- unspecified -- wp-spamfree%20anti-spam%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20096</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in WP-SpamFree Anti-Spam Plugin 2.1.1.4. This affects an unknown part. The manipulation leads to basic cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20096|2024-08-05T21:45:25.450Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 06:45:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20017|2024-08-05T21:45:24.591Z -- unspecified -- the%20next%20generation%20of%20genealogy%20sitebuilding
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20017</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in The Next Generation of Genealogy Sitebuilding up to 11.1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /timeline2.php. The manipulation of the argument primaryID leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 11.1.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20017|2024-08-05T21:45:24.591Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 05:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20093|2024-08-05T21:45:25.432Z -- unspecified -- download%20manager%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20093</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Download Manager Plugin 2.8.99. Affected is an unknown function. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20093|2024-08-05T21:45:25.432Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 06:45:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20034|2024-08-05T21:45:24.640Z -- unspecified -- phplist
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20034</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in PHPList 3.2.6. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /lists/admin/ of the component List Name. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting (Persistent). The attack can be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 3.3.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20034|2024-08-05T21:45:24.640Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 09:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20068|2024-08-05T21:45:25.249Z -- unspecified -- hindu%20matrimonial%20script
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20068</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Hindu Matrimonial Script. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/usermanagement.php. The manipulation leads to improper privilege management. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20068|2024-08-05T21:45:25.249Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 06:05:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20035|2024-08-05T21:45:24.543Z -- unspecified -- phplist
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20035</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in PHPList 3.2.6. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /lists/admin/ of the component Subscribe. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting (Persistent). The attack may be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 3.3.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20035|2024-08-05T21:45:24.543Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 09:30:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1084|2024-08-05T03:51:48.451Z -- unspecified -- corosync
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1084</link>
      <description>corosync before version 2.4.4 is vulnerable to an integer overflow in exec/totemcrypto.c.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1084|2024-08-05T03:51:48.451Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20033|2024-08-05T21:45:24.961Z -- unspecified -- phplist
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20033</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in PHPList 3.2.6. This affects an unknown part of the file /lists/admin/. The manipulation of the argument page with the input send\'\";&gt;&lt;script&gt;alert(8)&lt;/script&gt; leads to cross site scripting (Reflected). It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 3.3.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20033|2024-08-05T21:45:24.961Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 09:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20104|2024-08-05T21:45:25.964Z -- unspecified -- simplessus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20104</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Simplessus 3.7.7. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Cookie Handler. The manipulation of the argument UWA_SID leads to sql injection (Time). The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 3.8.3 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20104|2024-08-05T21:45:25.964Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 06:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20086|2024-08-05T21:45:25.266Z -- unspecified -- vaultpress%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20086</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in VaultPress Plugin 1.8.4. This affects an unknown part. The manipulation leads to code injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20086|2024-08-05T21:45:25.266Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 04:20:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20074|2024-08-05T21:45:25.260Z -- unspecified -- hindu%20matrimonial%20script
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20074</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Hindu Matrimonial Script and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/newsletter1.php. The manipulation leads to improper privilege management. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20074|2024-08-05T21:45:25.260Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 06:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1074|2024-08-05T03:51:48.452Z -- unspecified -- ovirt-engine
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1074</link>
      <description>ovirt-engine API and administration web portal before versions 4.2.2.5, 4.1.11.2 is vulnerable to an exposure of Power Management credentials, including cleartext passwords to Host Administrators. A Host Administrator could use this flaw to gain access to the power management systems of hosts they control.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1074|2024-08-05T03:51:48.452Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20071|2024-08-05T21:45:25.254Z -- unspecified -- hindu%20matrimonial%20script
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20071</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Hindu Matrimonial Script. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/renewaldue.php. The manipulation leads to improper privilege management. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20071|2024-08-05T21:45:25.254Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 06:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20076|2024-08-05T21:45:25.416Z -- unspecified -- hindu%20matrimonial%20script
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20076</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Hindu Matrimonial Script. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/searchview.php. The manipulation leads to improper privilege management. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20076|2024-08-05T21:45:25.416Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 06:05:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20102|2024-08-05T21:45:25.776Z -- unspecified -- album%20lock
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20102</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Album Lock 4.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /getImage. The manipulation of the argument filePaht leads to path traversal. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20102|2024-08-05T21:45:25.776Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 13:25:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20123|2024-08-05T21:45:25.965Z -- unspecified -- viscosity
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20123</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Viscosity 1.6.7. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the component DLL Handler. The manipulation leads to untrusted search path. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 1.6.8 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20123|2024-08-05T21:45:25.965Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 05:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20036|2024-08-05T21:45:25.003Z -- unspecified -- phplist
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20036</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in PHPList 3.2.6. Affected is an unknown function of the file /lists/admin/ of the component Bounce Rule. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting (Persistent). It is possible to launch the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 3.3.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20036|2024-08-05T21:45:25.003Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 09:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-25043|2024-08-05T12:26:39.629Z -- unspecified -- utorrent
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25043</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in uTorrent. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component PRNG. The manipulation leads to weak authentication. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-25043|2024-08-05T12:26:39.629Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 04:45:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20081|2024-08-05T21:45:25.256Z -- unspecified -- hindu%20matrimonial%20script
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20081</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Hindu Matrimonial Script. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/reports.php. The manipulation leads to improper privilege management. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20081|2024-08-05T21:45:25.256Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 06:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20028|2024-08-05T21:45:24.570Z -- unspecified -- humhub
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20028</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in HumHub 0.20.1/1.0.0-beta.3. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part. The manipulation leads to privilege escalation. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 1.0.0 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20028|2024-08-05T21:45:24.570Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 22:36:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2611|2024-08-05T14:02:06.500Z -- unspecified -- jenkins
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2611</link>
      <description>Jenkins before versions 2.44, 2.32.2 is vulnerable to an insufficient permission check for periodic processes (SECURITY-389). The URLs /workspaceCleanup and /fingerprintCleanup did not perform permission checks, allowing users with read access to Jenkins to trigger these background processes (that are otherwise performed daily), possibly causing additional load on Jenkins master and agents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2611|2024-08-05T14:02:06.500Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20030|2024-08-05T21:45:25.021Z -- unspecified -- phplist
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20030</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPList 3.2.6. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /lists/admin/ of the component Sending Campain. The manipulation leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 3.3.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20030|2024-08-05T21:45:25.021Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 09:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
