<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for unspecified -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/unspecified/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for unspecified -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 21:21:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10282|2024-08-04T10:58:39.958Z -- unspecified -- mavlink
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10282</link>
      <description>The Micro Air Vehicle Link (MAVLink) protocol presents no authentication mechanism on its version 1.0 (nor authorization) whichs leads to a variety of attacks including identity spoofing, unauthorized access, PITM attacks and more. According to literature, version 2.0 optionally allows for package signing which mitigates this flaw. Another source mentions that MAVLink 2.0 only provides a simple authentication system based on HMAC. This implies that the flying system overall should add the same symmetric key into all devices of network. If not the case, this may cause a security issue, that if one of the devices and its symmetric key are compromised, the whole authentication system is not reliable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10282|2024-08-04T10:58:39.958Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36623|2024-08-04T17:30:08.422Z -- unspecified -- pengu
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36623</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Pengu. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function runApp of the file src/index.js. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The name of the patch is aea66f12b8cdfc3c8c50ad6a9c89d8307e9d0a91. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-216475.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36623|2024-08-04T17:30:08.422Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36542|2024-08-04T17:30:08.147Z -- unspecified -- demokratian
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36542</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Demokratian. This affects an unknown part of the file install/install3.php. The manipulation leads to privilege escalation. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36542|2024-08-04T17:30:08.147Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 19:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36540|2024-08-04T17:30:08.049Z -- unspecified -- neetai%20tech
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36540</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Neetai Tech. Affected is an unknown function of the file /product.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36540|2024-08-04T17:30:08.049Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 19:10:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36527|2024-08-04T17:30:08.371Z -- unspecified -- server%20status
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36527</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Server Status. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component HTTP Status/SMTP Status. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36527|2024-08-04T17:30:08.371Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 14:55:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36541|2024-08-04T17:30:08.321Z -- unspecified -- demokratian
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36541</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Demokratian. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file basicos_php/genera_select.php. The manipulation of the argument id_provincia with the input -1%20union%20all%20select%201,2,3,4,database() leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36541|2024-08-04T17:30:08.321Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 19:10:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36539|2024-08-04T17:30:08.102Z -- unspecified -- l%C3%B3gico%20y%20creativo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36539</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Lógico y Creativo 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36539|2024-08-04T17:30:08.102Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 19:10:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36525|2024-08-04T17:30:08.336Z -- unspecified -- linking
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36525</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Linking. This affects an unknown part of the component New Windows Macro. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36525|2024-08-04T17:30:08.336Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 14:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36528|2024-08-04T17:30:08.351Z -- unspecified -- platinum%20mobile
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36528</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Platinum Mobile 1.0.4.850. Affected is /MobileHandler.ashx which leads to broken access control. The attack requires authentication. Upgrading to version 1.0.4.851 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36528|2024-08-04T17:30:08.351Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 14:55:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36536|2024-08-04T17:30:08.170Z -- unspecified -- brandbugle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36536</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Brandbugle. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /main.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36536|2024-08-04T17:30:08.170Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 19:10:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36619|2024-08-04T17:30:08.432Z -- unspecified -- multimon-ng
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36619</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in multimon-ng. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function add_ch of the file demod_flex.c. The manipulation of the argument ch leads to format string. Upgrading to version 1.2.0 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is e5a51c508ef952e81a6da25b43034dd1ed023c07. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-216269 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36619|2024-08-04T17:30:08.432Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36526|2024-08-04T17:30:08.095Z -- unspecified -- countdown%20timer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36526</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Countdown Timer. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Macro Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36526|2024-08-04T17:30:08.095Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 14:55:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10281|2024-08-04T10:58:40.402Z -- unspecified -- mavlink
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10281</link>
      <description>This vulnerability applies to the Micro Air Vehicle Link (MAVLink) protocol and allows a remote attacker to gain access to sensitive information provided it has access to the communication medium. MAVLink is a header-based protocol that does not perform encryption to improve transfer (and reception speed) and efficiency by design. The increasing popularity of the protocol (used accross different autopilots) has led to its use in wired and wireless mediums through insecure communication channels exposing sensitive information to a remote attacker with ability to intercept network traffic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10281|2024-08-04T10:58:40.402Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3879|2024-08-04T19:19:18.612Z -- unspecified -- ovirt-engine
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3879</link>
      <description>It was discovered that in the ovirt's REST API before version 4.3.2.1, RemoveDiskCommand is triggered as an internal command, meaning the permission validation that should be performed against the calling user is skipped. A user with low privileges (eg Basic Operations) could exploit this flaw to delete disks attached to guests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3879|2024-08-04T19:19:18.612Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 18:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36523|2024-08-04T17:30:08.328Z -- unspecified -- plantuml
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36523</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PlantUML 6.43. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the component Database Information Macro. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36523|2024-08-04T17:30:08.328Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 14:55:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36524|2024-08-04T17:30:08.129Z -- unspecified -- refined%20toolkit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36524</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Refined Toolkit. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component UI-Image/UI-Button. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36524|2024-08-04T17:30:08.129Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 14:55:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-36535|2024-08-04T17:30:08.355Z -- unspecified -- minmax
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36535</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in MINMAX. This affects an unknown part of the file /newsDia.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-36535|2024-08-04T17:30:08.355Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 19:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6149|2024-08-04T20:16:23.839Z -- unspecified -- unspecified
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6149</link>
      <description>An unquoted search path vulnerability was identified in Lenovo Dynamic Power Reduction Utility prior to version 2.2.2.0 that could allow a malicious user with local access to execute code with administrative privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6149|2024-08-04T20:16:23.839Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
