<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for unspecified -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/unspecified/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for unspecified -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:25:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-9587|2024-08-06T02:59:02.537Z -- unspecified -- ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-9587</link>
      <description>Ansible before versions 2.1.4, 2.2.1 is vulnerable to an improper input validation in Ansible's handling of data sent from client systems. An attacker with control over a client system being managed by Ansible and the ability to send facts back to the Ansible server could use this flaw to execute arbitrary code on the Ansible server using the Ansible server privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-9587|2024-08-06T02:59:02.537Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-9593|2024-08-06T02:59:03.223Z -- unspecified -- foreman-debug
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-9593</link>
      <description>foreman-debug before version 1.15.0 is vulnerable to a flaw in foreman-debug's logging. An attacker with access to the foreman log file would be able to view passwords, allowing them to access those systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-9593|2024-08-06T02:59:03.223Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-15004|2024-08-06T03:47:34.859Z -- unspecified -- infinitewp%20client%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-15004</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in InfiniteWP Client Plugin 1.5.1.3/1.6.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to injection. The attack can be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 1.6.1.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-15004|2024-08-06T03:47:34.859Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2022 06:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-15002|2024-08-06T03:47:34.624Z -- unspecified -- monyog%20ultimate
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-15002</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in MONyog Ultimate 6.63. This affects an unknown part of the component Cookie Handler. The manipulation of the argument HasServerEdit/IsAdmin leads to privilege escalation. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-15002|2024-08-06T03:47:34.624Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 06:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-9599|2024-08-06T02:59:03.011Z -- unspecified -- puppet-tripleo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-9599</link>
      <description>puppet-tripleo before versions 5.5.0, 6.2.0 is vulnerable to an access-control flaw in the IPtables rules management, which allowed the creation of TCP/UDP rules with empty port values. If SSL is enabled, a malicious user could use these open ports to gain access to unauthorized resources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-9599|2024-08-06T02:59:03.011Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-9601|2024-08-06T02:59:02.237Z -- unspecified -- ghostscript
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-9601</link>
      <description>ghostscript before version 9.21 is vulnerable to a heap based buffer overflow that was found in the ghostscript jbig2_decode_gray_scale_image function which is used to decode halftone segments in a JBIG2 image. A document (PostScript or PDF) with an embedded, specially crafted, jbig2 image could trigger a segmentation fault in ghostscript.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-9601|2024-08-06T02:59:02.237Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-9602|2024-08-06T02:59:03.165Z -- unspecified -- qemu
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-9602</link>
      <description>Qemu before version 2.9 is vulnerable to an improper link following when built with the VirtFS. A privileged user inside guest could use this flaw to access host file system beyond the shared folder and potentially escalating their privileges on a host.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-9602|2024-08-06T02:59:03.165Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-9594|2024-08-06T02:59:02.701Z -- unspecified -- curl
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-9594</link>
      <description>curl before version 7.52.1 is vulnerable to an uninitialized random in libcurl's internal function that returns a good 32bit random value.  Having a weak or virtually non-existent random value makes the operations that use it vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-9594|2024-08-06T02:59:02.701Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-9590|2024-08-06T02:59:02.247Z -- unspecified -- puppet-swift
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-9590</link>
      <description>puppet-swift before versions 8.2.1, 9.4.4 is vulnerable to an information-disclosure in Red Hat OpenStack Platform director's installation of Object Storage (swift). During installation, the Puppet script responsible for deploying the service incorrectly removes and recreates the proxy-server.conf file with world-readable permissions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-9590|2024-08-06T02:59:02.247Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-9592|2024-08-06T02:59:02.472Z -- unspecified -- openshift
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-9592</link>
      <description>openshift before versions 3.3.1.11, 3.2.1.23, 3.4 is vulnerable to a flaw when a volume fails to detach, which causes the delete operation to fail with 'VolumeInUse' error. Since the delete operation is retried every 30 seconds for each volume, this could lead to a denial of service attack as the number of API requests being sent to the cloud-provider exceeds the API's rate-limit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-9592|2024-08-06T02:59:02.472Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
