<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for unspecified -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/unspecified/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for unspecified -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 08:23:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4281|2024-08-03T01:34:50.060Z -- unspecified -- facepay
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4281</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Facepay 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /face-recognition-php/facepay-master/camera.php. The manipulation of the argument userId leads to authorization bypass. The attack can be launched remotely. The identifier VDB-214789 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4281|2024-08-03T01:34:50.060Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4493|2024-08-03T01:41:45.651Z -- unspecified -- scifio
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4493</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in scifio. Affected by this vulnerability is the function downloadAndUnpackResource of the file src/test/java/io/scif/util/DefaultSampleFilesService.java of the component ZIP File Handler. The manipulation leads to path traversal. The attack can be launched remotely. The name of the patch is fcb0dbca0ec72b22fe0c9ddc8abc9cb188a0ff31. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-215803.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4493|2024-08-03T01:41:45.651Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3966|2024-08-03T01:27:53.619Z -- unspecified -- ultimate%20member%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3966</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Ultimate Member Plugin up to 2.5.0. This issue affects the function load_template of the file includes/core/class-shortcodes.php of the component Template Handler. The manipulation of the argument tpl leads to pathname traversal. The attack may be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 2.5.1 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is e1bc94c1100f02a129721ba4be5fbc44c3d78ec4. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-213545 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3966|2024-08-03T01:27:53.619Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4011|2024-08-03T01:27:54.091Z -- unspecified -- simple%20history%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4011</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Simple History Plugin. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Header Handler. The manipulation of the argument X-Forwarded-For leads to improper output neutralization for logs. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-213785 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4011|2024-08-03T01:27:54.091Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3734|2024-08-03T01:20:57.545Z -- unspecified -- redis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3734</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in a port or fork of Redis. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code in the library C:/Program Files/Redis/dbghelp.dll. The manipulation leads to uncontrolled search path. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-212416. NOTE: The official Redis release is not affected. This issue might affect an unofficial fork or port on Windows only.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3734|2024-08-03T01:20:57.545Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4247|2024-08-03T01:34:49.838Z -- unspecified -- movie%20ticket%20booking%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4247</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Movie Ticket Booking System. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file booking.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-214624.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4247|2024-08-03T01:34:49.838Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3978|2024-08-03T01:27:54.153Z -- unspecified -- nodebb
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3978</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in NodeBB up to 2.5.7. This affects an unknown part of the file /register/abort. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 2.5.8 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is 2f9d8c350e54543f608d3d4c8e1a49bbb6cdea38. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-213555.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3978|2024-08-03T01:27:54.153Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-1837|2024-08-03T00:17:00.408Z -- unspecified -- home%20clean%20services%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1837</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Home Clean Services Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is register.php?link=registerand. The manipulation with the input &lt;?php phpinfo();?&gt; leads to code execution. The attack may be launched remotely but demands an authentication. Exploit details have been disclosed to the public.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-1837|2024-08-03T00:17:00.408Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 05:25:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4322|2024-08-03T01:34:50.144Z -- unspecified -- maku-boot
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4322</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in maku-boot up to 2.2.0. This affects the function doExecute of the file AbstractScheduleJob.java of the component Scheduled Task Handler. The manipulation leads to injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The name of the patch is 446eb7294332efca2bfd791bc37281cedac0d0ff. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier VDB-215013 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4322|2024-08-03T01:34:50.144Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-1590|2024-08-03T00:10:03.659Z -- unspecified -- bludit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1590</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Bludit 3.13.1. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects the endpoint /admin/new-content of the New Content module. The manipulation of the argument content with the input &lt;script&gt;alert(1)&lt;/script&gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely but requires an authentication. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-1590|2024-08-03T00:10:03.659Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 09:20:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-1838|2024-08-03T00:17:00.869Z -- unspecified -- home%20clean%20services%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1838</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Home Clean Services Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of admin/login.php. The manipulation of the argument username with the input admin%'/**/AND/**/(SELECT/**/5383/**/FROM/**/(SELECT(SLEEP(5)))JPeh)/**/AND/**/'frfq%'='frfq leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely but it requires authentication. Exploit details have been disclosed to the public.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-1838|2024-08-03T00:17:00.869Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 05:25:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3970|2024-08-03T01:27:53.968Z -- unspecified -- libtiff
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3970</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in LibTIFF. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function TIFFReadRGBATileExt of the file libtiff/tif_getimage.c. The manipulation leads to integer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The name of the patch is 227500897dfb07fb7d27f7aa570050e62617e3be. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier VDB-213549 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3970|2024-08-03T01:27:53.968Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4015|2024-08-03T01:27:54.058Z -- unspecified -- sports%20club%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4015</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Sports Club Management System 119. This affects an unknown part of the file admin/make_payments.php. The manipulation of the argument m_id/plan leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-213789 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4015|2024-08-03T01:27:54.058Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4248|2024-08-03T01:34:49.977Z -- unspecified -- movie%20ticket%20booking%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4248</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Movie Ticket Booking System. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file editBooking.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-214625 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4248|2024-08-03T01:34:49.977Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3957|2024-08-03T01:27:53.060Z -- unspecified -- gpac
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3957</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in GPAC. Affected by this vulnerability is the function svg_parse_preserveaspectratio of the file scenegraph/svg_attributes.c of the component SVG Parser. The manipulation leads to memory leak. The attack can be launched remotely. The name of the patch is 2191e66aa7df750e8ef01781b1930bea87b713bb. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-213463.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3957|2024-08-03T01:27:53.060Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4456|2024-08-03T01:41:44.710Z -- unspecified -- falling-fruit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4456</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in falling-fruit and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The name of the patch is 15adb8e1ea1f1c3e3d152fc266071f621ef0c621. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. VDB-215446 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4456|2024-08-03T01:41:44.710Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4202|2024-08-03T01:34:49.693Z -- unspecified -- gpac
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4202</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in GPAC 2.1-DEV-rev490-g68064e101-master. Affected is the function lsr_translate_coords of the file laser/lsr_dec.c. The manipulation leads to integer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The name of the patch is b3d821c4ae9ba62b3a194d9dcb5e99f17bd56908. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. VDB-214518 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4202|2024-08-03T01:34:49.693Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4582|2024-08-03T01:41:45.770Z -- unspecified -- starter-public-edition-4
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4582</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in starter-public-edition-4 up to 4.6.10. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 4.6.11 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is 2606983c20f6ea3430ac4b36b3d2e88aafef45da. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-216168.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4582|2024-08-03T01:41:45.770Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2647|2024-08-03T00:46:03.488Z -- unspecified -- jeecg-boot
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2647</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in jeecg-boot. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /api/. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-205594 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2647|2024-08-03T00:46:03.488Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 08:41:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4639|2024-08-03T01:48:39.657Z -- unspecified -- sslh
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4639</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in sslh. This issue affects the function hexdump of the file probe.c of the component Packet Dumping Handler. The manipulation of the argument msg_info leads to format string. The attack may be initiated remotely. The name of the patch is b19f8a6046b080e4c2e28354a58556bb26040c6f. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier VDB-216497 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4639|2024-08-03T01:48:39.657Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4641|2024-08-03T01:48:40.341Z -- unspecified -- pig-vector
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4641</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in pig-vector and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function LogisticRegression of the file src/main/java/org/apache/mahout/pig/LogisticRegression.java. The manipulation leads to insecure temporary file. The attack needs to be approached locally. The name of the patch is 1e7bd9fab5401a2df18d2eabd802adcf0dcf1f15. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-216500.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4641|2024-08-03T01:48:40.341Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23039|2024-08-03T03:28:42.973Z -- unspecified -- unspecified
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23039</link>
      <description>Linux PV device frontends vulnerable to attacks by backends T[his CNA information record relates to multiple CVEs; the text explains which aspects/vulnerabilities correspond to which CVE.] Several Linux PV device frontends are using the grant table interfaces for removing access rights of the backends in ways being subject to race conditions, resulting in potential data leaks, data corruption by malicious backends, and denial of service triggered by malicious backends: blkfront, netfront, scsifront and the gntalloc driver are testing whether a grant reference is still in use. If this is not the case, they assume that a following removal of the granted access will always succeed, which is not true in case the backend has mapped the granted page between those two operations. As a result the backend can keep access to the memory page of the guest no matter how the page will be used after the frontend I/O has finished. The xenbus driver has a similar problem, as it doesn't check the success of removing the granted access of a shared ring buffer. blkfront: CVE-2022-23036 netfront: CVE-2022-23037 scsifront: CVE-2022-23038 gntalloc: CVE-2022-23039 xenbus: CVE-2022-23040 blkfront, netfront, scsifront, usbfront, dmabuf, xenbus, 9p, kbdfront, and pvcalls are using a functionality to delay freeing a grant reference until it is no longer in use, but the freeing of the related data page is not synchronized with dropping the granted access. As a result the backend can keep access to the memory page even after it has been freed and then re-used for a different purpose. CVE-2022-23041 netfront will fail a BUG_ON() assertion if it fails to revoke access in the rx path. This will result in a Denial of Service (DoS) situation of the guest which can be triggered by the backend. CVE-2022-23042</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23039|2024-08-03T03:28:42.973Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 19:20:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3963|2024-08-03T01:27:54.131Z -- unspecified -- gnuboard5
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3963</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in gnuboard5. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file bbs/faq.php of the component FAQ Key ID Handler. The manipulation of the argument fm_id leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 5.5.8.2.1 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is ba062ca5b62809106d5a2f7df942ffcb44ecb5a9. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-213540.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3963|2024-08-03T01:27:54.131Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3965|2024-08-03T01:27:53.975Z -- unspecified -- ffmpeg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3965</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in ffmpeg. This vulnerability affects the function smc_encode_stream of the file libavcodec/smcenc.c of the component QuickTime Graphics Video Encoder. The manipulation of the argument y_size leads to out-of-bounds read. The attack can be initiated remotely. The name of the patch is 13c13109759090b7f7182480d075e13b36ed8edd. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-213544.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3965|2024-08-03T01:27:53.975Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4583|2024-08-03T01:41:45.872Z -- unspecified -- jlems
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4583</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in jLEMS. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function unpackJar of the file src/main/java/org/lemsml/jlems/io/util/JUtil.java. The manipulation leads to path traversal. The attack can be launched remotely. The name of the patch is 8c224637d7d561076364a9e3c2c375daeaf463dc. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier VDB-216169 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4583|2024-08-03T01:41:45.872Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3971|2024-08-03T01:27:53.979Z -- unspecified -- matrix-appservice-irc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3971</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in matrix-appservice-irc up to 0.35.1. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file src/datastore/postgres/PgDataStore.ts. The manipulation of the argument roomIds leads to sql injection. Upgrading to version 0.36.0 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is 179313a37f06b298150edba3e2b0e5a73c1415e7. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-213550 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3971|2024-08-03T01:27:53.979Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4275|2024-08-03T01:34:49.895Z -- unspecified -- house%20rental%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4275</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in House Rental System and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file search-property.php of the component POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument search_property leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-214771.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4275|2024-08-03T01:34:49.895Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2262|2024-08-03T00:32:09.552Z -- unspecified -- online%20hotel%20booking%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2262</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Online Hotel Booking System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file edit_all_room.php of the component Room Handler. The manipulation of the argument id with the input 2828%27%20AND%20(SELECT%203766%20FROM%20(SELECT(SLEEP(5)))BmIK)%20AND%20%27YLPl%27=%27YLPl leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2262|2024-08-03T00:32:09.552Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 14:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2726|2024-08-03T00:46:04.042Z -- unspecified -- semcms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2726</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SEMCMS. This affects an unknown part of the file Ant_Check.php. The manipulation of the argument DID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-205839.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2726|2024-08-03T00:46:04.042Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 07:11:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3704|2024-08-03T01:20:57.035Z -- unspecified -- ruby%20on%20rails
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3704</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Ruby on Rails. This affects an unknown part of the file actionpack/lib/action_dispatch/middleware/templates/routes/_table.html.erb. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. The name of the patch is be177e4566747b73ff63fd5f529fab564e475ed4. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-212319. NOTE: Maintainer declares that there isn’t a valid attack vector. The issue was wrongly reported as a security vulnerability by a non-member of the Rails team.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3704|2024-08-03T01:20:57.035Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4595|2024-08-03T01:41:45.780Z -- unspecified -- django-openipam
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4595</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in django-openipam. This affects an unknown part of the file openipam/report/templates/report/exposed_hosts.html. The manipulation of the argument description leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The name of the patch is a6223a1150d60cd036106ba6a8e676c1bfc3cc85. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier VDB-216189 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4595|2024-08-03T01:41:45.780Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4012|2024-08-03T01:27:54.096Z -- unspecified -- hospital%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4012</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Hospital Management Center. Affected is an unknown function of the file patient-info.php. The manipulation of the argument pt_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-213786 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4012|2024-08-03T01:27:54.096Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4526|2024-08-03T01:41:45.499Z -- unspecified -- django-photologue
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4526</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in django-photologue up to 3.15.1 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file photologue/templates/photologue/photo_detail.html of the component Default Template Handler. The manipulation of the argument object.caption leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 3.16 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is 960cb060ce5e2964e6d716ff787c72fc18a371e7. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. VDB-215906 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4526|2024-08-03T01:41:45.499Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-1536|2024-08-03T00:10:03.590Z -- unspecified -- automad
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1536</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in automad up to 1.10.9 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects the Dashboard. The manipulation of the argument title with the input Home&lt;/title&gt;&lt;script&gt;alert("home")&lt;/script&gt;&lt;title&gt; leads to a cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely but requires an authentication. The exploit details have disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-1536|2024-08-03T00:10:03.590Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 13:10:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4052|2024-08-03T01:27:54.496Z -- unspecified -- student%20attendance%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4052</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Student Attendance Management System and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /Admin/createClass.php. The manipulation of the argument Id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-213845 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4052|2024-08-03T01:27:54.496Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4276|2024-08-03T01:34:50.020Z -- unspecified -- house%20rental%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4276</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in House Rental System and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file tenant-engine.php of the component POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument id_photo leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-214772.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4276|2024-08-03T01:34:50.020Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3845|2024-08-03T01:20:58.793Z -- unspecified -- phpipam
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3845</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in phpipam and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file app/admin/import-export/import-load-data.php of the component Import Preview Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 1.5.0 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is 22c797c3583001211fe7d31bccd3f1d4aeeb3bbc. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-212863.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3845|2024-08-03T01:20:58.793Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3941|2024-08-03T01:27:53.074Z -- unspecified -- activity%20log%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3941</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Activity Log Plugin and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component HTTP Header Handler. The manipulation of the argument X-Forwarded-For leads to improper output neutralization for logs. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-213448.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3941|2024-08-03T01:27:53.074Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3502|2024-08-03T01:14:01.538Z -- unspecified -- human%20resource%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3502</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Human Resource Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the component Leave Handler. The manipulation of the argument Reason leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-210831.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3502|2024-08-03T01:14:01.538Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3559|2024-08-03T01:14:02.041Z -- unspecified -- exim
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3559</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Exim and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Regex Handler. The manipulation leads to use after free. The name of the patch is 4e9ed49f8f12eb331b29bd5b6dc3693c520fddc2. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier VDB-211073 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3559|2024-08-03T01:14:02.041Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4064|2024-08-03T01:27:54.189Z -- unspecified -- dalli
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4064</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Dalli. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is the function self.meta_set of the file lib/dalli/protocol/meta/request_formatter.rb of the component Meta Protocol Handler. The manipulation leads to injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The name of the patch is 48d594dae55934476fec61789e7a7c3700e0f50d. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. VDB-214026 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4064|2024-08-03T01:27:54.189Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3968|2024-08-03T01:27:53.667Z -- unspecified -- emlog
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3968</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in emlog and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file admin/article_save.php. The manipulation of the argument tag leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The name of the patch is 5bf7a79826e0ea09bcc8a21f69a0c74107761a02. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-213547.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3968|2024-08-03T01:27:53.667Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4593|2024-08-03T01:41:45.617Z -- unspecified -- retra-system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4593</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in retra-system. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The name of the patch is a6d94ab88f4a6f631a14c59b72461140fb57ae1f. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. VDB-216186 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4593|2024-08-03T01:41:45.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-1819|2024-08-03T00:17:00.705Z -- unspecified -- student%20information%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1819</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Student Information System 1.0. Affected is admin/?page=students of the Student Roll module. The manipulation with the input &lt;script&gt;alert(1)&lt;/script&gt; leads to authenticated cross site scripting. Exploit details have been disclosed to the public.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-1819|2024-08-03T00:17:00.705Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 05:25:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4300|2024-08-03T01:34:50.117Z -- unspecified -- fastcms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4300</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in FastCMS. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /template/edit of the component Template Handler. The manipulation leads to injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-214901 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4300|2024-08-03T01:34:50.117Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-1840|2024-08-03T00:17:00.795Z -- unspecified -- home%20clean%20services%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1840</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Home Clean Services Management System 1.0. This issue affects register.php?link=registerand. The manipulation with the input &lt;script&gt;alert(1)&lt;/script&gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely but demands authentication. Exploit details have been disclosed to the public.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-1840|2024-08-03T00:17:00.795Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 05:25:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2263|2024-08-03T00:32:09.528Z -- unspecified -- online%20hotel%20booking%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2263</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Online Hotel Booking System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file edit_room_cat.php of the component Room Handler. The manipulation of the argument roomname leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2263|2024-08-03T00:32:09.528Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 14:10:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4274|2024-08-03T01:34:49.986Z -- unspecified -- house%20rental%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4274</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in House Rental System. Affected is an unknown function of the file /view-property.php. The manipulation of the argument property_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-214770 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4274|2024-08-03T01:34:49.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3299|2024-08-03T01:07:06.494Z -- unspecified -- open5gs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3299</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Open5GS up to 2.4.10. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality in the library lib/sbi/client.c of the component AMF. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack can be launched remotely. The name of the patch is 724fa568435dae45ef0c3a48b2aabde052afae88. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier VDB-209545 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3299|2024-08-03T01:07:06.494Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 12:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2664|2024-08-03T00:46:03.376Z -- unspecified -- private%20cloud%20management%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2664</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Private Cloud Management Platform. Affected is an unknown function of the file /management/api/rcx_management/global_config_query of the component POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to improper authentication. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. VDB-205614 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2664|2024-08-03T00:46:03.376Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:45:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-1753|2024-08-03T00:16:59.968Z -- unspecified -- wowonder
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1753</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in WoWonder. Affected is the file /requests.php which is responsible to handle group messages. The manipulation of the argument group_id allows posting messages in other groups. It is possible to launch the attack remotely but it might require authentication. A video explaining the attack has been disclosed to the public.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-1753|2024-08-03T00:16:59.968Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 05:15:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4638|2024-08-03T01:48:39.567Z -- unspecified -- collective.contact.widget
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4638</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in collective.contact.widget up to 1.12. This vulnerability affects the function title of the file src/collective/contact/widget/widgets.py. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The name of the patch is 5da36305ca7ed433782be8901c47387406fcda12. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-216496.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4638|2024-08-03T01:48:39.567Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4572|2024-08-03T01:41:45.816Z -- unspecified -- ubi%20reader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4572</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in UBI Reader up to 0.8.0. Affected by this issue is the function ubireader_extract_files of the file ubireader/ubifs/output.py of the component UBIFS File Handler. The manipulation leads to path traversal. The attack may be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 0.8.5 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is d5d68e6b1b9f7070c29df5f67fc060f579ae9139. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-216146 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4572|2024-08-03T01:41:45.816Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3354|2024-08-03T01:07:06.484Z -- unspecified -- open5gs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3354</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Open5GS up to 2.4.10 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code in the library lib/core/ogs-tlv-msg.c of the component UDP Packet Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. VDB-209686 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3354|2024-08-03T01:07:06.484Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 15:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3988|2024-08-03T01:27:54.141Z -- unspecified -- frappe
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3988</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Frappe. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file frappe/templates/includes/navbar/navbar_search.html of the component Search. The manipulation of the argument q leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The name of the patch is bfab7191543961c6cb77fe267063877c31b616ce. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-213560.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3988|2024-08-03T01:27:54.141Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4051|2024-08-03T01:27:54.096Z -- unspecified -- hostel%20searching%20project
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4051</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Hostel Searching Project and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file view-property.php. The manipulation of the argument property_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-213844.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4051|2024-08-03T01:27:54.096Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23038|2024-08-03T03:28:43.103Z -- unspecified -- unspecified
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23038</link>
      <description>Linux PV device frontends vulnerable to attacks by backends T[his CNA information record relates to multiple CVEs; the text explains which aspects/vulnerabilities correspond to which CVE.] Several Linux PV device frontends are using the grant table interfaces for removing access rights of the backends in ways being subject to race conditions, resulting in potential data leaks, data corruption by malicious backends, and denial of service triggered by malicious backends: blkfront, netfront, scsifront and the gntalloc driver are testing whether a grant reference is still in use. If this is not the case, they assume that a following removal of the granted access will always succeed, which is not true in case the backend has mapped the granted page between those two operations. As a result the backend can keep access to the memory page of the guest no matter how the page will be used after the frontend I/O has finished. The xenbus driver has a similar problem, as it doesn't check the success of removing the granted access of a shared ring buffer. blkfront: CVE-2022-23036 netfront: CVE-2022-23037 scsifront: CVE-2022-23038 gntalloc: CVE-2022-23039 xenbus: CVE-2022-23040 blkfront, netfront, scsifront, usbfront, dmabuf, xenbus, 9p, kbdfront, and pvcalls are using a functionality to delay freeing a grant reference until it is no longer in use, but the freeing of the related data page is not synchronized with dropping the granted access. As a result the backend can keep access to the memory page even after it has been freed and then re-used for a different purpose. CVE-2022-23041 netfront will fail a BUG_ON() assertion if it fails to revoke access in the rx path. This will result in a Denial of Service (DoS) situation of the guest which can be triggered by the backend. CVE-2022-23042</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23038|2024-08-03T03:28:43.103Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 19:20:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23041|2024-08-03T03:28:42.964Z -- unspecified -- unspecified
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23041</link>
      <description>Linux PV device frontends vulnerable to attacks by backends T[his CNA information record relates to multiple CVEs; the text explains which aspects/vulnerabilities correspond to which CVE.] Several Linux PV device frontends are using the grant table interfaces for removing access rights of the backends in ways being subject to race conditions, resulting in potential data leaks, data corruption by malicious backends, and denial of service triggered by malicious backends: blkfront, netfront, scsifront and the gntalloc driver are testing whether a grant reference is still in use. If this is not the case, they assume that a following removal of the granted access will always succeed, which is not true in case the backend has mapped the granted page between those two operations. As a result the backend can keep access to the memory page of the guest no matter how the page will be used after the frontend I/O has finished. The xenbus driver has a similar problem, as it doesn't check the success of removing the granted access of a shared ring buffer. blkfront: CVE-2022-23036 netfront: CVE-2022-23037 scsifront: CVE-2022-23038 gntalloc: CVE-2022-23039 xenbus: CVE-2022-23040 blkfront, netfront, scsifront, usbfront, dmabuf, xenbus, 9p, kbdfront, and pvcalls are using a functionality to delay freeing a grant reference until it is no longer in use, but the freeing of the related data page is not synchronized with dropping the granted access. As a result the backend can keep access to the memory page even after it has been freed and then re-used for a different purpose. CVE-2022-23041 netfront will fail a BUG_ON() assertion if it fails to revoke access in the rx path. This will result in a Denial of Service (DoS) situation of the guest which can be triggered by the backend. CVE-2022-23042</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23041|2024-08-03T03:28:42.964Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 19:20:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4523|2024-08-03T01:41:45.561Z -- unspecified -- vexim2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4523</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in vexim2. This issue affects some unknown processing. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The name of the patch is 21c0a60d12e9d587f905cd084b2c70f9b1592065. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-215903.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4523|2024-08-03T01:41:45.561Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4596|2024-08-03T01:41:45.812Z -- unspecified -- shoplazza
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4596</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Shoplazza 1.1. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/api/admin/articles/ of the component Add Blog Post Handler. The manipulation of the argument Title leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-216191.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4596|2024-08-03T01:41:45.812Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3967|2024-08-03T01:27:54.186Z -- unspecified -- vesta%20control%20panel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3967</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Vesta Control Panel. Affected is an unknown function of the file func/main.sh of the component sed Handler. The manipulation leads to argument injection. An attack has to be approached locally. The name of the patch is 39561c32c12cabe563de48cc96eccb9e2c655e25. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. VDB-213546 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3967|2024-08-03T01:27:54.186Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-1817|2024-08-03T00:17:00.792Z -- unspecified -- badminton%20center%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1817</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Badminton Center Management System. This affects the userlist module at /bcms/admin/?page=user/list. The manipulation of the argument username with the input &lt;/td&gt;&lt;img src="" onerror="alert(1)"&gt;&lt;td&gt;1 leads to an authenticated cross site scripting. Exploit details have been disclosed to the public.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-1817|2024-08-03T00:17:00.792Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 11:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-1816|2024-08-03T00:16:59.912Z -- unspecified -- zoo%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1816</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Zoo Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is /zoo/admin/public_html/view_accounts?type=zookeeper of the content module. The manipulation of the argument admin_name with the input &lt;script&gt;alert(1)&lt;/script&gt; leads to an authenticated cross site scripting. Exploit details have been disclosed to the public.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-1816|2024-08-03T00:16:59.912Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 11:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3959|2024-08-03T01:27:53.071Z -- unspecified -- drogon
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3959</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in drogon up to 1.8.1. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Session Hash Handler. The manipulation leads to small space of random values. The attack may be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 1.8.2 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is c0d48da99f66aaada17bcd28b07741cac8697647. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-213464.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3959|2024-08-03T01:27:53.071Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3964|2024-08-03T01:27:53.103Z -- unspecified -- ffmpeg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3964</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in ffmpeg. This affects an unknown part of the file libavcodec/rpzaenc.c of the component QuickTime RPZA Video Encoder. The manipulation of the argument y_size leads to out-of-bounds read. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The name of the patch is 92f9b28ed84a77138105475beba16c146bdaf984. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-213543.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3964|2024-08-03T01:27:53.103Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4249|2024-08-03T01:34:49.855Z -- unspecified -- movie%20ticket%20booking%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4249</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Movie Ticket Booking System. Affected is an unknown function of the component POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument ORDER_ID leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-214626 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4249|2024-08-03T01:34:49.855Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4642|2024-08-03T01:48:40.359Z -- unspecified -- tatoeba2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4642</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in tatoeba2. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the component Profile Name Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version prod_2022-10-30 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is 91110777fc8ddf1b4a2cf4e66e67db69b9700361. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-216501 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4642|2024-08-03T01:48:40.359Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-1991|2024-08-03T00:24:43.700Z -- unspecified -- fast%20food%20ordering%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1991</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Fast Food Ordering System 1.0. Affected is the file Master.php of the Master List. The manipulation of the argument Description with the input foo "&gt;&lt;img src="" onerror="alert(document.cookie)"&gt; leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely but it requires authentication. Exploit details have been disclosed to the public.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-1991|2024-08-03T00:24:43.700Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 14:25:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3827|2024-08-03T01:20:58.378Z -- unspecified -- centreon
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3827</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in centreon. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file formContactGroup.php of the component Contact Groups Form. The manipulation of the argument cg_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The name of the patch is 293b10628f7d9f83c6c82c78cf637cbe9b907369. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. VDB-212794 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3827|2024-08-03T01:20:58.378Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3705|2024-08-03T01:20:57.031Z -- unspecified -- vim
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3705</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in vim and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function qf_update_buffer of the file quickfix.c of the component autocmd Handler. The manipulation leads to use after free. The attack may be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 9.0.0805 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is d0fab10ed2a86698937e3c3fed2f10bd9bb5e731. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-212324.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3705|2024-08-03T01:20:57.031Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4013|2024-08-03T01:27:54.154Z -- unspecified -- hospital%20management%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4013</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Hospital Management Center. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file appointment.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-213787.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4013|2024-08-03T01:27:54.154Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23040|2024-08-03T03:28:42.981Z -- unspecified -- unspecified
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23040</link>
      <description>Linux PV device frontends vulnerable to attacks by backends T[his CNA information record relates to multiple CVEs; the text explains which aspects/vulnerabilities correspond to which CVE.] Several Linux PV device frontends are using the grant table interfaces for removing access rights of the backends in ways being subject to race conditions, resulting in potential data leaks, data corruption by malicious backends, and denial of service triggered by malicious backends: blkfront, netfront, scsifront and the gntalloc driver are testing whether a grant reference is still in use. If this is not the case, they assume that a following removal of the granted access will always succeed, which is not true in case the backend has mapped the granted page between those two operations. As a result the backend can keep access to the memory page of the guest no matter how the page will be used after the frontend I/O has finished. The xenbus driver has a similar problem, as it doesn't check the success of removing the granted access of a shared ring buffer. blkfront: CVE-2022-23036 netfront: CVE-2022-23037 scsifront: CVE-2022-23038 gntalloc: CVE-2022-23039 xenbus: CVE-2022-23040 blkfront, netfront, scsifront, usbfront, dmabuf, xenbus, 9p, kbdfront, and pvcalls are using a functionality to delay freeing a grant reference until it is no longer in use, but the freeing of the related data page is not synchronized with dropping the granted access. As a result the backend can keep access to the memory page even after it has been freed and then re-used for a different purpose. CVE-2022-23041 netfront will fail a BUG_ON() assertion if it fails to revoke access in the rx path. This will result in a Denial of Service (DoS) situation of the guest which can be triggered by the backend. CVE-2022-23042</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23040|2024-08-03T03:28:42.981Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 19:20:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4250|2024-08-03T01:34:49.923Z -- unspecified -- movie%20ticket%20booking%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4250</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Movie Ticket Booking System and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file booking.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-214627.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4250|2024-08-03T01:34:49.923Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4251|2024-08-03T01:34:49.948Z -- unspecified -- movie%20ticket%20booking%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4251</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Movie Ticket Booking System and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file editBooking.php. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-214628.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4251|2024-08-03T01:34:49.948Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3969|2024-08-03T01:27:53.765Z -- unspecified -- openkm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3969</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in OpenKM up to 6.3.11 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function getFileExtension of the file src/main/java/com/openkm/util/FileUtils.java. The manipulation leads to insecure temporary file. Upgrading to version 6.3.12 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is c069e4d73ab8864345c25119d8459495f45453e1. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-213548.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3969|2024-08-03T01:27:53.765Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4561|2024-08-03T01:41:45.536Z -- unspecified -- semanticdrilldown%20extension
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4561</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SemanticDrilldown Extension. Affected is the function printFilterLine of the file includes/specials/SDBrowseDataPage.php of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument value leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The name of the patch is 6e18cf740a4548166c1d95f6d3a28541d298a3aa. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-215964.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4561|2024-08-03T01:41:45.536Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-1526|2024-08-03T00:10:03.367Z -- unspecified -- emlog%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1526</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Emlog Pro up to 1.2.2. This affects the POST parameter handling of articles. The manipulation with the input &lt;script&gt;alert(1);&lt;/script&gt; leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely but it requires a signup and login by the attacker. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-1526|2024-08-03T00:10:03.367Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 07:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4053|2024-08-03T01:27:54.046Z -- unspecified -- student%20attendance%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4053</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Student Attendance Management System. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file createClass.php. The manipulation of the argument className leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-213846 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4053|2024-08-03T01:27:54.046Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4014|2024-08-03T01:27:54.169Z -- unspecified -- feehicms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4014</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in FeehiCMS. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Post My Comment Tab. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be launched remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-213788.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4014|2024-08-03T01:27:54.169Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4631|2024-08-03T01:48:39.587Z -- unspecified -- wp-ban
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4631</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in WP-Ban. Affected is an unknown function of the file ban-options.php. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The name of the patch is 22b925449c84faa9b7496abe4f8f5661cb5eb3bf. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-216480.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4631|2024-08-03T01:48:39.587Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4603|2024-08-03T01:41:45.809Z -- unspecified -- ppp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4603</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in ppp. Affected is the function dumpppp of the file pppdump/pppdump.c of the component pppdump. The manipulation of the argument spkt.buf/rpkt.buf leads to improper validation of array index. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. The name of the patch is a75fb7b198eed50d769c80c36629f38346882cbf. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. VDB-216198 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: pppdump is not used in normal process of setting up a PPP connection, is not installed setuid-root, and is not invoked automatically in any scenario.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4603|2024-08-03T01:41:45.809Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4522|2024-08-03T01:41:45.599Z -- unspecified -- calendarxp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4522</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in CalendarXP up to 10.0.1. This vulnerability affects unknown code. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 10.0.2 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is e3715b2228ddefe00113296069969f9e184836da. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-215902 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4522|2024-08-03T01:41:45.599Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3783|2024-08-03T01:20:58.330Z -- unspecified -- node-red-dashboard
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3783</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in node-red-dashboard. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file components/ui-component/ui-component-ctrl.js of the component ui_text Format Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The name of the patch is 9305d1a82f19b235dfad24a7d1dd4ed244db7743. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-212555.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3783|2024-08-03T01:20:58.330Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4377|2024-08-03T01:41:44.202Z -- unspecified -- s-cms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4377</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in S-CMS 5.0 Build 20220328. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Contact Information Page. The manipulation of the argument Make a Call leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-215197 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4377|2024-08-03T01:41:44.202Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2870|2024-08-03T00:52:59.011Z -- unspecified -- laravel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2870</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in laravel 5.1 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-206501 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2870|2024-08-03T00:52:59.011Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 18:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23037|2024-08-03T03:28:43.061Z -- unspecified -- unspecified
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23037</link>
      <description>Linux PV device frontends vulnerable to attacks by backends T[his CNA information record relates to multiple CVEs; the text explains which aspects/vulnerabilities correspond to which CVE.] Several Linux PV device frontends are using the grant table interfaces for removing access rights of the backends in ways being subject to race conditions, resulting in potential data leaks, data corruption by malicious backends, and denial of service triggered by malicious backends: blkfront, netfront, scsifront and the gntalloc driver are testing whether a grant reference is still in use. If this is not the case, they assume that a following removal of the granted access will always succeed, which is not true in case the backend has mapped the granted page between those two operations. As a result the backend can keep access to the memory page of the guest no matter how the page will be used after the frontend I/O has finished. The xenbus driver has a similar problem, as it doesn't check the success of removing the granted access of a shared ring buffer. blkfront: CVE-2022-23036 netfront: CVE-2022-23037 scsifront: CVE-2022-23038 gntalloc: CVE-2022-23039 xenbus: CVE-2022-23040 blkfront, netfront, scsifront, usbfront, dmabuf, xenbus, 9p, kbdfront, and pvcalls are using a functionality to delay freeing a grant reference until it is no longer in use, but the freeing of the related data page is not synchronized with dropping the granted access. As a result the backend can keep access to the memory page even after it has been freed and then re-used for a different purpose. CVE-2022-23041 netfront will fail a BUG_ON() assertion if it fails to revoke access in the rx path. This will result in a Denial of Service (DoS) situation of the guest which can be triggered by the backend. CVE-2022-23042</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23037|2024-08-03T03:28:43.061Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 19:20:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4087|2024-08-03T01:27:54.389Z -- unspecified -- ipxe
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4087</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in iPXE. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function tls_new_ciphertext of the file src/net/tls.c of the component TLS. The manipulation of the argument pad_len leads to information exposure through discrepancy. The name of the patch is 186306d6199096b7a7c4b4574d4be8cdb8426729. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. VDB-214054 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4087|2024-08-03T01:27:54.389Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3464|2024-08-03T01:07:06.640Z -- unspecified -- puppycms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3464</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in puppyCMS up to 5.1. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/settings.php. The manipulation of the argument site_name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-210699.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3464|2024-08-03T01:07:06.640Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23042|2024-08-03T03:28:42.974Z -- unspecified -- unspecified
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23042</link>
      <description>Linux PV device frontends vulnerable to attacks by backends T[his CNA information record relates to multiple CVEs; the text explains which aspects/vulnerabilities correspond to which CVE.] Several Linux PV device frontends are using the grant table interfaces for removing access rights of the backends in ways being subject to race conditions, resulting in potential data leaks, data corruption by malicious backends, and denial of service triggered by malicious backends: blkfront, netfront, scsifront and the gntalloc driver are testing whether a grant reference is still in use. If this is not the case, they assume that a following removal of the granted access will always succeed, which is not true in case the backend has mapped the granted page between those two operations. As a result the backend can keep access to the memory page of the guest no matter how the page will be used after the frontend I/O has finished. The xenbus driver has a similar problem, as it doesn't check the success of removing the granted access of a shared ring buffer. blkfront: CVE-2022-23036 netfront: CVE-2022-23037 scsifront: CVE-2022-23038 gntalloc: CVE-2022-23039 xenbus: CVE-2022-23040 blkfront, netfront, scsifront, usbfront, dmabuf, xenbus, 9p, kbdfront, and pvcalls are using a functionality to delay freeing a grant reference until it is no longer in use, but the freeing of the related data page is not synchronized with dropping the granted access. As a result the backend can keep access to the memory page even after it has been freed and then re-used for a different purpose. CVE-2022-23041 netfront will fail a BUG_ON() assertion if it fails to revoke access in the rx path. This will result in a Denial of Service (DoS) situation of the guest which can be triggered by the backend. CVE-2022-23042</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23042|2024-08-03T03:28:42.974Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 19:20:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4282|2024-08-03T01:34:49.967Z -- unspecified -- springbootcms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4282</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in SpringBootCMS and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Template Management. The manipulation leads to injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-214790 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4282|2024-08-03T01:34:49.967Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3620|2024-08-03T01:14:02.510Z -- unspecified -- exim
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3620</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Exim and classified as problematic. This issue affects the function dmarc_dns_lookup of the file dmarc.c of the component DMARC Handler. The manipulation leads to use after free. The attack may be initiated remotely. The name of the patch is 12fb3842f81bcbd4a4519d5728f2d7e0e3ca1445. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-211919.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3620|2024-08-03T01:14:02.510Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23036|2024-08-03T03:28:42.946Z -- unspecified -- unspecified
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23036</link>
      <description>Linux PV device frontends vulnerable to attacks by backends T[his CNA information record relates to multiple CVEs; the text explains which aspects/vulnerabilities correspond to which CVE.] Several Linux PV device frontends are using the grant table interfaces for removing access rights of the backends in ways being subject to race conditions, resulting in potential data leaks, data corruption by malicious backends, and denial of service triggered by malicious backends: blkfront, netfront, scsifront and the gntalloc driver are testing whether a grant reference is still in use. If this is not the case, they assume that a following removal of the granted access will always succeed, which is not true in case the backend has mapped the granted page between those two operations. As a result the backend can keep access to the memory page of the guest no matter how the page will be used after the frontend I/O has finished. The xenbus driver has a similar problem, as it doesn't check the success of removing the granted access of a shared ring buffer. blkfront: CVE-2022-23036 netfront: CVE-2022-23037 scsifront: CVE-2022-23038 gntalloc: CVE-2022-23039 xenbus: CVE-2022-23040 blkfront, netfront, scsifront, usbfront, dmabuf, xenbus, 9p, kbdfront, and pvcalls are using a functionality to delay freeing a grant reference until it is no longer in use, but the freeing of the related data page is not synchronized with dropping the granted access. As a result the backend can keep access to the memory page even after it has been freed and then re-used for a different purpose. CVE-2022-23041 netfront will fail a BUG_ON() assertion if it fails to revoke access in the rx path. This will result in a Denial of Service (DoS) situation of the guest which can be triggered by the backend. CVE-2022-23042</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23036|2024-08-03T03:28:42.946Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 19:20:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-1839|2024-08-03T00:17:00.682Z -- unspecified -- home%20clean%20services%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1839</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Home Clean Services Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects the file login.php. The manipulation of the argument email with the input admin%'/**/AND/**/(SELECT/**/5383/**/FROM/**/(SELECT(SLEEP(2)))JPeh)/**/AND/**/'frfq%'='frfq leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely but it requires authentication. Exploit details have been disclosed to the public.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-1839|2024-08-03T00:17:00.682Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 05:25:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2886|2024-08-03T00:53:00.444Z -- unspecified -- laravel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2886</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Laravel 5.1. Affected is an unknown function. The manipulation leads to deserialization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-206688.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2886|2024-08-03T00:53:00.444Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 12:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
