<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for unspecified -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/unspecified/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for unspecified -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 23:22:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-125003|2024-08-06T14:10:56.500Z -- unspecified -- ffmpeg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125003</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in FFmpeg 2.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects the function get_siz of the file libavcodec/jpeg2000dec.c. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. The attack may be initiated remotely. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-125003|2024-08-06T14:10:56.500Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 06:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-125025|2024-08-06T14:10:56.568Z -- unspecified -- ffmpeg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125025</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in FFmpeg 2.0. This affects the function decode_pulses. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-125025|2024-08-06T14:10:56.568Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 06:10:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-125002|2024-08-06T14:10:56.509Z -- unspecified -- ffmpeg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125002</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in FFmpeg 2.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is the function dnxhd_init_rc of the file libavcodec/dnxhdenc.c. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-125002|2024-08-06T14:10:56.509Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 06:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-125021|2024-08-06T14:10:56.389Z -- unspecified -- ffmpeg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125021</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in FFmpeg 2.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects the function cmv_process_header. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. The attack may be initiated remotely. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-125021|2024-08-06T14:10:56.389Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 06:10:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-125022|2024-08-06T14:10:56.438Z -- unspecified -- ffmpeg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125022</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in FFmpeg 2.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is the function shorten_decode_frame of the component Bitstream Buffer. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-125022|2024-08-06T14:10:56.438Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 06:10:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-125007|2024-08-06T14:10:56.387Z -- unspecified -- ffmpeg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125007</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in FFmpeg 2.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function intra_pred of the file libavcodec/hevcpred_template.c. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. The attack can be launched remotely. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-125007|2024-08-06T14:10:56.387Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 06:15:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-9599|2024-08-06T02:59:03.011Z -- unspecified -- puppet-tripleo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-9599</link>
      <description>puppet-tripleo before versions 5.5.0, 6.2.0 is vulnerable to an access-control flaw in the IPtables rules management, which allowed the creation of TCP/UDP rules with empty port values. If SSL is enabled, a malicious user could use these open ports to gain access to unauthorized resources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-9599|2024-08-06T02:59:03.011Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-125020|2024-08-06T14:10:56.569Z -- unspecified -- ffmpeg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125020</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in FFmpeg 2.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function decode_update_thread_context. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. The attack can be initiated remotely. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-125020|2024-08-06T14:10:56.569Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 06:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-125011|2024-08-06T14:10:56.450Z -- unspecified -- ffmpeg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125011</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in FFmpeg 2.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function decode_frame of the file libavcodec/ansi.c. The manipulation leads to integer coercion error. The attack can be launched remotely. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-125011|2024-08-06T14:10:56.450Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 06:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-15004|2024-08-06T03:47:34.859Z -- unspecified -- infinitewp%20client%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-15004</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in InfiniteWP Client Plugin 1.5.1.3/1.6.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to injection. The attack can be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 1.6.1.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-15004|2024-08-06T03:47:34.859Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2022 06:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-125017|2024-08-06T14:10:56.533Z -- unspecified -- ffmpeg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125017</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in FFmpeg 2.0. This vulnerability affects the function rpza_decode_stream. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. The attack can be initiated remotely. The name of the patch is Fixes Invalid Writes. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-125017|2024-08-06T14:10:56.533Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 06:16:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-125014|2024-08-06T14:10:56.584Z -- unspecified -- ffmpeg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125014</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in FFmpeg 2.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component HEVC Video Decoder. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. The attack can be launched remotely. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-125014|2024-08-06T14:10:56.584Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 06:16:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-9592|2024-08-06T02:59:02.472Z -- unspecified -- openshift
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-9592</link>
      <description>openshift before versions 3.3.1.11, 3.2.1.23, 3.4 is vulnerable to a flaw when a volume fails to detach, which causes the delete operation to fail with 'VolumeInUse' error. Since the delete operation is retried every 30 seconds for each volume, this could lead to a denial of service attack as the number of API requests being sent to the cloud-provider exceeds the API's rate-limit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-9592|2024-08-06T02:59:02.472Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-9587|2024-08-06T02:59:02.537Z -- unspecified -- ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-9587</link>
      <description>Ansible before versions 2.1.4, 2.2.1 is vulnerable to an improper input validation in Ansible's handling of data sent from client systems. An attacker with control over a client system being managed by Ansible and the ability to send facts back to the Ansible server could use this flaw to execute arbitrary code on the Ansible server using the Ansible server privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-9587|2024-08-06T02:59:02.537Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-125019|2024-08-06T14:10:56.449Z -- unspecified -- ffmpeg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125019</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in FFmpeg 2.0. This affects the function decode_nal_unit of the component Slice Segment Handler. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-125019|2024-08-06T14:10:56.449Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 06:10:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-9594|2024-08-06T02:59:02.701Z -- unspecified -- curl
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-9594</link>
      <description>curl before version 7.52.1 is vulnerable to an uninitialized random in libcurl's internal function that returns a good 32bit random value.  Having a weak or virtually non-existent random value makes the operations that use it vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-9594|2024-08-06T02:59:02.701Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-125008|2024-08-06T14:10:56.579Z -- unspecified -- ffmpeg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125008</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in FFmpeg 2.0. Affected is the function vorbis_header of the file libavformat/oggparsevorbis.c. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-125008|2024-08-06T14:10:56.579Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 06:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-125005|2024-08-06T14:10:56.491Z -- unspecified -- ffmpeg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125005</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in FFmpeg 2.0. This affects the function decode_vol_header of the file libavcodec/mpeg4videodec.c. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-125005|2024-08-06T14:10:56.491Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 06:15:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-9602|2024-08-06T02:59:03.165Z -- unspecified -- qemu
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-9602</link>
      <description>Qemu before version 2.9 is vulnerable to an improper link following when built with the VirtFS. A privileged user inside guest could use this flaw to access host file system beyond the shared folder and potentially escalating their privileges on a host.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-9602|2024-08-06T02:59:03.165Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-125018|2024-08-06T14:10:56.861Z -- unspecified -- ffmpeg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125018</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in FFmpeg 2.0. Affected by this issue is the function decode_slice_header. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. The attack may be launched remotely. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-125018|2024-08-06T14:10:56.861Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 06:10:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-15002|2024-08-06T03:47:34.624Z -- unspecified -- monyog%20ultimate
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-15002</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in MONyog Ultimate 6.63. This affects an unknown part of the component Cookie Handler. The manipulation of the argument HasServerEdit/IsAdmin leads to privilege escalation. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-15002|2024-08-06T03:47:34.624Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 06:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-125009|2024-08-06T14:10:56.468Z -- unspecified -- ffmpeg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125009</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in FFmpeg 2.0. This affects the function add_yblock of the file libavcodec/snow.h. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-125009|2024-08-06T14:10:56.468Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 06:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-125016|2024-08-06T14:10:56.360Z -- unspecified -- ffmpeg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125016</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in FFmpeg 2.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects the function ff_init_buffer_info of the file utils.c. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. The attack may be initiated remotely. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-125016|2024-08-06T14:10:56.360Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 06:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-125012|2024-08-06T14:10:56.298Z -- unspecified -- ffmpeg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125012</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in FFmpeg 2.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file libavcodec/dxtroy.c. The manipulation leads to integer coercion error. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-125012|2024-08-06T14:10:56.298Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 06:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-125015|2024-08-06T14:10:56.558Z -- unspecified -- ffmpeg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125015</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in FFmpeg 2.0. Affected is the function read_var_block_data. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-125015|2024-08-06T14:10:56.558Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 06:16:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-125023|2024-08-06T14:10:56.347Z -- unspecified -- ffmpeg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125023</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in FFmpeg 2.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function truemotion1_decode_header of the component Truemotion1 Handler. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. The attack can be launched remotely. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-125023|2024-08-06T14:10:56.347Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 06:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-125024|2024-08-06T14:10:56.394Z -- unspecified -- ffmpeg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125024</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in FFmpeg 2.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function lag_decode_frame. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. The attack may be launched remotely. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-125024|2024-08-06T14:10:56.394Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 06:10:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-9590|2024-08-06T02:59:02.247Z -- unspecified -- puppet-swift
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-9590</link>
      <description>puppet-swift before versions 8.2.1, 9.4.4 is vulnerable to an information-disclosure in Red Hat OpenStack Platform director's installation of Object Storage (swift). During installation, the Puppet script responsible for deploying the service incorrectly removes and recreates the proxy-server.conf file with world-readable permissions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-9590|2024-08-06T02:59:02.247Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-125004|2024-08-06T14:10:56.553Z -- unspecified -- ffmpeg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125004</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in FFmpeg 2.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function decode_hextile of the file libavcodec/vmnc.c. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. The attack can be initiated remotely. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-125004|2024-08-06T14:10:56.553Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 06:15:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-9593|2024-08-06T02:59:03.223Z -- unspecified -- foreman-debug
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-9593</link>
      <description>foreman-debug before version 1.15.0 is vulnerable to a flaw in foreman-debug's logging. An attacker with access to the foreman log file would be able to view passwords, allowing them to access those systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-9593|2024-08-06T02:59:03.223Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-125013|2024-08-06T14:10:56.562Z -- unspecified -- ffmpeg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125013</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in FFmpeg 2.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects the function msrle_decode_frame of the file libavcodec/msrle.c. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. The attack may be initiated remotely. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-125013|2024-08-06T14:10:56.562Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 06:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-125010|2024-08-06T14:10:56.655Z -- unspecified -- ffmpeg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125010</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in FFmpeg 2.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function decode_slice_header of the file libavcodec/h64.c. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. The attack may be launched remotely. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-125010|2024-08-06T14:10:56.655Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 06:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-9601|2024-08-06T02:59:02.237Z -- unspecified -- ghostscript
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-9601</link>
      <description>ghostscript before version 9.21 is vulnerable to a heap based buffer overflow that was found in the ghostscript jbig2_decode_gray_scale_image function which is used to decode halftone segments in a JBIG2 image. A document (PostScript or PDF) with an embedded, specially crafted, jbig2 image could trigger a segmentation fault in ghostscript.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-9601|2024-08-06T02:59:02.237Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2014-125006|2024-08-06T14:10:56.347Z -- unspecified -- ffmpeg
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125006</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in FFmpeg 2.0. Affected by this issue is the function output_frame of the file libavcodec/h264.c. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. The attack may be launched remotely. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2014-125006|2024-08-06T14:10:56.347Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 06:15:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
