<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for unspecified -- Home Clean Services Management System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/unspecified/home%20clean%20services%20management%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for unspecified -- Home Clean Services Management System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:22:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-1837|2024-08-03T00:17:00.408Z -- unspecified -- home%20clean%20services%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1837</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Home Clean Services Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is register.php?link=registerand. The manipulation with the input &lt;?php phpinfo();?&gt; leads to code execution. The attack may be launched remotely but demands an authentication. Exploit details have been disclosed to the public.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-1837|2024-08-03T00:17:00.408Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 05:25:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-1838|2024-08-03T00:17:00.869Z -- unspecified -- home%20clean%20services%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1838</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Home Clean Services Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of admin/login.php. The manipulation of the argument username with the input admin%'/**/AND/**/(SELECT/**/5383/**/FROM/**/(SELECT(SLEEP(5)))JPeh)/**/AND/**/'frfq%'='frfq leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely but it requires authentication. Exploit details have been disclosed to the public.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-1838|2024-08-03T00:17:00.869Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 05:25:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-1840|2024-08-03T00:17:00.795Z -- unspecified -- home%20clean%20services%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1840</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Home Clean Services Management System 1.0. This issue affects register.php?link=registerand. The manipulation with the input &lt;script&gt;alert(1)&lt;/script&gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely but demands authentication. Exploit details have been disclosed to the public.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-1840|2024-08-03T00:17:00.795Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 05:25:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-1839|2024-08-03T00:17:00.682Z -- unspecified -- home%20clean%20services%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1839</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Home Clean Services Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects the file login.php. The manipulation of the argument email with the input admin%'/**/AND/**/(SELECT/**/5383/**/FROM/**/(SELECT(SLEEP(2)))JPeh)/**/AND/**/'frfq%'='frfq leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely but it requires authentication. Exploit details have been disclosed to the public.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-1839|2024-08-03T00:17:00.682Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 05:25:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
