<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for unspecified -- House Rental System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/unspecified/house%20rental%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for unspecified -- House Rental System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 09:23:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4275|2024-08-03T01:34:49.895Z -- unspecified -- house%20rental%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4275</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in House Rental System and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file search-property.php of the component POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument search_property leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-214771.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4275|2024-08-03T01:34:49.895Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4276|2024-08-03T01:34:50.020Z -- unspecified -- house%20rental%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4276</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in House Rental System and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file tenant-engine.php of the component POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument id_photo leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-214772.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4276|2024-08-03T01:34:50.020Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4274|2024-08-03T01:34:49.986Z -- unspecified -- house%20rental%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4274</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in House Rental System. Affected is an unknown function of the file /view-property.php. The manipulation of the argument property_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-214770 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4274|2024-08-03T01:34:49.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
