<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for unspecified -- Movie Ticket Booking System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/unspecified/movie%20ticket%20booking%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for unspecified -- Movie Ticket Booking System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 17:21:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4247|2024-08-03T01:34:49.838Z -- unspecified -- movie%20ticket%20booking%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4247</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Movie Ticket Booking System. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file booking.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-214624.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4247|2024-08-03T01:34:49.838Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4248|2024-08-03T01:34:49.977Z -- unspecified -- movie%20ticket%20booking%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4248</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Movie Ticket Booking System. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file editBooking.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-214625 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4248|2024-08-03T01:34:49.977Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4249|2024-08-03T01:34:49.855Z -- unspecified -- movie%20ticket%20booking%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4249</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Movie Ticket Booking System. Affected is an unknown function of the component POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument ORDER_ID leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-214626 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4249|2024-08-03T01:34:49.855Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4250|2024-08-03T01:34:49.923Z -- unspecified -- movie%20ticket%20booking%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4250</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Movie Ticket Booking System and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file booking.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-214627.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4250|2024-08-03T01:34:49.923Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4251|2024-08-03T01:34:49.948Z -- unspecified -- movie%20ticket%20booking%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4251</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Movie Ticket Booking System and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file editBooking.php. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-214628.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4251|2024-08-03T01:34:49.948Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
