<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for unspecified -- PHPList</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/unspecified/phplist.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for unspecified -- PHPList</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 22:22:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20032|2024-08-05T21:45:25.092Z -- unspecified -- phplist
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20032</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPList 3.2.6. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Subscription. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 3.3.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20032|2024-08-05T21:45:25.092Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 09:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20029|2024-08-05T21:45:24.944Z -- unspecified -- phplist
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20029</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPList 3.2.6 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /lists/index.php of the component Edit Subscription. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 3.3.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20029|2024-08-05T21:45:24.944Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 09:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20031|2024-08-05T21:45:24.994Z -- unspecified -- phplist
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20031</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPList 3.2.6. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality. The manipulation of the argument sortby with the input password leads to information disclosure. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 3.3.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20031|2024-08-05T21:45:24.994Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 09:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20034|2024-08-05T21:45:24.640Z -- unspecified -- phplist
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20034</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in PHPList 3.2.6. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /lists/admin/ of the component List Name. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting (Persistent). The attack can be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 3.3.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20034|2024-08-05T21:45:24.640Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 09:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20035|2024-08-05T21:45:24.543Z -- unspecified -- phplist
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20035</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in PHPList 3.2.6. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /lists/admin/ of the component Subscribe. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting (Persistent). The attack may be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 3.3.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20035|2024-08-05T21:45:24.543Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 09:30:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20033|2024-08-05T21:45:24.961Z -- unspecified -- phplist
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20033</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in PHPList 3.2.6. This affects an unknown part of the file /lists/admin/. The manipulation of the argument page with the input send\'\";&gt;&lt;script&gt;alert(8)&lt;/script&gt; leads to cross site scripting (Reflected). It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 3.3.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20033|2024-08-05T21:45:24.961Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 09:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20036|2024-08-05T21:45:25.003Z -- unspecified -- phplist
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20036</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in PHPList 3.2.6. Affected is an unknown function of the file /lists/admin/ of the component Bounce Rule. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting (Persistent). It is possible to launch the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 3.3.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20036|2024-08-05T21:45:25.003Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 09:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20030|2024-08-05T21:45:25.021Z -- unspecified -- phplist
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20030</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in PHPList 3.2.6. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /lists/admin/ of the component Sending Campain. The manipulation leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 3.3.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20030|2024-08-05T21:45:25.021Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 09:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
