<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Das -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/das/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Das -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 19:21:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3225|2024-08-05T14:16:28.243Z -- das -- u-boot
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3225</link>
      <description>Das U-Boot is a device bootloader that can read its configuration from an AES encrypted file. For devices utilizing this environment encryption mode, U-Boot's use of a zero initialization vector may allow attacks against the underlying cryptographic implementation and allow an attacker to decrypt the data. Das U-Boot's AES-CBC encryption feature uses a zero (0) initialization vector. This allows an attacker to perform dictionary attacks on encrypted data produced by Das U-Boot to learn information about the encrypted data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3225|2024-08-05T14:16:28.243Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3226|2024-08-05T14:16:28.456Z -- das -- u-boot
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3226</link>
      <description>Das U-Boot is a device bootloader that can read its configuration from an AES encrypted file. Devices that make use of Das U-Boot's AES-CBC encryption feature using environment encryption (i.e., setting the configuration parameter CONFIG_ENV_AES=y) read environment variables from disk as the encrypted disk image is processed. An attacker with physical access to the device can manipulate the encrypted environment data to include a crafted two-byte sequence which triggers an error in environment variable parsing. This error condition is improperly handled by Das U-Boot, resulting in an immediate process termination with a debugging message.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3226|2024-08-05T14:16:28.456Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
