<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Refirm Labs -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/refirm%20labs/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Refirm Labs -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 23:23:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4510|2024-08-03T01:41:45.526Z -- refirm%20labs -- binwalk
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4510</link>
      <description>
A path traversal vulnerability was identified in ReFirm Labs binwalk from version 2.1.2b through 2.3.3 included. By crafting a malicious PFS filesystem file, an attacker can get binwalk's PFS extractor to extract files at arbitrary locations when binwalk is run in extraction mode (-e option). Remote code execution can be achieved by building a PFS filesystem that, upon extraction, would extract a malicious binwalk module into the folder .config/binwalk/plugins.
 This vulnerability is associated with program files src/binwalk/plugins/unpfs.py.

This issue affects binwalk from 2.1.2b through 2.3.3 included.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4510|2024-08-03T01:41:45.526Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 12:25:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-4287|2024-08-03T17:23:10.402Z -- refirm%20labs -- binwalk
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4287</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in ReFirm Labs binwalk up to 2.3.2. Affected is an unknown function of the file src/binwalk/modules/extractor.py of the component Archive Extraction Handler. The manipulation leads to symlink following. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 2.3.3 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is fa0c0bd59b8588814756942fe4cb5452e76c1dcd. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-216876.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in ReFirm Labs binwalk bis 2.3.2 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei src/binwalk/modules/extractor.py der Komponente Archive Extraction Handler. Dank der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine symlink following-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 2.3.3 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als fa0c0bd59b8588814756942fe4cb5452e76c1dcd bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-4287|2024-08-03T17:23:10.402Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 10:32:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
