<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for CyberPower -- PowerPanel Enterprise</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cyberpower/powerpanel%20enterprise.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for CyberPower -- PowerPanel Enterprise</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 22:23:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3265|2024-08-02T06:48:08.459Z -- cyberpower -- powerpanel%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3265</link>
      <description>An authentication bypass exists on CyberPower PowerPanel Enterprise by failing to sanitize meta-characters from the username, allowing an attacker to login into the application with the default user "cyberpower" by appending a non-printable character.An unauthenticated attacker can leverage this vulnerability to log in to the CypberPower PowerPanel Enterprise as an administrator with hardcoded default credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3265|2024-08-02T06:48:08.459Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 04:08:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3267|2024-08-02T06:48:08.577Z -- cyberpower -- powerpanel%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3267</link>
      <description>When adding a remote backup location, an authenticated user can pass arbitrary OS commands through the username field. The username is passed without sanitization into CMD running as NT/Authority System. An authenticated attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code with system-level access to the CyberPower PowerPanel Enterprise server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3267|2024-08-02T06:48:08.577Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 04:11:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3266|2024-08-02T06:48:08.588Z -- cyberpower -- powerpanel%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3266</link>
      <description>A non-feature complete authentication mechanism exists in the production application allowing an attacker to bypass all authentication checks if LDAP authentication is selected.An unauthenticated attacker can leverage this vulnerability to log in to the CypberPower PowerPanel Enterprise as an administrator by selecting LDAP authentication from a hidden HTML combo box. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability also requires the attacker to know at least one username on the device, but any password will authenticate successfully.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3266|2024-08-02T06:48:08.588Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 04:09:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
