<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for leap13 -- Premium Addons for Elementor</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/leap13/premium%20addons%20for%20elementor.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for leap13 -- Premium Addons for Elementor</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 07:22:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8681|2024-09-27T06:53:59.289Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8681</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Media Grid widget in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.52 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8681|2024-09-27T06:53:59.289Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 06:53:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6824|2024-08-08T05:31:46.746Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6824</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification and loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'check_temp_validity' and 'update_template_title' functions in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.38. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to delete arbitrary content and update post and page titles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6824|2024-08-08T05:31:46.746Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 05:31:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32791|2024-08-02T02:20:35.518Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32791</link>
      <description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Leap13 Premium Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Premium Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 4.10.25.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32791|2024-08-02T02:20:35.518Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:45:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4379|2024-08-01T20:40:47.164Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4379</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Global Tooltip widget in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.31 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4379|2024-08-01T20:40:47.164Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 05:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3647|2024-08-01T20:20:00.375Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3647</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's post ticker widget in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.28 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This requires the premium version of the plugin to be installed and activated in order to be exploited.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3647|2024-08-01T20:20:00.375Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4378|2024-08-01T20:40:47.228Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4378</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's menu and shape widgets in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.30 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4378|2024-08-01T20:40:47.228Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:02:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4376|2024-08-01T20:40:46.506Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4376</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Fancy Text widget in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.31 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. While 4.10.32 is patched, it is recommended to update to 4.10.33 because 4.10.32 caused a fatal error.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4376|2024-08-01T20:40:46.506Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 05:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3885|2024-08-01T20:26:57.023Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3885</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the subcontainer value parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.28 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3885|2024-08-01T20:26:57.023Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4205|2024-08-01T20:33:52.902Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4205</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the get_template_content() function in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.31. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to retrieve Elementor template data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4205|2024-08-01T20:33:52.902Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 05:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4203|2024-08-01T20:33:52.945Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4203</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons Pro for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the maps widget in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.30 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. Please note this only affects sites running the premium version of the plugin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4203|2024-08-01T20:33:52.945Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0376|2024-08-01T18:04:49.499Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0376</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Wrapper Link Widget in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.16 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied URLs. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0376|2024-08-01T18:04:49.499Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:58:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37922|2024-07-20T08:57:56.380Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37922</link>
      <description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Leap13 Premium Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Premium Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 4.10.34.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37922|2024-07-20T08:57:56.380Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 08:57:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6495|2024-07-12T12:46:55.285Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6495</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Animated Text widget in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.36 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6495|2024-07-12T12:46:55.285Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 12:46:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6434|2024-07-04T08:32:21.508Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6434</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.35. This is due to processing user-supplied input as a regular expression. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to create and query a malicious post title, resulting in slowing server resources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6434|2024-07-04T08:32:21.508Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 08:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6340|2024-07-03T07:32:37.632Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6340</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Countdown widget in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.35 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6340|2024-07-03T07:32:37.632Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 07:32:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5553|2024-06-12T03:09:57.091Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5553</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting via several parameters in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.33 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses and edits an injected element, and subsequently clicks the element with the mouse scroll wheel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5553|2024-06-12T03:09:57.091Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 03:09:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2666|2024-06-04T17:29:33.482Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2666</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Bullet List Widget in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.24 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page and attempts to edit the content.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2666|2024-06-04T17:29:33.482Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 03:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2664|2024-06-04T17:30:00.859Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2664</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Countdown Widget in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.24 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2664|2024-06-04T17:30:00.859Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 03:09:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2665|2024-06-04T17:30:23.728Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2665</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's button in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.27 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2665|2024-06-04T17:30:23.728Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 03:09:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3885|2024-06-06T19:43:55.758Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3885</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the subcontainer value parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.28 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3885|2024-06-06T19:43:55.758Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3647|2024-06-04T17:31:47.494Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3647</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's post ticker widget in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.28 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This requires the premium version of the plugin to be installed and activated in order to be exploited.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3647|2024-06-04T17:31:47.494Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31278|2024-06-04T17:36:57.800Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31278</link>
      <description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Leap13 Premium Addons for Elementor.This issue affects Premium Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 4.10.22.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31278|2024-06-04T17:36:57.800Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 15:36:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32791|2024-06-04T17:50:29.173Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-32791</link>
      <description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Leap13 Premium Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Premium Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 4.10.25.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32791|2024-06-04T17:50:29.173Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:45:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4203|2024-06-04T17:53:00.701Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4203</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons Pro for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the maps widget in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.30 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. Please note this only affects sites running the premium version of the plugin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4203|2024-06-04T17:53:00.701Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4376|2024-06-04T17:54:02.483Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4376</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Fancy Text widget in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.31 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. While 4.10.32 is patched, it is recommended to update to 4.10.33 because 4.10.32 caused a fatal error.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4376|2024-06-04T17:54:02.483Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 05:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4205|2024-06-04T17:54:10.392Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4205</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the get_template_content() function in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.31. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to retrieve Elementor template data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4205|2024-06-04T17:54:10.392Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 05:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4378|2024-06-04T17:55:10.336Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4378</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's menu and shape widgets in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.30 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4378|2024-06-04T17:55:10.336Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:02:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4379|2024-06-04T17:55:26.846Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4379</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Global Tooltip widget in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.31 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4379|2024-06-04T17:55:26.846Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 05:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0376|2024-06-04T17:58:49.208Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0376</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Wrapper Link Widget in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.16 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied URLs. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0376|2024-06-04T17:58:49.208Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:58:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5553|2024-06-12T15:12:32.739Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5553</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting via several parameters in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.33 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses and edits an injected element, and subsequently clicks the element with the mouse scroll wheel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5553|2024-06-12T15:12:32.739Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 03:09:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6340|2024-07-03T18:31:53.586Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6340</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Countdown widget in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.35 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6340|2024-07-03T18:31:53.586Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 07:32:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6434|2024-07-05T13:54:14.363Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6434</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.35. This is due to processing user-supplied input as a regular expression. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to create and query a malicious post title, resulting in slowing server resources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6434|2024-07-05T13:54:14.363Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 08:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6495|2024-07-12T14:18:18.697Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6495</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Animated Text widget in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.36 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6495|2024-07-12T14:18:18.697Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 12:46:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37922|2024-07-22T13:35:00.312Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37922</link>
      <description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Leap13 Premium Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Premium Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 4.10.34.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37922|2024-07-22T13:35:00.312Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 08:57:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2664|2024-08-01T19:18:48.244Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2664</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Countdown Widget in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.24 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2664|2024-08-01T19:18:48.244Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 03:09:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2665|2024-08-01T19:18:48.258Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2665</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's button in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.27 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2665|2024-08-01T19:18:48.258Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 03:09:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2666|2024-08-01T19:18:48.305Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2666</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Bullet List Widget in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.24 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page and attempts to edit the content.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2666|2024-08-01T19:18:48.305Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 03:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6340|2024-08-01T21:33:05.364Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6340</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Countdown widget in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.35 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6340|2024-08-01T21:33:05.364Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 07:32:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6434|2024-08-01T21:41:03.413Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6434</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.35. This is due to processing user-supplied input as a regular expression. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to create and query a malicious post title, resulting in slowing server resources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6434|2024-08-01T21:41:03.413Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 08:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6495|2024-08-01T21:41:03.338Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6495</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Animated Text widget in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.36 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6495|2024-08-01T21:41:03.338Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 12:46:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5553|2024-08-01T21:18:06.327Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5553</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting via several parameters in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.33 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses and edits an injected element, and subsequently clicks the element with the mouse scroll wheel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5553|2024-08-01T21:18:06.327Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 03:09:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31278|2024-08-02T01:46:04.931Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31278</link>
      <description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Leap13 Premium Addons for Elementor.This issue affects Premium Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 4.10.22.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31278|2024-08-02T01:46:04.931Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 15:36:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37922|2024-08-02T04:04:24.588Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37922</link>
      <description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Leap13 Premium Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Premium Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 4.10.34.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37922|2024-08-02T04:04:24.588Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 08:57:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6824|2024-08-09T17:49:40.841Z -- leap13 -- premium%20addons%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6824</link>
      <description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification and loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'check_temp_validity' and 'update_template_title' functions in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.38. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to delete arbitrary content and update post and page titles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6824|2024-08-09T17:49:40.841Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 05:31:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
