<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Hewlett Packard Enterprise -- Aruba AirWave</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/hewlett%20packard%20enterprise/aruba%20airwave.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Hewlett Packard Enterprise -- Aruba AirWave</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 13:23:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-8526|2024-08-06T02:27:40.343Z -- hewlett%20packard%20enterprise -- aruba%20airwave
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-8526</link>
      <description>Aruba Airwave all versions up to, but not including, 8.2.3.1 is vulnerable to an XML external entities (XXE). XXEs are a way to permit XML parsers to access storage that exist on external systems. If an unprivileged user is permitted to control the contents of XML files, XXE can be used as an attack vector. Because the XML parser has access to the local filesystem and runs with the permissions of the web server, it can access any file that is readable by the web server and copy it to an external system of the attacker's choosing. This could include files that contain passwords, which could then lead to privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-8526|2024-08-06T02:27:40.343Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-8527|2024-08-06T02:27:40.339Z -- hewlett%20packard%20enterprise -- aruba%20airwave
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-8527</link>
      <description>Aruba Airwave all versions up to, but not including, 8.2.3.1 is vulnerable to a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS). The vulnerability is present in the VisualRF component of AirWave. By exploiting this vulnerability, an attacker who can trick a logged-in AirWave administrative user into clicking a link could obtain sensitive information, such as session cookies or passwords. The vulnerability requires that an administrative users click on the malicious link while currently logged into AirWave in the same browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-8527|2024-08-06T02:27:40.339Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
