<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Hewlett Packard Enterprise -- Windows firmware installer for Gen9, Gen8, G7,and G6 HPE servers</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/hewlett%20packard%20enterprise/windows%20firmware%20installer%20for%20gen9%2C%20gen8%2C%20g7%2Cand%20g6%20hpe%20servers.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Hewlett Packard Enterprise -- Windows firmware installer for Gen9, Gen8, G7,and G6 HPE servers</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 11:20:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7112|2024-08-05T06:17:17.526Z -- hewlett%20packard%20enterprise -- windows%20firmware%20installer%20for%20gen9%2C%20gen8%2C%20g7%2Cand%20g6%20hpe%20servers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7112</link>
      <description>The HPE-provided Windows firmware installer for certain Gen9, Gen8, G7,and G6 HPE servers allows local disclosure of privileged information. This issue was resolved in previously provided firmware updates as follows. The HPE Windows firmware installer was updated in the system ROM updates which also addressed the original Spectre/Meltdown set of vulnerabilities. At that time, the Windows firmware installer was also updated in the versions of HPE Integrated Lights-Out 2, 3, and 4 (iLO 2, 3, and 4) listed in the security bulletin. The updated HPE Windows firmware installer was released in the system ROM and HPE Integrated Lights-Out (iLO) releases documented in earlier HPE Security Bulletins: HPESBHF03805, HPESBHF03835, HPESBHF03831. Windows-based systems that have already been updated to the system ROM or iLO versions described in these security bulletins require no further action.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7112|2024-08-05T06:17:17.526Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
