<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for zhenfeng13 -- My-Blog</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/zhenfeng13/my-blog.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for zhenfeng13 -- My-Blog</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 07:22:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1937|2024-08-02T06:05:26.821Z -- zhenfeng13 -- my-blog
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1937</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in zhenfeng13 My-Blog. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/configurations/userInfo. The manipulation of the argument yourAvatar/yourName/yourEmail leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-225264.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in zhenfeng13 My-Blog gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei /admin/configurations/userInfo. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments yourAvatar/yourName/yourEmail mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross-site request forgery-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Dieses Produkt verzichtet auf eine Versionierung und verwendet stattdessen Rolling Releases. Deshalb sind keine Details zu betroffenen oder zu aktualisierende Versionen vorhanden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1937|2024-08-02T06:05:26.821Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 08:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
