<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for fiveai -- Cachet</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/fiveai/cachet.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for fiveai -- Cachet</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 13:23:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39173|2024-08-04T01:58:18.192Z -- fiveai -- cachet
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39173</link>
      <description>Cachet is an open source status page system. Prior to version 2.5.1 authenticated users, regardless of their privileges (User or Admin), can trick Cachet and install the instance again, leading to arbitrary code execution on the server. This issue was addressed in version 2.5.1 by improving the middleware `ReadyForUse`, which now performs a stricter validation of the instance name. As a workaround, only allow trusted source IP addresses to access to the administration dashboard.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39173|2024-08-04T01:58:18.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 23:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39165|2024-08-04T01:58:18.142Z -- fiveai -- cachet
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39165</link>
      <description>Cachet is an open source status page. With Cachet prior to and including 2.3.18, there is a SQL injection which is in the `SearchableTrait#scopeSearch()`. Attackers without authentication can utilize this vulnerability to exfiltrate sensitive data from the database such as administrator's password and session. The original repository of Cachet &lt;https://github.com/CachetHQ/Cachet&gt; is not active, the stable version 2.3.18 and it's developing 2.4 branch is affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39165|2024-08-04T01:58:18.142Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 20:25:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39172|2024-08-04T01:58:18.282Z -- fiveai -- cachet
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39172</link>
      <description>Cachet is an open source status page system. Prior to version 2.5.1, authenticated users, regardless of their privileges (User or Admin), can exploit a new line injection in the configuration edition feature (e.g. mail settings) and gain arbitrary code execution on the server. This issue was addressed in version 2.5.1 by improving `UpdateConfigCommandHandler` and preventing the use of new lines characters in new configuration values. As a workaround, only allow trusted source IP addresses to access to the administration dashboard.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39172|2024-08-04T01:58:18.282Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 22:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39174|2024-08-04T01:58:18.255Z -- fiveai -- cachet
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39174</link>
      <description>Cachet is an open source status page system. Prior to version 2.5.1, authenticated users, regardless of their privileges (User or Admin), can leak the value of any configuration entry of the dotenv file, e.g. the application secret (`APP_KEY`) and various passwords (email, database, etc). This issue was addressed in version 2.5.1 by improving `UpdateConfigCommandHandler` and preventing the use of nested variables in the resulting dotenv configuration file. As a workaround, only allow trusted source IP addresses to access to the administration dashboard.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39174|2024-08-04T01:58:18.255Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 23:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
