<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for techjewel -- Contact Form Plugin by Fluent Forms for Quiz, Survey, and Drag &amp; Drop WP Form Builder</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/techjewel/contact%20form%20plugin%20by%20fluent%20forms%20for%20quiz%2C%20survey%2C%20and%20drag%20%26%20drop%20wp%20form%20builder.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for techjewel -- Contact Form Plugin by Fluent Forms for Quiz, Survey, and Drag &amp; Drop WP Form Builder</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 22:02:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-4709|2024-05-18T07:38:34.748Z -- techjewel -- Contact Form Plugin by Fluent Forms for Quiz, Survey, and Drag &amp; Drop WP Form Builder
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4709</link><description>The Contact Form Plugin by Fluent Forms for Quiz, Survey, and Drag &amp; Drop WP Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘subject’ parameter in versions up to, and including, 5.1.16 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, and access granted by an administrator, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4709|2024-05-18T07:38:34.748Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 07:38:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4157|2024-05-22T07:37:24.259Z -- techjewel -- Contact Form Plugin by Fluent Forms for Quiz, Survey, and Drag &amp; Drop WP Form Builder
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4157</link><description>The Contact Form Plugin by Fluent Forms for Quiz, Survey, and Drag &amp; Drop WP Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.15 via deserialization of untrusted input in the extractDynamicValues function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code. Successful exploitation requires the attacker to have "View Form" and "Manage Form" permissions, which must be explicitly set by an administrator. However, this requirement can be bypassed when this vulnerability is chained with CVE-2024-2771.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4157|2024-05-22T07:37:24.259Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 07:37:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2771|2024-05-18T07:38:20.993Z -- techjewel -- Contact Form Plugin by Fluent Forms for Quiz, Survey, and Drag &amp; Drop WP Form Builder
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2771</link><description>The Contact Form Plugin by Fluent Forms for Quiz, Survey, and Drag &amp; Drop WP Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the /wp-json/fluentform/v1/managers REST API endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.16. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to grant users with Fluent Form management permissions which gives them access to all of the plugin's settings and features. This also makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete manager accounts.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2771|2024-05-18T07:38:20.993Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 07:38:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2782|2024-05-18T07:38:32.798Z -- techjewel -- Contact Form Plugin by Fluent Forms for Quiz, Survey, and Drag &amp; Drop WP Form Builder
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2782</link><description>The Contact Form Plugin by Fluent Forms for Quiz, Survey, and Drag &amp; Drop WP Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the /wp-json/fluentform/v1/global-settings REST API endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.16. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify all of the plugin's settings.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2782|2024-05-18T07:38:32.798Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 07:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2772|2024-05-18T07:38:33.407Z -- techjewel -- Contact Form Plugin by Fluent Forms for Quiz, Survey, and Drag &amp; Drop WP Form Builder
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2772</link><description>The Contact Form Plugin by Fluent Forms for Quiz, Survey, and Drag &amp; Drop WP Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via form settings in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.13 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with access to the Fluent Forms settings, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This can be chained with CVE-2024-2771 for a low-privileged user to inject malicious web scripts.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2772|2024-05-18T07:38:33.407Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 07:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>