<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for InfoDoc -- Document On-line Submission and Approval System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/infodoc/document%20on-line%20submission%20and%20approval%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for InfoDoc -- Document On-line Submission and Approval System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 22:23:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37290|2024-08-02T17:09:34.165Z -- infodoc -- document%20on-line%20submission%20and%20approval%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37290</link>
      <description>
InfoDoc Document On-line Submission and Approval System lacks sufficient restrictions on the available tags within its HTML to PDF conversion function, and allowing an unauthenticated attackers to load remote or local resources through HTML tags such as iframe. This vulnerability allows unauthenticated remote attackers to perform Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) attacks, gaining unauthorized access to arbitrary system files and uncovering the internal network topology.



</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37290|2024-08-02T17:09:34.165Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 10:55:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37289|2024-08-02T17:09:34.180Z -- infodoc -- document%20on-line%20submission%20and%20approval%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37289</link>
      <description>It is identified a vulnerability of Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type in the file uploading function in  InfoDoc Document On-line Submission and Approval System, which allows an unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit this vulnerability without logging system to upload and run arbitrary executable files to perform arbitrary system commands or disrupt service. This issue affects Document On-line Submission and Approval System: 22547, 22567.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37289|2024-08-02T17:09:34.180Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 02:45:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
