<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for anuko -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/anuko/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for anuko -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 18:24:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24708|2024-08-03T04:20:49.874Z -- anuko -- timetracker
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24708</link>
      <description>Anuko Time Tracker is an open source, web-based time tracking application written in PHP. ttUser.class.php in Time Tracker versions prior to 1.20.0.5646 was not escaping primary group name for display. Because of that, it was possible for a logged in user to modify primary group name with elements of JavaScript. Such script could then be executed in user browser on subsequent requests on pages where primary group name was displayed. This is vulnerability has been fixed in version 1.20.0.5646. Users who are unable to upgrade may modify ttUser.class.php to use an additional call to htmlspecialchars when printing group name.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24708|2024-08-03T04:20:49.874Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 23:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24707|2024-08-03T04:20:49.147Z -- anuko -- timetracker
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24707</link>
      <description>Anuko Time Tracker is an open source, web-based time tracking application written in PHP. UNION SQL injection and time-based blind injection vulnerabilities existed in Time Tracker Puncher plugin in versions of anuko timetracker prior to 1.20.0.5642. This was happening because the Puncher plugin was reusing code from other places and was relying on an unsanitized date parameter in POST requests. Because the parameter was not checked, it was possible to craft POST requests with malicious SQL for Time Tracker database. This issue has been resolved in in version 1.20.0.5642. Users unable to upgrade are advised to add their own checks to input.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24707|2024-08-03T04:20:49.147Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 23:50:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
