<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for anuko -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/anuko/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for anuko -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 21:22:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32066|2024-08-02T15:03:28.639Z -- anuko -- timetracker
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32066</link>
      <description>Time Tracker is an open source time tracking system. The week view plugin in Time Tracker versions 1.22.11.5782 and prior was not escaping titles for notes in week view table. Because of that, it was possible for a logged in user to enter notes with elements of JavaScript. Such script could then be executed in user browser on subsequent requests to week view. This issue is fixed in version 1.22.12.5783. As a workaround, use `htmlspecialchars` when calling `$field-&gt;setTitle` on line #245 in the `week.php` file,  as happens in version 1.22.12.5783.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32066|2024-08-02T15:03:28.639Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 15:28:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32308|2024-08-02T15:10:24.463Z -- anuko -- timetracker
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32308</link>
      <description>anuko timetracker is an open source time tracking system. Boolean-based blind SQL injection vulnerability existed in Time Tracker invoices.php in versions prior to 1.22.11.5781. This was happening because of a coding error after validating parameters in POST requests. There was no check for errors before adjusting invoice sorting order. Because of this, it was possible to craft a POST request with malicious SQL for Time Tracker database. This issue has been fixed in version 1.22.11.5781. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade may insert an additional check for errors in a condition before calling `ttGroupHelper::getActiveInvoices()` in invoices.php.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32308|2024-08-02T15:10:24.463Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 20:47:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32306|2024-08-02T15:10:24.449Z -- anuko -- timetracker
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32306</link>
      <description>Time Tracker is an open source time tracking system. A time-based blind injection vulnerability existed in Time Tracker reports in versions prior to 1.22.13.5792. This was happening because the `reports.php` page was not validating all parameters in POST requests. Because some parameters were not checked, it was possible to craft POST requests with malicious SQL for Time Tracker database. This issue is fixed in version 1.22.13.5792. As a workaround, use the fixed code in `ttReportHelper.class.php` from version 1.22.13.5792.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32306|2024-08-02T15:10:24.449Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 18:52:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
