<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for anuko -- timetracker</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/anuko/timetracker.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for anuko -- timetracker</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:23:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41139|2024-08-04T02:59:31.435Z -- anuko -- timetracker
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41139</link>
      <description>Anuko Time Tracker is an open source, web-based time tracking application written in PHP. When a logged on user selects a date in Time Tracker, it is being passed on via the date parameter in URI. Because of not checking this parameter for sanity in versions prior to 1.19.30.5600, it was possible to craft the URI with malicious JavaScript, use social engineering to convince logged on user to click on such link, and have the attacker-supplied JavaScript to be executed in user's browser. This issue is patched in version 1.19.30.5600. As a workaround, one may introduce `ttValidDbDateFormatDate` function as in the latest version and add a call to it within the access checks block in time.php.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41139|2024-08-04T02:59:31.435Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 17:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41156|2024-08-04T02:59:31.630Z -- anuko -- timetracker
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41156</link>
      <description>anuko/timetracker is an, open source time tracking system. In affected versions Time Tracker uses browser_today hidden control on a few pages to collect the today's date from user browsers. Because of not checking this parameter for sanity in versions prior to 1.19.30.5601, it was possible to craft an html form with malicious JavaScript, use social engineering to convince logged on users to execute a POST from such form, and have the attacker-supplied JavaScript to be executed in user's browser. This has been patched in version 1.19.30.5600. Upgrade is recommended. If it is not practical, introduce ttValidDbDateFormatDate function as in the latest version and add a call to it within the access checks block.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41156|2024-08-04T02:59:31.630Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 21:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43851|2024-08-04T04:10:16.291Z -- anuko -- timetracker
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43851</link>
      <description>Anuko Time Tracker is an open source, web-based time tracking application written in PHP. SQL injection vulnerability exist in multiple files in Time Tracker version 1.19.33.5606 and prior due to not properly checking of the "group" and "status" parameters in POST requests. Group parameter is posted along when navigating between organizational subgroups (groups.php file). Status parameter is used in multiple files to change a status of an entity such as making a project, task, or user inactive. This issue has been patched in version 1.19.33.5607. An upgrade is highly recommended. If an upgrade is not practical, introduce ttValidStatus function as in the latest version and start using it user input check blocks wherever status field is used. For groups.php fix, introduce ttValidInteger function as in the latest version and use it in the access check block in the file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43851|2024-08-04T04:10:16.291Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 23:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-15255|2024-08-04T13:08:23.253Z -- anuko -- timetracker
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-15255</link>
      <description>In Anuko Time Tracker before verion 1.19.23.5325, due to not properly filtered user input a CSV export of a report could contain cells that are treated as formulas by spreadsheet software (for example, when a cell value starts with an equal sign). This is fixed in version 1.19.23.5325.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-15255|2024-08-04T13:08:23.253Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 16:20:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
