<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Rapid7 -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/rapid7/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Rapid7 -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:26:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5559|2024-09-17T02:47:31.152Z -- rapid7 -- komand
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5559</link>
      <description>In Rapid7 Komand version 0.41.0 and prior, certain endpoints that are able to list the always encrypted-at-rest connection data could return some configurations of connection data without obscuring sensitive data from the API response sent over an encrypted channel. This issue does not affect Rapid7 Komand version 0.42.0 and later versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5559|2024-09-17T02:47:31.152Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3619|2024-09-17T03:59:06.926Z -- rapid7 -- velociraptor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3619</link>
      <description>Rapid7 Velociraptor 0.5.9 and prior is vulnerable to a post-authentication persistent cross-site scripting (XSS) issue, where an authenticated user could abuse MIME filetype sniffing to embed executable code on a malicious upload. This issue was fixed in version 0.6.0. Note that login rights to Velociraptor is nearly always reserved for trusted and verified users with IT security backgrounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3619|2024-09-17T03:59:06.926Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 19:07:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-31868|2024-09-17T01:16:12.557Z -- rapid7 -- nexpose
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-31868</link>
      <description>Rapid7 Nexpose version 6.6.95 and earlier allows authenticated users of the Security Console to view and edit any ticket in the legacy ticketing feature, regardless of the assignment of the ticket. This issue was resolved in version 6.6.96, released on August 4, 2021.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-31868|2024-09-17T01:16:12.557Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 15:25:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5645|2024-09-17T03:29:11.352Z -- rapid7 -- metasploit%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5645</link>
      <description>By sending a specially crafted HTTP GET request to a listening Rapid7 Metasploit HTTP handler, an attacker can register an arbitrary regular expression. When evaluated, this malicious handler can either prevent new HTTP handler sessions from being established, or cause a resource exhaustion on the Metasploit server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5645|2024-09-17T03:29:11.352Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 14:35:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7377|2024-09-17T03:43:45.123Z -- rapid7 -- metasploit%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7377</link>
      <description>The Metasploit Framework module "auxiliary/admin/http/telpho10_credential_dump" module is affected by a relative path traversal vulnerability in the untar method which can be exploited to write arbitrary files to arbitrary locations on the host file system when the module is run on a malicious HTTP server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7377|2024-09-17T03:43:45.123Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 19:10:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7354|2024-09-17T00:25:26.208Z -- rapid7 -- metasploit%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7354</link>
      <description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the 'host' field of a discovered scan asset in Rapid7 Metasploit Pro allows an attacker with a specially-crafted network service of a scan target to store an XSS sequence in the Metasploit Pro console, which will trigger when the operator views the record of that scanned host in the Metasploit Pro interface. This issue affects Rapid7 Metasploit Pro version 4.17.1-20200427 and prior versions, and is fixed in Metasploit Pro version 4.17.1-20200514. See also CVE-2020-7355, which describes a similar issue, but involving the generated 'notes' field of a discovered scan asset.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7354|2024-09-17T00:25:26.208Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 17:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7385|2024-09-17T01:30:50.001Z -- rapid7 -- metasploit%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7385</link>
      <description>By launching the drb_remote_codeexec exploit, a Metasploit Framework user will inadvertently expose Metasploit to the same deserialization issue that is exploited by that module, due to the reliance on the vulnerable Distributed Ruby class functions. Since Metasploit Framework typically runs with elevated privileges, this can lead to a system compromise on the Metasploit workstation. Note that an attacker would have to lie in wait and entice the Metasploit user to run the affected module against a malicious endpoint in a "hack-back" type of attack. Metasploit is only vulnerable when the drb_remote_codeexec module is running. In most cases, this cannot happen automatically.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7385|2024-09-17T01:30:50.001Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 15:35:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5615|2024-09-17T03:02:06.706Z -- rapid7 -- insightvm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5615</link>
      <description>Users with Site-level permissions can access files containing the username-encrypted passwords of Security Console Global Administrators and clear-text passwords for restoring backups, as well as the salt for those passwords. Valid credentials are required to access these files and malicious users would still need to perform additional work to decrypt the credentials and escalate privileges. This issue affects: Rapid7 InsightVM versions 6.5.11 through 6.5.49.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5615|2024-09-17T03:02:06.706Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 15:27:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5640|2024-09-17T00:15:52.087Z -- rapid7 -- nexpose
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5640</link>
      <description>Rapid7 Nexpose versions prior to 6.6.114 suffer from an information exposure issue whereby, when the user's session has ended due to inactivity, an attacker can use the inspect element browser feature to remove the login panel and view the details available in the last webpage visited by previous user</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5640|2024-09-17T00:15:52.087Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 16:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7355|2024-09-17T02:31:45.777Z -- rapid7 -- metasploit%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7355</link>
      <description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the 'notes' field of a discovered scan asset in Rapid7 Metasploit Pro allows an attacker with a specially-crafted network service of a scan target store an XSS sequence in the Metasploit Pro console, which will trigger when the operator views the record of that scanned host in the Metasploit Pro interface. This issue affects Rapid7 Metasploit Pro version 4.17.1-20200427 and prior versions, and is fixed in Metasploit Pro version 4.17.1-20200514. See also CVE-2020-7354, which describes a similar issue, but involving the generated 'host' field of a discovered scan asset.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7355|2024-09-17T02:31:45.777Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 17:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7350|2024-09-17T00:51:34.097Z -- rapid7 -- metasploit%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7350</link>
      <description>Rapid7 Metasploit Framework versions before 5.0.85 suffers from an instance of CWE-78: OS Command Injection, wherein the libnotify plugin accepts untrusted user-supplied data via a remote computer's hostname or service name. An attacker can create a specially-crafted hostname or service name to be imported by Metasploit from a variety of sources and trigger a command injection on the operator's terminal. Note, only the Metasploit Framework and products that expose the plugin system is susceptible to this issue -- notably, this does not include Rapid7 Metasploit Pro. Also note, this vulnerability cannot be triggered through a normal scan operation -- the attacker would have to supply a file that is processed with the db_import command.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7350|2024-09-17T00:51:34.097Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 21:25:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5642|2024-09-17T04:24:03.024Z -- rapid7 -- metasploit%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5642</link>
      <description>Rapid7 Metasploit Pro version 4.16.0-2019081901 and prior suffers from an instance of CWE-732, wherein the unique server.key is written to the file system during installation with world-readable permissions. This can allow other users of the same system where Metasploit Pro is installed to intercept otherwise private communications to the Metasploit Pro web interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5642|2024-09-17T04:24:03.024Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 18:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5624|2024-09-17T04:29:13.622Z -- rapid7 -- metasploit%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5624</link>
      <description>Rapid7 Metasploit Framework suffers from an instance of CWE-22, Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') in the Zip import function of Metasploit. Exploiting this vulnerability can allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code in Metasploit at the privilege level of the user running Metasploit. This issue affects: Rapid7 Metasploit Framework version 4.14.0 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5624|2024-09-17T04:29:13.622Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 16:53:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5647|2024-09-17T00:51:55.819Z -- rapid7 -- appspider
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5647</link>
      <description>The Chrome Plugin for Rapid7 AppSpider can incorrectly keep browser sessions active after recording a macro, even after a restart of the Chrome browser. This behavior could make future session hijacking attempts easier, since the user could believe a session was closed when it was not. This issue affects Rapid7 AppSpider version 3.8.213 and prior versions, and is fixed in version 3.8.215.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5647|2024-09-17T00:51:55.819Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 18:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-35630|2024-09-17T02:20:37.847Z -- rapid7 -- velociraptor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-35630</link>
      <description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) issue in generating a collection report made it possible for malicious clients to inject JavaScript code into the static HTML file. This issue was resolved in Velociraptor 0.6.5-2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-35630|2024-09-17T02:20:37.847Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 17:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8042|2024-09-09T17:12:45.623Z -- rapid7 -- insight%20platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8042</link>
      <description>Rapid7 Insight Platform versions between November 2019 and August 14, 2024 suffer from missing authorization issues whereby an attacker can intercept local requests to set the name and description of a new user group. This could potentially lead to an empty user group being added to the incorrect customer. This vulnerability is remediated as of August 14, 2024.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8042|2024-09-09T17:12:45.623Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 15:02:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0394|2024-08-22T14:59:24.319Z -- rapid7 -- minerva</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0394</link>
      <description>Rapid7 Minerva Armor versions below 4.5.5 suffer from a privilege escalation vulnerability whereby an authenticated attacker can elevate privileges and execute arbitrary code with SYSTEM privilege.  The vulnerability is caused by the product's implementation of OpenSSL's`OPENSSLDIR` parameter where it is set to a path accessible to low-privileged users.  The vulnerability has been remediated and fixed in version 4.5.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0394|2024-08-22T14:59:24.319Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 13:32:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6504|2024-08-01T21:41:03.465Z -- rapid7 -- insightvm</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6504</link>
      <description>Rapid7 InsightVM Console versions below 6.6.260 suffer from a protection mechanism failure whereby an attacker with network access to the InsightVM Console can cause it to overload or crash by sending repeated invalid REST requests in a short timeframe, to the Console's port 443 causing the console to enter an exception handling logging loop, exhausting the CPU.  There is no indication that an attacker can use this method to escalate privilege, acquire unauthorized access to data, or gain control of protected resources. This issue is fixed in version 6.6.261.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6504|2024-08-01T21:41:03.465Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 09:32:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2745|2024-08-01T19:25:41.647Z -- rapid7 -- insightvm</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2745</link>
      <description>Rapid7's InsightVM maintenance mode login page suffers from a sensitive information exposure vulnerability whereby, sensitive information is exposed through query strings in the URL when login is attempted before the page is fully loaded.  This vulnerability allows attackers to acquire sensitive information such as passwords, auth tokens, usernames etc.  
 
The vulnerability is remediated in version 6.6.244.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2745|2024-08-01T19:25:41.647Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 09:51:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6504|2024-07-18T13:11:19.400Z -- rapid7 -- insightvm</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6504</link>
      <description>Rapid7 InsightVM Console versions below 6.6.260 suffer from a protection mechanism failure whereby an attacker with network access to the InsightVM Console can cause it to overload or crash by sending repeated invalid REST requests in a short timeframe, to the Console's port 443 causing the console to enter an exception handling logging loop, exhausting the CPU.  There is no indication that an attacker can use this method to escalate privilege, acquire unauthorized access to data, or gain control of protected resources. This issue is fixed in version 6.6.261.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6504|2024-07-18T13:11:19.400Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 09:32:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2745|2024-07-10T13:16:15.364Z -- rapid7 -- insightvm</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2745</link>
      <description>Rapid7's InsightVM maintenance mode login page suffers from a sensitive information exposure vulnerability whereby, sensitive information is exposed through query strings in the URL when login is attempted before the page is fully loaded.  This vulnerability allows attackers to acquire sensitive information such as passwords, auth tokens, usernames etc.  
 
The vulnerability is remediated in version 6.6.244.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2745|2024-07-10T13:16:15.364Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 09:51:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2745|2024-04-02T09:51:52.370Z -- rapid7 -- insightvm</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2745</link>
      <description>Rapid7's InsightVM maintenance mode login page suffers from a sensitive information exposure vulnerability whereby, sensitive information is exposed through query strings in the URL when login is attempted before the page is fully loaded.  This vulnerability allows attackers to acquire sensitive information such as passwords, auth tokens, usernames etc.  
 
The vulnerability is remediated in version 6.6.244.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2745|2024-04-02T09:51:52.370Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 09:51:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3185|2024-06-04T17:32:34.224Z -- rapid7 -- insight%20agent</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3185</link>
      <description>A key used in logging.json does not follow the least privilege principle by default and is exposed to local users in the Rapid7 Platform.  This allows an attacker with local access to a machine with the logging.json file to use that key to authenticate to the platform with high privileges.  This was fixed in the Rapid7 platform starting 3 April 2024 via the introduction of a restricted role and the removal of automatic API key generation on installation of an agent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3185|2024-06-04T17:32:34.224Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 08:39:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0394|2024-04-03T13:32:07.211Z -- rapid7 -- minerva</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0394</link>
      <description>Rapid7 Minerva Armor versions below 4.5.5 suffer from a privilege escalation vulnerability whereby an authenticated attacker can elevate privileges and execute arbitrary code with SYSTEM privilege.  The vulnerability is caused by the product's implementation of OpenSSL's`OPENSSLDIR` parameter where it is set to a path accessible to low-privileged users.  The vulnerability has been remediated and fixed in version 4.5.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0394|2024-04-03T13:32:07.211Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 13:32:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6504|2024-07-18T09:32:03.231Z -- rapid7 -- insightvm</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6504</link>
      <description>Rapid7 InsightVM Console versions below 6.6.260 suffer from a protection mechanism failure whereby an attacker with network access to the InsightVM Console can cause it to overload or crash by sending repeated invalid REST requests in a short timeframe, to the Console's port 443 causing the console to enter an exception handling logging loop, exhausting the CPU.  There is no indication that an attacker can use this method to escalate privilege, acquire unauthorized access to data, or gain control of protected resources. This issue is fixed in version 6.6.261.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6504|2024-07-18T09:32:03.231Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 09:32:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0394|2024-08-01T18:04:49.644Z -- rapid7 -- minerva</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0394</link>
      <description>Rapid7 Minerva Armor versions below 4.5.5 suffer from a privilege escalation vulnerability whereby an authenticated attacker can elevate privileges and execute arbitrary code with SYSTEM privilege.  The vulnerability is caused by the product's implementation of OpenSSL's`OPENSSLDIR` parameter where it is set to a path accessible to low-privileged users.  The vulnerability has been remediated and fixed in version 4.5.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0394|2024-08-01T18:04:49.644Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 13:32:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3185|2024-08-01T20:05:08.199Z -- rapid7 -- insight%20agent</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3185</link>
      <description>A key used in logging.json does not follow the least privilege principle by default and is exposed to local users in the Rapid7 Platform.  This allows an attacker with local access to a machine with the logging.json file to use that key to authenticate to the platform with high privileges.  This was fixed in the Rapid7 platform starting 3 April 2024 via the introduction of a restricted role and the removal of automatic API key generation on installation of an agent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3185|2024-08-01T20:05:08.199Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 08:39:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0394|2024-08-22T14:55:58.642Z -- rapid7 -- minerva</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0394</link>
      <description>Rapid7 Minerva Armor versions below 4.5.5 suffer from a privilege escalation vulnerability whereby an authenticated attacker can elevate privileges and execute arbitrary code with SYSTEM privilege.  The vulnerability is caused by the product's implementation of OpenSSL's`OPENSSLDIR` parameter where it is set to a path accessible to low-privileged users.  The vulnerability has been remediated and fixed in version 4.5.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0394|2024-08-22T14:55:58.642Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 13:32:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8042|2024-09-09T15:02:38.681Z -- rapid7 -- insight%20platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8042</link>
      <description>Rapid7 Insight Platform versions between November 2019 and August 14, 2024 suffer from missing authorization issues whereby an attacker can intercept local requests to set the name and description of a new user group. This could potentially lead to an empty user group being added to the incorrect customer. This vulnerability is remediated as of August 14, 2024.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8042|2024-09-09T15:02:38.681Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 15:02:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
