<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Rapid7 -- Metasploit Framework</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/rapid7/metasploit%20framework.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Rapid7 -- Metasploit Framework</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 10:23:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7376|2024-08-04T09:25:49.061Z -- rapid7 -- metasploit%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7376</link>
      <description>The Metasploit Framework module "post/osx/gather/enum_osx module" is affected by a relative path traversal vulnerability in the get_keychains method which can be exploited to write arbitrary files to arbitrary locations on the host filesystem when the module is run on a malicious host.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7376|2024-08-04T09:25:49.061Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7377|2024-08-04T09:25:49.148Z -- rapid7 -- metasploit%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7377</link>
      <description>The Metasploit Framework module "auxiliary/admin/http/telpho10_credential_dump" module is affected by a relative path traversal vulnerability in the untar method which can be exploited to write arbitrary files to arbitrary locations on the host file system when the module is run on a malicious HTTP server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7377|2024-08-04T09:25:49.148Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7350|2024-08-04T09:25:49.030Z -- rapid7 -- metasploit%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7350</link>
      <description>Rapid7 Metasploit Framework versions before 5.0.85 suffers from an instance of CWE-78: OS Command Injection, wherein the libnotify plugin accepts untrusted user-supplied data via a remote computer's hostname or service name. An attacker can create a specially-crafted hostname or service name to be imported by Metasploit from a variety of sources and trigger a command injection on the operator's terminal. Note, only the Metasploit Framework and products that expose the plugin system is susceptible to this issue -- notably, this does not include Rapid7 Metasploit Pro. Also note, this vulnerability cannot be triggered through a normal scan operation -- the attacker would have to supply a file that is processed with the db_import command.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7350|2024-08-04T09:25:49.030Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7385|2024-08-04T09:25:48.987Z -- rapid7 -- metasploit%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7385</link>
      <description>By launching the drb_remote_codeexec exploit, a Metasploit Framework user will inadvertently expose Metasploit to the same deserialization issue that is exploited by that module, due to the reliance on the vulnerable Distributed Ruby class functions. Since Metasploit Framework typically runs with elevated privileges, this can lead to a system compromise on the Metasploit workstation. Note that an attacker would have to lie in wait and entice the Metasploit user to run the affected module against a malicious endpoint in a "hack-back" type of attack. Metasploit is only vulnerable when the drb_remote_codeexec module is running. In most cases, this cannot happen automatically.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7385|2024-08-04T09:25:48.987Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
