<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Rapid7 -- Nexpose</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/rapid7/nexpose.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Rapid7 -- Nexpose</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 20:23:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5638|2024-08-04T20:01:52.192Z -- rapid7 -- nexpose
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5638</link>
      <description>Rapid7 Nexpose versions 6.5.50 and prior suffer from insufficient session expiration when an administrator performs a security relevant edit on an existing, logged on user. For example, if a user's password is changed by an administrator due to an otherwise unrelated credential leak, that user account's current session is still valid after the password change, potentially allowing the attacker who originally compromised the credential to remain logged in and able to cause further damage.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5638|2024-08-04T20:01:52.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5640|2024-08-04T20:01:52.022Z -- rapid7 -- nexpose
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5640</link>
      <description>Rapid7 Nexpose versions prior to 6.6.114 suffer from an information exposure issue whereby, when the user's session has ended due to inactivity, an attacker can use the inspect element browser feature to remove the login panel and view the details available in the last webpage visited by previous user

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5640|2024-08-04T20:01:52.022Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7381|2024-08-04T09:25:49.053Z -- rapid7 -- nexpose
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7381</link>
      <description>In Rapid7 Nexpose installer versions prior to 6.6.40, the Nexpose installer calls an executable which can be placed in the appropriate directory by an attacker with access to the local machine. This would prevent the installer from distinguishing between a valid executable called during a Security Console installation and any arbitrary code executable using the same file name.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7381|2024-08-04T09:25:49.053Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 13:55:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7383|2024-08-04T09:25:49.045Z -- rapid7 -- nexpose
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7383</link>
      <description>A SQL Injection issue in Rapid7 Nexpose version prior to 6.6.49 that may have allowed an authenticated user with a low permission level to access resources &amp; make changes they should not have been able to access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7383|2024-08-04T09:25:49.045Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7382|2024-08-04T09:25:49.039Z -- rapid7 -- nexpose
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7382</link>
      <description>Rapid7 Nexpose installer version prior to 6.6.40 contains an Unquoted Search Path which may allow an attacker on the local machine to insert an arbitrary file into the executable path. This issue affects: Rapid7 Nexpose versions prior to 6.6.40.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7382|2024-08-04T09:25:49.039Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 13:55:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
