<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for themefusecom -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/themefusecom/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for themefusecom -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 21:54:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-1311|2024-03-13T15:27:18.889Z -- themefusecom -- Brizy – Page Builder
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1311</link><description>The Brizy – Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the storeImages function in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.40. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1311|2024-03-13T15:27:18.889Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:27:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1296|2024-03-13T15:26:45.344Z -- themefusecom -- Brizy – Page Builder
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1296</link><description>The Brizy – Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's block upload in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.40 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1296|2024-03-13T15:26:45.344Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:26:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1291|2024-03-13T15:27:27.025Z -- themefusecom -- Brizy – Page Builder
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1291</link><description>The Brizy – Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Countdown URL parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.40 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1291|2024-03-13T15:27:27.025Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:27:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1293|2024-03-13T15:26:50.158Z -- themefusecom -- Brizy – Page Builder
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1293</link><description>The Brizy – Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the embedded media custom block in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.40 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1293|2024-03-13T15:26:50.158Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:26:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1165|2024-02-24T09:38:22.454Z -- themefusecom -- Brizy – Page Builder
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1165</link><description>The Brizy – Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.39 via the 'id'. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to upload files to arbitrary locations on the server</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1165|2024-02-24T09:38:22.454Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 09:38:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3711|2024-05-23T05:32:15.933Z -- themefusecom -- Brizy – Page Builder
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3711</link><description>The Brizy – Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized plugin setting update due to a missing capability check on the functions action_request_disable, action_change_template, and action_request_enable in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.43. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or above, to enable/disable the Brizy editor and modify the template used.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3711|2024-05-23T05:32:15.933Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 05:32:15 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>