<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for TP-Link -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tp-link/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for TP-Link -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 21:24:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-5227|2024-05-23T21:55:48.347Z -- TP-Link -- Omada ER605
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5227</link><description>TP-Link Omada ER605 PPTP VPN username Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of TP-Link Omada ER605 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. However, devices are only vulnerable if configured to use a PPTP VPN with LDAP authentication.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of the username parameter provided to the /usr/bin/pppd endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-22446.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5227|2024-05-23T21:55:48.347Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 21:55:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5244|2024-05-23T21:56:08.846Z -- TP-Link -- Omada ER605
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5244</link><description>TP-Link Omada ER605 Reliance on Security Through Obscurity Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to access or spoof DDNS messages on affected installations of TP-Link Omada ER605 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. However, devices are vulnerable only if configured to use the Comexe DDNS service.

The specific flaw exists within the cmxddnsd executable. The issue results from reliance on obscurity to secure network data. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-22439.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5244|2024-05-23T21:56:08.846Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 21:56:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5228|2024-05-23T21:55:55.391Z -- TP-Link -- Omada ER605
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5228</link><description>TP-Link Omada ER605  Comexe DDNS Response Handling Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of TP-Link Omada ER605 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. However, devices are vulnerable only if configured to use the Comexe DDNS service.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of DNS responses. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-22383.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5228|2024-05-23T21:55:55.391Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 21:55:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5242|2024-05-23T21:55:59.756Z -- TP-Link -- Omada ER605
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5242</link><description>TP-Link Omada ER605 Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of TP-Link Omada ER605 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. However, devices are vulnerable only if configured to use the Comexe DDNS service.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of DDNS error codes. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-22522.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5242|2024-05-23T21:55:59.756Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 21:55:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5243|2024-05-23T21:56:04.395Z -- TP-Link -- Omada ER605
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5243</link><description>TP-Link Omada ER605 Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of TP-Link Omada ER605 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. However, devices are vulnerable only if configured to use the Comexe DDNS service.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of DNS names. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-22523.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5243|2024-05-23T21:56:04.395Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 21:56:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1179|2024-04-01T21:46:08.541Z -- TP-Link -- Omada ER605
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1179</link><description>TP-Link Omada ER605 DHCPv6 Client Options Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of TP-Link Omada ER605 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of DHCP options. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-22420.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1179|2024-04-01T21:46:08.541Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:46:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1180|2024-04-03T16:30:55.786Z -- TP-Link -- Omada ER605
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1180</link><description>TP-Link Omada ER605 Access Control Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of TP-Link Omada ER605. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific issue exists within the handling of the name field in the access control user interface. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-22227.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1180|2024-04-03T16:30:55.786Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:30:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21833|2024-01-10T23:25:25.755Z -- TP-Link -- Archer AX3000
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21833</link><description>Multiple TP-LINK products allow a network-adjacent unauthenticated attacker with access to the product to execute arbitrary OS commands. Affected products/versions are as follows: Archer AX3000 firmware versions prior to "Archer AX3000(JP)_V1_1.1.2 Build 20231115", Archer AX5400 firmware versions prior to "Archer AX5400(JP)_V1_1.1.2 Build 20231115", Archer AXE75 firmware versions prior to "Archer AXE75(JP)_V1_231115", Deco X50 firmware versions prior to "Deco X50(JP)_V1_1.4.1 Build 20231122", and Deco XE200 firmware versions prior to "Deco XE200(JP)_V1_1.2.5 Build 20231120".</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21833|2024-01-10T23:25:25.755Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 23:25:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21821|2024-01-10T23:25:07.433Z -- TP-Link -- Archer AX3000
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21821</link><description>Multiple TP-LINK products allow a network-adjacent authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary OS commands. Affected products/versions are as follows: Archer AX3000 firmware versions prior to "Archer AX3000(JP)_V1_1.1.2 Build 20231115", Archer AX5400 firmware versions prior to "Archer AX5400(JP)_V1_1.1.2 Build 20231115", and Archer AXE75 firmware versions prior to "Archer AXE75(JP)_V1_231115".</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21821|2024-01-10T23:25:07.433Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 23:25:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21773|2024-01-10T23:24:50.112Z -- TP-Link -- Archer AX3000
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21773</link><description>Multiple TP-LINK products allow a network-adjacent unauthenticated attacker with access to the product to execute arbitrary OS commands. Affected products/versions are as follows: Archer AX3000 firmware versions prior to "Archer AX3000(JP)_V1_1.1.2 Build 20231115", Archer AX5400 firmware versions prior to "Archer AX5400(JP)_V1_1.1.2 Build 20231115", Deco X50 firmware versions prior to "Deco X50(JP)_V1_1.4.1 Build 20231122", and Deco XE200 firmware versions prior to "Deco XE200(JP)_V1_1.2.5 Build 20231120".</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21773|2024-01-10T23:24:50.112Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 23:24:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31340|2024-05-22T05:29:04.007Z -- TP-Link  -- TP-Link Tether
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31340</link><description>TP-Link Tether versions prior to 4.5.13 and TP-Link Tapo versions prior to 3.3.6 do not properly validate certificates, which may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to eavesdrop on an encrypted communication via a man-in-the-middle attack.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31340|2024-05-22T05:29:04.007Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 05:29:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2188|2024-03-05T12:15:25.297Z -- TP-Link -- Archer AX50
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2188</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability stored in TP-Link Archer AX50 affecting firmware version 1.0.11 build 2022052. This vulnerability could allow an unauthenticated attacker to create a port mapping rule via a SOAP request and store a malicious JavaScript payload within that rule, which could result in an execution of the JavaScript payload when the rule is loaded.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2188|2024-03-05T12:15:25.297Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 12:15:25 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>