<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for TP-Link -- Archer A7</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tp-link/archer%20a7.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for TP-Link -- Archer A7</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:23:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10881|2024-08-04T11:14:15.617Z -- tp-link -- archer%20a7
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10881</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of TP-Link Archer A7 Firmware Ver: 190726 AC1750 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of DNS responses. A crafted DNS message can trigger an overflow of a fixed-length, stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the root user. Was ZDI-CAN-9660.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10881|2024-08-04T11:14:15.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 19:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10888|2024-08-04T11:14:15.895Z -- tp-link -- archer%20a7
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10888</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of TP-Link Archer A7 Firmware Ver: 190726 AC1750 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of SSH port forwarding requests during initial setup. The issue results from the lack of proper authentication prior to establishing SSH port forwarding rules. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges to resources normally protected from the WAN interface. Was ZDI-CAN-9664.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10888|2024-08-04T11:14:15.895Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 19:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10886|2024-08-04T11:14:15.619Z -- tp-link -- archer%20a7
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10886</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of TP-Link Archer A7 Firmware Ver: 190726 AC1750 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the tmpServer service, which listens on TCP port 20002. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-9662.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10886|2024-08-04T11:14:15.619Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 19:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10884|2024-08-04T11:14:15.710Z -- tp-link -- archer%20a7
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10884</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers execute arbitrary code on affected installations of TP-Link Archer A7 Firmware Ver: 190726 AC1750 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the tdpServer service, which listens on UDP port 20002 by default. This issue results from the use of hard-coded encryption key. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-9652.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10884|2024-08-04T11:14:15.710Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 19:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10882|2024-08-04T11:14:15.768Z -- tp-link -- archer%20a7
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10882</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of TP-Link Archer A7 Firmware Ver: 190726 AC1750 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the tdpServer service, which listens on UDP port 20002 by default. When parsing the slave_mac parameter, the process does not properly validate a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the root user. Was ZDI-CAN-9650.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10882|2024-08-04T11:14:15.768Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 19:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10887|2024-08-04T11:14:15.707Z -- tp-link -- archer%20a7
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10887</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows a firewall bypass on affected installations of TP-Link Archer A7 Firmware Ver: 190726 AC1750 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of IPv6 connections. The issue results from the lack of proper filtering of IPv6 SSH connections. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-9663.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10887|2024-08-04T11:14:15.707Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 19:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10885|2024-08-04T11:14:15.886Z -- tp-link -- archer%20a7
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10885</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of TP-Link Archer A7 Firmware Ver: 190726 AC1750 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of DNS responses. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of DNS reponses prior to further processing. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the root user. Was ZDI-CAN-9661.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10885|2024-08-04T11:14:15.886Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 19:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-10883|2024-08-04T11:14:15.683Z -- tp-link -- archer%20a7
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-10883</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of TP-Link Archer A7 Firmware Ver: 190726 AC1750 routers. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the file system. The issue lies in the lack of proper permissions set on the file system. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges. Was ZDI-CAN-9651.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-10883|2024-08-04T11:14:15.683Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 19:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
