<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for TP-LINK -- Archer C50</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tp-link/archer%20c50.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for TP-LINK -- Archer C50</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 16:24:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32619|2024-08-02T15:25:35.693Z -- tp-link -- archer%20c50
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32619</link>
      <description>Archer C50 firmware versions prior to 'Archer C50(JP)_V3_230505' and Archer C55 firmware versions prior to 'Archer C55(JP)_V1_230506' use hard-coded credentials to login to the affected device, which may allow a network-adjacent unauthenticated attacker to execute an arbitrary OS command.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32619|2024-08-02T15:25:35.693Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 09:27:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31188|2024-08-02T14:45:26.119Z -- tp-link -- archer%20c50
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31188</link>
      <description>Multiple TP-LINK products allow a network-adjacent authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary OS commands. Affected products/versions are as follows: Archer C50 firmware versions prior to 'Archer C50(JP)_V3_230505', Archer C55 firmware versions prior to 'Archer C55(JP)_V1_230506', and Archer C20 firmware versions prior to 'Archer C20(JP)_V1_230616'.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31188|2024-08-02T14:45:26.119Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 09:28:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0936|2024-08-02T05:32:45.158Z -- tp-link -- archer%20c50
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0936</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in TP-Link Archer C50 V2_160801. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack can only be initiated within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-221552.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in TP-Link Archer C50 V2_160801 ausgemacht. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Komponente Web Management Interface. Dank Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine denial of service-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann im lokalen Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0936|2024-08-02T05:32:45.158Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 09:24:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
