<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for eyale-vc -- Contact Form Builder by vcita</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/eyale-vc/contact%20form%20builder%20by%20vcita.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for eyale-vc -- Contact Form Builder by vcita</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2300|2023-06-03T04:35:12.522Z -- eyale-vc -- contact%20form%20builder%20by%20vcita
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-2300</link>
      <description>The Contact Form Builder by vcita plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'email' parameter in versions up to, and including, 4.9.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with the edit_posts capability, such as contributors and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2300|2023-06-03T04:35:12.522Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 04:35:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2301|2023-06-03T04:35:15.116Z -- eyale-vc -- contact%20form%20builder%20by%20vcita
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-2301</link>
      <description>The Contact Form Builder by vcita plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 4.9.1. This is due to missing nonce validation on the ls_parse_vcita_callback function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify the plugin's settings and inject malicious JavaScript via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2301|2023-06-03T04:35:15.116Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 04:35:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2303|2023-06-03T04:35:13.759Z -- eyale-vc -- contact%20form%20builder%20by%20vcita
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-2303</link>
      <description>The Contact Form and Calls To Action by vcita plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 2.6.4. This is due to missing nonce validation in the vcita-callback.php file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify the plugin's settings and inject malicious JavaScript via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2303|2023-06-03T04:35:13.759Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 04:35:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
