<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Hathway -- Skyworth Router CM5100</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/hathway/skyworth%20router%20cm5100.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Hathway -- Skyworth Router CM5100</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 23:21:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51719|2024-08-02T22:40:34.207Z -- hathway -- skyworth%20router%20cm5100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51719</link>
      <description>This vulnerability exist in Skyworth Router CM5100, version 4.1.1.24, due to insufficient validation of user supplied input for the Traceroute parameter at its web interface.  A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying specially crafted input to the parameter at the web interface of the vulnerable targeted system.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to perform stored XSS attacks on the targeted system.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51719|2024-08-02T22:40:34.207Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 06:48:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51738|2024-08-02T22:40:34.229Z -- hathway -- skyworth%20router%20cm5100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51738</link>
      <description>This vulnerability exist in Skyworth Router CM5100, version 4.1.1.24, due to insufficient validation of user supplied input for the Network Name (SSID) parameter at its web interface.  A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying specially crafted input to the parameter at the web interface of the vulnerable targeted system.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to perform stored XSS attacks on the targeted system.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51738|2024-08-02T22:40:34.229Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 07:19:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51722|2024-08-02T22:40:34.210Z -- hathway -- skyworth%20router%20cm5100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51722</link>
      <description>This vulnerability exist in Skyworth Router CM5100, version 4.1.1.24, due to insufficient validation of user supplied input for the Time Server 3 parameter at its web interface.  A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying specially crafted input to the parameter at the web interface of the vulnerable targeted system.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to perform stored XSS attacks on the targeted system.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51722|2024-08-02T22:40:34.210Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 06:52:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51734|2024-08-02T22:40:34.269Z -- hathway -- skyworth%20router%20cm5100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51734</link>
      <description>This vulnerability exist in Skyworth Router CM5100, version 4.1.1.24, due to insufficient validation of user supplied input for the Identity parameter under Remote endpoint settings at its web interface.  A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying specially crafted input to the parameter at the web interface of the vulnerable targeted system.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to perform stored XSS attacks on the targeted system.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51734|2024-08-02T22:40:34.269Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 07:13:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51725|2024-08-02T22:40:34.236Z -- hathway -- skyworth%20router%20cm5100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51725</link>
      <description>This vulnerability exist in Skyworth Router CM5100, version 4.1.1.24, due to insufficient validation of user supplied input for the Contact Email Address parameter at its web interface.  A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying specially crafted input to the parameter at the web interface of the vulnerable targeted system.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to perform stored XSS attacks on the targeted system.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51725|2024-08-02T22:40:34.236Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 06:57:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51728|2024-08-02T22:40:34.318Z -- hathway -- skyworth%20router%20cm5100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51728</link>
      <description>This vulnerability exist in Skyworth Router CM5100, version 4.1.1.24, due to insufficient validation of user supplied input for the SMTP Password parameter at its web interface.  A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying specially crafted input to the parameter at the web interface of the vulnerable targeted system.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to perform stored XSS attacks on the targeted system.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51728|2024-08-02T22:40:34.318Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 07:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51729|2024-08-02T22:40:34.163Z -- hathway -- skyworth%20router%20cm5100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51729</link>
      <description>This vulnerability exist in Skyworth Router CM5100, version 4.1.1.24, due to insufficient validation of user supplied input for the DDNS Username parameter at its web interface.  A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying specially crafted input to the parameter at the web interface of the vulnerable targeted system.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to perform stored XSS attacks on the targeted system.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51729|2024-08-02T22:40:34.163Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 07:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51724|2024-08-02T22:40:34.352Z -- hathway -- skyworth%20router%20cm5100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51724</link>
      <description>This vulnerability exist in Skyworth Router CM5100, version 4.1.1.24, due to insufficient validation of user supplied input for the URL parameter at its web interface.  A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying specially crafted input to the parameter at the web interface of the vulnerable targeted system.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to perform stored XSS attacks on the targeted system.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51724|2024-08-02T22:40:34.352Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 06:56:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51730|2024-08-02T22:40:34.226Z -- hathway -- skyworth%20router%20cm5100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51730</link>
      <description>This vulnerability exist in Skyworth Router CM5100, version 4.1.1.24, due to insufficient validation of user supplied input for the DDNS Password parameter at its web interface.  A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying specially crafted input to the parameter at the web interface of the vulnerable targeted system.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to perform stored XSS attacks on the targeted system.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51730|2024-08-02T22:40:34.226Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 07:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51731|2024-08-02T22:40:34.319Z -- hathway -- skyworth%20router%20cm5100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51731</link>
      <description>This vulnerability exist in Skyworth Router CM5100, version 4.1.1.24, due to insufficient validation of user supplied input for the Hostname parameter at its web interface.  A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying specially crafted input to the parameter at the web interface of the vulnerable targeted system.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to perform stored XSS attacks on the targeted system.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51731|2024-08-02T22:40:34.319Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 07:06:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51737|2024-08-02T22:40:34.267Z -- hathway -- skyworth%20router%20cm5100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51737</link>
      <description>This vulnerability exist in Skyworth Router CM5100, version 4.1.1.24, due to insufficient validation of user supplied input for the Preshared Phrase parameter at its web interface.  A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying specially crafted input to the parameter at the web interface of the vulnerable targeted system.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to perform stored XSS attacks on the targeted system.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51737|2024-08-02T22:40:34.267Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 07:17:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51732|2024-08-02T22:40:34.391Z -- hathway -- skyworth%20router%20cm5100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51732</link>
      <description>This vulnerability exist in Skyworth Router CM5100, version 4.1.1.24, due to insufficient validation of user supplied input for the IPsec Tunnel Name parameter at its web interface.  A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying specially crafted input to the parameter at the web interface of the vulnerable targeted system.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to perform stored XSS attacks on the targeted system.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51732|2024-08-02T22:40:34.391Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 07:07:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51733|2024-08-02T22:40:34.248Z -- hathway -- skyworth%20router%20cm5100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51733</link>
      <description>This vulnerability exist in Skyworth Router CM5100, version 4.1.1.24, due to insufficient validation of user supplied input for the Identity parameter under Local endpoint settings at its web interface.  A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying specially crafted input to the parameter at the web interface of the vulnerable targeted system.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to perform stored XSS attacks on the targeted system.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51733|2024-08-02T22:40:34.248Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 07:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51723|2024-08-02T22:40:34.201Z -- hathway -- skyworth%20router%20cm5100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51723</link>
      <description>This vulnerability exist in Skyworth Router CM5100, version 4.1.1.24, due to insufficient validation of user supplied input for the Description parameter at its web interface.  A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying specially crafted input to the parameter at the web interface of the vulnerable targeted system.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to perform stored XSS attacks on the targeted system.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51723|2024-08-02T22:40:34.201Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 06:54:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51739|2024-08-02T22:40:34.202Z -- hathway -- skyworth%20router%20cm5100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51739</link>
      <description>This vulnerability exist in Skyworth Router CM5100, version 4.1.1.24, due to insufficient validation of user supplied input for the Device Name parameter at its web interface.  A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying specially crafted input to the parameter at the web interface of the vulnerable targeted system.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to perform stored XSS attacks on the targeted system.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51739|2024-08-02T22:40:34.202Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 07:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51743|2024-08-02T22:40:34.176Z -- hathway -- skyworth%20router%20cm5100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51743</link>
      <description>This vulnerability exist in Skyworth Router CM5100, version 4.1.1.24, due to insufficient validation of user supplied input for the Set Upstream Channel ID (UCID) parameter at its web interface. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying specially crafted input to the parameter at the web interface of the vulnerable targeted system.   

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to perform a Denial of Service (DoS) attack on the targeted system.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51743|2024-08-02T22:40:34.176Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 08:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51726|2024-08-02T22:40:34.165Z -- hathway -- skyworth%20router%20cm5100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51726</link>
      <description>This vulnerability exist in Skyworth Router CM5100, version 4.1.1.24, due to insufficient validation of user supplied input for the SMTP Server Name parameter at its web interface.  A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying specially crafted input to the parameter at the web interface of the vulnerable targeted system.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to perform stored XSS attacks on the targeted system.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51726|2024-08-02T22:40:34.165Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 06:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51720|2024-08-02T22:40:34.319Z -- hathway -- skyworth%20router%20cm5100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51720</link>
      <description>This vulnerability exist in Skyworth Router CM5100, version 4.1.1.24, due to insufficient validation of user supplied input for the Time Server 1 parameter at its web interface.  A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying specially crafted input to the parameter at the web interface of the vulnerable targeted system.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to perform stored XSS attacks on the targeted system.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51720|2024-08-02T22:40:34.319Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 06:50:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51741|2024-08-02T22:40:34.343Z -- hathway -- skyworth%20router%20cm5100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51741</link>
      <description>This vulnerability exist in Skyworth Router CM5100, version 4.1.1.24, due to transmission of authentication credentials in plaintext over the network. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by eavesdropping on the victim’s network traffic to extract username and password from the web interface (Password Reset Page) of the vulnerable targeted system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51741|2024-08-02T22:40:34.343Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 07:26:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51742|2024-08-02T22:40:34.244Z -- hathway -- skyworth%20router%20cm5100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51742</link>
      <description>This vulnerability exist in Skyworth Router CM5100, version 4.1.1.24, due to insufficient validation of user supplied input for the Add Downstream Frequency parameter at its web interface. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying specially crafted input to the parameter at the web interface of the vulnerable targeted system.   

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to perform a Denial of Service (DoS) attack on the targeted system.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51742|2024-08-02T22:40:34.244Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 07:57:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51735|2024-08-02T22:40:34.318Z -- hathway -- skyworth%20router%20cm5100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51735</link>
      <description>This vulnerability exist in Skyworth Router CM5100, version 4.1.1.24, due to insufficient validation of user supplied input for the Pre-shared key parameter at its web interface.  A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying specially crafted input to the parameter at the web interface of the vulnerable targeted system.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to perform stored XSS attacks on the targeted system.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51735|2024-08-02T22:40:34.318Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 07:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51721|2024-08-02T22:40:34.198Z -- hathway -- skyworth%20router%20cm5100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51721</link>
      <description>This vulnerability exist in Skyworth Router CM5100, version 4.1.1.24, due to insufficient validation of user supplied input for the Time Server 2 parameter at its web interface.  A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying specially crafted input to the parameter at the web interface of the vulnerable targeted system.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to perform stored XSS attacks on the targeted system.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51721|2024-08-02T22:40:34.198Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 06:51:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51727|2024-08-02T22:40:34.218Z -- hathway -- skyworth%20router%20cm5100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51727</link>
      <description>This vulnerability exist in Skyworth Router CM5100, version 4.1.1.24, due to insufficient validation of user supplied input for the SMTP Username parameter at its web interface.  A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying specially crafted input to the parameter at the web interface of the vulnerable targeted system.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to perform stored XSS attacks on the targeted system.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51727|2024-08-02T22:40:34.218Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 07:01:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51740|2024-08-02T22:40:34.176Z -- hathway -- skyworth%20router%20cm5100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51740</link>
      <description>This vulnerability exist in Skyworth Router CM5100, version 4.1.1.24, due to transmission of authentication credentials in plaintext over the network. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by eavesdropping on the victim’s network traffic to extract username and password from the web interface (Login Page) of the vulnerable targeted system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51740|2024-08-02T22:40:34.176Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 07:25:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51736|2024-08-02T22:40:34.209Z -- hathway -- skyworth%20router%20cm5100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51736</link>
      <description>This vulnerability exist in Skyworth Router CM5100, version 4.1.1.24, due to insufficient validation of user supplied input for the L2TP/PPTP Username parameter at its web interface.  A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by supplying specially crafted input to the parameter at the web interface of the vulnerable targeted system.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to perform stored XSS attacks on the targeted system.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51736|2024-08-02T22:40:34.209Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 07:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
