<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd. -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd./all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd. -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 20:23:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17143|2024-09-16T16:13:49.119Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- dp300%3B%20rp200%3B%20rse6500%3B%20te30%3B%20te40%3B%20te50%3B%20te60%3B%20tp3106%3B%20tp3206%3B%20viewpoint%209030%3B%20espace%20u1960%3B%20espace%20u1981
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17143</link>
      <description>SIP module in Huawei DP300 V500R002C00; V500R002C00SPC100; V500R002C00SPC200; V500R002C00SPC300; V500R002C00SPC400; V500R002C00SPC500; V500R002C00SPC600; V500R002C00SPC800; V500R002C00SPC900; V500R002C00SPCa00; RP200 V500R002C00SPC200; V600R006C00; V600R006C00SPC200; RSE6500 V500R002C00SPC100; V500R002C00SPC200; V500R002C00SPC300; V500R002C00SPC300T; V500R002C00SPC500; V500R002C00SPC600; V500R002C00SPC700; V500R002C00T; TE30 V100R001C10; V100R001C10SPC100; V100R001C10SPC200B010; V100R001C10SPC300; V100R001C10SPC500; V100R001C10SPC600; V100R001C10SPC700B010; V100R001C10SPC800; V500R002C00SPC200; V500R002C00SPC500; V500R002C00SPC600; V500R002C00SPC700; V500R002C00SPC900; V500R002C00SPCb00; V600R006C00; TE40 V500R002C00SPC600; V500R002C00SPC700; V500R002C00SPC900; V500R002C00SPCb00; V600R006C00; V600R006C00SPC200; TE50 V500R002C00SPC600; V500R002C00SPC700; V500R002C00SPCb00; V600R006C00; V600R006C00SPC200; TE60 V100R001C01SPC100; V100R001C01SPC107TB010; V100R001C10; V100R001C10SPC300; V100R001C10SPC400; V100R001C10SPC500; V100R001C10SPC600; V100R001C10SPC700; V100R001C10SPC800; V100R001C10SPC900; V500R002C00; V500R002C00SPC100; V500R002C00SPC200; V500R002C00SPC300; V500R002C00SPC600; V500R002C00SPC700; V500R002C00SPC800; V500R002C00SPC900; V500R002C00SPCa00; V500R002C00SPCb00; V500R002C00SPCd00; V600R006C00; V600R006C00SPC100; V600R006C00SPC200; V600R006C00SPC300; TP3106 V100R002C00; V100R002C00SPC200; V100R002C00SPC400; V100R002C00SPC600; V100R002C00SPC700; V100R002C00SPC800; TP3206 V100R002C00; V100R002C00SPC200; V100R002C00SPC400; V100R002C00SPC600; V100R002C00SPC700; V100R002C10; ViewPoint 9030 V100R011C02SPC100; V100R011C03B012SP15; V100R011C03B012SP16; V100R011C03B015SP03; V100R011C03LGWL01SPC100; V100R011C03SPC100; V100R011C03SPC200; V100R011C03SPC300; V100R011C03SPC400; V100R011C03SPC500; eSpace U1960 V200R003C30SPC200; eSpace U1981 V100R001C20SPC700; V200R003C20SPCa00 has an overflow vulnerability that the module cannot parse a malformed SIP message when validating variables. Attacker can exploit it to make one process reboot at random.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17143|2024-09-16T16:13:49.119Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8168|2024-09-16T19:25:15.106Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- fusionsphere%20openstack
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8168</link>
      <description>FusionSphere OpenStack with software V100R006C00SPC102(NFV) and V100R006C10 have an information leak vulnerability. Due to an incorrect configuration item, the information transmitted by a transmission channel is not encrypted. An attacker accessing the internal network may obtain sensitive information transmitted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8168|2024-09-16T19:25:15.106Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8182|2024-09-16T18:08:52.142Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- nice-al00
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8182</link>
      <description>MTK platform in Huawei smart phones with software of earlier than Nice-AL00C00B160 versions, earlier than Nice-AL10C00B140 versions has a out-of-bound read vulnerability. An attacker tricks a user into installing a malicious application on the smart phone, and send given parameter and cause to memory out-of-bound read.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8182|2024-09-16T18:08:52.142Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8170|2024-09-16T17:53:09.689Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- vie-l09
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8170</link>
      <description>Huawei smart phones with software earlier than VIE-L09C40B360 versions have a buffer overflow vulnerability due to the lack of parameter validation. An attacker tricks a user into installing a malicious APP which has the root privilege; the APP can send a specific parameter to the smart phone, causing the smartphone restart or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8170|2024-09-16T17:53:09.689Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8211|2024-09-16T17:59:51.422Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- honor%205c%2Chonor%206x
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8211</link>
      <description>The driver of honor 5C,honor 6x Huawei smart phones with software of versions earlier than NEM-AL10C00B356, versions earlier than Berlin-L21HNC432B360 have a buffer overflow vulnerability due to the lack of parameter validation. An attacker tricks a user into installing a malicious APP which has the root privilege of the Android system, the APP can send a specific parameter to the driver of the smart phone, causing a system reboot or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8211|2024-09-16T17:59:51.422Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8162|2024-09-16T19:41:24.286Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- ar120-s%2Car1200%2Car1200-s%2Car150%2Car150-s%2Car160%2Car200%2Car200-s%2Car2200%2Car2200-s%2Car3200%2Car510%2Cnetengine16ex%2Csmc2.0%2Csrg1300%2Csrg2300%2Csrg3300
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8162</link>
      <description>AR120-S with software V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30,AR1200 with software V200R006C10, V200R006C13, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30,AR1200-S with software V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30,AR150 with software V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30,AR150-S with software V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30,AR160 with software V200R006C10, V200R006C12, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30,AR200 with software V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R008C20, V200R008C30,AR200-S with software V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30,AR2200 with software V200R006C10, V200R006C13, V200R006C16PWE, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30,AR2200-S with software V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30,AR3200 with software V200R006C10, V200R006C11, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R007C02, V200R008C00, V200R008C10, V200R008C20, V200R008C30,AR510 with software V200R006C10, V200R006C12, V200R006C13, V200R006C15, V200R006C16, V200R006C17, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30,NetEngine16EX with software V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30,SMC2.0 with software V100R003C10, V100R005C00, V500R002C00, V600R006C00,SRG1300 with software V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30,SRG2300 with software V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30,SRG3300 with software V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30 have a DoS vulnerability. Due to incorrect malformed message processing logic, an authenticated, remote attacker could send specially crafted message to the target device.Successful exploit of the vulnerability could cause stack overflow and make a service unavailable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8162|2024-09-16T19:41:24.286Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2690|2024-09-16T17:59:42.224Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- softco%2Cespace%20u1910%2Cespace%20u1911%2Cespace%20u1930%2Cespace%20u1960%2Cespace%20u1980%2Cespace%20u1981
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2690</link>
      <description>SoftCo with software V200R003C20,eSpace U1910 with software V200R003C00, V200R003C20 and V200R003C30,eSpace U1911 with software V200R003C20, V200R003C30,eSpace U1930 with software V200R003C20 and V200R003C30,eSpace U1960 with software V200R003C20, V200R003C30,eSpace U1980 with software V200R003C20, V200R003C30,eSpace U1981 with software V200R003C20 and V200R003C30 have an denial of service (DoS) vulnerability, which allow an attacker with specific permission to craft a file containing malicious data and upload it to the device to exhaust memory, causing a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2690|2024-09-16T17:59:42.224Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8206|2024-09-16T19:47:01.452Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- honor%207%20lite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8206</link>
      <description>HONOR 7 Lite mobile phones with software of versions earlier than NEM-L21C432B352 have an App Lock bypass vulnerability. An attacker could perform specific operations to bypass the App Lock to use apps on a target mobile phone temporarily.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8206|2024-09-16T19:47:01.452Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-15316|2024-09-16T17:48:54.343Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- mate%209
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-15316</link>
      <description>The GPU driver of Mate 9 Huawei smart phones with software before MHA-AL00B 8.0.0.334(C00) and Mate 9 Pro Huawei smart phones with software before LON-AL00B 8.0.0.334(C00) has a memory double free vulnerability. An attacker tricks a user into installing a malicious application, and the application can call special API, which triggers double free and causes a system crash or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-15316|2024-09-16T17:48:54.343Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2737|2024-09-16T18:48:42.973Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- vcm5010
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2737</link>
      <description>VCM5010 with software versions earlier before V100R002C50SPC100 has an arbitrary file upload vulnerability. The software does not validate the files that uploaded. An authenticated attacker could upload arbitrary files to the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2737|2024-09-16T18:48:42.973Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17131|2024-09-16T17:09:06.692Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- dp300%3B%20rp200%3B%20te30%3B%20te50%3B%20te60%3B%20vp9660
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17131</link>
      <description>Huawei DP300 V500R002C00; RP200 V500R002C00; V600R006C00; TE30 V100R001C10; V600R006C00; TE50 V600R006C00; TE60 V100R001C10; V500R002C00; V600R006C00; VP9660 V500R002C10 have an DoS vulnerability due to insufficient validation of the parameter when a putty comment key is loaded. An authenticated remote attacker can place a malformed putty key file in system when a system manager load the key an infinite loop happens which lead to reboot the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17131|2024-09-16T17:09:06.692Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2728|2024-09-16T17:53:45.135Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- honor%206x
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2728</link>
      <description>Some Huawei mobile phones Honor 6X Berlin-L22C636B150 and earlier versions have a Bluetooth unlock bypassing vulnerability. If a user has enabled the smart unlock function, an attacker can impersonate the user's Bluetooth device to unlock the user's mobile phone screen.uawei mobile phones have a Bluetooth unlock bypassing vulnerability due to the lack of validation on Bluetooth devices. If a user has enabled the smart unlock function, an attacker can impersonate the user's Bluetooth device to unlock the user's mobile phone screen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2728|2024-09-16T17:53:45.135Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2704|2024-09-16T18:39:09.872Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- smarthome%2Chiapp%2Chwparentcontrol%2Chwparentcontrolparent%2Ccrowdtest%2Chiwallet%2Chuawei%20pay%2Cskytone%2Chwclouddrive%28emui6.0%29%2Chwphonefinder%3F%26%23xa1%3B%26%23xa7%3Bemui6.0%3F%3F%2Chwphonefinder%3F%26%23xa1%3B%26%23xa7%3Bemui5.1%3F%3F%2C
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2704</link>
      <description>Smarthome 1.0.2.364 and earlier versions,HiAPP 7.3.0.303 and earlier versions,HwParentControl 2.0.0 and earlier versions,HwParentControlParent 5.1.0.12 and earlier versions,Crowdtest 1.5.3 and earlier versions,HiWallet 8.0.0.301 and earlier versions,Huawei Pay 8.0.0.300 and earlier versions,Skytone 8.1.2.300 and earlier versions,HwCloudDrive(EMUI6.0) 8.0.0.307 and earlier versions,HwPhoneFinder(EMUI6.0) 9.3.0.310 and earlier versions,HwPhoneFinder(EMUI5.1) 9.2.2.303 and earlier versions,HiCinema 8.0.2.300 and earlier versions,HuaweiWear 21.0.0.360 and earlier versions,HiHealthApp 3.0.3.300 and earlier versions have an information exposure vulnerability. Encryption keys are stored in the system. The attacker can implement reverse engineering to obtain the encryption keys, causing information exposure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2704|2024-09-16T18:39:09.872Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8124|2024-09-16T19:05:42.567Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- uma
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8124</link>
      <description>The UMA product with software V200R001 has a privilege elevation vulnerability due to insufficient validation or improper processing of parameters. An attacker could craft specific packets to exploit these vulnerabilities to gain elevated privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8124|2024-09-16T19:05:42.567Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8132|2024-09-16T17:09:08.649Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- fusionsphere%20openstack
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8132</link>
      <description>The FusionSphere OpenStack with software V100R006C00 and V100R006C10 has a command injection vulnerability due to the insufficient input validation on four TCP listening ports. An unauthenticated attacker can exploit the vulnerabilities to gain root privileges by sending some messages with malicious commands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8132|2024-09-16T17:09:08.649Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8141|2024-09-16T19:20:24.068Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- p10%20plus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8141</link>
      <description>The Touch Panel (TP) driver in P10 Plus smart phones with software versions earlier than VKY-AL00C00B153 has a memory double free vulnerability. An attacker with the root privilege of the Android system tricks a user into installing a malicious application, and the application can start multiple threads and try to free specific memory, which could triggers double free and causes a system crash or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8141|2024-09-16T19:20:24.068Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2730|2024-09-16T19:40:04.204Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- huawei%20hilink%20app%20%28for%20ios%29%2C%20huawei%20tech%20support%20app%20%28for%20ios%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2730</link>
      <description>HUAWEI HiLink APP (for IOS) versions earlier before 5.0.25.306 and HUAWEI Tech Support APP (for IOS) versions earlier before 5.0.0 have an information leak vulnerability. When an iPhone with these APPs installed access the Wi-Fi hotpot built by attacker, the attacker can collect the information of iPhone mode and firmware version.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2730|2024-09-16T19:40:04.204Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8173|2024-09-16T18:24:14.588Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- maya-l02%2Cvky-l09%2Cvtr-l29%2Cvicky-al00a%2Cvictoria-al00a%2Cwarsaw-al00
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8173</link>
      <description>Maya-L02,VKY-L09,VTR-L29,Vicky-AL00A,Victoria-AL00A,Warsaw-AL00 smart phones with software of earlier than Maya-L02C636B126 versions,earlier than VKY-L29C10B151 versions,earlier than VTR-L29C10B151 versions,earlier than Vicky-AL00AC00B162 versions,earlier than Victoria-AL00AC00B167 versions,earlier than Warsaw-AL00C00B200 versions have a Factory Reset Protection (FRP) bypass security vulnerability. When re-configuring the mobile phone using the factory reset protection (FRP) function, an attacker can login the configuration flow by some secret code and can perform some operations to update the Google account. As a result, the FRP function is bypassed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8173|2024-09-16T18:24:14.588Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2721|2024-09-16T19:56:17.268Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- berlin-l21%2Cberlin-l21hn%2Cberlin-l22%2Cberlin-l22hn%2Cberlin-l23%2Cberlin-l24hn%2Cfrd-l02%2Cfrd-l04%2Cfrd-l09%2Cfrd-l14%2Cfrd-l19%2C
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2721</link>
      <description>Some Huawei smart phones with software Berlin-L21C10B130,Berlin-L21C185B133,Berlin-L21HNC10B131,Berlin-L21HNC185B140,Berlin-L21HNC432B151,Berlin-L22C636B160,Berlin-L22HNC636B130,Berlin-L22HNC675B150CUSTC675D001,Berlin-L23C605B131,Berlin-L24HNC567B110,FRD-L02C432B120,FRD-L02C635B130,FRD-L02C675B170CUSTC675D001,FRD-L04C567B162,FRD-L04C605B131,FRD-L09C10B130,FRD-L09C185B130,FRD-L09C432B131,FRD-L09C636B130,FRD-L14C567B162,FRD-L19C10B130,FRD-L19C432B131,FRD-L19C636B130 have a factory Reset Protection (FRP) bypass security vulnerability. When re-configuring the mobile phone using the factory reset protection (FRP) function, an attacker can login the configuration flow by Swype Keyboard and can perform some operations to update the Google account. As a result, the FRP function is bypassed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2721|2024-09-16T19:56:17.268Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8163|2024-09-16T18:09:25.595Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- ar120-s%2Car1200%2Car1200-s%2Car150%2Car150-s%2Car160%2Car200%2Car200-s%2Car2200%2Car2200-s%2Car3200%2Car510%2Cnetengine16ex%2Csmc2.0%2Csrg1300%2Csrg2300%2Csrg3300
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8163</link>
      <description>AR120-S with software V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30,AR1200 with software V200R006C10, V200R006C13, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30,AR1200-S with software V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30,AR150 with software V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30,AR150-S with software V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30,AR160 with software V200R006C10, V200R006C12, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30,AR200 with software V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R008C20, V200R008C30,AR200-S with software V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30,AR2200 with software V200R006C10, V200R006C13, V200R006C16PWE, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30,AR2200-S with software V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30,AR3200 with software V200R006C10, V200R006C11, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R007C02, V200R008C00, V200R008C10, V200R008C20, V200R008C30,AR510 with software V200R006C10, V200R006C12, V200R006C13, V200R006C15, V200R006C16, V200R006C17, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30,NetEngine16EX with software V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30,SMC2.0 with software V100R003C10, V100R005C00, V500R002C00, V600R006C00,SRG1300 with software V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30,SRG2300 with software V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30,SRG3300 with software V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30 have an out-of-bounds read vulnerability. Due to insufficient input validation, an authenticated, remote attacker could send specially crafted message to the target device.Successful exploit of the vulnerability could cause out-of-bounds read and system crash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8163|2024-09-16T18:09:25.595Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-15308|2024-09-16T18:07:47.674Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- ireader
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-15308</link>
      <description>Huawei iReader app before 8.0.2.301 has an input validation vulnerability due to insufficient validation on the URL used for loading network data. An attacker can control app access and load malicious websites created by the attacker, and the code in webpages would be loaded and run.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-15308|2024-09-16T18:07:47.674Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2712|2024-09-16T17:18:28.209Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- s3300
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2712</link>
      <description>S3300 V100R006C05 have an Ethernet in the First Mile (EFM) flapping vulnerability due to the lack of type-length-value (TLV) consistency check. An attacker may craft malformed packets and send them to a device to cause EFM flapping.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2712|2024-09-16T17:18:28.209Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-15307|2024-09-16T19:14:47.687Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- honor%208
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-15307</link>
      <description>Huawei Honor 8 smartphone with software versions earlier than FRD-L04C567B389 and earlier than FRD-L14C567B389 have a permission control vulnerability due to improper authorization configuration on specific device information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-15307|2024-09-16T19:14:47.687Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8138|2024-09-16T19:00:29.212Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- hedex%20lite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8138</link>
      <description>HedEx Earlier than V200R006C00 versions has a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability. An attacker could trick a user into accessing a website containing malicious scripts which may tamper with configurations and interrupt normal services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8138|2024-09-16T19:00:29.212Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17313|2024-09-16T16:23:50.913Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- huawei%20p9%20lite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17313</link>
      <description>The inputhub driver of HUAWEI P9 Lite mobile phones with Versions earlier than VNS-L21C02B341, Versions earlier than VNS-L21C22B380, Versions earlier than VNS-L31C02B341, Versions earlier than VNS-L31C440B390, Versions earlier than VNS-L31C636B396 has a buffer overflow vulnerability due to the lack of parameter validation. An attacker tricks a user into installing a malicious APP and the APP may sends specific data to the inputhub driver to exploit this vulnerability, successful exploit could cause the system reboot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17313|2024-09-16T16:23:50.913Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17136|2024-09-16T16:49:17.056Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- dp300%3B%20ips%20module%3B%20ngfw%20module%3B%20nip6300%3B%20nip6600%3B%20rp200%3B%20s12700%3B%20s1700%3B%20s2700%3B%20s5700%3B%20s6700%3B%20s7700%3B%20s9700%3B%20secospace%20usg6300%3B%20secospace%20usg6500%3B%20secospace%20usg6600%3B%20te30%3B%20te
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17136</link>
      <description>PEM module of Huawei DP300 V500R002C00; IPS Module V500R001C00; V500R001C30; NGFW Module V500R001C00; V500R002C00; NIP6300 V500R001C00; V500R001C30; NIP6600 V500R001C00; V500R001C30; RP200 V500R002C00; V600R006C00; S12700 V200R007C00; V200R007C01; V200R008C00; V200R009C00; V200R010C00; S1700 V200R006C10; V200R009C00; V200R010C00; S2700 V200R006C10; V200R007C00; V200R008C00; V200R009C00; V200R010C00; S5700 V200R006C00; V200R007C00; V200R008C00; V200R009C00; V200R010C00; S6700 V200R008C00; V200R009C00; V200R010C00; S7700 V200R007C00; V200R008C00; V200R009C00; V200R010C00; S9700 V200R007C00; V200R007C01; V200R008C00; V200R009C00; V200R010C00; Secospace USG6300 V500R001C00; V500R001C30; Secospace USG6500 V500R001C00; V500R001C30; Secospace USG6600 V500R001C00; V500R001C30S; TE30 V100R001C02; V100R001C10; V500R002C00; V600R006C00; TE40 V500R002C00; V600R006C00; TE50 V500R002C00; V600R006C00; TE60 V100R001C01; V100R001C10; V500R002C00; V600R006C00; TP3106 V100R002C00; TP3206 V100R002C00; V100R002C10; USG9500 V500R001C00; V500R001C30; ViewPoint 9030 V100R011C02; V100R011C03 has a heap overflow vulnerability due to insufficient verification. An authenticated local attacker can make processing crash by a malicious certificate. The attacker can exploit this vulnerability to cause a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17136|2024-09-16T16:49:17.056Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8145|2024-09-16T19:20:17.219Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- p10%2C%20p10%20plus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8145</link>
      <description>The call module of P10 and P10 Plus smartphones with software versions before VTR-AL00C00B167, versions before VTR-TL00C01B167, versions before VKY-AL00C00B167, versions before VKY-TL00C01B167 has a DoS vulnerability. An attacker may trick a user into installing a malicious application, and the application can send given parameter to call module to crash the call and data communication process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8145|2024-09-16T19:20:17.219Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8156|2024-09-16T17:17:41.313Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- b2338-168
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8156</link>
      <description>The outdoor unit of Customer Premise Equipment (CPE) product B2338-168 V100R001C00 has a no authentication vulnerability on the serial port. An attacker can access the serial port on the circuit board of the outdoor unit and log in to the CPE without authentication. Successful exploit could allow the attacker to take control over the outdoor unit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8156|2024-09-16T17:17:41.313Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8213|2024-09-16T17:54:04.082Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- smc2.0
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8213</link>
      <description>Huawei SMC2.0 with software of V100R003C10, V100R005C00SPC100, V100R005C00SPC101B001T, V100R005C00SPC102, V100R005C00SPC103, V100R005C00SPC200, V100R005C00SPC201T, V500R002C00, V600R006C00 has an input validation vulnerability when handle TLS and DTLS handshake with certificate. Due to the insufficient validation of received PKI certificates, remote attackers could exploit this vulnerability to crash the TLS module.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8213|2024-09-16T17:54:04.082Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8205|2024-09-16T19:09:16.589Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- honor%209
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8205</link>
      <description>The Bastet driver of Honor 9 Huawei smart phones with software of versions earlier than Stanford-AL10C00B175 has integer overflow vulnerability due to the lack of parameter validation. An attacker tricks a user into installing a malicious APP which has the root privilege; the APP can send a specific parameter to the driver of the smart phone, causing arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8205|2024-09-16T19:09:16.589Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7920|2024-09-16T17:02:44.446Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- ar1200%2C%20ar160%2C%20ar200%2C%20ar2200%2C%20ar3200
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7920</link>
      <description>Huawei AR1200 V200R006C10SPC300, AR160 V200R006C10SPC300, AR200 V200R006C10SPC300, AR2200 V200R006C10SPC300, AR3200 V200R006C10SPC300 devices have an improper resource management vulnerability. Due to the improper implementation of ACL mechanism, a remote attacker may send TCP messages to the management interface of the affected device to exploit this vulnerability. Successful exploit could exhaust the socket resource of management interface, leading to a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7920|2024-09-16T17:02:44.446Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-15319|2024-09-16T17:33:21.408Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- rp200
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-15319</link>
      <description>RP200 V500R002C00, V600R006C00; TE30 V100R001C10, V500R002C00, V600R006C00; TE40 V500R002C00, V600R006C00; TE50 V500R002C00, V600R006C00; TE60 V100R001C10, V500R002C00, V600R006C00 have an out-of-bounds read vulnerabilities in some Huawei products. Due to insufficient input validation, a remote attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending specially crafted SS7 related packets to the target devices. Successful exploit will cause out-of-bounds read and possibly crash the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-15319|2024-09-16T17:33:21.408Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8147|2024-09-16T17:03:05.616Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- ac6005%2Cac6605%2Car1200%2Car200%2Car3200%2Ccloudengine%2012800%2Ccloudengine%205800%2Ccloudengine%206800%2Ccloudengine%207800%2Ccloudengine%208800%2Ce600%2Cs12700%2Cs1700%2Cs2300%2Cs2700%2Cs5300%2Cs5700%2Cs6300%2Cs6700%2Cs7700%2Cs9300%2Cs9700%2Cseco
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8147</link>
      <description>AC6005 V200R006C10SPC200,AC6605 V200R006C10SPC200,AR1200 with software V200R005C10CP0582T, V200R005C10HP0581T, V200R005C20SPC026T,AR200 with software V200R005C20SPC026T,AR3200 V200R005C20SPC026T,CloudEngine 12800 with software V100R003C00, V100R005C00, V100R005C10, V100R006C00, V200R001C00,CloudEngine 5800 with software V100R003C00, V100R005C00, V100R005C10, V100R006C00, V200R001C00,CloudEngine 6800 with software V100R003C00, V100R005C00, V100R005C10, V100R006C00, V200R001C00,CloudEngine 7800 with software V100R003C00, V100R005C00, V100R005C10, V100R006C00, V200R001C00,CloudEngine 8800 with software V100R006C00, V200R001C00,E600 V200R008C00,S12700 with software V200R005C00, V200R006C00, V200R007C00, V200R008C00,S1700 with software V100R006C00, V100R007C00, V200R006C00,S2300 with software V100R005C00, V100R006C00, V100R006C03, V100R006C05, V200R003C00, V200R003C02, V200R003C10, V200R005C00, V200R005C01, V200R005C02, V200R005C03, V200R006C00, V200R007C00, V200R008C00,S2700 with software V100R005C00, V100R006C00, V100R006C03, V100R006C05, V200R003C00, V200R003C02, V200R003C10, V200R005C00, V200R005C01, V200R005C02, V200R005C03, V200R006C00, V200R007C00, V200R008C00,S5300 with software V100R005C00, V100R006C00, V100R006C01, V200R001C00, V200R001C01, V200R002C00, V200R003C00, V200R003C02, V200R003C10, V200R005C00, V200R006C00, V200R007C00, V200R008C00,S5700 with software V100R005C00, V100R006C00, V100R006C01, V200R001C00, V200R001C01, V200R002C00, V200R003C00, V200R003C02, V200R003C10, V200R005C00, V200R006C00, V200R007C00, V200R008C00,S6300 with software V100R006C00, V200R001C00, V200R001C01, V200R002C00, V200R003C00, V200R003C02, V200R003C10, V200R005C00, V200R008C00,S6700 with software V100R006C00, V200R001C00, V200R001C01, V200R002C00, V200R003C00, V200R003C02, V200R003C10, V200R005C00, V200R006C00, V200R007C00, V200R008C00,S7700 with software V100R003C00, V100R006C00, V200R001C00, V200R001C01, V200R002C00, V200R003C00, V200R005C00, V200R006C00, V200R007C00, V200R008C00,S9300 with software V100R001C00, V100R002C00, V100R003C00, V100R006C00, V200R001C00, V200R002C00, V200R003C00, V200R005C00, V200R006C00, V200R007C00, V200R008C00, V200R008C10,S9700 with software V200R001C00, V200R002C00, V200R003C00, V200R005C00, V200R006C00, V200R007C00, V200R008C00,Secospace USG6600 V500R001C00SPC050 have a MaxAge LSA vulnerability due to improper OSPF implementation. When the device receives special LSA packets, the LS (Link Status) age would be set to MaxAge, 3600 seconds. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability to poison the route table and launch a DoS attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8147|2024-09-16T17:03:05.616Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2706|2024-09-16T19:52:31.579Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- mate%209
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2706</link>
      <description>Mate 9 smartphones with software MHA-AL00AC00B125 have a directory traversal vulnerability in Push module. Since the system does not verify the file name during decompression, system directories are traversed. It could be exploited to cause the attacker to replace files and impact the service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2706|2024-09-16T19:52:31.579Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17133|2024-09-16T16:18:23.021Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- vp9660
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17133</link>
      <description>Huawei VP9660 V500R002C10 has a null pointer reference vulnerability in license module due to insufficient verification. An authenticated local attacker could place a malicious license file into system which cause memory null pointer accessing and related processing crash. The attacker can exploit this vulnerability to cause a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17133|2024-09-16T16:18:23.021Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2691|2024-09-16T19:35:38.240Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- huawei%20p9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2691</link>
      <description>Huawei P9 versions earlier before EVA-AL10C00B373, versions earlier before EVA-CL00C92B373, versions earlier before EVA-DL00C17B373, versions earlier before EVA-TL00C01B373 have a lock-screen bypass vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker could force the phone to the fastboot mode and delete the user's password file during the reboot process, then login the phone without screen lock password after reboot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2691|2024-09-16T19:35:38.240Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2716|2024-09-16T19:01:35.238Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- mate%209
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2716</link>
      <description>The camerafs driver in Mate 9 Versions earlier than MHA-AL00BC00B173 has buffer overflow vulnerability. An attacker tricks a user into installing a malicious application which has the system privilege of the Android system and sends a specific parameter to the driver of the smart phone, causing a system crash or privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2716|2024-09-16T19:01:35.238Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8216|2024-09-16T18:08:28.638Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- warsaw
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8216</link>
      <description>Warsaw Huawei Smart phones with software of versions earlier than Warsaw-AL00C00B180, versions earlier than Warsaw-TL10C01B180 have a permission control vulnerability. Due to improper authorization on specific processes, an attacker with the root privilege of a mobile Android system can exploit this vulnerability to obtain some information of the user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8216|2024-09-16T18:08:28.638Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8148|2024-09-16T18:17:50.876Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- p9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8148</link>
      <description>Audio driver in P9 smartphones with software The versions before EVA-AL10C00B389 has a denial of service (DoS) vulnerability. An attacker tricks a user into installing a malicious application on the smart phone, and the race condition cause null pointer accessing during the application access shared resource, which make the system reboot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8148|2024-09-16T18:17:50.876Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2732|2024-09-16T19:36:25.305Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- huawei%20hilink%20app%20%28for%20ios%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2732</link>
      <description>Huawei Hilink APP Versions earlier before 5.0.25.306 has an information leak vulnerability. An attacker may trick a user into installing a malicious application and application can access Hilink APP data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2732|2024-09-16T19:36:25.305Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8159|2024-09-16T19:40:02.593Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- agassi-l09hn%2Cagassi-w09hn%2Ckobe-l09ahn%2Ckobe-w09chn%2C
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8159</link>
      <description>Some Huawei smartphones with software AGS-L09C233B019,AGS-W09C233B019,KOB-L09C233B017,KOB-W09C233B012 have a type confusion vulnerability. The program initializes a variable using one type, but it later accesses that variable using a type that is different with the original type when do certain register operation. Successful exploit could result in buffer overflow then may cause malicious code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8159|2024-09-16T19:40:02.593Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8196|2024-09-16T16:18:54.511Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- fusionsphere
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8196</link>
      <description>FusionSphere V100R006C00SPC102(NFV) has an incorrect authorization vulnerability. An authenticated attacker could execute commands that he/she should have had no permission to perform, thereby querying, modifying, and deleting certain service data and making the service unavailable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8196|2024-09-16T16:18:54.511Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2736|2024-09-16T18:19:02.117Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- vcm5010
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2736</link>
      <description>VCM5010 with software versions earlier before V100R002C50SPC100 has a command injection vulnerability. This is due to insufficient validation of user's input. An authenticated attacker could launch a command injection attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2736|2024-09-16T18:19:02.117Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8198|2024-09-16T17:22:40.441Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- fusionsphere
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8198</link>
      <description>FusionSphere V100R006C00SPC102(NFV) has an SQL injection vulnerability. An authenticated, remote attacker could craft interface messages carrying malicious SQL statements and send them to a target device. Successful exploit could allow the attacker to launch an SQL injection attack and execute SQL commands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8198|2024-09-16T17:22:40.441Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8157|2024-09-16T18:55:14.643Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- oceanstor%205800%20v3%2C%20oceanstor%206900%20v3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8157</link>
      <description>OceanStor 5800 V3 with software V300R002C00 and V300R002C10, OceanStor 6900 V3 V300R001C00 has an information leakage vulnerability. Products use TLS1.0 to encrypt. Attackers can exploit TLS1.0's vulnerabilities to decrypt data to obtain sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8157|2024-09-16T18:55:14.643Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8149|2024-09-16T19:36:58.329Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- p10%2C%20p10%20plus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8149</link>
      <description>The boot loaders of P10 and P10 Plus Huawei mobile phones with software the versions before Victoria-L09AC605B162, the versions before Victoria-L29AC605B162, the versions before Vicky-L29AC605B162 have an out-of-bounds memory access vulnerability due to the lack of parameter validation. An attacker with the root privilege of an Android system may trick a user into installing a malicious APP. the APP can modify specific data to cause buffer overflow in the next system reboot, causing out-of-bounds memory read which can continuous system reboot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8149|2024-09-16T19:36:58.329Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8127|2024-09-16T18:38:18.173Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- uma
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8127</link>
      <description>The UMA product with software V200R001 has a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could craft malicious links or scripts to launch XSS attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8127|2024-09-16T18:38:18.173Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-15318|2024-09-16T16:58:54.555Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- rp200
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-15318</link>
      <description>RP200 V500R002C00, V600R006C00; TE30 V100R001C10, V500R002C00, V600R006C00; TE40 V500R002C00, V600R006C00; TE50 V500R002C00, V600R006C00; TE60 V100R001C10, V500R002C00, V600R006C00 have an out-of-bounds read vulnerabilities in some Huawei products. Due to insufficient input validation, a remote attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending specially crafted SS7 related packets to the target devices. Successful exploit will cause out-of-bounds read and possibly crash the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-15318|2024-09-16T16:58:54.555Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2708|2024-09-16T19:41:47.213Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- nice
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2708</link>
      <description>The 'Find Phone' function in Nice smartphones with software versions earlier before Nice-AL00C00B0135 has an authentication bypass vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker may wipe and factory reset the phone by special steps. Due to missing authentication of the 'Find Phone' function, an attacker may exploit the vulnerability to bypass the 'Find Phone' function in order to use the phone normally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2708|2024-09-16T19:41:47.213Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8214|2024-09-16T19:56:55.971Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- honor%208%2Chonor%20v8%2Chonor%209%2Chonor%20v9%2Cnova%202%2Cnova%202%20plus%2Cp9%2Cp10%20plus%2Ctoronto
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8214</link>
      <description>Honor 8,Honor V8,Honor 9,Honor V9,Nova 2,Nova 2 Plus,P9,P10 Plus,Toronto Huawei smart phones with software of versions earlier than FRD-AL00C00B391, versions earlier than FRD-DL00C00B391, versions earlier than KNT-AL10C00B391, versions earlier than KNT-AL20C00B391, versions earlier than KNT-UL10C00B391, versions earlier than KNT-TL10C00B391, versions earlier than Stanford-AL00C00B175, versions earlier than Stanford-AL10C00B175, versions earlier than Stanford-TL00C01B175, versions earlier than Duke-AL20C00B191, versions earlier than Duke-TL30C01B191, versions earlier than Picasso-AL00C00B162, versions earlier than Picasso-TL00C01B162 , versions earlier than Barca-AL00C00B162, versions earlier than Barca-TL00C00B162, versions earlier than EVA-AL10C00B396SP03, versions earlier than EVA-CL00C92B396, versions earlier than EVA-DL00C17B396, versions earlier than EVA-TL00C01B396 , versions earlier than Vicky-AL00AC00B172, versions earlier than Toronto-AL00AC00B191, versions earlier than Toronto-TL10C01B191 have an unlock code verification bypassing vulnerability. An attacker with the root privilege of a mobile can exploit this vulnerability to bypass the unlock code verification and unlock the mobile phone bootloader.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8214|2024-09-16T19:56:55.971Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2726|2024-09-16T19:35:21.989Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- p10%20plus%2Cp10
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2726</link>
      <description>Bastet in P10 Plus and P10 smart phones with software earlier than VKY-AL00C00B123 versions, earlier than VTR-AL00C00B123 versions have a buffer overflow vulnerability. An attacker with the root privilege of an Android system may trick a user into installing a malicious APP. The APP can modify specific data to cause buffer overflow in the next system reboot, causing continuous system reboot or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2726|2024-09-16T19:35:21.989Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8150|2024-09-16T16:48:35.815Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- p10%2C%20p10%20plus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8150</link>
      <description>The boot loaders of P10 and P10 Plus Huawei mobile phones with software the versions before Victoria-L09AC605B162, the versions before Victoria-L29AC605B162, the versions before Vicky-L29AC605B162 have an arbitrary memory write vulnerability due to the lack of parameter validation. An attacker with the root privilege of an Android system may trick a user into installing a malicious APP. The APP can modify specific data to cause arbitrary memory writing in the next system reboot, causing continuous system reboot or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8150|2024-09-16T16:48:35.815Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8120|2024-09-16T17:19:03.398Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- uma
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8120</link>
      <description>The UMA product with software V200R001 and V300R001 has a privilege elevation vulnerability due to insufficient validation or improper processing of parameters. An attacker could craft specific packets to exploit these vulnerabilities to gain elevated privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8120|2024-09-16T17:19:03.398Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8142|2024-09-16T19:04:22.668Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- mate%209%2C%20mate%209%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8142</link>
      <description>The Trusted Execution Environment (TEE) module driver of Mate 9 and Mate 9 Pro smart phones with software versions earlier than MHA-AL00BC00B221 and versions earlier than LON-AL00BC00B221 has a use after free (UAF) vulnerability. An attacker tricks a user into installing a malicious application, and the application can start multiple threads and try to create and free specific memory, which could triggers access memory after free it and causes a system crash or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8142|2024-09-16T19:04:22.668Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2720|2024-09-16T18:28:20.258Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- fusionsphere%20openstack
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2720</link>
      <description>FusionSphere OpenStack V100R006C00 has an information exposure vulnerability. The software uses hard-coded cryptographic key to encrypt messages between certain components, which significantly increases the possibility that encrypted data may be recovered and results in information exposure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2720|2024-09-16T18:28:20.258Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2724|2024-09-16T17:08:46.366Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- p10%20plus%2Cp10
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2724</link>
      <description>Bastet in P10 Plus and P10 smart phones with software earlier than VKY-AL00C00B123 versions, earlier than VTR-AL00C00B123 versions have a buffer overflow vulnerability. An attacker with the root privilege of an Android system may trick a user into installing a malicious APP. The APP can modify specific data to cause buffer overflow in the next system reboot, causing continuous system reboot or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2724|2024-09-16T17:08:46.366Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2702|2024-09-16T16:48:33.458Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- mate%209
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2702</link>
      <description>Phone Finder in versions earlier before MHA-AL00C00B170 can be bypass. An attacker can bypass the Phone Finder by special steps and obtain the owner of the phone.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2702|2024-09-16T16:48:33.458Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2714|2024-09-16T17:28:20.699Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- fusionsphere%20openstack
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2714</link>
      <description>The GaussDB in FusionSphere OpenStack V100R005C10SPC705 and earlier versions has a buffer overflow vulnerability. An authenticated attacker on the LAN can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code or cause a denial of service (DoS) condition in the affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2714|2024-09-16T17:28:20.699Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2700|2024-09-16T16:53:35.031Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- ac6005%2Cac6605
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2700</link>
      <description>AC6005 with software V200R006C10, AC6605 with software V200R006C10 have a DoS Vulnerability. An attacker can send malformed packets to the device, which causes the device memory leaks, leading to DoS attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2700|2024-09-16T16:53:35.031Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-15313|2024-09-16T18:24:49.452Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- smartcare
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-15313</link>
      <description>Huawei SmartCare V200R003C10 has a CSV injection vulnerability. An remote authenticated attacker could inject malicious CSV expression to the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-15313|2024-09-16T18:24:49.452Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
