<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd. -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd./all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd. -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 13:23:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7911|2024-08-05T06:37:59.589Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- alp-al00b%2C%20alp-al00b-rsc%2C%20bla-tl00b%2C%20charlotte-al00a%2C%20emily-al00a%2C
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7911</link>
      <description>Some Huawei smart phones ALP-AL00B 8.0.0.106(C00), 8.0.0.113(SP2C00), 8.0.0.113(SP3C00), 8.0.0.113(SP7C00), 8.0.0.118(C00), 8.0.0.120(SP2C00), 8.0.0.125(SP1C00), 8.0.0.125(SP3C00), 8.0.0.126(SP2C00), 8.0.0.126(SP5C00), 8.0.0.127(SP1C00), 8.0.0.128(SP2C00), ALP-AL00B-RSC 1.0.0.2, BLA-TL00B 8.0.0.113(SP7C01), 8.0.0.118(C01), 8.0.0.120(SP2C01), 8.0.0.125(SP1C01), 8.0.0.125(SP2C01), 8.0.0.125(SP3C01), 8.0.0.126(SP2C01), 8.0.0.126(SP5C01), 8.0.0.127(SP1C01), 8.0.0.128(SP2C01), 8.0.0.129(SP2C01), Charlotte-AL00A 8.1.0.105(SP7C00), 8.1.0.106(SP3C00), 8.1.0.107(SP5C00), 8.1.0.107(SP7C00), 8.1.0.108(SP3C00), 8.1.0.108(SP6C00), 8.1.0.109(SP2C00), Emily-AL00A 8.1.0.105(SP6C00), 8.1.0.106(SP2C00), 8.1.0.107(SP5C00), 8.1.0.107(SP7C00), 8.1.0.108(SP2C00), 8.1.0.108(SP6C00), 8.1.0.109(SP5C00) have a Factory Reset Protection (FRP) bypass security vulnerability. When re-configuring the mobile phone using the factory reset protection (FRP) function, an attacker can login the configuration flow by Gaode Map and can perform some operations to update the Google account. As a result, the FRP function is bypassed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7911|2024-08-05T06:37:59.589Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7940|2024-08-05T06:37:59.778Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- huawei%20mate%2010%2C%20huawei%20mate%2010%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7940</link>
      <description>Huawei smart phones Mate 10 and Mate 10 Pro with earlier versions than 8.0.0.129(SP2C00) and earlier versions than 8.0.0.129(SP2C01) have an authentication bypass vulnerability. An attacker with high privilege obtains the smart phone and bypass the activation function by some specific operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7940|2024-08-05T06:37:59.778Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7901|2024-08-05T06:37:59.620Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- alp-al00b%2C%20bla-al00b
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7901</link>
      <description>RCS module in Huawei ALP-AL00B smart phones with software versions earlier than 8.0.0.129, BLA-AL00B smart phones with software versions earlier than 8.0.0.129 has a remote control vulnerability. An attacker can trick a user to install a malicious application. When the application connects with RCS for the first time, it needs user to manually click to agree. In addition, the attacker needs to obtain the key that RCS uses to authenticate the application. Successful exploitation may cause the attacker to control keyboard remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7901|2024-08-05T06:37:59.620Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7902|2024-08-05T06:37:59.561Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- 1288h%20v5%3B%202288h%20v5
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7902</link>
      <description>Huawei 1288H V5 and 288H V5 with software of V100R005C00 have a JSON injection vulnerability. An authenticated, remote attacker can launch a JSON injection to modify the password of administrator. Due to insufficient verification of the input, this could be exploited to obtain the management privilege of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7902|2024-08-05T06:37:59.561Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7904|2024-08-05T06:37:59.664Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- 1288h%20v5%3B%202288h%20v5
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7904</link>
      <description>Huawei 1288H V5 and 288H V5 with software of V100R005C00 have a JSON injection vulnerability. An authenticated, remote attacker can launch a JSON injection to modify the password of administrator. Due to insufficient verification of the input, this could be exploited to obtain the management privilege of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7904|2024-08-05T06:37:59.664Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7903|2024-08-05T06:37:59.644Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- 1288h%20v5%3B%202288h%20v5
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7903</link>
      <description>Huawei 1288H V5 and 288H V5 with software of V100R005C00 have a JSON injection vulnerability. An authenticated, remote attacker can launch a JSON injection to modify the password of administrator. Due to insufficient verification of the input, this could be exploited to obtain the management privilege of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7903|2024-08-05T06:37:59.644Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7929|2024-08-05T06:37:59.615Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- mate%20rs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7929</link>
      <description>Huawei Mate RS smartphones with the versions before NEO-AL00D 8.1.0.167(C786) have a lock-screen bypass vulnerability. An attacker could unlock and use the phone through certain operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7929|2024-08-05T06:37:59.615Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7922|2024-08-05T06:37:59.643Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- alp-l09
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7922</link>
      <description>Huawei ALP-L09 smart phones with versions earlier than ALP-L09 8.0.0.150(C432) have an insufficient input validation vulnerability due to lack of parameter check. An attacker tricks the user who has root privilege to install a crafted application, the application may modify the specific data to exploit the vulnerability. Successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7922|2024-08-05T06:37:59.643Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7934|2024-08-05T06:37:59.577Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- mate%2010%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7934</link>
      <description>Some Huawei mobile phone with the versions before BLA-L29 8.0.0.145(C432) have a denial of service (DoS) vulnerability because they do not adapt to specific screen gestures. An attacker may trick users into installing a malicious app. As a result, apps running on the frontend crash after the users make specific screen gestures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7934|2024-08-05T06:37:59.577Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7921|2024-08-05T06:37:59.642Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- b315s-22
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7921</link>
      <description>Huawei B315s-22 products with software of 21.318.01.00.26 have an information leak vulnerability. Unauthenticated adjacent attackers may exploit this vulnerability to obtain device information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7921|2024-08-05T06:37:59.642Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7992|2024-08-05T06:37:59.654Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- mediapad%20m3%3B%20mate%209%20pro%3B%20p10%20plus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7992</link>
      <description>Mdapt Driver of Huawei MediaPad M3 BTV-W09C128B353CUSTC128D001; Mate 9 Pro versions earlier than 8.0.0.356(C00); P10 Plus versions earlier than 8.0.0.357(C00) has a buffer overflow vulnerability. The driver does not sufficiently validate the input, an attacker could trick the user to install a malicious application which would send crafted parameters to the driver. Successful exploit could cause a denial of service condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7992|2024-08-05T06:37:59.654Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7939|2024-08-05T06:37:59.646Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- g9%20lite%2C%20honor%205a%2C%20honor%206x%2C%20honor%208
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7939</link>
      <description>Huawei smart phones G9 Lite, Honor 5A, Honor 6X, Honor 8 with the versions before VNS-L53C605B120CUSTC605D103, the versions before CAM-L03C605B143CUSTC605D008, the versions before CAM-L21C10B145, the versions before CAM-L21C185B156, the versions before CAM-L21C223B133, the versions before CAM-L21C432B210, the versions before CAM-L21C464B170, the versions before CAM-L21C636B245, the versions before Berlin-L21C10B372, the versions before Berlin-L21C185B363, the versions before Berlin-L21C464B137, the versions before Berlin-L23C605B161, the versions before FRD-L09C10B387, the versions before FRD-L09C185B387, the versions before FRD-L09C432B398, the versions before FRD-L09C636B387, the versions before FRD-L19C10B387, the versions before FRD-L19C432B399, the versions before FRD-L19C636B387 have a Factory Reset Protection (FRP) bypass security vulnerability. When re-configuring the mobile phone using the factory reset protection (FRP) function, an attacker can disable the boot wizard by enable the talkback function. As a result, the FRP function is bypassed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7939|2024-08-05T06:37:59.646Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7936|2024-08-05T06:37:59.650Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- mate%2010%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7936</link>
      <description>Mate 10 Pro Huawei smart phones with the versions before BLA-L29 8.0.0.148(C432) have a Factory Reset Protection (FRP) bypass security vulnerability. When re-configuring the mobile phone using the factory reset protection (FRP) function, an attacker can connect the phone with PC and send special instructions to install third party desktop and disable the boot wizard. As a result, the FRP function is bypassed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7936|2024-08-05T06:37:59.650Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7976|2024-08-05T06:37:59.634Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- espace%20desktop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7976</link>
      <description>There is a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Huawei eSpace Desktop V300R001C00 and V300R001C50 version. Due to the insufficient validation of the input, an authenticated, remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to send abnormal messages to the system and perform a XSS attack. A successful exploit could cause the eSpace Desktop to hang up, and the function will restore to normal after restarting the eSpace Desktop.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7976|2024-08-05T06:37:59.634Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7994|2024-08-05T06:37:59.640Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- ngfw%20module%3B%20nip6300%3B%20nip6600%3B%20nip6800%3B%20secospace%20usg6600%3B%20usg9500
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7994</link>
      <description>Some Huawei products IPS Module V500R001C50; NGFW Module V500R001C50; V500R002C10; NIP6300 V500R001C50; NIP6600 V500R001C50; NIP6800 V500R001C50; Secospace USG6600 V500R001C50; USG9500 V500R001C50 have a memory leak vulnerability. The software does not release allocated memory properly when processing Protal questionnaire. A remote attacker could send a lot questionnaires to the device, successful exploit could cause the device to reboot since running out of memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7994|2024-08-05T06:37:59.640Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7950|2024-08-05T06:37:59.581Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- 1288h%20v5%3B%202288h%20v5%3B%202488%20v5%20%3B%20ch121%20v3%3B%20ch121l%20v3%3B%20ch121l%20v5%20%3B%20ch121%20v5%20%3B%20ch140%20v3%3B%20ch140l%20v3%3B%20ch220%20v3%3B%20ch222%20v3%3B%20ch242%20v3%3B%20ch242%20v5%20%3B%20rh1288%20v3%3B%20rh2288%20v3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7950</link>
      <description>The iBMC (Intelligent Baseboard Management Controller) of some Huawei servers have a JSON injection vulnerability due to insufficient input validation. An authenticated, remote attacker can launch a JSON injection to modify the password of administrator. Successful exploit may allow attackers to obtain the management privilege of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7950|2024-08-05T06:37:59.581Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7993|2024-08-05T06:37:59.689Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- huawei%20mate%2010
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7993</link>
      <description>HUAWEI Mate 10 smartphones with versions earlier than ALP-AL00 8.1.0.311 have a use after free vulnerability on mediaserver component. An attacker tricks the user install a malicious application, which make the software to reference memory after it has been freed. Successful exploit could cause execution of arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7993|2024-08-05T06:37:59.689Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7924|2024-08-05T06:37:59.606Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- anne-al00
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7924</link>
      <description>Anne-AL00 Huawei phones with versions earlier than 8.0.0.151(C00) have an information leak vulnerability. Due to improper permission settings for specific commands, attackers who can connect to a mobile phone via the USB interface may exploit this vulnerability to obtain specific device information of the mobile phone.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7924|2024-08-05T06:37:59.606Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7961|2024-08-05T06:37:59.690Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- emily-al00a
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7961</link>
      <description>There is a smart SMS verification code vulnerability in some Huawei smart phones. An attacker should trick a user to access malicious Website or malicious App and register. Due to incorrect processing of the smart SMS verification code, successful exploitation can cause sensitive information leak.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7961|2024-08-05T06:37:59.690Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7959|2024-08-05T06:37:59.691Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- espace%207950
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7959</link>
      <description>There is a short key vulnerability in Huawei eSpace product. An unauthenticated, remote attacker launches man-in-the-middle attack to intercept and decrypt the call information when the user enables SRTP to make a call. Successful exploitation may cause sensitive information leak.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7959|2024-08-05T06:37:59.691Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7930|2024-08-05T06:37:59.746Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- mate%209
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7930</link>
      <description>The Near Field Communication (NFC) module in Mate 9 Huawei mobile phones with the versions before MHA-L29B 8.0.0.366(C567) has an information leak vulnerability due to insufficient validation on data transfer requests. When an affected mobile phone sends files to an attacker's mobile phone using the NFC function, the attacker can obtain arbitrary files from the mobile phone, causing information leaks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7930|2024-08-05T06:37:59.746Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7988|2024-08-05T06:37:59.673Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- huawei%20nova%202%20plus%2C%20huawei%20mate9%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7988</link>
      <description>There is a Factory Reset Protection (FRP) bypass vulnerability on several smartphones. The system does not sufficiently verify the permission, an attacker uses a data cable to connect the smartphone to another smartphone and then perform a series of specific operations. Successful exploit could allow the attacker bypass the FRP protection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7988|2024-08-05T06:37:59.673Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7926|2024-08-05T06:37:59.641Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- huawei%20watch%202
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7926</link>
      <description>Huawei Watch 2 with versions and earlier than OWDD.180707.001.E1 have an improper authorization vulnerability. Due to improper permission configuration for specific operations, an attacker who obtained the Huawei ID bound to the watch can bypass permission verification to perform specific operations and modify some data on the watch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7926|2024-08-05T06:37:59.641Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7923|2024-08-05T06:37:59.640Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- alp-l09
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7923</link>
      <description>Huawei ALP-L09 smart phones with versions earlier than ALP-L09 8.0.0.150(C432) have an insufficient input validation vulnerability due to lack of parameter check. An attacker tricks the user who has root privilege to install a crafted application, the application may modify the specific data to exploit the vulnerability. Successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7923|2024-08-05T06:37:59.640Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7989|2024-08-05T06:37:59.692Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- mate%2010%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7989</link>
      <description>Huawei Mate 10 pro smartphones with the versions before BLA-AL00B 8.1.0.326(C00) have an improper authentication vulnerability. App Lock is a function to prevent unauthorized use of apps on smartphones, an attacker could directly change the lock password after a series of operations. Successful exploit could allow the attacker to use the application which is locked.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7989|2024-08-05T06:37:59.692Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7991|2024-08-05T06:37:59.760Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- mate10
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7991</link>
      <description>Huawei smartphones Mate10 with versions earlier before ALP-AL00B 8.0.0.110(C00) have a Factory Reset Protection (FRP) bypass vulnerability. The system does not sufficiently verify the permission, an attacker uses a data cable to connect the smartphone to the computer and then perform some specific operations. Successful exploit could allow the attacker bypass the FRP protection to access the system setting page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7991|2024-08-05T06:37:59.760Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7925|2024-08-05T06:37:59.625Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- emily-al00a
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7925</link>
      <description>The radio module of some Huawei smartphones Emily-AL00A The versions before 8.1.0.171(C00) have a lock-screen bypass vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker could start third-part input method APP through certain operations to bypass lock-screen by exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7925|2024-08-05T06:37:59.625Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7928|2024-08-05T06:37:59.646Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- mycloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7928</link>
      <description>There is a security vulnerability which could lead to Factory Reset Protection (FRP) bypass in the MyCloud APP with the versions before 8.1.2.303 installed on some Huawei smart phones. When re-configuring the mobile phone using the FRP function, an attacker can replace the old account with a new one through special steps by exploit this vulnerability. As a result, the FRP function is bypassed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7928|2024-08-05T06:37:59.646Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7949|2024-08-05T06:37:59.717Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- 1288h%20v5%3B%202288h%20v5%3B%202488%20v5%20%3B%20ch121%20v3%3B%20ch121l%20v3%3B%20ch121l%20v5%20%3B%20ch121%20v5%20%3B%20ch140%20v3%3B%20ch140l%20v3%3B%20ch220%20v3%3B%20ch222%20v3%3B%20ch242%20v3%3B%20ch242%20v5%20%3B%20rh1288%20v3%3B%20rh2288%20v3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7949</link>
      <description>The iBMC (Intelligent Baseboard Management Controller) of some Huawei servers have a privilege escalation vulnerability. A remote attacker may send some specially crafted login messages to the affected products. Due to improper authentication design, successful exploit enables low privileged users to get or modify passwords of highly privileged users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7949|2024-08-05T06:37:59.717Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7899|2024-08-05T06:37:59.612Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- berkeley-al20%2C%20berkeley-bd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7899</link>
      <description>The Mali Driver of Huawei Berkeley-AL20 and Berkeley-BD smart phones with software Berkeley-AL20 8.0.0.105(C00), 8.0.0.111(C00), 8.0.0.112D(C00), 8.0.0.116(C00), 8.0.0.119(C00), 8.0.0.119D(C00), 8.0.0.122(C00), 8.0.0.132(C00), 8.0.0.132D(C00), 8.0.0.142(C00), 8.0.0.151(C00), Berkeley-BD 1.0.0.21, 1.0.0.22, 1.0.0.23, 1.0.0.24, 1.0.0.26, 1.0.0.29 has a double free vulnerability. An attacker can trick a user to install a malicious application and exploit this vulnerability when in the exception handling process. Successful exploitation may cause system reboot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7899|2024-08-05T06:37:59.612Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7910|2024-08-05T06:37:59.598Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- alp-al00b%2C%20alp-tl00b%2C%20bla-al00b%2C%20bla-l09c%2C%20bla-l29c
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7910</link>
      <description>Some Huawei smartphones ALP-AL00B 8.0.0.118D(C00), ALP-TL00B 8.0.0.118D(C01), BLA-AL00B 8.0.0.118D(C00), BLA-L09C 8.0.0.127(C432), 8.0.0.128(C432), 8.0.0.137(C432), BLA-L29C 8.0.0.129(C432), 8.0.0.137(C432) have an authentication bypass vulnerability. When the attacker obtains the user's smartphone, the vulnerability can be used to replace the start-up program so that the attacker can obtain the information in the smartphone and achieve the purpose of controlling the smartphone.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7910|2024-08-05T06:37:59.598Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7947|2024-08-05T06:37:59.881Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- emily-al00a
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7947</link>
      <description>Huawei mobile phones with versions earlier before Emily-AL00A 8.1.0.153(C00) have an authentication bypass vulnerability. An attacker could trick the user to connect to a malicious device. In the debug mode, the malicious software in the device may exploit the vulnerability to bypass some specific function. Successful exploit may cause some malicious applications to be installed in the mobile phones.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7947|2024-08-05T06:37:59.881Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7942|2024-08-05T06:37:59.683Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- 1288h%20v5%3B%202288h%20v5%3B%202488%20v5%3B%20ch121%20v3%3B%20ch121l%20v3%3B%20ch121l%20v5%3B%20ch121%20v5%3B%20ch140%20v3%3B%20ch140l%20v3%3B%20ch220%20v3%3B%20ch222%20v3%3B%20ch242%20v3%3B%20ch242%20v5%3B%20rh1288%20v3%3B%20rh2288%20v3%3B%20rh2288
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7942</link>
      <description>The iBMC (Intelligent Baseboard Management Controller) of some Huawei servers have an authentication bypass vulnerability. An unauthenticated, remote attacker may send some specially crafted messages to the affected products. Due to improper authentication design, successful exploit may cause some information leak.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7942|2024-08-05T06:37:59.683Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7937|2024-08-05T06:37:59.688Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- hirouter-cd20%2C%20ws5200-10
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7937</link>
      <description>In Huawei HiRouter-CD20-10 with the versions before 1.9.6 and WS5200-10 with the versions before 1.9.6, there is a plug-in signature bypass vulnerability due to insufficient plug-in verification. An attacker may tamper with a legitimate plug-in to build a malicious plug-in and trick users into installing it. Successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain the root permission of the device and take full control over the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7937|2024-08-05T06:37:59.688Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7960|2024-08-05T06:37:59.756Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- espace%207950
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7960</link>
      <description>There is a SRTP icon display vulnerability in Huawei eSpace product. An unauthenticated, remote attacker launches man-in-the-middle attack to intercept the packets in non-secure transmission mode. Successful exploitation may intercept and tamper with the call information, eventually cause sensitive information leak.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7960|2024-08-05T06:37:59.756Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7907|2024-08-05T06:37:59.653Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- agassi-l09%2Cagassi-w09%2Cbaggio2-u01a%2Cbond-al00c%2Cbond-al10b%2Cbond-tl10b%2Cbond-tl10c%2Chaydn-l1jb%2Ckobe-l09a%2Ckobe-l09ahn%2Ckobe-w09c%2Clelandp-l22c%2Clelandp-l22d%2Crhone-al00%2Cselina-l02%2Cstanford-l09s%2Ctoronto-al00%2Ctoronto-al00a%2Ctor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7907</link>
      <description>Some Huawei products Agassi-L09 AGS-L09C100B257CUSTC100D001, AGS-L09C170B253CUSTC170D001, AGS-L09C199B251CUSTC199D001, AGS-L09C229B003CUSTC229D001, Agassi-W09 AGS-W09C100B257CUSTC100D001, AGS-W09C128B252CUSTC128D001, AGS-W09C170B252CUSTC170D001, AGS-W09C229B251CUSTC229D001, AGS-W09C331B003CUSTC331D001, AGS-W09C794B001CUSTC794D001, Baggio2-U01A BG2-U01C100B160CUSTC100D001, BG2-U01C170B160CUSTC170D001, BG2-U01C199B162CUSTC199D001, BG2-U01C209B160CUSTC209D001, BG2-U01C333B160CUSTC333D001, Bond-AL00C Bond-AL00CC00B201, Bond-AL10B Bond-AL10BC00B201, Bond-TL10B Bond-TL10BC01B201, Bond-TL10C Bond-TL10CC01B131, Haydn-L1JB HDN-L1JC137B068, Kobe-L09A KOB-L09C100B252CUSTC100D001, KOB-L09C209B002CUSTC209D001, KOB-L09C362B001CUSTC362D001, Kobe-L09AHN KOB-L09C233B226, Kobe-W09C KOB-W09C128B251CUSTC128D001, LelandP-L22C 8.0.0.101(C675CUSTC675D2), LelandP-L22D 8.0.0.101(C675CUSTC675D2), Rhone-AL00 Rhone-AL00C00B186, Selina-L02 Selina-L02C432B153, Stanford-L09S Stanford-L09SC432B183, Toronto-AL00 Toronto-AL00C00B223, Toronto-AL00A Toronto-AL00AC00B223, Toronto-TL10 Toronto-TL10C01B223 have a sensitive information leak vulnerability. An attacker can trick a user to install a malicious application to exploit this vulnerability. Due to insufficient verification of the input, successful exploitation can cause sensitive information leak.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7907|2024-08-05T06:37:59.653Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7920|2024-08-05T06:37:59.640Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- ar1200%2C%20ar160%2C%20ar200%2C%20ar2200%2C%20ar3200
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7920</link>
      <description>Huawei AR1200 V200R006C10SPC300, AR160 V200R006C10SPC300, AR200 V200R006C10SPC300, AR2200 V200R006C10SPC300, AR3200 V200R006C10SPC300 devices have an improper resource management vulnerability. Due to the improper implementation of ACL mechanism, a remote attacker may send TCP messages to the management interface of the affected device to exploit this vulnerability. Successful exploit could exhaust the socket resource of management interface, leading to a DoS condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7920|2024-08-05T06:37:59.640Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7900|2024-08-05T06:37:59.608Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- some%20hg%20products
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7900</link>
      <description>There is an information leak vulnerability in some Huawei HG products. An attacker may obtain information about the HG device by exploiting this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7900|2024-08-05T06:37:59.608Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7990|2024-08-05T06:37:59.688Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- mate10%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7990</link>
      <description>Mate10 Pro Huawei smart phones with the versions before 8.1.0.326(C00) have a FRP bypass vulnerability. During the mobile phone reseting process, an attacker could bypass "Find My Phone" protect after a series of voice and keyboard operations. Successful exploit could allow an attacker to bypass FRP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7990|2024-08-05T06:37:59.688Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7906|2024-08-05T06:37:59.582Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- leland-al00%2C%20leland-al00a
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7906</link>
      <description>Some Huawei smart phones with software of Leland-AL00 8.0.0.114(C636), Leland-AL00A 8.0.0.171(C00) have a denial of service (DoS) vulnerability. An attacker can trick a user to install a malicious application to exploit this vulnerability. Due to insufficient verification of the parameter, successful exploitation can cause the smartphone black screen until restarting the phone.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7906|2024-08-05T06:37:59.582Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7987|2024-08-05T06:37:59.689Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- huawei%20p20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7987</link>
      <description>There is an out-of-bounds write vulnerability on Huawei P20 smartphones with versions before 8.1.0.171(C00). The software does not handle the response message properly when the user doing certain inquiry operation, an attacker could send crafted message to the device, successful exploit could cause a denial of service condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7987|2024-08-05T06:37:59.689Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7931|2024-08-05T06:37:59.634Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- appgallery
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7931</link>
      <description>Huawei AppGallery versions before 8.0.4.301 has a whitelist mechanism bypass vulnerability. An attacker may set up a malicious network environment and trick user into accessing a malicious web page to bypass the whitelist mechanism.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7931|2024-08-05T06:37:59.634Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7943|2024-08-05T06:37:59.625Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- 1288h%20v5%3B%202288h%20v5%3B%202488%20v5%20%3B%20ch121%20v3%3B%20ch121l%20v3%3B%20ch121l%20v5%20%3B%20ch121%20v5%20%3B%20ch140%20v3%3B%20ch140l%20v3%3B%20ch220%20v3%3B%20ch222%20v3%3B%20ch242%20v3%3B%20ch242%20v5%20%3B%20rh1288%20v3%3B%20rh2288%20v3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7943</link>
      <description>There is an authentication bypass vulnerability in some Huawei servers. A remote attacker with low privilege may bypass the authentication by some special operations. Due to insufficient authentication, an attacker may exploit the vulnerability to get some sensitive information and high-level users' privilege.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7943|2024-08-05T06:37:59.625Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7941|2024-08-05T06:37:59.759Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- ibmc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7941</link>
      <description>Huawei iBMC V200R002C60 have an authentication bypass vulnerability. A remote attacker with low privilege may craft specific messages to upload authentication certificate to the affected products. Due to improper validation of the upload authority, successful exploit may cause privilege elevation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7941|2024-08-05T06:37:59.759Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7956|2024-08-05T06:37:59.663Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- huawei%20vip%20app
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7956</link>
      <description>Huawei VIP App is a mobile app for Malaysia customers that purchased P20 Series, Nova 3/3i and Mate 20. There is a vulnerability in versions before 4.0.5 that attackers can conduct bruteforce to the VIP App Web Services to get user information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7956|2024-08-05T06:37:59.663Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7933|2024-08-05T06:37:59.671Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- hirouter-cd20%2C%20ws5200
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7933</link>
      <description>Huawei home gateway products HiRouter-CD20 and WS5200 with the versions before HiRouter-CD20-10 1.9.6 and the versions before WS5200-10 1.9.6 have a path traversal vulnerability. Due to the lack of validation while these home gateway products install APK plugins, an attacker tricks a user into installing a malicious APK plugin, and plugin can overwrite arbitrary file of devices. Successful exploit may result in arbitrary code execution or privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7933|2024-08-05T06:37:59.671Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7946|2024-08-05T06:37:59.637Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- huawei%20honor%207a%2C%20huawei%20honor%209%20lite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7946</link>
      <description>There is an information leak vulnerability in some Huawei smartphones. An attacker may do some specific configuration in the smartphone and trick a user into inputting some sensitive information. Due to improper design, successful exploit may cause some information leak.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7946|2024-08-05T06:37:59.637Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7958|2024-08-05T06:37:59.643Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- espace%207950
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7958</link>
      <description>There is an anonymous TLS cipher suites supported vulnerability in Huawei eSpace product. An unauthenticated, remote attacker launches man-in-the-middle attack to hijack the connection from a client when the user signs up to log in by TLS. Due to insufficient authentication, which may be exploited to intercept and tamper with the data information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7958|2024-08-05T06:37:59.643Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7957|2024-08-05T06:37:59.616Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- victoria-al00
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7957</link>
      <description>Huawei smartphones with software Victoria-AL00 8.0.0.336a(C00) have an information leakage vulnerability. Because an interface does not verify authorization correctly, attackers can exploit an application with the authorization of phone state to obtain user location additionally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7957|2024-08-05T06:37:59.616Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7951|2024-08-05T06:37:59.585Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- 1288h%20v5%3B%202288h%20v5%3B%202488%20v5%20%3B%20ch121%20v3%3B%20ch121l%20v3%3B%20ch121l%20v5%20%3B%20ch121%20v5%20%3B%20ch140%20v3%3B%20ch140l%20v3%3B%20ch220%20v3%3B%20ch222%20v3%3B%20ch242%20v3%3B%20ch242%20v5%20%3B%20rh1288%20v3%3B%20rh2288%20v3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7951</link>
      <description>The iBMC (Intelligent Baseboard Management Controller) of some Huawei servers have a JSON injection vulnerability due to insufficient input validation. An authenticated, remote attacker can launch a JSON injection to modify the password of administrator. Successful exploit may allow attackers to obtain the management privilege of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7951|2024-08-05T06:37:59.585Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7944|2024-08-05T06:37:59.713Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- emily-al00a
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7944</link>
      <description>Huawei smart phones Emily-AL00A with software 8.1.0.106(SP2C00) and 8.1.0.107(SP5C00) have a Factory Reset Protection (FRP) bypass vulnerability. An attacker gets some user's smart phone and performs some special operations in the guide function. The attacker may exploit the vulnerability to bypass FRP function and use the phone normally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7944|2024-08-05T06:37:59.713Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7938|2024-08-05T06:37:59.691Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- p10
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7938</link>
      <description>P10 Huawei smartphones with the versions before Victoria-AL00AC00B217 have an information leak vulnerability due to the lack of permission validation. An attacker tricks a user into installing a malicious application on the smart phone, and the application can read some hardware serial number, which may cause sensitive information leak.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7938|2024-08-05T06:37:59.691Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7977|2024-08-05T06:37:59.665Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- fusionsphere%20openstack
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7977</link>
      <description>There is an information leakage vulnerability on several Huawei products. Due to insufficient communication protection for specific services, a remote, unauthorized attacker can exploit this vulnerability to connect to specific services to obtain additional information. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability can lead to information leakage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7977|2024-08-05T06:37:59.665Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
