<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd. -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd./all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd. -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 17:22:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17143|2024-09-16T16:13:49.119Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- dp300%3B%20rp200%3B%20rse6500%3B%20te30%3B%20te40%3B%20te50%3B%20te60%3B%20tp3106%3B%20tp3206%3B%20viewpoint%209030%3B%20espace%20u1960%3B%20espace%20u1981
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17143</link>
      <description>SIP module in Huawei DP300 V500R002C00; V500R002C00SPC100; V500R002C00SPC200; V500R002C00SPC300; V500R002C00SPC400; V500R002C00SPC500; V500R002C00SPC600; V500R002C00SPC800; V500R002C00SPC900; V500R002C00SPCa00; RP200 V500R002C00SPC200; V600R006C00; V600R006C00SPC200; RSE6500 V500R002C00SPC100; V500R002C00SPC200; V500R002C00SPC300; V500R002C00SPC300T; V500R002C00SPC500; V500R002C00SPC600; V500R002C00SPC700; V500R002C00T; TE30 V100R001C10; V100R001C10SPC100; V100R001C10SPC200B010; V100R001C10SPC300; V100R001C10SPC500; V100R001C10SPC600; V100R001C10SPC700B010; V100R001C10SPC800; V500R002C00SPC200; V500R002C00SPC500; V500R002C00SPC600; V500R002C00SPC700; V500R002C00SPC900; V500R002C00SPCb00; V600R006C00; TE40 V500R002C00SPC600; V500R002C00SPC700; V500R002C00SPC900; V500R002C00SPCb00; V600R006C00; V600R006C00SPC200; TE50 V500R002C00SPC600; V500R002C00SPC700; V500R002C00SPCb00; V600R006C00; V600R006C00SPC200; TE60 V100R001C01SPC100; V100R001C01SPC107TB010; V100R001C10; V100R001C10SPC300; V100R001C10SPC400; V100R001C10SPC500; V100R001C10SPC600; V100R001C10SPC700; V100R001C10SPC800; V100R001C10SPC900; V500R002C00; V500R002C00SPC100; V500R002C00SPC200; V500R002C00SPC300; V500R002C00SPC600; V500R002C00SPC700; V500R002C00SPC800; V500R002C00SPC900; V500R002C00SPCa00; V500R002C00SPCb00; V500R002C00SPCd00; V600R006C00; V600R006C00SPC100; V600R006C00SPC200; V600R006C00SPC300; TP3106 V100R002C00; V100R002C00SPC200; V100R002C00SPC400; V100R002C00SPC600; V100R002C00SPC700; V100R002C00SPC800; TP3206 V100R002C00; V100R002C00SPC200; V100R002C00SPC400; V100R002C00SPC600; V100R002C00SPC700; V100R002C10; ViewPoint 9030 V100R011C02SPC100; V100R011C03B012SP15; V100R011C03B012SP16; V100R011C03B015SP03; V100R011C03LGWL01SPC100; V100R011C03SPC100; V100R011C03SPC200; V100R011C03SPC300; V100R011C03SPC400; V100R011C03SPC500; eSpace U1960 V200R003C30SPC200; eSpace U1981 V100R001C20SPC700; V200R003C20SPCa00 has an overflow vulnerability that the module cannot parse a malformed SIP message when validating variables. Attacker can exploit it to make one process reboot at random.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17143|2024-09-16T16:13:49.119Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17313|2024-09-16T16:23:50.913Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- huawei%20p9%20lite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17313</link>
      <description>The inputhub driver of HUAWEI P9 Lite mobile phones with Versions earlier than VNS-L21C02B341, Versions earlier than VNS-L21C22B380, Versions earlier than VNS-L31C02B341, Versions earlier than VNS-L31C440B390, Versions earlier than VNS-L31C636B396 has a buffer overflow vulnerability due to the lack of parameter validation. An attacker tricks a user into installing a malicious APP and the APP may sends specific data to the inputhub driver to exploit this vulnerability, successful exploit could cause the system reboot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17313|2024-09-16T16:23:50.913Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17136|2024-09-16T16:49:17.056Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- dp300%3B%20ips%20module%3B%20ngfw%20module%3B%20nip6300%3B%20nip6600%3B%20rp200%3B%20s12700%3B%20s1700%3B%20s2700%3B%20s5700%3B%20s6700%3B%20s7700%3B%20s9700%3B%20secospace%20usg6300%3B%20secospace%20usg6500%3B%20secospace%20usg6600%3B%20te30%3B%20te
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17136</link>
      <description>PEM module of Huawei DP300 V500R002C00; IPS Module V500R001C00; V500R001C30; NGFW Module V500R001C00; V500R002C00; NIP6300 V500R001C00; V500R001C30; NIP6600 V500R001C00; V500R001C30; RP200 V500R002C00; V600R006C00; S12700 V200R007C00; V200R007C01; V200R008C00; V200R009C00; V200R010C00; S1700 V200R006C10; V200R009C00; V200R010C00; S2700 V200R006C10; V200R007C00; V200R008C00; V200R009C00; V200R010C00; S5700 V200R006C00; V200R007C00; V200R008C00; V200R009C00; V200R010C00; S6700 V200R008C00; V200R009C00; V200R010C00; S7700 V200R007C00; V200R008C00; V200R009C00; V200R010C00; S9700 V200R007C00; V200R007C01; V200R008C00; V200R009C00; V200R010C00; Secospace USG6300 V500R001C00; V500R001C30; Secospace USG6500 V500R001C00; V500R001C30; Secospace USG6600 V500R001C00; V500R001C30S; TE30 V100R001C02; V100R001C10; V500R002C00; V600R006C00; TE40 V500R002C00; V600R006C00; TE50 V500R002C00; V600R006C00; TE60 V100R001C01; V100R001C10; V500R002C00; V600R006C00; TP3106 V100R002C00; TP3206 V100R002C00; V100R002C10; USG9500 V500R001C00; V500R001C30; ViewPoint 9030 V100R011C02; V100R011C03 has a heap overflow vulnerability due to insufficient verification. An authenticated local attacker can make processing crash by a malicious certificate. The attacker can exploit this vulnerability to cause a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17136|2024-09-16T16:49:17.056Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17133|2024-09-16T16:18:23.021Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- vp9660
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17133</link>
      <description>Huawei VP9660 V500R002C10 has a null pointer reference vulnerability in license module due to insufficient verification. An authenticated local attacker could place a malicious license file into system which cause memory null pointer accessing and related processing crash. The attacker can exploit this vulnerability to cause a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17133|2024-09-16T16:18:23.021Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8196|2024-09-16T16:18:54.511Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- fusionsphere
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8196</link>
      <description>FusionSphere V100R006C00SPC102(NFV) has an incorrect authorization vulnerability. An authenticated attacker could execute commands that he/she should have had no permission to perform, thereby querying, modifying, and deleting certain service data and making the service unavailable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8196|2024-09-16T16:18:54.511Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-15318|2024-09-16T16:58:54.555Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- rp200
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-15318</link>
      <description>RP200 V500R002C00, V600R006C00; TE30 V100R001C10, V500R002C00, V600R006C00; TE40 V500R002C00, V600R006C00; TE50 V500R002C00, V600R006C00; TE60 V100R001C10, V500R002C00, V600R006C00 have an out-of-bounds read vulnerabilities in some Huawei products. Due to insufficient input validation, a remote attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by sending specially crafted SS7 related packets to the target devices. Successful exploit will cause out-of-bounds read and possibly crash the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-15318|2024-09-16T16:58:54.555Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8150|2024-09-16T16:48:35.815Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- p10%2C%20p10%20plus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8150</link>
      <description>The boot loaders of P10 and P10 Plus Huawei mobile phones with software the versions before Victoria-L09AC605B162, the versions before Victoria-L29AC605B162, the versions before Vicky-L29AC605B162 have an arbitrary memory write vulnerability due to the lack of parameter validation. An attacker with the root privilege of an Android system may trick a user into installing a malicious APP. The APP can modify specific data to cause arbitrary memory writing in the next system reboot, causing continuous system reboot or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8150|2024-09-16T16:48:35.815Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2702|2024-09-16T16:48:33.458Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- mate%209
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2702</link>
      <description>Phone Finder in versions earlier before MHA-AL00C00B170 can be bypass. An attacker can bypass the Phone Finder by special steps and obtain the owner of the phone.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2702|2024-09-16T16:48:33.458Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2700|2024-09-16T16:53:35.031Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- ac6005%2Cac6605
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2700</link>
      <description>AC6005 with software V200R006C10, AC6605 with software V200R006C10 have a DoS Vulnerability. An attacker can send malformed packets to the device, which causes the device memory leaks, leading to DoS attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2700|2024-09-16T16:53:35.031Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
