<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd. -- AR120-S,AR1200,AR1200-S,AR150,AR150-S,AR160,AR200,AR200-S,AR2200,AR2200-S,AR3200,AR3600,AR510,IPS Module,NIP6300,NetEngine16EX</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd./ar120-s%2Car1200%2Car1200-s%2Car150%2Car150-s%2Car160%2Car200%2Car200-s%2Car2200%2Car2200-s%2Car3200%2Car3600%2Car510%2Cips%20module%2Cnip6300%2Cnetengine16ex.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd. -- AR120-S,AR1200,AR1200-S,AR150,AR150-S,AR160,AR200,AR200-S,AR2200,AR2200-S,AR3200,AR3600,AR510,IPS Module,NIP6300,NetEngine16EX</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:23:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17299|2024-08-05T20:51:30.606Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- ar120-s%2Car1200%2Car1200-s%2Car150%2Car150-s%2Car160%2Car200%2Car200-s%2Car2200%2Car2200-s%2Car3200%2Car3600%2Car510%2Cips%20module%2Cnip6300%2Cnetengine16ex
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17299</link>
      <description>Huawei AR120-S V200R006C10, V200R007C00, AR1200 V200R006C10, V200R006C13, V200R007C00, V200R007C02, AR1200-S V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, AR150 V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C02, AR150-S V200R006C10, V200R007C00, AR160 V200R006C10, V200R006C12, V200R007C00S, V200R007C02, AR200 V200R006C10, V200R007C00, AR200-S V200R006C10, V200R007C00, AR2200 V200R006C10, V200R006C13, V200R006C16, V200R007C00, V200R007C02, AR2200-S V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, AR3200 V200R006C10, V200R006C11, V200R007C00, V200R007C02, AR3600 V200R006C10, V200R007C00, AR510 V200R006C12, V200R006C13, V200R006C15, V200R006C16, V200R006C17, V200R007C00, IPS Module V500R001C30, NIP6300 V500R001C30, NetEngine16EX V200R006C10, V200R007C00 have an insufficient input validation vulnerability. An unauthenticated, remote attacker may send crafted IKE V2 messages to the affected products. Due to the insufficient validation of the messages, successful exploit will cause invalid memory access and result in a denial of service on the affected products.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17299|2024-08-05T20:51:30.606Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
