<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd. -- AR120-S,AR1200,AR1200-S,AR150,AR150-S,AR160,AR200,AR200-S,AR2200,AR2200-S,AR3200,AR3600,AR510,NetEngine16EX,SRG1300,SRG2300,SRG3300</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd./ar120-s%2Car1200%2Car1200-s%2Car150%2Car150-s%2Car160%2Car200%2Car200-s%2Car2200%2Car2200-s%2Car3200%2Car3600%2Car510%2Cnetengine16ex%2Csrg1300%2Csrg2300%2Csrg3300.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd. -- AR120-S,AR1200,AR1200-S,AR150,AR150-S,AR160,AR200,AR200-S,AR2200,AR2200-S,AR3200,AR3600,AR510,NetEngine16EX,SRG1300,SRG2300,SRG3300</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 22:22:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17287|2024-08-05T20:44:00.340Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- ar120-s%2Car1200%2Car1200-s%2Car150%2Car150-s%2Car160%2Car200%2Car200-s%2Car2200%2Car2200-s%2Car3200%2Car3600%2Car510%2Cnetengine16ex%2Csrg1300%2Csrg2300%2Csrg3300
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17287</link>
      <description>Huawei AR120-S V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR1200 V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR1200-S V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR150 V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR150-S V200R005C32, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR160 V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR200 V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR200-S V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30,AR2200 V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR2200-S V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR3200 V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R006C11, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R007C02, V200R008C00, V200R008C10, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR3600 V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R008C20, AR510 V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, NetEngine16EX V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, SRG1300 V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, SRG2300 V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, SRG3300 V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30 have an out-of-bound read vulnerability in some Huawei products. Due to insufficient input validation, a remote, unauthenticated attacker may send crafted signature to the affected products. Successful exploit may cause buffer overflow, services abnormal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17287|2024-08-05T20:44:00.340Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17286|2024-08-05T20:43:59.900Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- ar120-s%2Car1200%2Car1200-s%2Car150%2Car150-s%2Car160%2Car200%2Car200-s%2Car2200%2Car2200-s%2Car3200%2Car3600%2Car510%2Cnetengine16ex%2Csrg1300%2Csrg2300%2Csrg3300
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17286</link>
      <description>Huawei AR120-S V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR1200 V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR1200-S V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR150 V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR150-S V200R005C32, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR160 V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR200 V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR200-S V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR2200 V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR2200-S V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR3200 V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R006C11, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R007C02, V200R008C00, V200R008C10, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR3600 V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R008C20, AR510 V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, NetEngine16EX V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, SRG1300 V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, SRG2300 V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, SRG3300 V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30 have an out-of-bound write vulnerability. Due to insufficient input validation, a remote, unauthenticated attacker may craft encryption key to the affected products. Successful exploit may cause buffer overflow, services abnormal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17286|2024-08-05T20:43:59.900Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17202|2024-08-05T20:43:59.884Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- ar120-s%2Car1200%2Car1200-s%2Car150%2Car150-s%2Car160%2Car200%2Car200-s%2Car2200%2Car2200-s%2Car3200%2Car3600%2Car510%2Cnetengine16ex%2Csrg1300%2Csrg2300%2Csrg3300
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17202</link>
      <description>Huawei AR120-S V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR1200 V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR1200-S V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR150 V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR150-S V200R005C32, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR160 V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR200 V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR200-S V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR2200 V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR2200-S V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR3200 V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R006C11, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R007C02, V200R008C00, V200R008C10, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR3600 V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R008C20, AR510 V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, NetEngine16EX V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, SRG1300 V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, SRG2300 V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, SRG3300 V200R005C32, V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30 have an out-of-bounds read vulnerability due to insufficient input validation. An unauthenticated, remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malformed Session Initiation Protocol(SIP) packets to the target device. Successful exploit could make the device read out of bounds and thus cause a service to be unavailable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17202|2024-08-05T20:43:59.884Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17160|2024-08-05T20:43:59.870Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- ar120-s%2Car1200%2Car1200-s%2Car150%2Car150-s%2Car160%2Car200%2Car200-s%2Car2200%2Car2200-s%2Car3200%2Car3600%2Car510%2Cnetengine16ex%2Csrg1300%2Csrg2300%2Csrg3300
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17160</link>
      <description>Huawei AR120-S V200R006C10, V200R007C00, AR1200 V200R006C10, V200R006C13, V200R007C00, V200R007C02, AR1200-S V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, AR150 V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C02, AR150-S V200R006C10, V200R007C00, AR160 V200R006C10, V200R006C12, V200R007C00, V200R007C02, AR200 V200R006C10, V200R007C00, AR200-S V200R006C10, V200R007C00, AR2200 V200R006C10, V200R006C13, V200R006C16PWE, V200R007C00, V200R007C02, AR2200-S V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, AR3200 V200R006C10, V200R006C11, V200R007C00, V200R007C02, AR3600 V200R006C10, V200R007C00, AR510 V200R006C12, V200R006C13, V200R006C15, V200R006C16, V200R006C17, V200R007C00, NetEngine16EX V200R006C10, V200R007C00, SRG1300 V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C02, SRG2300 V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C02, SRG3300 V200R006C10, V200R007C00 have a buffer overflow vulnerability due to incomplete range checks of the input data. An unauthenticated, remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious IKE packets to the targeted device. An exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to write out of bound and restart.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17160|2024-08-05T20:43:59.870Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
