<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd. -- AR120-S</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd./ar120-s.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd. -- AR120-S</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 14:22:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-15317|2024-09-17T03:23:23.187Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- ar120-s
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-15317</link>
      <description>AR120-S V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30; AR1200 V200R006C10, V200R006C13, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30; AR1200-S V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30; AR150 V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30; AR150-S V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30; AR160 V200R006C10, V200R006C12, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30; AR200 V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R008C20, V200R008C30; AR200-S V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30; AR2200 V200R006C10, V200R006C13, V200R006C16, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30; AR2200-S V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30; AR3200 V200R006C10, V200R006C11, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R007C02, V200R008C00, V200R008C10, V200R008C20, V200R008C30; AR510 V200R006C10, V200R006C12, V200R006C13, V200R006C15, V200R006C16, V200R006C17, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30; SRG1300 V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30; SRG2300 V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30; SRG3300 V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30 have an input validation vulnerability in Huawei multiple products. Due to the insufficient input validation, an unauthenticated, remote attacker may craft a malformed Stream Control Transmission Protocol (SCTP) packet and send it to the device, causing the device to read out of bounds and restart.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-15317|2024-09-17T03:23:23.187Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
