<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd. -- AR120-S,AR1200,AR1200-S,AR150,AR150-S,AR160,AR200,AR200-S,AR2200,AR2200-S,AR3200,AR3600,AR510,DP300,NetEngine16EX,RP200,SRG1300,SRG2300,SRG3300,TE30,TE40,TE50,TE60,TP3106,TP3206,ViewPoint9030</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd./ar120-s%2Car1200%2Car1200-s%2Car150%2Car150-s%2Car160%2Car200%2Car200-s%2Car2200%2Car2200-s%2Car3200%2Car3600%2Car510%2Cdp300%2Cnetengine16ex%2Crp200%2Csrg1300%2Csrg2300%2Csrg3300%2Cte30%2Cte40%2Cte50%2Cte60%2Ctp3106%2Ctp3206%2Cviewpoint9030.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd. -- AR120-S,AR1200,AR1200-S,AR150,AR150-S,AR160,AR200,AR200-S,AR2200,AR2200-S,AR3200,AR3600,AR510,DP300,NetEngine16EX,RP200,SRG1300,SRG2300,SRG3300,TE30,TE40,TE50,TE60,TP3106,TP3206,ViewPoint9030</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 22:22:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17298|2024-08-05T20:51:30.531Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- ar120-s%2Car1200%2Car1200-s%2Car150%2Car150-s%2Car160%2Car200%2Car200-s%2Car2200%2Car2200-s%2Car3200%2Car3600%2Car510%2Cdp300%2Cnetengine16ex%2Crp200%2Csrg1300%2Csrg2300%2Csrg3300%2Cte30%2Cte40%2Cte50%2Cte60%2Ctp3106%2Ctp3206%2Cviewpoint9030
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17298</link>
      <description>Huawei AR120-S V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR1200 V200R006C10, V200R006C13, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR1200-S V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR150 V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR150-S V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR160 V200R006C10, V200R006C12, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR200 V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR200-S V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR2200 V200R006C10, V200R006C13, V200R006C16, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR2200-S V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR3200 V200R006C10, V200R006C11, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R007C02, V200R008C00, V200R008C10, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, AR3600 V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C01, V200R008C20, AR510 V200R006C10, V200R006C12, V200R006C13, V200R006C15, V200R006C16, V200R006C17, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, DP300 V500R002C00, NetEngine16EX V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, RP200 V500R002C00, V600R006C00, SRG1300 V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, SRG2300 V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R007C02, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, SRG3300 V200R006C10, V200R007C00, V200R008C20, V200R008C30, TE30 V100R001C02, V100R001C10, V500R002C00, V600R006C00, TE40 V500R002C00, V600R006C00, TE50 V500R002C00, V600R006C00, TE60 V100R001C01, V100R001C10, V500R002C00, V600R006C00, TP3106 V100R002C00, TP3206 V100R002C00, V100R002C10, ViewPoint 9030 V100R011C02, V100R011C03 have a buffer overflow vulnerability. An unauthenticated, remote attacker may send specially crafted certificates to the affected products. Due to insufficient validation of the certificates, successful exploit may cause buffer overflow and some service abnormal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17298|2024-08-05T20:51:30.531Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
