<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd. -- Emily-AL00A</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd./emily-al00a.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd. -- Emily-AL00A</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:23:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7961|2024-08-05T06:37:59.690Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- emily-al00a
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7961</link>
      <description>There is a smart SMS verification code vulnerability in some Huawei smart phones. An attacker should trick a user to access malicious Website or malicious App and register. Due to incorrect processing of the smart SMS verification code, successful exploitation can cause sensitive information leak.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7961|2024-08-05T06:37:59.690Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7925|2024-08-05T06:37:59.625Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- emily-al00a
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7925</link>
      <description>The radio module of some Huawei smartphones Emily-AL00A The versions before 8.1.0.171(C00) have a lock-screen bypass vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker could start third-part input method APP through certain operations to bypass lock-screen by exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7925|2024-08-05T06:37:59.625Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7947|2024-08-05T06:37:59.881Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- emily-al00a
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7947</link>
      <description>Huawei mobile phones with versions earlier before Emily-AL00A 8.1.0.153(C00) have an authentication bypass vulnerability. An attacker could trick the user to connect to a malicious device. In the debug mode, the malicious software in the device may exploit the vulnerability to bypass some specific function. Successful exploit may cause some malicious applications to be installed in the mobile phones.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7947|2024-08-05T06:37:59.881Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7944|2024-08-05T06:37:59.713Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- emily-al00a
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7944</link>
      <description>Huawei smart phones Emily-AL00A with software 8.1.0.106(SP2C00) and 8.1.0.107(SP5C00) have a Factory Reset Protection (FRP) bypass vulnerability. An attacker gets some user's smart phone and performs some special operations in the guide function. The attacker may exploit the vulnerability to bypass FRP function and use the phone normally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7944|2024-08-05T06:37:59.713Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
