<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd. -- eSpace 7950</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd./espace%207950.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd. -- eSpace 7950</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 19:21:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7959|2024-08-05T06:37:59.691Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- espace%207950
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7959</link>
      <description>There is a short key vulnerability in Huawei eSpace product. An unauthenticated, remote attacker launches man-in-the-middle attack to intercept and decrypt the call information when the user enables SRTP to make a call. Successful exploitation may cause sensitive information leak.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7959|2024-08-05T06:37:59.691Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7960|2024-08-05T06:37:59.756Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- espace%207950
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7960</link>
      <description>There is a SRTP icon display vulnerability in Huawei eSpace product. An unauthenticated, remote attacker launches man-in-the-middle attack to intercept the packets in non-secure transmission mode. Successful exploitation may intercept and tamper with the call information, eventually cause sensitive information leak.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7960|2024-08-05T06:37:59.756Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7958|2024-08-05T06:37:59.643Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- espace%207950
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7958</link>
      <description>There is an anonymous TLS cipher suites supported vulnerability in Huawei eSpace product. An unauthenticated, remote attacker launches man-in-the-middle attack to hijack the connection from a client when the user signs up to log in by TLS. Due to insufficient authentication, which may be exploited to intercept and tamper with the data information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7958|2024-08-05T06:37:59.643Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
