<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd. -- G9 Lite, Honor 5A, Honor 6X, Honor 8</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd./g9%20lite%2C%20honor%205a%2C%20honor%206x%2C%20honor%208.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd. -- G9 Lite, Honor 5A, Honor 6X, Honor 8</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:23:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7939|2024-08-05T06:37:59.646Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- g9%20lite%2C%20honor%205a%2C%20honor%206x%2C%20honor%208
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7939</link>
      <description>Huawei smart phones G9 Lite, Honor 5A, Honor 6X, Honor 8 with the versions before VNS-L53C605B120CUSTC605D103, the versions before CAM-L03C605B143CUSTC605D008, the versions before CAM-L21C10B145, the versions before CAM-L21C185B156, the versions before CAM-L21C223B133, the versions before CAM-L21C432B210, the versions before CAM-L21C464B170, the versions before CAM-L21C636B245, the versions before Berlin-L21C10B372, the versions before Berlin-L21C185B363, the versions before Berlin-L21C464B137, the versions before Berlin-L23C605B161, the versions before FRD-L09C10B387, the versions before FRD-L09C185B387, the versions before FRD-L09C432B398, the versions before FRD-L09C636B387, the versions before FRD-L19C10B387, the versions before FRD-L19C432B399, the versions before FRD-L19C636B387 have a Factory Reset Protection (FRP) bypass security vulnerability. When re-configuring the mobile phone using the factory reset protection (FRP) function, an attacker can disable the boot wizard by enable the talkback function. As a result, the FRP function is bypassed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7939|2024-08-05T06:37:59.646Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
