<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd. -- Mate 9</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd./mate%209.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd. -- Mate 9</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:22:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7930|2024-08-05T06:37:59.746Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- mate%209
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7930</link>
      <description>The Near Field Communication (NFC) module in Mate 9 Huawei mobile phones with the versions before MHA-L29B 8.0.0.366(C567) has an information leak vulnerability due to insufficient validation on data transfer requests. When an affected mobile phone sends files to an attacker's mobile phone using the NFC function, the attacker can obtain arbitrary files from the mobile phone, causing information leaks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7930|2024-08-05T06:37:59.746Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2706|2024-08-05T14:02:07.619Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- mate%209
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2706</link>
      <description>Mate 9 smartphones with software MHA-AL00AC00B125 have a directory traversal vulnerability in Push module. Since the system does not verify the file name during decompression, system directories are traversed. It could be exploited to cause the attacker to replace files and impact the service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2706|2024-08-05T14:02:07.619Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2716|2024-08-05T14:02:07.475Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- mate%209
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2716</link>
      <description>The camerafs driver in Mate 9 Versions earlier than MHA-AL00BC00B173 has buffer overflow vulnerability. An attacker tricks a user into installing a malicious application which has the system privilege of the Android system and sends a specific parameter to the driver of the smart phone, causing a system crash or privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2716|2024-08-05T14:02:07.475Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2701|2024-08-05T14:02:07.368Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- mate%209
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2701</link>
      <description>Mate 9 with software MHA-AL00AC00B125 has a denial of service (DoS) vulnerability. An attacker tricks a user into installing a malicious application. Since the system does not verify the broadcasting message from the application, it could be exploited to cause some functions of system unavailable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2701|2024-08-05T14:02:07.368Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2707|2024-08-05T14:02:07.656Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- mate%209
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2707</link>
      <description>Mate 9 smartphones with software MHA-AL00AC00B125 have a privilege escalation vulnerability in Push module. An attacker tricks a user to save a rich media into message on the smart phone, which could be exploited to cause the attacker to delete message or fake user to send message.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2707|2024-08-05T14:02:07.656Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2702|2024-08-05T14:02:07.490Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- mate%209
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2702</link>
      <description>Phone Finder in versions earlier before MHA-AL00C00B170 can be bypass. An attacker can bypass the Phone Finder by special steps and obtain the owner of the phone.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2702|2024-08-05T14:02:07.490Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
