<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd. -- Mate 9 Pro</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd./mate%209%20pro.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd. -- Mate 9 Pro</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 21:23:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17173|2024-08-05T20:43:59.978Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- mate%209%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17173</link>
      <description>Due to insufficient parameters verification GPU driver of Mate 9 Pro Huawei smart phones with the versions before LON-AL00B 8.0.0.356(C00) has an arbitrary memory free vulnerability. An attacker can tricks a user into installing a malicious application on the smart phone, and send given parameter to driver to release special kernel memory resource. Successful exploit may result in phone crash or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17173|2024-08-05T20:43:59.978Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17279|2024-08-05T20:43:59.895Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- mate%209%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17279</link>
      <description>The soundtrigger module in Huawei Mate 9 Pro smart phones with software of the versions before LON-AL00B 8.0.0.343(C00) has an authentication bypass vulnerability due to the improper design of the module. An attacker tricks a user into installing a malicious application, and the application can exploit the vulnerability and make attacker bypass the authentication, the attacker can control the phone to sent short messages and make call within audio range to the phone.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17279|2024-08-05T20:43:59.895Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17225|2024-08-05T20:43:59.976Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- mate%209%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17225</link>
      <description>The Near Field Communication (NFC) module in Huawei Mate 9 Pro mobile phones with the versions before LON-AL00B 8.0.0.340a(C00) has a buffer overflow vulnerability due to the lack of input validation. An attacker may use an NFC card reader or another device to inject malicious data into a target mobile phone. Successful exploit could lead to system restart or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17225|2024-08-05T20:43:59.976Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-15347|2024-08-05T19:50:16.674Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- mate%209%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-15347</link>
      <description>Huawei Mate 9 Pro mobile phones with software of versions earlier than LON-AL00BC00B235 have a use after free (UAF) vulnerability. An attacker tricks a user into installing a malicious application, and the application can riggers access memory after free it. A local attacker may exploit this vulnerability to cause the mobile phone to crash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-15347|2024-08-05T19:50:16.674Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17320|2024-08-05T20:51:30.549Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- mate%209%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17320</link>
      <description>Huawei Mate 9 Pro smartphones with software of LON-AL00BC00B139D, LON-AL00BC00B229, LON-L29DC721B188 have a memory double free vulnerability. The system does not manage the memory properly, that frees on the same memory address twice. An attacker tricks the user who has root privilege to install a crafted application, successful exploit could result in malicious code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17320|2024-08-05T20:51:30.549Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17175|2024-08-05T20:44:00.248Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- mate%209%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17175</link>
      <description>Short Message Service (SMS) module of Mate 9 Pro Huawei smart phones with the versions before LON-AL00B 8.0.0.354(C00) has a Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker may set up a pseudo base station, and send special malware text message to the phone, causing the mobile phone to fail to make calls and send and receive text messages.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17175|2024-08-05T20:44:00.248Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17326|2024-08-05T20:51:31.098Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- mate%209%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17326</link>
      <description>Huawei Mate 9 Pro Smartphones with software of LON-AL00BC00B139D; LON-AL00BC00B229 have an activation lock bypass vulnerability. The smartphone is supposed to be activated by the former account after reset if find my phone function is on. The software does not have a sufficient protection of activation lock. Successful exploit could allow an attacker to bypass the activation lock and activate the smartphone by a new account after a series of operation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17326|2024-08-05T20:51:31.098Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17324|2024-08-05T20:51:30.718Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- mate%209%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17324</link>
      <description>Huawei Mate 9 Pro smartphones with software LON-AL00BC00B139D; LON-AL00BC00B229 have an integer overflow vulnerability. The camera driver does not validate the external input parameters and causes an integer overflow, which in the after processing results in a buffer overflow. An attacker tricks the user to install a crafted application, successful exploit could cause malicious code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17324|2024-08-05T20:51:30.718Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
