<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd. -- Mate 10 pro</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd./mate%2010%20pro.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd. -- Mate 10 pro</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 07:21:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7934|2024-08-05T06:37:59.577Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- mate%2010%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7934</link>
      <description>Some Huawei mobile phone with the versions before BLA-L29 8.0.0.145(C432) have a denial of service (DoS) vulnerability because they do not adapt to specific screen gestures. An attacker may trick users into installing a malicious app. As a result, apps running on the frontend crash after the users make specific screen gestures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7934|2024-08-05T06:37:59.577Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7936|2024-08-05T06:37:59.650Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- mate%2010%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7936</link>
      <description>Mate 10 Pro Huawei smart phones with the versions before BLA-L29 8.0.0.148(C432) have a Factory Reset Protection (FRP) bypass security vulnerability. When re-configuring the mobile phone using the factory reset protection (FRP) function, an attacker can connect the phone with PC and send special instructions to install third party desktop and disable the boot wizard. As a result, the FRP function is bypassed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7936|2024-08-05T06:37:59.650Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7989|2024-08-05T06:37:59.692Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- mate%2010%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7989</link>
      <description>Huawei Mate 10 pro smartphones with the versions before BLA-AL00B 8.1.0.326(C00) have an improper authentication vulnerability. App Lock is a function to prevent unauthorized use of apps on smartphones, an attacker could directly change the lock password after a series of operations. Successful exploit could allow the attacker to use the application which is locked.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7989|2024-08-05T06:37:59.692Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
