<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd. -- Mate 9</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd./mate%209.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd. -- Mate 9</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 20:23:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-15316|2024-09-16T17:48:54.343Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- mate%209
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-15316</link>
      <description>The GPU driver of Mate 9 Huawei smart phones with software before MHA-AL00B 8.0.0.334(C00) and Mate 9 Pro Huawei smart phones with software before LON-AL00B 8.0.0.334(C00) has a memory double free vulnerability. An attacker tricks a user into installing a malicious application, and the application can call special API, which triggers double free and causes a system crash or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-15316|2024-09-16T17:48:54.343Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2706|2024-09-16T19:52:31.579Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- mate%209
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2706</link>
      <description>Mate 9 smartphones with software MHA-AL00AC00B125 have a directory traversal vulnerability in Push module. Since the system does not verify the file name during decompression, system directories are traversed. It could be exploited to cause the attacker to replace files and impact the service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2706|2024-09-16T19:52:31.579Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2716|2024-09-16T19:01:35.238Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- mate%209
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2716</link>
      <description>The camerafs driver in Mate 9 Versions earlier than MHA-AL00BC00B173 has buffer overflow vulnerability. An attacker tricks a user into installing a malicious application which has the system privilege of the Android system and sends a specific parameter to the driver of the smart phone, causing a system crash or privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2716|2024-09-16T19:01:35.238Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2702|2024-09-16T16:48:33.458Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- mate%209
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2702</link>
      <description>Phone Finder in versions earlier before MHA-AL00C00B170 can be bypass. An attacker can bypass the Phone Finder by special steps and obtain the owner of the phone.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2702|2024-09-16T16:48:33.458Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
