<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd. -- P10, P10 Plus</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd./p10%2C%20p10%20plus.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd. -- P10, P10 Plus</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 20:23:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8145|2024-09-16T19:20:17.219Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- p10%2C%20p10%20plus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8145</link>
      <description>The call module of P10 and P10 Plus smartphones with software versions before VTR-AL00C00B167, versions before VTR-TL00C01B167, versions before VKY-AL00C00B167, versions before VKY-TL00C01B167 has a DoS vulnerability. An attacker may trick a user into installing a malicious application, and the application can send given parameter to call module to crash the call and data communication process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8145|2024-09-16T19:20:17.219Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8149|2024-09-16T19:36:58.329Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- p10%2C%20p10%20plus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8149</link>
      <description>The boot loaders of P10 and P10 Plus Huawei mobile phones with software the versions before Victoria-L09AC605B162, the versions before Victoria-L29AC605B162, the versions before Vicky-L29AC605B162 have an out-of-bounds memory access vulnerability due to the lack of parameter validation. An attacker with the root privilege of an Android system may trick a user into installing a malicious APP. the APP can modify specific data to cause buffer overflow in the next system reboot, causing out-of-bounds memory read which can continuous system reboot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8149|2024-09-16T19:36:58.329Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8150|2024-09-16T16:48:35.815Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- p10%2C%20p10%20plus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8150</link>
      <description>The boot loaders of P10 and P10 Plus Huawei mobile phones with software the versions before Victoria-L09AC605B162, the versions before Victoria-L29AC605B162, the versions before Vicky-L29AC605B162 have an arbitrary memory write vulnerability due to the lack of parameter validation. An attacker with the root privilege of an Android system may trick a user into installing a malicious APP. The APP can modify specific data to cause arbitrary memory writing in the next system reboot, causing continuous system reboot or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8150|2024-09-16T16:48:35.815Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
