<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd. -- P9 Plus</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd./p9%20plus.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd. -- P9 Plus</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 21:22:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2731|2024-09-17T02:11:33.325Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- p9%20plus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2731</link>
      <description>The vibrator service in P9 Plus smart phones with software versions earlier before VIE-AL10C00B386 has DoS vulnerability. An attacker can tricks a user into installing a malicious application on the smart phone, and send given parameter to smart phone vibrator service interface to crash the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2731|2024-09-17T02:11:33.325Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-8140|2024-09-17T02:42:29.955Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- p9%20plus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-8140</link>
      <description>The soundtrigger driver in P9 Plus smart phones with software versions earlier than VIE-AL10BC00B353 has a memory double free vulnerability. An attacker tricks a user into installing a malicious application, and the application can start multiple threads and try to free specific memory, which could triggers double free and causes a system crash or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-8140|2024-09-17T02:42:29.955Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2711|2024-09-17T00:06:08.187Z -- huawei%20technologies%20co.%2C%20ltd. -- p9%20plus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2711</link>
      <description>P9 Plus smartphones with software earlier than VIE-AL10C00B352 versions have an input validation vulnerability in the touchscreen Driver. An attacker can tricks a user into installing a malicious application on the smart phone, and send given parameter to smart phone to crash the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2711|2024-09-17T00:06:08.187Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
