<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco Systems, Inc. -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco%20systems%2C%20inc./all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco Systems, Inc. -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 05:23:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6786|2024-09-17T02:42:15.704Z -- cisco%20systems%2C%20inc. -- elastic%20services%20controller
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6786</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Elastic Services Controller could allow an authenticated, local, unprivileged attacker to access sensitive information, including credentials for system accounts, on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to improper protection of sensitive log files. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by logging in to an affected system and accessing unprotected log files. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access sensitive log files, which may include system credentials, on the affected system. Cisco Bug IDs: CSCvc76616. Known Affected Releases: 2.2(9.76).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6786|2024-09-17T02:42:15.704Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0415|2024-09-17T03:43:36.450Z -- cisco%20systems%2C%20inc. -- small%20business%20100%20series%20wireless%20access%20points
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0415</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of Extensible Authentication Protocol over LAN (EAPOL) functionality in Cisco Small Business 100 Series Wireless Access Points and Cisco Small Business 300 Series Wireless Access Points could allow an authenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to the improper processing of certain EAPOL frames. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a stream of crafted EAPOL frames to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to force the access point (AP) to disassociate all the associated stations (STAs) and to disallow future, new association requests. Cisco Bug IDs: CSCvj97472.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0415|2024-09-17T03:43:36.450Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6785|2024-09-17T03:18:55.237Z -- cisco%20systems%2C%20inc. -- unified%20communications%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6785</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in configuration modification permissions validation for Cisco Unified Communications Manager could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform a horizontal privilege escalation where one user can modify another user's configuration. The vulnerability is due to lack of proper Role Based Access Control (RBAC) when certain user configuration changes are requested. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending an authenticated, crafted HTTP request to the targeted application. An exploit could allow the attacker to impact the integrity of the application where one user can modify the configuration of another user's information. Cisco Bug IDs: CSCve27331. Known Affected Releases: 10.5(2.10000.5), 11.0(1.10000.10), 11.5(1.10000.6).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6785|2024-09-17T03:18:55.237Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6768|2024-09-17T01:41:54.517Z -- cisco%20systems%2C%20inc. -- application%20policy%20infrastructure%20controller%20%28apic%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6768</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the build procedure for certain executable system files installed at boot time on Cisco Application Policy Infrastructure Controller (APIC) devices could allow an authenticated, local attacker to gain root-level privileges. The vulnerability is due to a custom executable system file that was built to use relative search paths for libraries without properly validating the library to be loaded. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device and loading a malicious library that can escalate the privilege level. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain root-level privileges and take full control of the device. The attacker must have valid user credentials to log in to the device. Cisco Bug IDs: CSCvc96087. Known Affected Releases: 1.1(0.920a), 1.1(1j), 1.1(3f); 1.2 Base, 1.2(2), 1.2(3), 1.2.2; 1.3(1), 1.3(2), 1.3(2f); 2.0 Base, 2.0(1).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6768|2024-09-17T01:41:54.517Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0419|2024-09-17T01:30:51.889Z -- cisco%20systems%2C%20inc. -- email%20security%20appliance%20%28esa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0419</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in certain attachment detection mechanisms of Cisco Email Security Appliances (ESA) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass the filtering functionality of an affected system. The vulnerability is due to the improper detection of content within executable (EXE) files. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a customized EXE file that is not recognized and blocked by the ESA. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to send email messages that contain malicious executable files to unsuspecting users. Cisco Bug IDs: CSCvh03786.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0419|2024-09-17T01:30:51.889Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6771|2024-09-17T01:21:39.369Z -- cisco%20systems%2C%20inc. -- ultra%20services%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6771</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the AutoVNF automation tool of the Cisco Ultra Services Framework could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to acquire sensitive information. The vulnerability is due to insufficient protection of sensitive data. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by browsing to a specific URL of an affected device. An exploit could allow the attacker to view sensitive configuration information about the deployment. Cisco Bug IDs: CSCvd29358. Known Affected Releases: 21.0.v0.65839.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6771|2024-09-17T01:21:39.369Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6773|2024-09-17T02:21:21.737Z -- cisco%20systems%2C%20inc. -- staros%20for%20asr%205000%20series%20aggregated%20services%20routers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6773</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco ASR 5000 Series Aggregated Services Routers running the Cisco StarOS operating system could allow an authenticated, local attacker to bypass the CLI restrictions and execute commands on the underlying operating system. The vulnerability is due to insufficient input sanitization of user-supplied input at the CLI. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by crafting a script on the device that will allow them to bypass built-in restrictions. An exploit could allow the unauthorized user to launch the CLI directly from a command shell. Cisco Bug IDs: CSCvd47722. Known Affected Releases: 21.0.v0.65839.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6773|2024-09-17T02:21:21.737Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0386|2024-09-17T04:24:30.071Z -- cisco%20systems%2C%20inc. -- unified%20communications%20domain%20manager%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0386</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Unified Communications Domain Manager Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to improper validation of input that is passed to the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the affected software to access a malicious URL. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access sensitive, browser-based information on the affected system or perform arbitrary actions in the affected software in the security context of the user. Cisco Bug IDs: CSCvh49694.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0386|2024-09-17T04:24:30.071Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0428|2024-09-17T00:25:37.090Z -- cisco%20systems%2C%20inc. -- web%20security%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0428</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the account management subsystem of Cisco Web Security Appliance (WSA) could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate privileges to root. The attacker must authenticate with valid administrator credentials. The vulnerability is due to improper implementation of access controls. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the device as a specific user to gain the information needed to elevate privileges to root in a separate login shell. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to escape the CLI subshell and execute system-level commands on the underlying operating system as root. Cisco Bug IDs: CSCvj93548.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0428|2024-09-17T00:25:37.090Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6781|2024-09-17T02:15:39.209Z -- cisco%20systems%2C%20inc. -- policy%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6781</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the management of shell user accounts for Cisco Policy Suite (CPS) Software for CPS appliances could allow an authenticated, local attacker to gain elevated privileges on an affected system. The affected privilege level is not at the root level. The vulnerability is due to incorrect role-based access control (RBAC) for shell user accounts. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to an affected appliance and providing crafted user input via the CLI. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to acquire a higher privilege level than should have been granted. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must log in to the appliance with valid credentials. Cisco Bug IDs: CSCve37724. Known Affected Releases: 9.0.0, 9.1.0, 10.0.0, 11.0.0, 12.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6781|2024-09-17T02:15:39.209Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6774|2024-09-17T03:49:16.049Z -- cisco%20systems%2C%20inc. -- staros%20for%20asr%205000%20series%20aggregated%20services%20routers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6774</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco ASR 5000 Series Aggregated Services Routers running the Cisco StarOS operating system could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to overwrite or modify sensitive system files. The vulnerability is due to the inclusion of sensitive system files within specific FTP subdirectories. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by overwriting sensitive configuration files through FTP. An exploit could allow the attacker to overwrite configuration files on an affected system. Cisco Bug IDs: CSCvd47739. Known Affected Releases: 21.0.v0.65839.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6774|2024-09-17T03:49:16.049Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0367|2024-09-17T02:06:17.178Z -- cisco%20systems%2C%20inc. -- registered%20envelope%20service
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0367</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of the Cisco Registered Envelope Service could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface of the affected service. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input that is processed by the web-based management interface of the affected service. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a malicious link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface or access sensitive browser-based information. Cisco Bug IDs: CVE-2018-0367.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0367|2024-09-17T02:06:17.178Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
