<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco Systems, Inc. -- Elastic Services Controller</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco%20systems%2C%20inc./elastic%20services%20controller.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco Systems, Inc. -- Elastic Services Controller</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 17:22:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6776|2024-08-05T15:41:17.129Z -- cisco%20systems%2C%20inc. -- elastic%20services%20controller
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6776</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the web framework of Cisco Elastic Services Controller (ESC) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web interface. The vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by convincing a user to access a malicious link or by intercepting a user request and injecting malicious code into the request. An exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected site or allow the attacker to access sensitive browser-based information. Cisco Bug IDs: CSCvd76324. Known Affected Releases: 2.2(9.76) and 2.3(1).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6776|2024-08-05T15:41:17.129Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6786|2024-08-05T15:41:17.471Z -- cisco%20systems%2C%20inc. -- elastic%20services%20controller
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6786</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Elastic Services Controller could allow an authenticated, local, unprivileged attacker to access sensitive information, including credentials for system accounts, on an affected system. The vulnerability is due to improper protection of sensitive log files. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by logging in to an affected system and accessing unprotected log files. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access sensitive log files, which may include system credentials, on the affected system. Cisco Bug IDs: CSCvc76616. Known Affected Releases: 2.2(9.76).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6786|2024-08-05T15:41:17.471Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6772|2024-08-05T15:41:17.206Z -- cisco%20systems%2C%20inc. -- elastic%20services%20controller
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6772</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Cisco Elastic Services Controller (ESC) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to view sensitive information. The vulnerability is due to insufficient protection of sensitive data. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the application and navigating to certain configuration files. An exploit could allow the attacker to view sensitive system configuration files. Cisco Bug IDs: CSCvd29408. Known Affected Releases: 2.3(2).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6772|2024-08-05T15:41:17.206Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6777|2024-08-05T15:41:17.313Z -- cisco%20systems%2C%20inc. -- elastic%20services%20controller
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6777</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the ConfD server of the Cisco Elastic Services Controller (ESC) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to acquire sensitive system information. The vulnerability is due to insufficient protection of sensitive files on the system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by logging into the ConfD server and executing certain commands. An exploit could allow an unprivileged user to view configuration parameters that can be maliciously used. Cisco Bug IDs: CSCvd76409. Known Affected Releases: 2.3, 2.3(2).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6777|2024-08-05T15:41:17.313Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
