<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco Systems, Inc. -- Small Business 100 Series Wireless Access Points</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco%20systems%2C%20inc./small%20business%20100%20series%20wireless%20access%20points.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco Systems, Inc. -- Small Business 100 Series Wireless Access Points</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 17:22:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0412|2024-08-05T03:21:15.608Z -- cisco%20systems%2C%20inc. -- small%20business%20100%20series%20wireless%20access%20points
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0412</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of Extensible Authentication Protocol over LAN (EAPOL) functionality in Cisco Small Business 100 Series Wireless Access Points and Cisco Small Business 300 Series Wireless Access Points could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to force the downgrade of the encryption algorithm that is used between an authenticator (access point) and a supplicant (Wi-Fi client). The vulnerability is due to the improper processing of certain EAPOL messages that are received during the Wi-Fi handshake process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by establishing a man-in-the-middle position between a supplicant and an authenticator and manipulating an EAPOL message exchange to force usage of a WPA-TKIP cipher instead of the more secure AES-CCMP cipher. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to conduct subsequent cryptographic attacks, which could lead to the disclosure of confidential information. Cisco Bug IDs: CSCvj29229.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0412|2024-08-05T03:21:15.608Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-0415|2024-08-05T03:21:15.471Z -- cisco%20systems%2C%20inc. -- small%20business%20100%20series%20wireless%20access%20points
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-0415</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the implementation of Extensible Authentication Protocol over LAN (EAPOL) functionality in Cisco Small Business 100 Series Wireless Access Points and Cisco Small Business 300 Series Wireless Access Points could allow an authenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device. The vulnerability is due to the improper processing of certain EAPOL frames. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a stream of crafted EAPOL frames to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to force the access point (AP) to disassociate all the associated stations (STAs) and to disallow future, new association requests. Cisco Bug IDs: CSCvj97472.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-0415|2024-08-05T03:21:15.471Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
