<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Cisco Systems, Inc. -- Web Security Appliance (WSA)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/cisco%20systems%2C%20inc./web%20security%20appliance%20%28wsa%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Cisco Systems, Inc. -- Web Security Appliance (WSA)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 20:23:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6783|2024-08-05T15:41:17.252Z -- cisco%20systems%2C%20inc. -- web%20security%20appliance%20%28wsa%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6783</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in SNMP polling for the Cisco Web Security Appliance (WSA), Email Security Appliance (ESA), and Content Security Management Appliance (SMA) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to discover confidential information about the appliances that should be available only to an administrative user. The vulnerability occurs because the appliances do not protect confidential information at rest in response to Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) poll requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by doing a crafted SNMP poll request to the targeted security appliance. An exploit could allow the attacker to discover confidential information that should be restricted, and the attacker could use this information to conduct additional reconnaissance. The attacker must know the configured SNMP community string to exploit this vulnerability. Cisco Bug IDs: CSCve26106, CSCve26202, CSCve26224. Known Affected Releases: 10.0.0-230 (Web Security Appliance), 9.7.2-065 (Email Security Appliance), and 10.1.0-037 (Content Security Management Appliance).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6783|2024-08-05T15:41:17.252Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
