<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for The Eclipse Foundation -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/the%20eclipse%20foundation/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for The Eclipse Foundation -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:23:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27224|2024-08-04T16:11:36.023Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20theia
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27224</link>
      <description>In Eclipse Theia versions up to and including 1.2.0, the Markdown Preview (@theia/preview), can be exploited to execute arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27224|2024-08-04T16:11:36.023Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 16:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41042|2024-08-04T02:59:31.150Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20lyo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41042</link>
      <description>In Eclipse Lyo versions 1.0.0 to 4.1.0, a TransformerFactory is initialized with the defaults that do not restrict DTD loading when working with RDF/XML. This allows an attacker to cause an external DTD to be retrieved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41042|2024-08-04T02:59:31.150Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 20:55:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-10249|2024-08-04T22:17:19.691Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20xtext
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-10249</link>
      <description>All Xtext &amp; Xtend versions prior to 2.18.0 were built using HTTP instead of HTTPS file transfer and thus the built artifacts may have been compromised.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-10249|2024-08-04T22:17:19.691Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 16:12:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34430|2024-08-04T00:12:50.067Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20tinydtls
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34430</link>
      <description>Eclipse TinyDTLS through 0.9-rc1 relies on the rand function in the C library, which makes it easier for remote attackers to compute the master key and then decrypt DTLS traffic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34430|2024-08-04T00:12:50.067Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 03:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41039|2024-08-04T02:59:31.087Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20mosquitto
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41039</link>
      <description>In versions 1.6 to 2.0.11 of Eclipse Mosquitto, an MQTT v5 client connecting with a large number of user-property properties could cause excessive CPU usage, leading to a loss of performance and possible denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41039|2024-08-04T02:59:31.087Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-10243|2024-08-04T22:17:19.791Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20kura
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-10243</link>
      <description>In Eclipse Kura versions up to 4.0.0, Kura exposes the underlying Ui Web server version in its replies. This can be used as a hint by an attacker to specifically craft attacks to the web server run by Kura.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-10243|2024-08-04T22:17:19.791Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 15:42:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27221|2024-08-04T16:11:35.952Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20openj9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27221</link>
      <description>In Eclipse OpenJ9 up to and including version 0.23, there is potential for a stack-based buffer overflow when the virtual machine or JNI natives are converting from UTF-8 characters to platform encoding.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27221|2024-08-04T16:11:35.952Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 04:55:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27217|2024-08-04T16:11:35.953Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20hono
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27217</link>
      <description>In Eclipse Hono version 1.3.0 and 1.4.0 the AMQP protocol adapter does not verify the size of AMQP messages received from devices. In particular, a device may send messages that are bigger than the max-message-size that the protocol adapter has indicated during link establishment. While the AMQP 1.0 protocol explicitly disallows a peer to send such messages, a hand crafted AMQP 1.0 client could exploit this behavior in order to send a message of unlimited size to the adapter, eventually causing the adapter to fail with an out of memory exception.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27217|2024-08-04T16:11:35.953Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 19:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41035|2024-08-04T02:59:30.989Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20omr
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41035</link>
      <description>In Eclipse Openj9 before version 0.29.0, the JVM does not throw IllegalAccessError for MethodHandles that invoke inaccessible interface methods.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41035|2024-08-04T02:59:30.989Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 15:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34432|2024-08-04T00:12:50.095Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20mosquitto
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34432</link>
      <description>In Eclipse Mosquitto versions 2.07 and earlier, the server will crash if the client tries to send a PUBLISH packet with topic length = 0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34432|2024-08-04T00:12:50.095Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 15:25:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-10245|2024-08-04T22:17:19.773Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20openj9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-10245</link>
      <description>In Eclipse OpenJ9 prior to the 0.14.0 release, the Java bytecode verifier incorrectly allows a method to execute past the end of bytecode array causing crashes. Eclipse OpenJ9 v0.14.0 correctly detects this case and rejects the attempted class load.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-10245|2024-08-04T22:17:19.773Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 13:43:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-10247|2024-08-04T22:17:19.834Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20jetty
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-10247</link>
      <description>In Eclipse Jetty version 7.x, 8.x, 9.2.27 and older, 9.3.26 and older, and 9.4.16 and older, the server running on any OS and Jetty version combination will reveal the configured fully qualified directory base resource location on the output of the 404 error for not finding a Context that matches the requested path. The default server behavior on jetty-distribution and jetty-home will include at the end of the Handler tree a DefaultHandler, which is responsible for reporting this 404 error, it presents the various configured contexts as HTML for users to click through to. This produced HTML includes output that contains the configured fully qualified directory base resource location for each context.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-10247|2024-08-04T22:17:19.834Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 20:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41038|2024-08-04T02:59:30.930Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- %40theia%2Fplugin-ext
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41038</link>
      <description>In versions of the @theia/plugin-ext component of Eclipse Theia prior to 1.18.0, Webview contents can be hijacked via postMessage().</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41038|2024-08-04T02:59:30.930Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 17:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-10242|2024-08-04T22:17:20.146Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20kura
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-10242</link>
      <description>In Eclipse Kura versions up to 4.0.0, the SkinServlet did not checked the path passed during servlet call, potentially allowing path traversal in get requests for a limited number of file types.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-10242|2024-08-04T22:17:20.146Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 15:42:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41036|2024-08-04T02:59:31.302Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20paho%20mqtt%20c%20client
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41036</link>
      <description>In versions prior to 1.1 of the Eclipse Paho MQTT C Client, the client does not check rem_len size in readpacket.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41036|2024-08-04T02:59:31.302Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 23:15:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27216|2024-08-04T16:11:36.150Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20jetty
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27216</link>
      <description>In Eclipse Jetty versions 1.0 thru 9.4.32.v20200930, 10.0.0.alpha1 thru 10.0.0.beta2, and 11.0.0.alpha1 thru 11.0.0.beta2O, on Unix like systems, the system's temporary directory is shared between all users on that system. A collocated user can observe the process of creating a temporary sub directory in the shared temporary directory and race to complete the creation of the temporary subdirectory. If the attacker wins the race then they will have read and write permission to the subdirectory used to unpack web applications, including their WEB-INF/lib jar files and JSP files. If any code is ever executed out of this temporary directory, this can lead to a local privilege escalation vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27216|2024-08-04T16:11:36.150Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 00:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27220|2024-08-04T16:11:36.045Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20hono
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27220</link>
      <description>The Eclipse Hono AMQP and MQTT protocol adapters do not check whether an authenticated gateway device is authorized to receive command &amp; control messages when it has subscribed only to commands for a specific device. The missing check involves verifying that the command target device is configured giving permission for the gateway device to act on its behalf. This means an authenticated device of a certain tenant, notably also a non-gateway device acting like a gateway, may receive command &amp; control messages targeted at a different device of the same tenant without corresponding permissions getting checked.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27220|2024-08-04T16:11:36.045Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 22:35:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-10241|2024-08-04T22:17:19.587Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20jetty
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-10241</link>
      <description>In Eclipse Jetty version 9.2.26 and older, 9.3.25 and older, and 9.4.15 and older, the server is vulnerable to XSS conditions if a remote client USES a specially formatted URL against the DefaultServlet or ResourceHandler that is configured for showing a Listing of directory contents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-10241|2024-08-04T22:17:19.587Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 20:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41033|2024-08-04T02:59:30.351Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20equinox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41033</link>
      <description>In all released versions of Eclipse Equinox, at least until version 4.21 (September 2021), installation can be vulnerable to man-in-the-middle attack if using p2 repos that are HTTP; that can then be exploited to serve incorrect p2 metadata and entirely alter the local installation, particularly by installing plug-ins that may then run malicious code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41033|2024-08-04T02:59:30.351Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 20:55:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41034|2024-08-04T02:59:31.177Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20che
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41034</link>
      <description>The build of some language stacks of Eclipse Che version 6 includes pulling some binaries from an unsecured HTTP endpoint. As a consequence the builds of such stacks are vulnerable to MITM attacks that allow the replacement of the original binaries with arbitrary ones. The stacks involved are Java 8 (alpine and centos), Android and PHP. The vulnerability is not exploitable at runtime but only when building Che.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41034|2024-08-04T02:59:31.177Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 21:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34429|2024-08-04T00:12:50.169Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20jetty
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34429</link>
      <description>For Eclipse Jetty versions 9.4.37-9.4.42, 10.0.1-10.0.5 &amp; 11.0.1-11.0.5, URIs can be crafted using some encoded characters to access the content of the WEB-INF directory and/or bypass some security constraints. This is a variation of the vulnerability reported in CVE-2021-28164/GHSA-v7ff-8wcx-gmc5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34429|2024-08-04T00:12:50.169Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 17:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41041|2024-08-04T02:59:31.309Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20openj9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41041</link>
      <description>In Eclipse Openj9 before version 0.32.0, Java 8 &amp; 11 fail to throw the exception captured during bytecode verification when verification is triggered by a MethodHandle invocation, allowing unverified methods to be invoked using MethodHandles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41041|2024-08-04T02:59:31.309Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 02:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34433|2024-08-04T00:12:50.235Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20californium
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34433</link>
      <description>In Eclipse Californium version 2.0.0 to 2.6.4 and 3.0.0-M1 to 3.0.0-M3, the certificate based (x509 and RPK) DTLS handshakes accidentally succeeds without verifying the server side's signature on the client side, if that signature is not included in the server's ServerKeyExchange.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34433|2024-08-04T00:12:50.235Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 17:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34436|2024-08-04T00:12:50.189Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20theia
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34436</link>
      <description>In Eclipse Theia 0.1.1 to 0.2.0, it is possible to exploit the default build to obtain remote code execution (and XXE) via the theia-xml-extension. This extension uses lsp4xml (recently renamed to LemMinX) in order to provide language support for XML. This is installed by default.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34436|2024-08-04T00:12:50.189Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 20:55:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27222|2024-08-04T16:11:36.000Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20californium
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27222</link>
      <description>In Eclipse Californium version 2.3.0 to 2.6.0, the certificate based (x509 and RPK) DTLS handshakes accidentally fails, because the DTLS server side sticks to a wrong internal state. That wrong internal state is set by a previous certificate based DTLS handshake failure with TLS parameter mismatch. The DTLS server side must be restarted to recover this. This allow clients to force a DoS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27222|2024-08-04T16:11:36.000Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 15:45:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-10246|2024-08-04T22:17:19.655Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20jetty
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-10246</link>
      <description>In Eclipse Jetty version 9.2.27, 9.3.26, and 9.4.16, the server running on Windows is vulnerable to exposure of the fully qualified Base Resource directory name on Windows to a remote client when it is configured for showing a Listing of directory contents. This information reveal is restricted to only the content in the configured base resource directories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-10246|2024-08-04T22:17:19.655Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 20:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34427|2024-08-04T00:12:50.360Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20birt
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34427</link>
      <description>In Eclipse BIRT versions 4.8.0 and earlier, an attacker can use query parameters to create a JSP file which is accessible from remote (current BIRT viewer dir) to inject JSP code into the running instance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34427|2024-08-04T00:12:50.360Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34431|2024-08-04T00:12:50.247Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20mosquitto
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34431</link>
      <description>In Eclipse Mosquitto version 1.6 to 2.0.10, if an authenticated client that had connected with MQTT v5 sent a crafted CONNECT message to the broker a memory leak would occur, which could be used to provide a DoS attack against the broker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34431|2024-08-04T00:12:50.247Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 13:45:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27219|2024-08-04T16:11:36.119Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20hawkbit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27219</link>
      <description>In all version of Eclipse Hawkbit prior to 0.3.0M7, the HTTP 404 (Not Found) JSON response body returned by the REST API may contain unsafe characters within the path attribute. Sending a POST request to a non existing resource will return the full path from the given URL unescaped to the client.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27219|2024-08-04T16:11:36.119Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 22:20:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27225|2024-08-04T16:11:36.031Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27225</link>
      <description>In versions 4.18 and earlier of the Eclipse Platform, the Help Subsystem does not authenticate active help requests to the local help web server, allowing an unauthenticated local attacker to issue active help commands to the associated Eclipse Platform process or Eclipse Rich Client Platform process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27225|2024-08-04T16:11:36.031Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 18:15:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34428|2024-08-04T00:12:50.169Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20jetty
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34428</link>
      <description>For Eclipse Jetty versions &lt;= 9.4.40, &lt;= 10.0.2, &lt;= 11.0.2, if an exception is thrown from the SessionListener#sessionDestroyed() method, then the session ID is not invalidated in the session ID manager. On deployments with clustered sessions and multiple contexts this can result in a session not being invalidated. This can result in an application used on a shared computer being left logged in.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34428|2024-08-04T00:12:50.169Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 14:45:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-10240|2024-08-04T22:17:19.603Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20hawkbit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-10240</link>
      <description>Eclipse hawkBit versions prior to 0.3.0M2 resolved Maven build artifacts for the Vaadin based UI over HTTP instead of HTTPS. Any of these dependent artifacts could have been maliciously compromised by a MITM attack. Hence produced build artifacts of hawkBit might be infected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-10240|2024-08-04T22:17:19.603Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 18:04:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41037|2024-08-04T02:59:30.336Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20equinox%20p2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41037</link>
      <description>In Eclipse p2, installable units are able to alter the Eclipse Platform installation and the local machine via touchpoints during installation. Those touchpoints can, for example, alter the command-line used to start the application, injecting things like agent or other settings that usually require particular attention in term of security. Although p2 has built-in strategies to ensure artifacts are signed and then to help establish trust, there is no such strategy for the metadata part that does configure such touchpoints. As a result, it's possible to install a unit that will run malicious code during installation without user receiving any warning about this installation step being risky when coming from untrusted source.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41037|2024-08-04T02:59:30.336Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 03:50:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34434|2024-08-04T00:12:50.159Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20mosquitto
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34434</link>
      <description>In Eclipse Mosquitto versions 2.0 to 2.0.11, when using the dynamic security plugin, if the ability for a client to make subscriptions on a topic is revoked when a durable client is offline, then existing subscriptions for that client are not revoked.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34434|2024-08-04T00:12:50.159Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27218|2024-08-04T16:11:36.083Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20jetty
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27218</link>
      <description>In Eclipse Jetty version 9.4.0.RC0 to 9.4.34.v20201102, 10.0.0.alpha0 to 10.0.0.beta2, and 11.0.0.alpha0 to 11.0.0.beta2, if GZIP request body inflation is enabled and requests from different clients are multiplexed onto a single connection, and if an attacker can send a request with a body that is received entirely but not consumed by the application, then a subsequent request on the same connection will see that body prepended to its body. The attacker will not see any data but may inject data into the body of the subsequent request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27218|2024-08-04T16:11:36.083Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-10248|2024-08-04T22:17:20.094Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20vorto
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-10248</link>
      <description>Eclipse Vorto versions prior to 0.11 resolved Maven build artifacts for the Xtext project over HTTP instead of HTTPS. Any of these dependent artifacts could have been maliciously compromised by a MITM attack. Hence produced build artifacts of Vorto might be infected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-10248|2024-08-04T22:17:20.094Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 20:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-10244|2024-08-04T22:17:19.931Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20kura
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-10244</link>
      <description>In Eclipse Kura versions up to 4.0.0, the Web UI package and component services, the Artemis simple Mqtt component and the emulator position service (not part of the device distribution) could potentially be target of XXE attack due to an improper factory and parser initialisation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-10244|2024-08-04T22:17:19.931Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 15:42:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27223|2024-08-04T16:11:36.050Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20jetty
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27223</link>
      <description>In Eclipse Jetty 9.4.6.v20170531 to 9.4.36.v20210114 (inclusive), 10.0.0, and 11.0.0 when Jetty handles a request containing multiple Accept headers with a large number of “quality” (i.e. q) parameters, the server may enter a denial of service (DoS) state due to high CPU usage processing those quality values, resulting in minutes of CPU time exhausted processing those quality values.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27223|2024-08-04T16:11:36.050Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 21:55:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34435|2024-08-04T00:12:50.149Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20theia
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34435</link>
      <description>In Eclipse Theia 0.3.9 to 1.8.1, the "mini-browser" extension allows a user to preview HTML files in an iframe inside the IDE. But with the way it is made it is possible for a previewed HTML file to trigger an RCE. This exploit only happens if a user previews a malicious file..</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34435|2024-08-04T00:12:50.149Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 17:20:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
