<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for The Eclipse Foundation -- Eclipse Memory Analyzer</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/the%20eclipse%20foundation/eclipse%20memory%20analyzer.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for The Eclipse Foundation -- Eclipse Memory Analyzer</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 19:21:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17635|2024-08-05T01:47:13.610Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20memory%20analyzer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17635</link>
      <description>Eclipse Memory Analyzer version 1.9.1 and earlier is subject to a deserialization vulnerability if an index file of a parsed heap dump is replaced by a malicious version and the heap dump is reopened in Memory Analyzer. The user must chose to reopen an already parsed heap dump with an untrusted index for the problem to occur. The problem can be averted if the index files from an untrusted source are deleted and the heap dump is opened and reparsed. Also some local configuration data is subject to a deserialization vulnerability if the local data were to be replaced with a malicious version. This can be averted if the local configuration data stored on the file system cannot be changed by an attacker. The vulnerability could possibly allow code execution on the local system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17635|2024-08-05T01:47:13.610Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 18:35:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-17634|2024-08-05T01:47:13.640Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20memory%20analyzer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-17634</link>
      <description>Eclipse Memory Analyzer version 1.9.1 and earlier is subject to a cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability when generating an HTML report from a malicious heap dump. The user must chose todownload, open the malicious heap dump and generate an HTML report for the problem to occur. The heap dump could be specially crafted, or could come from a crafted application or from an application processing malicious data. The vulnerability is present whena report is generated and opened from the Memory Analyzer graphical user interface, or when a report generated in batch mode is then opened in Memory Analyzer or by a web browser. The vulnerability could possibly allow code execution on the local system whenthe report is opened in Memory Analyzer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-17634|2024-08-05T01:47:13.640Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 18:35:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
