<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for The Eclipse Foundation -- Eclipse Mosquitto</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/the%20eclipse%20foundation/eclipse%20mosquitto.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for The Eclipse Foundation -- Eclipse Mosquitto</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 16:24:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12551|2024-08-05T08:38:06.296Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20mosquitto
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12551</link>
      <description>When Eclipse Mosquitto version 1.0 to 1.5.5 (inclusive) is configured to use a password file for authentication, any malformed data in the password file will be treated as valid. This typically means that the malformed data becomes a username and no password. If this occurs, clients can circumvent authentication and get access to the broker by using the malformed username. In particular, a blank line will be treated as a valid empty username. Other security measures are unaffected. Users who have only used the mosquitto_passwd utility to create and modify their password files are unaffected by this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12551|2024-08-05T08:38:06.296Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 17:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12550|2024-08-05T08:38:06.290Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20mosquitto
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12550</link>
      <description>When Eclipse Mosquitto version 1.0 to 1.5.5 (inclusive) is configured to use an ACL file, and that ACL file is empty, or contains only comments or blank lines, then Mosquitto will treat this as though no ACL file has been defined and use a default allow policy. The new behaviour is to have an empty ACL file mean that all access is denied, which is not a useful configuration but is not unexpected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12550|2024-08-05T08:38:06.290Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 17:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12546|2024-08-05T08:38:06.266Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20mosquitto
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12546</link>
      <description>In Eclipse Mosquitto version 1.0 to 1.5.5 (inclusive) when a client publishes a retained message to a topic, then has its access to that topic revoked, the retained message will still be published to clients that subscribe to that topic in the future. In some applications this may result in clients being able cause effects that would otherwise not be allowed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12546|2024-08-05T08:38:06.266Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 17:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-12543|2024-08-05T08:38:06.301Z -- the%20eclipse%20foundation -- eclipse%20mosquitto
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-12543</link>
      <description>In Eclipse Mosquitto versions 1.5 to 1.5.2 inclusive, if a message is published to Mosquitto that has a topic starting with $, but that is not $SYS, e.g. $test/test, then an assert is triggered that should otherwise not be reachable and Mosquitto will exit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-12543|2024-08-05T08:38:06.301Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
