<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Dahua Technologies -- Dahua IP Camera and IP PTZ IPC-HFW1XXX, IPC-HDW1XXX, IPC-HDBW1XXX, IPC-HFW2XXX, IPC-HDW2XXX, IPC-HDBW2XXX, IPC-HFW4XXX, IPC-HDW4XXX, IPC-HDBW4XXX, IPC-HF5XXX, IPC-HFW5XXX, IPC-HDW5XXX, IPC-HDBW5XXX, IPC-HF8XXX, IPC-HFW8XXX, IPC-HDBW8XXX, IPC-EBW8XXX, IPC-PFW8xxx, IPC-PDBW8xxx, IPC-HUM8xxx, PSD8xxxx, DH-SD2XXXXX, DH-SD4XXXXX, DH-SD5XXXXX, DH-SD6XXXXX</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/dahua%20technologies/dahua%20ip%20camera%20and%20ip%20ptz%20ipc-hfw1xxx%2C%20ipc-hdw1xxx%2C%20ipc-hdbw1xxx%2C%20ipc-hfw2xxx%2C%20ipc-hdw2xxx%2C%20ipc-hdbw2xxx%2C%20ipc-hfw4xxx%2C%20ipc-hdw4xxx%2C%20ipc-hdbw4xxx%2C%20ipc-hf5xxx%2C%20ipc-hfw5xxx%2C%20ipc-hdw5xxx%2C%20ipc-h.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Dahua Technologies -- Dahua IP Camera and IP PTZ IPC-HFW1XXX, IPC-HDW1XXX, IPC-HDBW1XXX, IPC-HFW2XXX, IPC-HDW2XXX, IPC-HDBW2XXX, IPC-HFW4XXX, IPC-HDW4XXX, IPC-HDBW4XXX, IPC-HF5XXX, IPC-HFW5XXX, IPC-HDW5XXX, IPC-HDBW5XXX, IPC-HF8XXX, IPC-HFW8XXX, IPC-HDBW8XXX, IPC-EBW8XXX, IPC-PFW8xxx, IPC-PDBW8xxx, IPC-HUM8xxx, PSD8xxxx, DH-SD2XXXXX, DH-SD4XXXXX, DH-SD5XXXXX, DH-SD6XXXXX</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 20:23:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-9315|2024-08-05T17:02:44.242Z -- dahua%20technologies -- dahua%20ip%20camera%20and%20ip%20ptz%20ipc-hfw1xxx%2C%20ipc-hdw1xxx%2C%20ipc-hdbw1xxx%2C%20ipc-hfw2xxx%2C%20ipc-hdw2xxx%2C%20ipc-hdbw2xxx%2C%20ipc-hfw4xxx%2C%20ipc-hdw4xxx%2C%20ipc-hdbw4xxx%2C%20ipc-hf5xxx%2C%20ipc-hfw5xxx%2C%20ipc-hdw5xxx%2C%20ipc-h
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-9315</link>
      <description>Customer of Dahua IP camera or IP PTZ could submit relevant device information to receive a time limited temporary password from Dahua authorized dealer to reset the admin password. The algorithm used in this mechanism is potentially at risk of being compromised and subsequently utilized by attacker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-9315|2024-08-05T17:02:44.242Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
