<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for labibahmed42 -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/labibahmed42/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for labibahmed42 -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 20:22:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-4383|2024-08-03T17:23:10.754Z -- labibahmed42 -- wp%20quick%20frontend%20editor%20%E2%80%93%20wordpress%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4383</link>
      <description>The WP Quick FrontEnd Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to page content injection in versions up to, and including, 5.5. This is due to missing capability checks in the plugin's page-editing functionality. This makes it possible for low-authenticated attackers, such as subscribers, to edit/create any page or post on the blog.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-4383|2024-08-03T17:23:10.754Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 01:51:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-4363|2024-08-03T17:23:10.713Z -- labibahmed42 -- wp%20quick%20frontend%20editor%20%E2%80%93%20wordpress%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4363</link>
      <description>The WP Quick FrontEnd Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting in versions up to, and including, 5.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the 'save_content_front' function that uses print_r on the user-supplied $_REQUEST values . This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-4363|2024-08-03T17:23:10.713Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 01:51:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-4378|2024-08-03T17:23:10.714Z -- labibahmed42 -- wp%20quick%20frontend%20editor%20%E2%80%93%20wordpress%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4378</link>
      <description>The WP Quick FrontEnd Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in versions up to, and including, 5.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with minimal permissions like subscribers, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-4378|2024-08-03T17:23:10.714Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 01:51:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-4371|2024-08-03T17:23:10.723Z -- labibahmed42 -- wp%20quick%20frontend%20editor%20%E2%80%93%20wordpress%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4371</link>
      <description>The WP Quick FrontEnd Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Setting Changs in versions up to, and including, 5.5. This is due to lacking both a security nonce and a capabilities check. This makes it possible for low-authenticated attackers to change plugin settings even when they do not have the capabilities to do so.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-4371|2024-08-03T17:23:10.723Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 01:51:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
