<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Endress+Hauser -- RSG35 - Ecograph T</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/endress%2Bhauser/rsg35%20-%20ecograph%20t.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Endress+Hauser -- RSG35 - Ecograph T</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:23:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-12495|2024-08-04T11:56:52.046Z -- endress%2Bhauser -- rsg35%20-%20ecograph%20t
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12495</link>
      <description>Endress+Hauser Ecograph T (Neutral/Private Label) (RSG35, ORSG35) with Firmware version prior to V2.0.0 is prone to improper privilege management. The affected device has a web-based user interface with a role-based access system. Users with different roles have different write and read privileges. The access system is based on dynamic "tokens". The vulnerability is that user sessions are not closed correctly and a user with fewer rights is assigned the higher rights when he logs on.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-12495|2024-08-04T11:56:52.046Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-12496|2024-08-04T11:56:52.113Z -- endress%2Bhauser -- rsg35%20-%20ecograph%20t
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12496</link>
      <description>Endress+Hauser Ecograph T (Neutral/Private Label) (RSG35, ORSG35) and Memograph M (Neutral/Private Label) (RSG45, ORSG45) with Firmware version V2.0.0 and above is prone to exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor. The firmware release has a dynamic token for each request submitted to the server, which makes repeating requests and analysis complex enough. Nevertheless, it's possible and during the analysis it was discovered that it also has an issue with the access-control matrix on the server-side. It was found that a user with low rights can get information from endpoints that should not be available to this user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-12496|2024-08-04T11:56:52.113Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
