<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for dd32 -- Debug Bar Plugin</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/dd32/debug%20bar%20plugin.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for dd32 -- Debug Bar Plugin</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:19:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2013-10021|2024-08-06T18:09:17.006Z -- dd32 -- debug%20bar%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2013-10021</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in dd32 Debug Bar Plugin up to 0.8 on WordPress. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function render of the file panels/class-debug-bar-queries.php. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 0.8.1 is able to address this issue. The patch is named 0842af8f8a556bc3e39b9ef758173b0a8a9ccbfc. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-222739.
In dd32 Debug Bar Plugin bis 0.8 für WordPress wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Hierbei betrifft es die Funktion render der Datei panels/class-debug-bar-queries.php. Dank der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 0.8.1 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als 0842af8f8a556bc3e39b9ef758173b0a8a9ccbfc bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2013-10021|2024-08-06T18:09:17.006Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 20:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
