<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Liferay -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/liferay/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Liferay -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 20:24:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-26265|2024-10-02T15:35:51.464Z -- liferay -- portal
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26265</link>
      <description>The Image Uploader module in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.15, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 16, 7.3 before update 4, 7.2 before fix pack 19, and older unsupported versions relies on a request parameter to limit the size of files that can be uploaded, which allows remote authenticated users to upload arbitrarily large files to the system's temp folder by modifying the `maxFileSize` parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-26265|2024-10-02T15:35:51.464Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 12:51:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25144|2024-10-02T15:31:02.494Z -- liferay -- portal
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25144</link>
      <description>The IFrame widget in Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.3.26, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.4 before update 27, 7.3 before update 6, 7.2 before fix pack 19, and older unsupported versions does not check the URL of the IFrame, which allows remote authenticated users to cause a denial-of-service (DoS) via a self referencing IFrame.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25144|2024-10-02T15:31:02.494Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 03:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3426|2024-10-02T15:24:59.097Z -- liferay -- dxp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3426</link>
      <description>The organization selector in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.81 through 7.4.3.85, and Liferay DXP 7.4 update 81 through 85 does not check user permission, which allows remote authenticated users to obtain a list of all organizations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3426|2024-10-02T15:24:59.097Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 09:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25148|2024-10-02T15:34:33.761Z -- liferay -- portal
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25148</link>
      <description>In Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.4.1, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack 15, and older unsupported versions the `doAsUserId` URL parameter may get leaked when creating linked content using the WYSIWYG editor and while impersonating a user. This may allow remote authenticated users to impersonate a user after accessing the linked content.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25148|2024-10-02T15:34:33.761Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 03:43:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25143|2024-10-02T15:29:27.818Z -- liferay -- dxp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25143</link>
      <description>The Document and Media widget In Liferay Portal 7.2.0 through 7.3.6, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 7.3 before service pack 3, 7.2 before fix pack 13, and older unsupported versions, does not limit resource consumption when generating a preview image, which allows remote authenticated users to cause a denial of service (memory consumption) via crafted PNG images.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25143|2024-10-02T15:29:27.818Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 14:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
