<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Axiomatic -- Bento4</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/axiomatic/bento4.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Axiomatic -- Bento4</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 01:42:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3668|2024-08-03T01:14:03.307Z -- axiomatic -- bento4
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3668</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Axiomatic Bento4 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function AP4_AtomFactory::CreateAtomFromStream of the component mp4edit. The manipulation leads to memory leak. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-212008.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3668|2024-08-03T01:14:03.307Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3817|2024-08-03T01:20:58.562Z -- axiomatic -- bento4
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3817</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Axiomatic Bento4 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component mp4mux. The manipulation leads to memory leak. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-212683.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3817|2024-08-03T01:20:58.562Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3663|2024-08-03T01:14:03.213Z -- axiomatic -- bento4
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3663</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Axiomatic Bento4. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects the function AP4_StsdAtom of the file Ap4StsdAtom.cpp of the component MP4fragment. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-212003.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3663|2024-08-03T01:14:03.213Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3784|2024-08-03T01:20:58.219Z -- axiomatic -- bento4
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3784</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Axiomatic Bento4 5e7bb34. Affected by this vulnerability is the function AP4_Mp4AudioDsiParser::ReadBits of the file Ap4Mp4AudioInfo.cpp of the component mp4hls. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-212563.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3784|2024-08-03T01:20:58.219Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3809|2024-08-03T01:20:58.412Z -- axiomatic -- bento4
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3809</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Axiomatic Bento4 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function ParseCommandLine of the file Mp4Tag/Mp4Tag.cpp of the component mp4tag. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-212666 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3809|2024-08-03T01:20:58.412Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3662|2024-08-03T01:14:03.292Z -- axiomatic -- bento4
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3662</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Axiomatic Bento4. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function GetOffset of the file Ap4Sample.h of the component mp42hls. The manipulation leads to use after free. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-212002 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3662|2024-08-03T01:14:03.292Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3665|2024-08-03T01:14:03.299Z -- axiomatic -- bento4
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3665</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Axiomatic Bento4. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file AvcInfo.cpp of the component avcinfo. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-212005 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3665|2024-08-03T01:14:03.299Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3670|2024-08-03T01:14:03.242Z -- axiomatic -- bento4
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3670</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Axiomatic Bento4. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function WriteSample of the component mp42hevc. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-212010 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3670|2024-08-03T01:14:03.242Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3785|2024-08-03T01:20:58.346Z -- axiomatic -- bento4
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3785</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Axiomatic Bento4. Affected by this issue is the function AP4_DataBuffer::SetDataSize of the component Avcinfo. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-212564.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3785|2024-08-03T01:20:58.346Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3814|2024-08-03T01:20:58.383Z -- axiomatic -- bento4
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3814</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Axiomatic Bento4. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component mp4decrypt. The manipulation leads to memory leak. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-212680.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3814|2024-08-03T01:20:58.383Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3816|2024-08-03T01:20:58.324Z -- axiomatic -- bento4
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3816</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Axiomatic Bento4. Affected is an unknown function of the component mp4decrypt. The manipulation leads to memory leak. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-212682 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3816|2024-08-03T01:20:58.324Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3666|2024-08-03T01:14:03.242Z -- axiomatic -- bento4
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3666</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Axiomatic Bento4. Affected by this issue is the function AP4_LinearReader::Advance of the file Ap4LinearReader.cpp of the component mp42ts. The manipulation leads to use after free. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-212006 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3666|2024-08-03T01:14:03.242Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3664|2024-08-03T01:14:03.297Z -- axiomatic -- bento4
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3664</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Axiomatic Bento4. Affected is the function AP4_BitStream::WriteBytes of the file Ap4BitStream.cpp of the component avcinfo. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-212004.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3664|2024-08-03T01:14:03.297Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3812|2024-08-03T01:20:58.336Z -- axiomatic -- bento4
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3812</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Axiomatic Bento4. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function AP4_ContainerAtom::AP4_ContainerAtom of the component mp4encrypt. The manipulation leads to memory leak. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-212678 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3812|2024-08-03T01:20:58.336Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3974|2024-08-03T01:27:53.928Z -- axiomatic -- bento4
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3974</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Axiomatic Bento4. Affected by this vulnerability is the function AP4_StdcFileByteStream::ReadPartial of the file Ap4StdCFileByteStream.cpp of the component mp4info. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-213553 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3974|2024-08-03T01:27:53.928Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3813|2024-08-03T01:20:58.490Z -- axiomatic -- bento4
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3813</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Axiomatic Bento4. This affects an unknown part of the component mp4edit. The manipulation leads to memory leak. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-212679.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3813|2024-08-03T01:20:58.490Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3815|2024-08-03T01:20:58.475Z -- axiomatic -- bento4
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3815</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Axiomatic Bento4. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component mp4decrypt. The manipulation leads to memory leak. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-212681 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3815|2024-08-03T01:20:58.475Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3669|2024-08-03T01:14:03.220Z -- axiomatic -- bento4
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3669</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Axiomatic Bento4 and classified as problematic. This issue affects the function AP4_AvccAtom::Create of the component mp4edit. The manipulation leads to memory leak. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-212009 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3669|2024-08-03T01:14:03.220Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3810|2024-08-03T01:20:58.312Z -- axiomatic -- bento4
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3810</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Axiomatic Bento4. It has been classified as problematic. This affects the function AP4_File::AP4_File of the file Mp42Hevc.cpp of the component mp42hevc. The manipulation leads to denial of service. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-212667.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3810|2024-08-03T01:20:58.312Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3667|2024-08-03T01:14:03.343Z -- axiomatic -- bento4
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3667</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Axiomatic Bento4. This affects the function AP4_MemoryByteStream::WritePartial of the file Ap4ByteStream.cpp of the component mp42aac. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-212007.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3667|2024-08-03T01:14:03.343Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3807|2024-08-03T01:20:58.428Z -- axiomatic -- bento4
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3807</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Axiomatic Bento4. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Incomplete Fix CVE-2019-13238. The manipulation leads to resource consumption. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-212660.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3807|2024-08-03T01:20:58.428Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
