<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for openhab -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/openhab/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for openhab -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 18:24:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-42467|2024-08-12T17:34:04.341Z -- openhab -- openhab-webui
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42467</link>
      <description>openHAB, a provider of open-source home automation software, has add-ons including the visualization add-on CometVisu. Prior to version 4.2.1, the proxy endpoint of openHAB's CometVisu add-on can be accessed without authentication. This proxy-feature can be exploited as Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) to induce GET HTTP requests to internal-only servers, in case openHAB is exposed in a non-private network. Furthermore, this proxy-feature can also be exploited as a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability, as an attacker is able to re-route a request to their server and return a page with malicious JavaScript code. Since the browser receives this data directly from the openHAB CometVisu UI, this JavaScript code will be executed with the origin of the CometVisu UI. This allows an attacker to exploit call endpoints on an openHAB server even if the openHAB server is located in a private network. (e.g. by sending an openHAB admin a link that proxies malicious JavaScript.) This issue may lead up to Remote Code Execution (RCE) when chained with other vulnerabilities. Users should upgrade to version 4.2.1 of the CometVisu add-on of openHAB to receive a patch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-42467|2024-08-12T17:34:04.341Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 18:06:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-42469|2024-08-09T18:32:18.245Z -- openhab -- openhab-webui</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42469</link>
      <description>openHAB, a provider of open-source home automation software, has add-ons including the visualization add-on CometVisu. Prior to version 4.2.1, CometVisu's file system endpoints don't require authentication and additionally the endpoint to update an existing file is susceptible to path traversal. This makes it possible for an attacker to overwrite existing files on the openHAB instance. If the overwritten file is a shell script that is executed at a later time, this vulnerability can allow remote code execution by an attacker. Users should upgrade to version 4.2.1 to receive a patch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-42469|2024-08-09T18:32:18.245Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 18:12:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-42468|2024-08-09T18:10:20.660Z -- openhab -- openhab-webui</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42468</link>
      <description>openHAB, a provider of open-source home automation software, has add-ons including the visualization add-on CometVisu. CometVisuServlet in versions prior to 4.2.1 is susceptible to an unauthenticated path traversal vulnerability. Local files on the server can be requested via HTTP GET on the CometVisuServlet. This issue may lead to information disclosure. Users should upgrade to version 4.2.1 of the CometVisu add-on of openHAB to receive a patch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-42468|2024-08-09T18:10:20.660Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 18:10:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-42470|2024-08-09T18:02:12.061Z -- openhab -- openhab-webui</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42470</link>
      <description>openHAB, a provider of open-source home automation software, has add-ons including the visualization add-on CometVisu. Several endpoints in versions prior to 4.2.1 of the CometVisu add-on of openHAB don't require authentication. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify or to steal sensitive data. This issue may lead to sensitive information disclosure. Users should upgrade to version 4.2.1 of the CometVisu add-on of openHAB to receive a patch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-42470|2024-08-09T18:02:12.061Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 18:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-42467|2024-08-09T18:06:34.059Z -- openhab -- openhab-webui</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42467</link>
      <description>openHAB, a provider of open-source home automation software, has add-ons including the visualization add-on CometVisu. Prior to version 4.2.1, the proxy endpoint of openHAB's CometVisu add-on can be accessed without authentication. This proxy-feature can be exploited as Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) to induce GET HTTP requests to internal-only servers, in case openHAB is exposed in a non-private network. Furthermore, this proxy-feature can also be exploited as a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability, as an attacker is able to re-route a request to their server and return a page with malicious JavaScript code. Since the browser receives this data directly from the openHAB CometVisu UI, this JavaScript code will be executed with the origin of the CometVisu UI. This allows an attacker to exploit call endpoints on an openHAB server even if the openHAB server is located in a private network. (e.g. by sending an openHAB admin a link that proxies malicious JavaScript.) This issue may lead up to Remote Code Execution (RCE) when chained with other vulnerabilities. Users should upgrade to version 4.2.1 of the CometVisu add-on of openHAB to receive a patch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-42467|2024-08-09T18:06:34.059Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 18:06:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-42470|2024-08-09T21:32:13.351Z -- openhab -- openhab-webui</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42470</link>
      <description>openHAB, a provider of open-source home automation software, has add-ons including the visualization add-on CometVisu. Several endpoints in versions prior to 4.2.1 of the CometVisu add-on of openHAB don't require authentication. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify or to steal sensitive data. This issue may lead to sensitive information disclosure. Users should upgrade to version 4.2.1 of the CometVisu add-on of openHAB to receive a patch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-42470|2024-08-09T21:32:13.351Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 18:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
