<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for bareos -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/bareos/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for bareos -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 23:23:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24755|2024-08-03T04:20:50.122Z -- bareos -- bareos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24755</link>
      <description>Bareos is open source software for backup, archiving, and recovery of data for operating systems. When Bareos Director &gt;= 18.2 &gt;= 18.2 but prior to 21.1.0, 20.0.6, and 19.2.12 is built and configured for PAM authentication, it will skip authorization checks completely. Expired accounts and accounts with expired passwords can still login. This problem will affect users that have PAM enabled. Currently there is no authorization (e.g. check for expired or disabled accounts), but only plain authentication (i.e. check if username and password match). Bareos Director versions 21.1.0, 20.0.6 and 19.2.12 implement the authorization check that was previously missing. The only workaround is to make sure that authentication fails if the user is not authorized.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24755|2024-08-03T04:20:50.122Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 14:35:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24756|2024-08-03T04:20:50.456Z -- bareos -- bareos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24756</link>
      <description>Bareos is open source software for backup, archiving, and recovery of data for operating systems. When Bareos Director &gt;= 18.2 but prior to 21.1.0, 20.0.6, and 19.2.12 is built and configured for PAM authentication, a failed PAM authentication will leak a small amount of memory. An attacker that is able to use the PAM Console (i.e. by knowing the shared secret or via the WebUI) can flood the Director with failing login attempts which will eventually lead to an out-of-memory condition in which the Director will not work anymore. Bareos Director versions 21.1.0, 20.0.6 and 19.2.12 contain a Bugfix for this problem. Users who are unable to upgrade may disable PAM authentication as a workaround.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24756|2024-08-03T04:20:50.456Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 14:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
