<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Google LLC -- Asylo</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/google%20llc/asylo.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Google LLC -- Asylo</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 19:19:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8938|2024-08-04T10:12:11.012Z -- google%20llc -- asylo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8938</link>
      <description>An arbitrary memory overwrite vulnerability in Asylo versions up to 0.6.0 allows an attacker to make a host call to FromkLinuxSockAddr with attacker controlled content and size of klinux_addr which allows an attacker to write memory values from within the enclave. We recommend upgrading past commit a37fb6a0e7daf30134dbbf357c9a518a1026aa02</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8938|2024-08-04T10:12:11.012Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 14:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8943|2024-08-04T10:12:11.017Z -- google%20llc -- asylo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8943</link>
      <description>An arbitrary memory read vulnerability in Asylo versions up to 0.6.0 allows an untrusted attacker to make a call to enc_untrusted_recvfrom whose return size was not validated against the requested size. The parameter size is unchecked allowing the attacker to read memory locations outside of the intended buffer size including memory addresses within the secure enclave. We recommend upgrading past commit 6e158d558abd3c29a0208e30c97c9a8c5bd4230f</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8943|2024-08-04T10:12:11.017Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 14:55:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8941|2024-08-04T10:12:10.981Z -- google%20llc -- asylo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8941</link>
      <description>An arbitrary memory read vulnerability in Asylo versions up to 0.6.0 allows an untrusted attacker to make a call to enc_untrusted_inet_pton using an attacker controlled klinux_addr_buffer parameter. The parameter size is unchecked allowing the attacker to read memory locations outside of the intended buffer size including memory addresses within the secure enclave. We recommend upgrading past commit 8fed5e334131abaf9c5e17307642fbf6ce4a57ec</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8941|2024-08-04T10:12:10.981Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 14:55:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8940|2024-08-04T10:12:10.977Z -- google%20llc -- asylo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8940</link>
      <description>An arbitrary memory read vulnerability in Asylo versions up to 0.6.0 allows an untrusted attacker to make a call to enc_untrusted_recvmsg using an attacker controlled result parameter. The parameter size is unchecked allowing the attacker to read memory locations outside of the intended buffer size including memory addresses within the secure enclave. We recommend upgrading or past commit fa6485c5d16a7355eab047d4a44345a73bc9131e</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8940|2024-08-04T10:12:10.977Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 14:55:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8944|2024-08-04T10:12:10.992Z -- google%20llc -- asylo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8944</link>
      <description>An arbitrary memory write vulnerability in Asylo versions up to 0.6.0 allows an untrusted attacker to make a call to ecall_restore using the attribute output which fails to check the range of a pointer. An attacker can use this pointer to write to arbitrary memory addresses including those within the secure enclave We recommend upgrading past commit 382da2b8b09cbf928668a2445efb778f76bd9c8a</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8944|2024-08-04T10:12:10.992Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 14:55:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8905|2024-08-04T10:12:11.061Z -- google%20llc -- asylo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8905</link>
      <description>A buffer length validation vulnerability in Asylo versions prior to 0.6.0 allows an attacker to read data they should not have access to. The 'enc_untrusted_recvfrom' function generates a return value which is deserialized by 'MessageReader', and copied into three different 'extents'. The length of the third 'extents' is controlled by the outside world, and not verified on copy, allowing the attacker to force Asylo to copy trusted memory data into an untrusted buffer of significantly small length.. We recommend updating Asylo to version 0.6.0 or later.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8905|2024-08-04T10:12:11.061Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8935|2024-08-04T10:12:11.011Z -- google%20llc -- asylo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8935</link>
      <description>An arbitrary memory overwrite vulnerability in Asylo versions up to 0.6.0 allow an attacker to make an Ecall_restore function call to reallocate untrusted code and overwrite sections of the Enclave memory address. We recommend updating your library.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8935|2024-08-04T10:12:11.011Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 14:55:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8904|2024-08-04T10:12:11.014Z -- google%20llc -- asylo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8904</link>
      <description>An arbitrary memory overwrite vulnerability in the trusted memory of Asylo exists in versions prior to 0.6.0. As the ecall_restore function fails to validate the range of the output_len pointer, an attacker can manipulate the tmp_output_len value and write to an arbitrary location in the trusted (enclave) memory. We recommend updating Asylo to version 0.6.0 or later.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8904|2024-08-04T10:12:11.014Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8936|2024-08-04T10:12:11.009Z -- google%20llc -- asylo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8936</link>
      <description>An arbitrary memory overwrite vulnerability in Asylo versions up to 0.6.0 allows an attacker to make a host call to UntrustedCall. UntrustedCall failed to validate the buffer range within sgx_params and allowed the host to return a pointer that was an address within the enclave memory. This allowed an attacker to read memory values from within the enclave.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8936|2024-08-04T10:12:11.009Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 14:55:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8942|2024-08-04T10:12:11.000Z -- google%20llc -- asylo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8942</link>
      <description>An arbitrary memory read vulnerability in Asylo versions up to 0.6.0 allows an untrusted attacker to make a call to enc_untrusted_read whose return size was not validated against the requrested size. The parameter size is unchecked allowing the attacker to read memory locations outside of the intended buffer size including memory addresses within the secure enclave. We recommend upgrading past commit b1d120a2c7d7446d2cc58d517e20a1b184b82200</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8942|2024-08-04T10:12:11.000Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 14:55:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8937|2024-08-04T10:12:11.093Z -- google%20llc -- asylo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8937</link>
      <description>An arbitrary memory overwrite vulnerability in Asylo versions up to 0.6.0 allows an attacker to make a host call to enc_untrusted_create_wait_queue that uses a pointer queue that relies on UntrustedLocalMemcpy, which fails to validate where the pointer is located. This allows an attacker to write memory values from within the enclave. We recommend upgrading past commit a37fb6a0e7daf30134dbbf357c9a518a1026aa02</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8937|2024-08-04T10:12:11.093Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 14:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8939|2024-08-04T10:12:11.010Z -- google%20llc -- asylo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8939</link>
      <description>An out of bounds read on the enc_untrusted_inet_ntop function allows an attack to extend the result size that is used by memcpy() to read memory from within the enclave heap. We recommend upgrading past commit 6ff3b77ffe110a33a2f93848a6333f33616f02c4</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8939|2024-08-04T10:12:11.010Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 14:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
