<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for ICEPAY -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/icepay/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for ICEPAY -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 05:22:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-15028|2024-08-06T03:47:34.929Z -- icepay -- rest-api-net
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-15028</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in ICEPAY REST-API-NET 0.9. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function RestClient of the file Classes/RestClient.cs of the component Checksum Validation. The manipulation leads to improper validation of integrity check value. The attack can be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. Upgrading to version 1.0 is able to address this issue. The patch is named 61f6b8758e5c971abff5f901cfa9f231052b775f. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-222847.
In ICEPAY REST-API-NET 0.9 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Betroffen ist die Funktion RestClient der Datei Classes/RestClient.cs der Komponente Checksum Validation. Durch das Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine improper validation of integrity check value-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Sie gilt als schwierig ausnutzbar. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 1.0 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als 61f6b8758e5c971abff5f901cfa9f231052b775f bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-15028|2024-08-06T03:47:34.929Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 14:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
