<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for Juanpao -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/juanpao/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for Juanpao -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 21:54:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-1258|2024-04-29T11:09:54.704Z -- Juanpao -- JPShop
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1258</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Juanpao JPShop up to 1.5.02. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file api/config/params.php of the component API. The manipulation of the argument JWT_KEY_ADMIN leads to use of hard-coded cryptographic key&#13; . The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252997 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In Juanpao JPShop bis 1.5.02 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei api/config/params.php der Komponente API. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments JWT_KEY_ADMIN mit unbekannten Daten kann eine use of hard-coded cryptographic key&#13; -Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Sie gilt als schwierig ausnutzbar. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1258|2024-04-29T11:09:54.704Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 20:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1262|2024-02-09T19:13:30.162Z -- Juanpao -- JPShop
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1262</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Juanpao JPShop up to 1.5.02. This issue affects the function actionUpdate of the file /api/controllers/merchant/design/MaterialController.php of the component API. The manipulation of the argument pic_url leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-253001 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Juanpao JPShop bis 1.5.02 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um die Funktion actionUpdate der Datei /api/controllers/merchant/design/MaterialController.php der Komponente API. Dank Manipulation des Arguments pic_url mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1262|2024-02-09T19:13:30.162Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 22:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1263|2024-02-09T19:13:59.496Z -- Juanpao -- JPShop
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1263</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Juanpao JPShop up to 1.5.02. Affected is the function actionUpdate of the file /api/controllers/merchant/shop/PosterController.php of the component API. The manipulation of the argument pic_url leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-253002 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Juanpao JPShop bis 1.5.02 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um die Funktion actionUpdate der Datei /api/controllers/merchant/shop/PosterController.php der Komponente API. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments pic_url mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1263|2024-02-09T19:13:59.496Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 23:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1259|2024-02-09T19:13:43.265Z -- Juanpao -- JPShop
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1259</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Juanpao JPShop up to 1.5.02. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /api/controllers/admin/app/AppController.php of the component API. The manipulation of the argument app_pic_url leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252998 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Juanpao JPShop bis 1.5.02 ausgemacht. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei /api/controllers/admin/app/AppController.php der Komponente API. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments app_pic_url mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1259|2024-02-09T19:13:43.265Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 21:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1264|2024-02-09T19:13:50.515Z -- Juanpao -- JPShop
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1264</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Juanpao JPShop up to 1.5.02 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function actionUpdate of the file /api/controllers/common/UploadsController.php. The manipulation of the argument imgage leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-253003.
In Juanpao JPShop bis 1.5.02 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei geht es um die Funktion actionUpdate der Datei /api/controllers/common/UploadsController.php. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments imgage mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1264|2024-02-09T19:13:50.515Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 23:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1260|2024-02-09T19:13:56.602Z -- Juanpao -- JPShop
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1260</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Juanpao JPShop up to 1.5.02. This affects the function actionIndex of the file /api/controllers/admin/app/ComboController.php of the component API. The manipulation of the argument pic_url leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252999.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Juanpao JPShop bis 1.5.02 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist die Funktion actionIndex der Datei /api/controllers/admin/app/ComboController.php der Komponente API. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments pic_url mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1260|2024-02-09T19:13:56.602Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 21:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1261|2024-02-09T19:13:34.281Z -- Juanpao -- JPShop
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1261</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Juanpao JPShop up to 1.5.02. This vulnerability affects the function actionIndex of the file /api/controllers/merchant/app/ComboController.php of the component API. The manipulation of the argument pic_url leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-253000.
In Juanpao JPShop bis 1.5.02 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht um die Funktion actionIndex der Datei /api/controllers/merchant/app/ComboController.php der Komponente API. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments pic_url mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1261|2024-02-09T19:13:34.281Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 22:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>