<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Juanpao -- JPShop</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/juanpao/jpshop.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Juanpao -- JPShop</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 22:23:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1258|2024-08-19T20:24:12.690Z -- juanpao -- jpshop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1258</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Juanpao JPShop up to 1.5.02. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file api/config/params.php of the component API. The manipulation of the argument JWT_KEY_ADMIN leads to use of hard-coded cryptographic key&#13; . The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252997 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In Juanpao JPShop bis 1.5.02 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei api/config/params.php der Komponente API. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments JWT_KEY_ADMIN mit unbekannten Daten kann eine use of hard-coded cryptographic key&#13; -Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Sie gilt als schwierig ausnutzbar. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1258|2024-08-19T20:24:12.690Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 20:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1263|2024-08-19T20:11:22.610Z -- juanpao -- jpshop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1263</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Juanpao JPShop up to 1.5.02. Affected is the function actionUpdate of the file /api/controllers/merchant/shop/PosterController.php of the component API. The manipulation of the argument pic_url leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-253002 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Juanpao JPShop bis 1.5.02 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um die Funktion actionUpdate der Datei /api/controllers/merchant/shop/PosterController.php der Komponente API. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments pic_url mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1263|2024-08-19T20:11:22.610Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 23:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
