<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for tj-actions -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tj-actions/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for tj-actions -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-49291|2023-12-04T23:21:33.367Z -- tj-actions -- branch-names
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-49291</link>
      <description>tj-actions/branch-names is a Github action to retrieve branch or tag names with support for all events. The `tj-actions/branch-names` GitHub Actions improperly references the `github.event.pull_request.head.ref` and `github.head_ref` context variables within a GitHub Actions `run` step. The head ref variable is the branch name and can be used to execute arbitrary code using a specially crafted branch name. As a result an attacker can use this vulnerability to steal secrets from or abuse `GITHUB_TOKEN` permissions. This vulnerability has been addressed in version 7.0.7. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-49291|2023-12-04T23:21:33.367Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 23:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-52137|2023-12-29T17:08:49.356Z -- tj-actions -- verify-changed-files
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-52137</link>
      <description>The [`tj-actions/verify-changed-files`](https://github.com/tj-actions/verify-changed-files) action allows for command injection in changed filenames, allowing an attacker to execute arbitrary code and potentially leak secrets. The [`verify-changed-files`](https://github.com/tj-actions/verify-changed-files) workflow returns the list of files changed within a workflow execution. This could potentially allow filenames that contain special characters such as `;` which can be used by an attacker to take over the [GitHub Runner](https://docs.github.com/en/actions/using-github-hosted-runners/about-github-hosted-runners) if the output value is used in a raw fashion (thus being directly replaced before execution) inside a `run` block. By running custom commands, an attacker may be able to steal secrets such as `GITHUB_TOKEN` if triggered on other events than `pull_request`.

This has been patched in versions [17](https://github.com/tj-actions/verify-changed-files/releases/tag/v17) and [17.0.0](https://github.com/tj-actions/verify-changed-files/releases/tag/v17.0.0) by enabling `safe_output` by default and returning filename paths escaping special characters for bash environments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-52137|2023-12-29T17:08:49.356Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 17:08:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51664|2023-12-27T16:58:31.908Z -- tj-actions -- changed-files
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51664</link>
      <description>tj-actions/changed-files is a Github action to retrieve all files and directories. Prior to 41.0.0, the `tj-actions/changed-files` workflow allows for command injection in changed filenames, allowing an attacker to execute arbitrary code and potentially leak secrets. This issue may lead to arbitrary command execution in the GitHub Runner. This vulnerability has been addressed in version 41.0.0. Users are advised to upgrade.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51664|2023-12-27T16:58:31.908Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 16:58:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
