<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for wclovers -- WCFM – Frontend Manager for WooCommerce along with Bookings Subscription Listings Compatible</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/wclovers/wcfm%20%E2%80%93%20frontend%20manager%20for%20woocommerce%20along%20with%20bookings%20subscription%20listings%20compatible.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for wclovers -- WCFM – Frontend Manager for WooCommerce along with Bookings Subscription Listings Compatible</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 13:22:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4937|2024-08-03T01:55:46.100Z -- wclovers -- wcfm%20%E2%80%93%20frontend%20manager%20for%20woocommerce%20along%20with%20bookings%20subscription%20listings%20compatible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4937</link>
      <description>The WCFM Frontend Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification and access of data in versions up to, and including, 6.6.0 due to missing capability checks on various AJAX actions. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with minimal permissions such as subscribers, to perform a wide variety of actions such as modifying knowledge bases, modifying notices, modifying payments, managing vendors, capabilities, and so much more. There were hundreds of AJAX endpoints affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4937|2024-08-03T01:55:46.100Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 17:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4938|2024-08-03T01:55:46.068Z -- wclovers -- wcfm%20%E2%80%93%20frontend%20manager%20for%20woocommerce%20along%20with%20bookings%20subscription%20listings%20compatible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4938</link>
      <description>The WCFM Frontend Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 6.6.0 due to missing nonce checks on various AJAX actions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to perform a wide variety of actions such as modifying knowledge bases, modifying notices, modifying payments, managing vendors, capabilities, and so much more, via a forged request granted they can trick a site's administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. There were hundreds of AJAX endpoints affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4938|2024-08-03T01:55:46.068Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 17:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
