<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for npm -- cli</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/npm/cli.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for npm -- cli</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 02:29:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-16777|2024-08-05T01:24:47.252Z -- npm -- cli
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-16777</link>
      <description>Versions of the npm CLI prior to 6.13.4 are vulnerable to an Arbitrary File Overwrite. It fails to prevent existing globally-installed binaries to be overwritten by other package installations. For example, if a package was installed globally and created a serve binary, any subsequent installs of packages that also create a serve binary would overwrite the previous serve binary. This behavior is still allowed in local installations and also through install scripts. This vulnerability bypasses a user using the --ignore-scripts install option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-16777|2024-08-05T01:24:47.252Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 01:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-16776|2024-08-05T01:24:48.040Z -- npm -- cli
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-16776</link>
      <description>Versions of the npm CLI prior to 6.13.3 are vulnerable to an Arbitrary File Write. It fails to prevent access to folders outside of the intended node_modules folder through the bin field. A properly constructed entry in the package.json bin field would allow a package publisher to modify and/or gain access to arbitrary files on a user's system when the package is installed. This behavior is still possible through install scripts. This vulnerability bypasses a user using the --ignore-scripts install option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-16776|2024-08-05T01:24:48.040Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 00:55:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-16775|2024-08-05T01:24:48.326Z -- npm -- cli
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-16775</link>
      <description>Versions of the npm CLI prior to 6.13.3 are vulnerable to an Arbitrary File Write. It is possible for packages to create symlinks to files outside of thenode_modules folder through the bin field upon installation. A properly constructed entry in the package.json bin field would allow a package publisher to create a symlink pointing to arbitrary files on a user's system when the package is installed. This behavior is still possible through install scripts. This vulnerability bypasses a user using the --ignore-scripts install option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-16775|2024-08-05T01:24:48.326Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 00:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
