<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for hu60t -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/hu60t/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for hu60t -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 23:22:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5835|2024-08-02T08:14:24.270Z -- hu60t -- hu60wap6
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5835</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in hu60t hu60wap6. Affected by this vulnerability is the function markdown of the file src/class/ubbparser.php. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The patch is named a1cd9f12d7687243bfcb7ce295665acb83b9174e. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-243775.
In hu60t hu60wap6 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Es geht um die Funktion markdown der Datei src/class/ubbparser.php. Durch Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Dieses Produkt setzt Rolling Releases ein. Aus diesem Grund sind Details zu betroffenen oder zu aktualisierende Versionen nicht verfügbar. Der Patch wird als a1cd9f12d7687243bfcb7ce295665acb83b9174e bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5835|2024-08-02T08:14:24.270Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 13:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
