<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for weaveworks -- vscode-gitops-tools</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/weaveworks/vscode-gitops-tools.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for weaveworks -- vscode-gitops-tools</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 12:25:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-35976|2024-08-03T09:51:59.661Z -- weaveworks -- vscode-gitops-tools
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-35976</link>
      <description>The GitOps Tools Extension for VSCode relies on kubeconfigs in order to communicate with Kubernetes clusters. A specially crafted kubeconfig leads to arbitrary code execution on behalf of the user running VSCode. Users relying on kubeconfigs that are generated or altered by other processes or users are affected by this issue. Please note that the vulnerability is specific to this extension, and the same kubeconfig would not result in arbitrary code execution when used with kubectl. Using only trust-worthy kubeconfigs is a safe mitigation. However, updating to the latest version of the extension is still highly recommended.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-35976|2024-08-03T09:51:59.661Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 18:50:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-35975|2024-08-03T09:51:59.831Z -- weaveworks -- vscode-gitops-tools
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-35975</link>
      <description>The GitOps Tools Extension for VSCode can make it easier to manage Flux objects. A specially crafted Flux object may allow for remote code execution in the machine running the extension, in the context of the user that is running VSCode. Users using the VSCode extension to manage clusters that are shared amongst other users are affected by this issue. The only safe mitigation is to update to the latest version of the extension.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-35975|2024-08-03T09:51:59.831Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 17:55:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
