<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for WSO2 -- carbon-registry</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/wso2/carbon-registry.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for WSO2 -- carbon-registry</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 15:23:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4520|2024-08-03T01:41:45.634Z -- wso2 -- carbon-registry
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4520</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in WSO2 carbon-registry up to 4.8.11. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file components/registry/org.wso2.carbon.registry.search.ui/src/main/resources/web/search/advancedSearchForm-ajaxprocessor.jsp of the component Advanced Search. The manipulation of the argument mediaType/rightOp/leftOp/rightPropertyValue/leftPropertyValue leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 4.8.12 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is 0c827cc1b14b82d8eb86117ab2e43c34bb91ddb4. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-215900.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4520|2024-08-03T01:41:45.634Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4521|2024-08-03T01:41:45.620Z -- wso2 -- carbon-registry
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4521</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in WSO2 carbon-registry up to 4.8.6. This affects an unknown part of the component Request Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument parentPath/path/username/path/profile_menu leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 4.8.7 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is 9f967abfde9317bee2cda469dbc09b57d539f2cc. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-215901 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in WSO2 carbon-registry bis 4.8.6 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Komponente Request Parameter Handler. Durch Manipulation des Arguments parentPath/path/username/path/profile_menu mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 4.8.7 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als 9f967abfde9317bee2cda469dbc09b57d539f2cc bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4521|2024-08-03T01:41:45.620Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
