<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for nocodb -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/nocodb/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for nocodb -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 20:23:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5104|2024-08-02T07:44:53.785Z -- nocodb -- nocodb%2Fnocodb
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5104</link>
      <description>Improper Input Validation in GitHub repository nocodb/nocodb prior to 0.96.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5104|2024-08-02T07:44:53.785Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 08:44:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43794|2024-08-02T19:52:11.128Z -- nocodb -- nocodb
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43794</link>
      <description>Nocodb is an open source Airtable alternative. Affected versions of nocodb contain a SQL injection vulnerability, that allows an authenticated attacker with creator access to query the underlying database. By supplying a specially crafted payload to the given an attacker can inject arbitrary SQL queries to be executed. Since this is a blind SQL injection, an attacker may need to use time-based payloads which would include a function to delay execution for a given number of seconds. The response time indicates, whether the result of the query execution was true or false. Depending on the result, the HTTP response will be returned after a given number of seconds, indicating TRUE, or immediately, indicating FALSE. In that way, an attacker can reveal the data present in the database. This vulnerability has been addressed in version 0.111.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability. This issue is also tracked as `GHSL-2023-141`.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43794|2024-08-02T19:52:11.128Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 20:02:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50718|2024-05-13T16:08:09.198Z -- nocodb -- nocodb</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50718</link>
      <description>NocoDB is software for building databases as spreadsheets. Prior to version 0.202.10, an authenticated attacker with create access could conduct a SQL Injection attack on MySQL DB using unescaped `table_name`. This vulnerability may result in leakage of sensitive data in the database. Version 0.202.10 contains a patch for the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50718|2024-05-13T16:08:09.198Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 16:08:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50717|2024-06-04T17:17:55.790Z -- nocodb -- nocodb</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50717</link>
      <description>NocoDB is software for building databases as spreadsheets. Starting in verson 0.202.6 and prior to version 0.202.10, an attacker can upload a html file with malicious content. If user tries to open that file in browser malicious scripts can be executed leading  stored cross-site scripting attack. This allows remote attacker to execute JavaScript code in the context of the user accessing the vector. An attacker could have used this vulnerability to execute requests in the name of a logged-in user or potentially collect information about the attacked user by displaying a malicious form. Version 0.202.10 contains a patch for the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50717|2024-06-04T17:17:55.790Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 16:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-49781|2024-06-04T17:27:51.204Z -- nocodb -- nocodb</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-49781</link>
      <description>NocoDB is software for building databases as spreadsheets. Prior to 0.202.9, a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists within the Formula virtual cell comments functionality. The nc-gui/components/virtual-cell/Formula.vue displays a v-html tag with the value of "urls" whose contents are processed by the function replaceUrlsWithLink(). This function recognizes the pattern URI::(XXX) and creates a hyperlink tag &lt;a&gt; with href=XXX. However, it leaves all the other contents outside of the pattern URI::(XXX) unchanged. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.202.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-49781|2024-06-04T17:27:51.204Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 18:54:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
