<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for vova07 -- Yii2 FileAPI Widget</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/vova07/yii2%20fileapi%20widget.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for vova07 -- Yii2 FileAPI Widget</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:23:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20158|2024-08-05T21:45:25.988Z -- vova07 -- yii2%20fileapi%20widget
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20158</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in vova07 Yii2 FileAPI Widget up to 0.1.8. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function run of the file actions/UploadAction.php. The manipulation of the argument file leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 0.1.9 is able to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is c00d1e4fc912257fca1fce66d7a163bdbb4c8222. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-217141 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.
In vova07 Yii2 FileAPI Widget bis 0.1.8 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Das betrifft die Funktion run der Datei actions/UploadAction.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments file mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 0.1.9 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als c00d1e4fc912257fca1fce66d7a163bdbb4c8222 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20158|2024-08-05T21:45:25.988Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 10:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
