<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for boldthemes -- Bold Page Builder</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/boldthemes/bold%20page%20builder.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for boldthemes -- Bold Page Builder</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 21:24:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-1157|2024-02-13T09:31:27.725Z -- boldthemes -- Bold Page Builder
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1157</link><description>The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's button URL in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1157|2024-02-13T09:31:27.725Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:31:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1160|2024-02-13T09:31:27.103Z -- boldthemes -- Bold Page Builder
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1160</link><description>The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Icon Link in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1160|2024-02-13T09:31:27.103Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:31:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1159|2024-02-13T09:31:28.196Z -- boldthemes -- Bold Page Builder
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1159</link><description>The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1159|2024-02-13T09:31:28.196Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:31:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30442|2024-03-29T17:13:12.845Z -- BoldThemes -- Bold Page Builder
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30442</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in BoldThemes Bold Page Builder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Bold Page Builder: from n/a through 4.8.0.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30442|2024-03-29T17:13:12.845Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 17:13:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30179|2024-03-27T11:25:24.532Z -- BoldThemes -- Bold Page Builder
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30179</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in BoldThemes Bold Page Builder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Bold Page Builder: from n/a through 4.7.6.

</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30179|2024-03-27T11:25:24.532Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 11:25:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3267|2024-04-09T18:59:32.395Z -- boldthemes -- Bold Page Builder
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3267</link><description>The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's bt_bb_price_list shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3267|2024-04-09T18:59:32.395Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:59:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3266|2024-04-09T18:58:38.187Z -- boldthemes -- Bold Page Builder
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3266</link><description>The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the URL attribute of widgets in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3266|2024-04-09T18:58:38.187Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:58:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2736|2024-04-10T04:30:20.195Z -- boldthemes -- Bold Page Builder
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2736</link><description>The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via HTML Tags in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2736|2024-04-10T04:30:20.195Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 04:30:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2734|2024-04-10T04:30:19.296Z -- boldthemes -- Bold Page Builder
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2734</link><description>The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's AI features all versions up to, and including, 4.8.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2734|2024-04-10T04:30:19.296Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 04:30:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2735|2024-04-10T04:30:19.748Z -- boldthemes -- Bold Page Builder
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2735</link><description>The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'Price List' element in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2735|2024-04-10T04:30:19.748Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 04:30:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2733|2024-04-10T03:31:20.853Z -- boldthemes -- Bold Page Builder
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2733</link><description>The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's "Separator" element in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2733|2024-04-10T03:31:20.853Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 03:31:20 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>