<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for PowerDNS -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/powerdns/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for PowerDNS -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 17:23:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-15093|2024-09-17T00:35:38.803Z -- powerdns -- powerdns%20recursor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-15093</link>
      <description>When api-config-dir is set to a non-empty value, which is not the case by default, the API in PowerDNS Recursor 4.x up to and including 4.0.6 and 3.x up to and including 3.7.4 allows an authorized user to update the Recursor's ACL by adding and removing netmasks, and to configure forward zones. It was discovered that the new netmask and IP addresses of forwarded zones were not sufficiently validated, allowing an authenticated user to inject new configuration directives into the Recursor's configuration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-15093|2024-09-17T00:35:38.803Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-15092|2024-09-17T03:27:42.169Z -- powerdns -- powerdns%20recursor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-15092</link>
      <description>A cross-site scripting issue has been found in the web interface of PowerDNS Recursor from 4.0.0 up to and including 4.0.6, where the qname of DNS queries was displayed without any escaping, allowing a remote attacker to inject HTML and Javascript code into the web interface, altering the content.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-15092|2024-09-17T03:27:42.169Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25583|2024-06-04T17:35:23.421Z -- powerdns -- recursor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25583</link>
      <description>A crafted response from an upstream server the recursor has been configured to forward-recurse to can cause a Denial of Service in the Recursor. The default configuration of the Recursor does not use recursive forwarding and is not affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25583|2024-06-04T17:35:23.421Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 09:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25581|2024-05-13T11:49:24.500Z -- powerdns -- dnsdist</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25581</link>
      <description>When incoming DNS over HTTPS support is enabled using the nghttp2 provider, and queries are routed to a tcp-only or DNS over TLS backend, an attacker can trigger an assertion failure in DNSdist by sending a request for a zone transfer (AXFR or IXFR) over DNS over HTTPS, causing the process to stop and thus leading to a Denial of Service. DNS over HTTPS is not enabled by default, and backends are using plain DNS (Do53) by default.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25581|2024-05-13T11:49:24.500Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 11:49:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
