<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Kofax -- Power PDF</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/kofax/power%20pdf.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Kofax -- Power PDF</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 02:28:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30373|2024-08-02T01:32:07.224Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30373</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF JPF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22092.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30373|2024-08-02T01:32:07.224Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:20:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5306|2024-08-01T21:11:11.638Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5306</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22930.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5306|2024-08-01T21:11:11.638Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:18:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5302|2024-08-01T21:11:12.458Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5302</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22918.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5302|2024-08-01T21:11:12.458Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:54:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5307|2024-08-01T21:11:12.411Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5307</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF AcroForm Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22933.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5307|2024-08-01T21:11:12.411Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:19:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5301|2024-08-01T21:11:11.015Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5301</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PSD File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PSD files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22917.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5301|2024-08-01T21:11:11.015Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:54:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5303|2024-08-01T21:11:12.434Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5303</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PSD File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PSD files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22919.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5303|2024-08-01T21:11:12.434Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:03:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5304|2024-08-01T21:11:12.312Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5304</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF TGA File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of TGA files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22920.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5304|2024-08-01T21:11:12.312Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5305|2024-08-01T21:11:12.084Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5305</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22921.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5305|2024-08-01T21:11:12.084Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27343|2024-07-29T13:50:45.159Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27343</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22929.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27343|2024-07-29T13:50:45.159Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51606|2024-07-23T17:12:27.767Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51606</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.
. Was ZDI-CAN-21759.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51606|2024-07-23T17:12:27.767Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37359|2024-07-23T17:17:04.413Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37359</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20470.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37359|2024-07-23T17:17:04.413Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37352|2024-07-23T17:15:08.615Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37352</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF JPG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPG files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20454.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37352|2024-07-23T17:15:08.615Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37355|2024-07-23T17:14:00.193Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37355</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF JPG File Parsing Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPG files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20460.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37355|2024-07-23T17:14:00.193Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38078|2024-07-23T17:16:05.419Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38078</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF U3D File Parsing Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20472.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38078|2024-07-23T17:16:05.419Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38077|2024-07-23T17:16:33.525Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38077</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20471.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38077|2024-07-23T17:16:33.525Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37348|2024-07-23T17:15:29.748Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37348</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20445.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37348|2024-07-23T17:15:29.748Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37356|2024-07-23T17:14:37.795Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37356</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF GIF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of GIF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20461.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37356|2024-07-23T17:14:37.795Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37353|2024-07-23T17:17:31.014Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37353</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF JPG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPG files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20455.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37353|2024-07-23T17:17:31.014Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37351|2024-07-23T17:18:00.613Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37351</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20453.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37351|2024-07-23T17:18:00.613Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37358|2024-07-05T21:00:54.727Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37358</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20469.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37358|2024-07-05T21:00:54.727Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27340|2024-06-19T19:23:50.332Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27340</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22926.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27340|2024-06-19T19:23:50.332Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:18:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51607|2024-06-17T20:56:15.186Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51607</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PNG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PNG files.
The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21829.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51607|2024-06-17T20:56:15.186Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30373|2024-06-07T09:53:59.144Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-30373</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF JPF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22092.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30373|2024-06-07T09:53:59.144Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:20:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27346|2024-06-04T17:46:25.837Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27346</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22934.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27346|2024-06-04T17:46:25.837Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27340|2024-04-03T16:18:40.669Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27340</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22926.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27340|2024-04-03T16:18:40.669Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:18:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27337|2024-04-03T16:18:03.144Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27337</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF TIF File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of TIF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22033.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27337|2024-04-03T16:18:03.144Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27336|2024-06-04T17:46:53.756Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27336</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PNG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PNG files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22022.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27336|2024-06-04T17:46:53.756Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:17:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27341|2024-06-04T17:46:56.166Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27341</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22927.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27341|2024-06-04T17:46:56.166Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:18:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27342|2024-04-03T16:19:09.484Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27342</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22928.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27342|2024-04-03T16:19:09.484Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27339|2024-04-03T16:18:26.722Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27339</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22925.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27339|2024-04-03T16:18:26.722Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:18:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27335|2024-04-03T16:17:09.187Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27335</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PNG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of PNG files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22018.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27335|2024-04-03T16:17:09.187Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27334|2024-06-04T17:47:07.659Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27334</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF JPG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPG files.
The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21978.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27334|2024-06-04T17:47:07.659Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 23:11:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27338|2024-04-03T16:18:14.686Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27338</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF app response Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the app.response method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22588.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27338|2024-04-03T16:18:14.686Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27343|2024-04-03T16:19:25.276Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27343</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22929.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27343|2024-04-03T16:19:25.276Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27333|2024-06-04T17:47:18.417Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27333</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF GIF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of GIF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21976.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27333|2024-06-04T17:47:18.417Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 23:04:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27344|2024-04-03T16:19:35.249Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27344</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22931.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27344|2024-04-03T16:19:35.249Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27345|2024-04-03T16:19:45.349Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27345</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22932.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27345|2024-04-03T16:19:45.349Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5306|2024-06-07T09:54:40.017Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5306</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22930.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5306|2024-06-07T09:54:40.017Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:18:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5307|2024-06-06T20:30:54.823Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5307</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF AcroForm Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22933.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5307|2024-06-06T20:30:54.823Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:19:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5301|2024-06-07T09:56:32.060Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5301</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PSD File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PSD files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22917.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5301|2024-06-07T09:56:32.060Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:54:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5302|2024-06-07T09:56:17.225Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5302</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22918.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5302|2024-06-07T09:56:17.225Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:54:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5303|2024-06-06T20:39:29.624Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5303</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PSD File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PSD files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22919.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5303|2024-06-06T20:39:29.624Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:03:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5304|2024-06-07T09:55:37.998Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5304</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF TGA File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of TGA files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22920.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5304|2024-06-07T09:55:37.998Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5305|2024-06-06T20:36:31.598Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5305</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22921.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5305|2024-06-06T20:36:31.598Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44435|2024-06-06T12:35:13.322Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-44435</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22040.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44435|2024-06-06T12:35:13.322Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44434|2024-06-04T17:19:21.130Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-44434</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21979.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44434|2024-06-04T17:19:21.130Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44433|2024-06-06T12:34:31.717Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-44433</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF AcroForm Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21977.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44433|2024-06-06T12:34:31.717Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44432|2024-06-06T12:35:33.173Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-44432</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21584.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44432|2024-06-06T12:35:33.173Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44436|2024-06-06T12:35:55.674Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-44436</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22045.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44436|2024-06-06T12:35:55.674Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51569|2024-06-04T17:20:14.899Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51569</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF BMP File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of BMP files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22016.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51569|2024-06-04T17:20:14.899Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51565|2024-06-04T17:20:17.421Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51565</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF XPS File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of XPS files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21975.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51565|2024-06-04T17:20:17.421Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51564|2024-06-04T17:20:17.855Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51564</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files.
The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21606.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51564|2024-06-04T17:20:17.855Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51568|2024-06-05T14:48:02.105Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51568</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF OXPS File Parsing Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of OXPS files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21990.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51568|2024-06-05T14:48:02.105Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51563|2024-06-04T17:20:27.299Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51563</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF XPS File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of XPS files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20573.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51563|2024-06-04T17:20:27.299Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51607|2024-05-03T02:15:32.807Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51607</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PNG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PNG files.
The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21829.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51607|2024-05-03T02:15:32.807Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51611|2024-06-04T17:20:29.819Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51611</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF JP2 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JP2 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21836.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51611|2024-06-04T17:20:29.819Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51610|2024-06-04T17:20:31.018Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51610</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF JP2 File Parsing Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JP2 files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21835.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51610|2024-06-04T17:20:31.018Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51606|2024-05-09T22:21:07.721Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51606</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.
. Was ZDI-CAN-21759.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51606|2024-05-09T22:21:07.721Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51597|2024-06-04T17:20:31.854Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51597</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21755.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51597|2024-06-04T17:20:31.854Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51609|2024-06-04T17:20:37.182Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51609</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF JP2 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JP2 files.
The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21834.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51609|2024-06-04T17:20:37.182Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51612|2024-06-04T17:20:44.765Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51612</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF JP2 File Parsing Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JP2 files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21837.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51612|2024-06-04T17:20:44.765Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51608|2024-06-04T17:20:48.717Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51608</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF J2K File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of J2K files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21833.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51608|2024-06-04T17:20:48.717Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51567|2024-06-04T17:20:53.666Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51567</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF OXPS File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of OXPS files.
The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21988.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51567|2024-06-04T17:20:53.666Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51566|2024-06-04T17:20:57.979Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51566</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF OXPS File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of OXPS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21980.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51566|2024-06-04T17:20:57.979Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37341|2024-06-04T17:24:19.537Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37341</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PNG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PNG files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20397.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37341|2024-06-04T17:24:19.537Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37357|2024-05-03T01:58:42.112Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37357</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20468.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37357|2024-05-03T01:58:42.112Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37336|2024-06-04T17:24:20.385Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37336</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF TIF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of TIF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20392.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37336|2024-06-04T17:24:20.385Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37337|2024-06-04T17:24:22.053Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37337</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF JP2 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JP2 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20393.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37337|2024-06-04T17:24:22.053Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37356|2024-05-03T01:58:41.380Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37356</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF GIF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of GIF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20461.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37356|2024-05-03T01:58:41.380Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37340|2024-06-04T17:24:23.293Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37340</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PNG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PNG files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20396.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37340|2024-06-04T17:24:23.293Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37330|2024-06-04T17:24:24.545Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37330</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF exportAsText Exposed Dangerous Method Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the exportAsText method. The application exposes a JavaScript interface that allows the attacker to write arbitrary files. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-20230.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37330|2024-06-04T17:24:24.545Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37347|2024-06-04T17:24:25.813Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37347</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20444.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37347|2024-06-04T17:24:25.813Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37351|2024-05-03T01:58:37.629Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37351</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20453.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37351|2024-05-03T01:58:37.629Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37350|2024-06-04T17:24:26.649Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37350</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF TIF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of TIF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20452.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37350|2024-06-04T17:24:26.649Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37346|2024-06-04T17:24:27.064Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37346</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF TIF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of TIF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20443.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37346|2024-06-04T17:24:27.064Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37331|2024-06-04T17:24:28.287Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37331</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF GIF File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of GIF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20373.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37331|2024-06-04T17:24:28.287Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37349|2024-06-04T17:24:29.138Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37349</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20451.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37349|2024-06-04T17:24:29.138Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37332|2024-06-04T17:24:29.568Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37332</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PNG File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PNG files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20388.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37332|2024-06-04T17:24:29.568Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37353|2024-05-03T01:58:39.082Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37353</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF JPG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPG files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20455.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37353|2024-05-03T01:58:39.082Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37345|2024-06-04T17:24:30.454Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37345</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF J2K File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of J2K files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20442.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37345|2024-06-04T17:24:30.454Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37344|2024-06-04T17:24:32.936Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37344</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF BMP File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of BMP files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20441.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37344|2024-06-04T17:24:32.936Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37352|2024-05-03T01:58:38.340Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37352</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF JPG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPG files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20454.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37352|2024-05-03T01:58:38.340Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37333|2024-06-04T17:24:33.765Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37333</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PCX File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PCX files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20389.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37333|2024-06-04T17:24:33.765Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37348|2024-05-03T01:58:35.383Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37348</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20445.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37348|2024-05-03T01:58:35.383Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37355|2024-05-03T01:58:40.604Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37355</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF JPG File Parsing Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPG files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20460.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37355|2024-05-03T01:58:40.604Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37343|2024-06-04T17:24:35.015Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37343</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF JP2 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JP2 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20440.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37343|2024-06-04T17:24:35.015Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37338|2024-06-04T17:24:35.860Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37338</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF GIF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of GIF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20394.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37338|2024-06-04T17:24:35.860Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37359|2024-05-03T01:58:43.691Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37359</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20470.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37359|2024-05-03T01:58:43.691Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37334|2024-06-04T17:24:37.528Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37334</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20390.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37334|2024-06-04T17:24:37.528Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37335|2024-06-04T17:24:38.776Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37335</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF BMP File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of BMP files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20391.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37335|2024-06-04T17:24:38.776Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37358|2024-05-03T01:58:42.822Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37358</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20469.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37358|2024-05-03T01:58:42.822Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37339|2024-06-04T17:24:40.022Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37339</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PCX File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PCX files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20395.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37339|2024-06-04T17:24:40.022Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37342|2024-06-04T17:24:41.264Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37342</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PNG File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PNG files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20439.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37342|2024-06-04T17:24:41.264Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37354|2024-06-04T17:24:41.674Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37354</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PNG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PNG files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20458.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37354|2024-06-04T17:24:41.674Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42037|2024-06-05T20:53:37.336Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42037</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21583.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42037|2024-06-05T20:53:37.336Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42036|2024-06-05T20:53:21.537Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42036</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21582.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42036|2024-06-05T20:53:21.537Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42100|2024-05-03T02:13:11.973Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42100</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21604.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42100|2024-05-03T02:13:11.973Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42039|2024-06-06T12:29:12.343Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42039</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21603.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42039|2024-06-06T12:29:12.343Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42127|2024-06-04T17:25:34.928Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42127</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21585.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42127|2024-06-04T17:25:34.928Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42038|2024-06-05T20:53:48.509Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-42038</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21602.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42038|2024-06-05T20:53:48.509Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38077|2024-05-03T01:58:44.497Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38077</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20471.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38077|2024-05-03T01:58:44.497Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38082|2024-06-04T17:27:59.936Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38082</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF GIF File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of GIF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20488.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38082|2024-06-04T17:27:59.936Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38094|2024-06-04T17:28:00.339Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38094</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF replacePages Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the replacePages method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20605.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38094|2024-06-04T17:28:00.339Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38083|2024-06-04T17:28:04.063Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38083</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF JP2 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JP2 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20489.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38083|2024-06-04T17:28:04.063Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38084|2024-06-04T17:28:05.828Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38084</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20490.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38084|2024-06-04T17:28:05.828Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38092|2024-06-04T17:28:06.291Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38092</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF importDataObject Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the importDataObject method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20603.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38092|2024-06-04T17:28:06.291Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38088|2024-06-04T17:28:08.460Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38088</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF printf Uninitialized Variable Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of util objects. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of memory prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20566.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38088|2024-06-04T17:28:08.460Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38089|2024-06-04T17:28:11.465Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38089</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF clearInterval Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of app objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20567.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38089|2024-06-04T17:28:11.465Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38093|2024-06-04T17:28:13.728Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38093</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF saveAs Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the saveAs method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20604.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38093|2024-06-04T17:28:13.728Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38085|2024-06-05T20:19:31.814Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38085</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF JP2 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JP2 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20491.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38085|2024-06-05T20:19:31.814Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38090|2024-06-04T17:28:16.402Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38090</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF popUpMenu Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the app.popUpMenu method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20588.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38090|2024-06-04T17:28:16.402Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38086|2024-06-05T20:20:35.734Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38086</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20529.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38086|2024-06-05T20:20:35.734Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38087|2024-06-04T17:28:19.530Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38087</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF clearTimeOut Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of app objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20560.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38087|2024-06-04T17:28:19.530Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38091|2024-06-04T17:28:20.840Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38091</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF response Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the app.response method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a type confusion condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20601.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38091|2024-06-04T17:28:20.840Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38079|2024-06-04T17:28:25.670Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38079</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF JP2 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JP2 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20485.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38079|2024-06-04T17:28:25.670Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38080|2024-06-05T20:16:56.288Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38080</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20486.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38080|2024-06-05T20:16:56.288Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38081|2024-06-04T17:28:27.028Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38081</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF JP2 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JP2 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20487.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38081|2024-06-04T17:28:27.028Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38078|2024-05-03T01:58:45.304Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38078</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF U3D File Parsing Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20472.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38078|2024-05-03T01:58:45.304Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42039|2024-06-18T18:13:03.848Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42039</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21603.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42039|2024-06-18T18:13:03.848Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:12:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42100|2024-07-02T19:39:35.157Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42100</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21604.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42100|2024-07-02T19:39:35.157Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27335|2024-07-16T14:10:52.996Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27335</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PNG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of PNG files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22018.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27335|2024-07-16T14:10:52.996Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27345|2024-07-16T14:06:47.789Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27345</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22932.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27345|2024-07-16T14:06:47.789Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37357|2024-07-24T20:42:35.646Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37357</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-20468.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37357|2024-07-24T20:42:35.646Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:58:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27338|2024-07-31T20:28:27.298Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27338</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF app response Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the app.response method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22588.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27338|2024-07-31T20:28:27.298Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27344|2024-08-02T00:34:51.482Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27344</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22931.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27344|2024-08-02T00:34:51.482Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27345|2024-08-02T00:34:51.404Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27345</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22932.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27345|2024-08-02T00:34:51.404Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27342|2024-08-02T00:34:51.940Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27342</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22928.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27342|2024-08-02T00:34:51.940Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27336|2024-08-02T00:34:52.157Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27336</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PNG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PNG files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22022.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27336|2024-08-02T00:34:52.157Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:17:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27346|2024-08-02T00:34:51.391Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27346</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22934.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27346|2024-08-02T00:34:51.391Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27343|2024-08-02T00:34:51.385Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27343</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22929.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27343|2024-08-02T00:34:51.385Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27335|2024-08-02T00:34:51.335Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27335</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PNG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of PNG files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22018.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27335|2024-08-02T00:34:51.335Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27337|2024-08-02T00:34:52.024Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27337</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF TIF File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of TIF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22033.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27337|2024-08-02T00:34:52.024Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27340|2024-08-02T00:34:51.532Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27340</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22926.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27340|2024-08-02T00:34:51.532Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:18:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27334|2024-08-02T00:34:52.136Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27334</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF JPG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPG files.
The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21978.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27334|2024-08-02T00:34:52.136Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 23:11:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27333|2024-08-02T00:34:51.381Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27333</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF GIF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of GIF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21976.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27333|2024-08-02T00:34:51.381Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 23:04:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27341|2024-08-02T00:34:51.399Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27341</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22927.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27341|2024-08-02T00:34:51.399Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:18:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27339|2024-08-02T00:34:51.407Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27339</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22925.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27339|2024-08-02T00:34:51.407Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:18:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27338|2024-08-02T00:34:51.607Z -- kofax -- power%20pdf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27338</link>
      <description>Kofax Power PDF app response Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the app.response method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22588.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27338|2024-08-02T00:34:51.607Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
