<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for ProPump and Controls, Inc. -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/propump%20and%20controls%2C%20inc./all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for ProPump and Controls, Inc. -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 18:25:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28654|2024-08-02T13:43:23.597Z -- propump%20and%20controls%2C%20inc. -- osprey%20pump%20controller
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28654</link>
      <description>Osprey Pump Controller version 1.01 has a hidden administrative account that has the hardcoded password that allows full access to the web management interface configuration. The user is not visible in Usernames and Passwords menu list of the application and the password cannot be changed through any normal operation of the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28654|2024-08-02T13:43:23.597Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 20:03:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28375|2024-08-02T12:38:25.071Z -- propump%20and%20controls%2C%20inc. -- osprey%20pump%20controller
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28375</link>
      <description>Osprey Pump Controller version 1.01 is vulnerable to an unauthenticated file disclosure. Using a GET parameter, attackers can disclose arbitrary files on the affected device and disclose sensitive and system information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28375|2024-08-02T12:38:25.071Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 20:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28395|2024-08-02T12:38:25.093Z -- propump%20and%20controls%2C%20inc. -- osprey%20pump%20controller
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28395</link>
      <description>Osprey Pump Controller version 1.01 is vulnerable to a weak session token generation algorithm that can be predicted and can aid in authentication and authorization bypass. This may allow an attacker to hijack a session by predicting the session id and gain unauthorized access to the product.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28395|2024-08-02T12:38:25.093Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 19:59:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28648|2024-08-02T13:43:23.561Z -- propump%20and%20controls%2C%20inc. -- osprey%20pump%20controller
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28648</link>
      <description>Osprey Pump Controller version 1.01 inputs passed to a GET parameter are not properly sanitized before being returned to the user. This can be exploited to execute arbitrary HTML/JS code in a user's browser session in context of an affected site.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28648|2024-08-02T13:43:23.561Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 20:06:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27394|2024-08-02T12:09:43.401Z -- propump%20and%20controls%2C%20inc. -- osprey%20pump%20controller
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27394</link>
      <description>Osprey Pump Controller version 1.01 is vulnerable an unauthenticated OS command injection vulnerability. This can be exploited to inject and execute arbitrary shell commands through a HTTP GET parameter called by DataLogView.php, EventsView.php and AlarmsView.php scripts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27394|2024-08-02T12:09:43.401Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 20:05:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28398|2024-08-02T12:38:25.301Z -- propump%20and%20controls%2C%20inc. -- osprey%20pump%20controller
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28398</link>
      <description>Osprey Pump Controller version 1.01 could allow an unauthenticated user to create an account and bypass authentication, thereby gaining unauthorized access to the system. A threat actor could exploit this vulnerability to create a user account without providing valid credentials. A threat actor who successfully exploits this vulnerability could gain access to the pump controller and cause disruption in operation, modify data, or shut down the controller.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28398|2024-08-02T12:38:25.301Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 20:08:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28718|2024-08-02T13:43:23.859Z -- propump%20and%20controls%2C%20inc. -- osprey%20pump%20controller
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28718</link>
      <description>Osprey Pump Controller version 1.01 allows users to perform certain actions via HTTP requests without performing any checks to verify the requests. This may allow an attacker to perform certain actions with administrative privileges if a logged-in user visits a malicious website.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28718|2024-08-02T13:43:23.859Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 20:09:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27886|2024-08-02T12:23:29.843Z -- propump%20and%20controls%2C%20inc. -- osprey%20pump%20controller
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27886</link>
      <description>Osprey Pump Controller version 1.01 is vulnerable to an unauthenticated OS command injection vulnerability. This can be exploited to inject and execute arbitrary shell commands through a HTTP POST parameter called by index.php script.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27886|2024-08-02T12:23:29.843Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 20:04:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28712|2024-08-02T13:43:23.682Z -- propump%20and%20controls%2C%20inc. -- osprey%20pump%20controller
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28712</link>
      <description>Osprey Pump Controller version 1.01 contains an unauthenticated command injection vulnerability that could allow system access with www-data permissions. </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28712|2024-08-02T13:43:23.682Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 20:10:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
