<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for mindsdb -- mindsdb</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/mindsdb/mindsdb.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for mindsdb -- mindsdb</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 22:23:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-49795|2024-08-02T22:01:26.010Z -- mindsdb -- mindsdb
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49795</link>
      <description>MindsDB connects artificial intelligence models to real time data. Versions prior to 23.11.4.1 contain a server-side request forgery vulnerability in `file.py`. This can lead to limited information disclosure. Users should use MindsDB's `staging` branch or v23.11.4.1, which contain a fix for the issue.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-49795|2024-08-02T22:01:26.010Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 19:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38699|2024-08-02T17:46:56.667Z -- mindsdb -- mindsdb
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38699</link>
      <description>MindsDB's AI Virtual Database allows developers to connect any AI/ML model to any datasource. Prior to version 23.7.4.0, a call to requests with `verify=False` disables SSL certificate checks. This rule enforces always verifying SSL certificates for methods in the Requests library. In version 23.7.4.0, certificates are validated by default, which is the desired behavior.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38699|2024-08-02T17:46:56.667Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 17:53:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-30620|2024-08-02T14:28:51.816Z -- mindsdb -- mindsdb
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30620</link>
      <description>mindsdb is a Machine Learning platform to help developers build AI solutions. In affected versions an unsafe extraction is being performed using `tarfile.extractall()` from a remotely retrieved tarball. Which may lead to the writing of the extracted files to an unintended location. Sometimes, the vulnerability is called a TarSlip or a ZipSlip variant. An attacker may leverage this vulnerability to overwrite any local file which the server process has access to. There is no risk of file exposure with this vulnerability. This issue has been addressed in release `23.2.1.0 `. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-30620|2024-08-02T14:28:51.816Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 20:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-49796|2024-08-02T22:01:26.096Z -- mindsdb -- mindsdb
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49796</link>
      <description>MindsDB connects artificial intelligence models to real time data. Versions prior to 23.11.4.1 contain a limited file write vulnerability in `file.py` Users should use MindsDB's `staging` branch or v23.11.4.1, which contain a fix for the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-49796|2024-08-02T22:01:26.096Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 20:38:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
