<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for Allegro -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/allegro/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for Allegro -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 22:02:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-0522|2024-01-14T23:00:04.867Z -- Allegro -- RomPager
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0522</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Allegro RomPager 4.01. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file usertable.htm?action=delete of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument username leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 4.30 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250692. NOTE: The vendor explains that this is a very old issue that got fixed 20 years ago but without a public disclosure.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in Allegro RomPager 4.01 ausgemacht. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei usertable.htm?action=delete der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments username mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross-site request forgery-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 4.30 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0522|2024-01-14T23:00:04.867Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 23:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>