<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for divisupreme -- Supreme Modules Lite – Divi Theme, Extra Theme and Divi Builder</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/divisupreme/supreme%20modules%20lite%20%E2%80%93%20divi%20theme%2C%20extra%20theme%20and%20divi%20builder.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for divisupreme -- Supreme Modules Lite – Divi Theme, Extra Theme and Divi Builder</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 20:20:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-5501|2024-06-01T05:38:10.770Z -- divisupreme -- Supreme Modules Lite – Divi Theme, Extra Theme and Divi Builder</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5501</link><description>The Supreme Modules Lite – Divi Theme, Extra Theme and Divi Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘button_one_id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.51 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5501|2024-06-01T05:38:10.770Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 05:38:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4334|2024-05-02T16:51:49.677Z -- divisupreme -- Supreme Modules Lite – Divi Theme, Extra Theme and Divi Builder</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4334</link><description>The Supreme Modules Lite – Divi Theme, Extra Theme and Divi Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to DOM-Based Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘typing_cursor’ parameter in versions up to, and including, 2.5.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4334|2024-05-02T16:51:49.677Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:51:49 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>