<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Hesburgh Libraries of Notre Dame -- Sipity</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/hesburgh%20libraries%20of%20notre%20dame/sipity.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Hesburgh Libraries of Notre Dame -- Sipity</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 21:21:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-4298|2024-08-03T17:23:10.724Z -- hesburgh%20libraries%20of%20notre%20dame -- sipity
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4298</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Hesburgh Libraries of Notre Dame Sipity. This affects the function SearchCriteriaForWorksParameter of the file app/parameters/sipity/parameters/search_criteria_for_works_parameter.rb. The manipulation leads to sql injection. Upgrading to version 2021.8 is able to address this issue. The patch is named d1704c7363b899ffce65be03a796a0ee5fdbfbdc. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-217179.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Hesburgh Libraries of Notre Dame Sipity entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist die Funktion SearchCriteriaForWorksParameter der Datei app/parameters/sipity/parameters/search_criteria_for_works_parameter.rb. Mittels Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 2021.8 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als d1704c7363b899ffce65be03a796a0ee5fdbfbdc bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-4298|2024-08-03T17:23:10.724Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 07:53:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
