<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Linksys -- WRT54GL Wireless-G Broadband Router</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/linksys/wrt54gl%20wireless-g%20broadband%20router.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Linksys -- WRT54GL Wireless-G Broadband Router</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 14:22:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-43972|2024-08-03T13:47:05.079Z -- linksys -- wrt54gl%20wireless-g%20broadband%20router
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43972</link>
      <description>A null pointer dereference vulnerability exists in Linksys WRT54GL Wireless-G Broadband Router with firmware &lt;= 4.30.18.006. A null pointer dereference in the soap_action function within the upnp binary can be triggered by an unauthenticated attacker via a malicious POST request invoking the AddPortMapping action.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-43972|2024-08-03T13:47:05.079Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-43970|2024-08-03T13:47:05.265Z -- linksys -- wrt54gl%20wireless-g%20broadband%20router
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43970</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow vulnerability exists in Linksys WRT54GL Wireless-G Broadband Router with firmware &lt;= 4.30.18.006. A stack-based buffer overflow in the Start_EPI function within the httpd binary allows an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system as root. This vulnerablity can be triggered over the network via a malicious POST request to /apply.cgi.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-43970|2024-08-03T13:47:05.265Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-43973|2024-08-03T13:47:04.537Z -- linksys -- wrt54gl%20wireless-g%20broadband%20router
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43973</link>
      <description>An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exisits in Linksys WRT54GL Wireless-G Broadband Router with firmware &lt;= 4.30.18.006. The Check_TSSI function within the httpd binary uses unvalidated user input in the construction of a system command. An authenticated attacker with administrator privileges can leverage this vulnerability over the network via a malicious POST request to /apply.cgi to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system as root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-43973|2024-08-03T13:47:04.537Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
