<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Red Hat, Inc. -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/red%20hat%2C%20inc./all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Red Hat, Inc. -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 17:22:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1049|2024-08-05T03:44:11.848Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- systemd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1049</link>
      <description>In systemd prior to 234 a race condition exists between .mount and .automount units such that automount requests from kernel may not be serviced by systemd resulting in kernel holding the mountpoint and any processes that try to use said mount will hang. A race condition like this may lead to denial of service, until mount points are unmounted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1049|2024-08-05T03:44:11.848Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1104|2024-08-05T03:51:48.555Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- ansible%20tower
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1104</link>
      <description>Ansible Tower through version 3.2.3 has a vulnerability that allows users only with access to define variables for a job template to execute arbitrary code on the Tower server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1104|2024-08-05T03:51:48.555Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7550|2024-08-05T16:04:12.039Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- ansible
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7550</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the way Ansible (2.3.x before 2.3.3, and 2.4.x before 2.4.1) passed certain parameters to the jenkins_plugin module. Remote attackers could use this flaw to expose sensitive information from a remote host's logs. This flaw was fixed by not allowing passwords to be specified in the "params" argument, and noting this in the module documentation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7550|2024-08-05T16:04:12.039Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2628|2024-08-05T14:02:06.934Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- curl
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2628</link>
      <description>curl, as shipped in Red Hat Enterprise Linux 6 before version 7.19.7-53, did not correctly backport the fix for CVE-2015-3148 because it did not reflect the fact that the HAVE_GSSAPI define was meanwhile substituted by USE_HTTP_NEGOTIATE. This issue was introduced in RHEL 6.7 and affects RHEL 6 curl only.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2628|2024-08-05T14:02:06.934Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1102|2024-08-05T03:51:49.044Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- atomic-openshift
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1102</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in source-to-image function as shipped with Openshift Enterprise 3.x. An improper path validation of tar files in ExtractTarStreamFromTarReader in tar/tar.go leads to privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1102|2024-08-05T03:51:49.044Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7480|2024-08-05T16:04:11.545Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- rkhunter
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7480</link>
      <description>rkhunter versions before 1.4.4 are vulnerable to file download over insecure channel when doing mirror update resulting into potential remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7480|2024-08-05T16:04:11.545Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1088|2024-08-05T03:51:48.797Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- glusterfs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1088</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation flaw was found in gluster 3.x snapshot scheduler. Any gluster client allowed to mount gluster volumes could also mount shared gluster storage volume and escalate privileges by scheduling malicious cronjob via symlink.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1088|2024-08-05T03:51:48.797Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7474|2024-08-05T16:04:11.544Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- keycloak%20node.js%20adapter
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7474</link>
      <description>It was found that the Keycloak Node.js adapter 2.5 - 3.0 did not handle invalid tokens correctly.  An attacker could use this flaw to bypass authentication and gain access to restricted information, or to possibly conduct further attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7474|2024-08-05T16:04:11.544Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1047|2024-08-05T03:44:12.035Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- wildfly
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1047</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Wildfly 9.x. A path traversal vulnerability through the org.wildfly.extension.undertow.deployment.ServletResourceManager.getResource method could lead to information disclosure of arbitrary local files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1047|2024-08-05T03:44:12.035Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1106|2024-08-05T03:51:48.983Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- packagekit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1106</link>
      <description>An authentication bypass flaw has been found in PackageKit before 1.1.10 that allows users without administrator privileges to install signed packages. A local attacker can use this vulnerability to install vulnerable packages to further compromise a system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1106|2024-08-05T03:51:48.983Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1131|2024-08-05T03:51:48.906Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- infinispan
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1131</link>
      <description>Infinispan permits improper deserialization of trusted data via XML and JSON transcoders under certain server configurations. A user with authenticated access to the server could send a malicious object to a cache configured to accept certain types of objects, achieving code execution and possible further attacks. Versions 9.0.3.Final, 9.1.7.Final, 8.2.10.Final, 9.2.2.Final, 9.3.0.Alpha1 are believed to be affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1131|2024-08-05T03:51:48.906Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1054|2024-08-05T03:44:11.950Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- 389-ds-base
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1054</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds memory read flaw was found in the way 389-ds-base handled certain LDAP search filters, affecting all versions including 1.4.x. A remote, unauthenticated attacker could potentially use this flaw to make ns-slapd crash via a specially crafted LDAP request, thus resulting in denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1054|2024-08-05T03:44:11.950Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1069|2024-08-05T03:51:47.337Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- openshift%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1069</link>
      <description>Red Hat OpenShift Enterprise version 3.7 is vulnerable to access control override for container network filesystems. An attacker could override the UserId and GroupId for GlusterFS and NFS to read and write any data on the network filesystem.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1069|2024-08-05T03:51:47.337Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7556|2024-08-05T16:04:12.050Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- hawtio
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7556</link>
      <description>Hawtio versions up to and including 1.5.3 are vulnerable to CSRF vulnerability allowing remote attackers to trick the user to visit their website containing a malicious script which can be submitted to hawtio server on behalf of the user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7556|2024-08-05T16:04:12.050Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7544|2024-08-05T16:04:12.004Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- libexif
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7544</link>
      <description>libexif through 0.6.21 is vulnerable to out-of-bounds heap read vulnerability in exif_data_save_data_entry function in libexif/exif-data.c caused by improper length computation of the allocated data of an ExifMnote entry which can cause denial-of-service or possibly information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7544|2024-08-05T16:04:12.004Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7555|2024-08-05T16:04:12.052Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- augeas
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7555</link>
      <description>Augeas versions up to and including 1.8.0 are vulnerable to heap-based buffer overflow due to improper handling of escaped strings. Attacker could send crafted strings that would cause the application using augeas to copy past the end of a buffer, leading to a crash or possible code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7555|2024-08-05T16:04:12.052Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7501|2024-08-05T16:04:11.810Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- rpm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7501</link>
      <description>It was found that versions of rpm before 4.13.0.2 use temporary files with predictable names when installing an RPM. An attacker with ability to write in a directory where files will be installed could create symbolic links to an arbitrary location and modify content, and possibly permissions to arbitrary files, which could be used for denial of service or possibly privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7501|2024-08-05T16:04:11.810Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1081|2024-08-05T03:51:48.685Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- moodle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1081</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Moodle 3.4 to 3.4.1, 3.3 to 3.3.4, 3.2 to 3.2.7, 3.1 to 3.1.10 and earlier unsupported versions. Unauthenticated users can trigger custom messages to admin via paypal enrol script. Paypal IPN callback script should only send error emails to admin after request origin was verified, otherwise admin email can be spammed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1081|2024-08-05T03:51:48.685Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10861|2024-08-05T07:46:47.425Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- ceph
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10861</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the way ceph mon handles user requests. Any authenticated ceph user having read access to ceph can delete, create ceph storage pools and corrupt snapshot images. Ceph branches master, mimic, luminous and jewel are believed to be affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10861|2024-08-05T07:46:47.425Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7559|2024-08-05T16:04:12.009Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- undertow
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7559</link>
      <description>In Undertow 2.x before 2.0.0.Alpha2, 1.4.x before 1.4.17.Final, and 1.3.x before 1.3.31.Final, it was found that the fix for CVE-2017-2666 was incomplete and invalid characters are still allowed in the query string and path parameters. This could be exploited, in conjunction with a proxy that also permitted the invalid characters but with a different interpretation, to inject data into the HTTP response. By manipulating the HTTP response the attacker could poison a web-cache, perform an XSS attack, or obtain sensitive information from requests other than their own.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7559|2024-08-05T16:04:12.009Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7536|2024-08-05T16:04:11.963Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- hibernate-validator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7536</link>
      <description>In Hibernate Validator 5.2.x before 5.2.5 final, 5.3.x, and 5.4.x, it was found that when the security manager's reflective permissions, which allows it to access the private members of the class, are granted to Hibernate Validator, a potential privilege escalation can occur. By allowing the calling code to access those private members without the permission an attacker may be able to validate an invalid instance and access the private member value via ConstraintViolation#getInvalidValue().</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7536|2024-08-05T16:04:11.963Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7557|2024-08-05T16:04:12.023Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- dnsdist
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7557</link>
      <description>dnsdist version 1.1.0 is vulnerable to a flaw in authentication mechanism for REST API potentially allowing CSRF attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7557|2024-08-05T16:04:12.023Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1082|2024-08-05T03:51:48.369Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- moodle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1082</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Moodle 3.4 to 3.4.1, and 3.3 to 3.3.4. If a user account using OAuth2 authentication method was once confirmed but later suspended, the user could still login to the site.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1082|2024-08-05T03:51:48.369Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1051|2024-08-05T03:44:11.805Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- resteasy
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1051</link>
      <description>It was found that the fix for CVE-2016-9606 in versions 3.0.22 and 3.1.2 was incomplete and Yaml unmarshalling in Resteasy is still possible via `Yaml.load()` in YamlProvider.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1051|2024-08-05T03:44:11.805Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7475|2024-08-05T16:04:11.628Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- cairo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7475</link>
      <description>Cairo version 1.15.4 is vulnerable to a NULL pointer dereference related to the FT_Load_Glyph and FT_Render_Glyph resulting in an application crash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7475|2024-08-05T16:04:11.628Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1129|2024-08-05T03:51:48.711Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- ceph
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1129</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the way signature calculation was handled by cephx authentication protocol. An attacker having access to ceph cluster network who is able to alter the message payload was able to bypass signature checks done by cephx protocol. Ceph branches master, mimic, luminous and jewel are believed to be vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1129|2024-08-05T03:51:48.711Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1128|2024-08-05T03:51:48.733Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- ceph
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1128</link>
      <description>It was found that cephx authentication protocol did not verify ceph clients correctly and was vulnerable to replay attack. Any attacker having access to ceph cluster network who is able to sniff packets on network can use this vulnerability to authenticate with ceph service and perform actions allowed by ceph service. Ceph branches master, mimic, luminous and jewel are believed to be vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1128|2024-08-05T03:51:48.733Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1041|2024-08-05T03:44:11.948Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- jboss-remoting
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1041</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in the way RemoteMessageChannel, introduced in jboss-remoting versions 3.3.10, reads from an empty buffer. An attacker could use this flaw to cause denial of service via high CPU caused by an infinite loop.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1041|2024-08-05T03:44:11.948Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7504|2024-08-05T16:04:11.874Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- jboss
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7504</link>
      <description>HTTPServerILServlet.java in JMS over HTTP Invocation Layer of the JbossMQ implementation, which is enabled by default in Red Hat Jboss Application Server &lt;= Jboss 4.X does not restrict the classes for which it performs deserialization, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via crafted serialized data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7504|2024-08-05T16:04:11.874Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1059|2024-08-05T03:44:11.812Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- dpdk
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1059</link>
      <description>The DPDK vhost-user interface does not check to verify that all the requested guest physical range is mapped and contiguous when performing Guest Physical Addresses to Host Virtual Addresses translations. This may lead to a malicious guest exposing vhost-user backend process memory. All versions before 18.02.1 are vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1059|2024-08-05T03:44:11.812Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7561|2024-08-05T16:04:12.046Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- resteasy
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7561</link>
      <description>Red Hat JBoss EAP version 3.0.7 through before 4.0.0.Beta1 is vulnerable to a server-side cache poisoning or CORS requests in the JAX-RS component resulting in a moderate impact.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7561|2024-08-05T16:04:12.046Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7540|2024-08-05T16:04:11.899Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- rubygem-safemode
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7540</link>
      <description>rubygem-safemode, as used in Foreman, versions 1.3.2 and earlier are vulnerable to bypassing safe mode limitations via special Ruby syntax. This can lead to deletion of objects for which the user does not have delete permissions or possibly to privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7540|2024-08-05T16:04:11.899Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7503|2024-08-05T16:04:11.831Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- jboss%20enterprise%20application%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7503</link>
      <description>It was found that the Red Hat JBoss EAP 7.0.5 implementation of javax.xml.transform.TransformerFactory is vulnerable to XXE. An attacker could use this flaw to launch DoS or SSRF attacks, or read files from the server where EAP is deployed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7503|2024-08-05T16:04:11.831Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7549|2024-08-05T16:04:12.059Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- instack-undercloud
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7549</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in instack-undercloud 7.2.0 as packaged in Red Hat OpenStack Platform Pike, 6.1.0 as packaged in Red Hat OpenStack Platform Oacta, 5.3.0 as packaged in Red Hat OpenStack Newton, where pre-install and security policy scripts used insecure temporary files. A local user could exploit this flaw to conduct a symbolic-link attack, allowing them to overwrite the contents of arbitrary files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7549|2024-08-05T16:04:12.059Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7523|2024-08-05T16:04:11.820Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- cygwin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7523</link>
      <description>Cygwin versions 1.7.2 up to and including 1.8.0 are vulnerable to buffer overflow vulnerability in wcsxfrm/wcsxfrm_l functions resulting into denial-of-service by crashing the process or potential hijack of the process running with administrative privileges triggered by specially crafted input string.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7523|2024-08-05T16:04:11.820Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1048|2024-08-05T03:44:11.828Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- undertow%20as%20shipped%20in%20jboss%20eap%207.1.0.ga
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1048</link>
      <description>It was found that the AJP connector in undertow, as shipped in Jboss EAP 7.1.0.GA, does not use the ALLOW_ENCODED_SLASH option and thus allow the the slash / anti-slash characters encoded in the url which may lead to path traversal and result in the information disclosure of arbitrary local files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1048|2024-08-05T03:44:11.828Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7515|2024-08-05T16:04:11.824Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- poppler
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7515</link>
      <description>poppler through version 0.55.0 is vulnerable to an uncontrolled recursion in pdfunite resulting into potential denial-of-service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7515|2024-08-05T16:04:11.824Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2017 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1101|2024-08-05T03:51:48.446Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- ansible%20tower
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1101</link>
      <description>Ansible Tower before version 3.2.4 has a flaw in the management of system and organization administrators that allows for privilege escalation. System administrators that are members of organizations can have their passwords reset by organization administrators, allowing organization administrators access to the entire system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1101|2024-08-05T03:51:48.446Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7534|2024-08-05T16:04:11.828Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- openshift
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7534</link>
      <description>OpenShift Enterprise version 3.x is vulnerable to a stored XSS via the log viewer for pods. The flaw is due to lack of sanitation of user input, specifically terminal escape characters, and the creation of clickable links automatically when viewing the log files for a pod.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7534|2024-08-05T16:04:11.828Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1098|2024-08-05T03:51:48.502Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- etcd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1098</link>
      <description>A cross-site request forgery flaw was found in etcd 3.3.1 and earlier. An attacker can set up a website that tries to send a POST request to the etcd server and modify a key. Adding a key is done with PUT so it is theoretically safe (can't PUT from an HTML form or such) but POST allows creating in-order keys that an attacker can send.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1098|2024-08-05T03:51:48.502Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7560|2024-08-05T16:04:12.054Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- rhnsd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7560</link>
      <description>It was found that rhnsd PID files are created as world-writable that allows local attackers to fill the disks or to kill selected processes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7560|2024-08-05T16:04:12.054Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7496|2024-08-05T16:04:11.869Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- fedora-arm-installer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7496</link>
      <description>fedora-arm-installer up to and including 1.99.16 is vulnerable to local privilege escalation due to lack of checking the error condition of mount operation failure on unsafely created temporary directories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7496|2024-08-05T16:04:11.869Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2585|2024-08-05T13:55:06.129Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- keycloak
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2585</link>
      <description>Red Hat Keycloak before version 2.5.1 has an implementation of HMAC verification for JWS tokens that uses a method that runs in non-constant time, potentially leaving the application vulnerable to timing attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2585|2024-08-05T13:55:06.129Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1099|2024-08-05T03:51:48.412Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- etcd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1099</link>
      <description>DNS rebinding vulnerability found in etcd 3.3.1 and earlier. An attacker can control his DNS records to direct to localhost, and trick the browser into sending requests to localhost (or any other address).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1099|2024-08-05T03:51:48.412Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
