<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Red Hat, Inc. -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/red%20hat%2C%20inc./all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Red Hat, Inc. -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 11:20:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1049|2024-08-05T03:44:11.848Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- systemd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1049</link>
      <description>In systemd prior to 234 a race condition exists between .mount and .automount units such that automount requests from kernel may not be serviced by systemd resulting in kernel holding the mountpoint and any processes that try to use said mount will hang. A race condition like this may lead to denial of service, until mount points are unmounted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1049|2024-08-05T03:44:11.848Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1104|2024-08-05T03:51:48.555Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- ansible%20tower
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1104</link>
      <description>Ansible Tower through version 3.2.3 has a vulnerability that allows users only with access to define variables for a job template to execute arbitrary code on the Tower server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1104|2024-08-05T03:51:48.555Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1102|2024-08-05T03:51:49.044Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- atomic-openshift
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1102</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in source-to-image function as shipped with Openshift Enterprise 3.x. An improper path validation of tar files in ExtractTarStreamFromTarReader in tar/tar.go leads to privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1102|2024-08-05T03:51:49.044Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1088|2024-08-05T03:51:48.797Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- glusterfs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1088</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation flaw was found in gluster 3.x snapshot scheduler. Any gluster client allowed to mount gluster volumes could also mount shared gluster storage volume and escalate privileges by scheduling malicious cronjob via symlink.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1088|2024-08-05T03:51:48.797Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1047|2024-08-05T03:44:12.035Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- wildfly
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1047</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Wildfly 9.x. A path traversal vulnerability through the org.wildfly.extension.undertow.deployment.ServletResourceManager.getResource method could lead to information disclosure of arbitrary local files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1047|2024-08-05T03:44:12.035Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1106|2024-08-05T03:51:48.983Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- packagekit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1106</link>
      <description>An authentication bypass flaw has been found in PackageKit before 1.1.10 that allows users without administrator privileges to install signed packages. A local attacker can use this vulnerability to install vulnerable packages to further compromise a system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1106|2024-08-05T03:51:48.983Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1131|2024-08-05T03:51:48.906Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- infinispan
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1131</link>
      <description>Infinispan permits improper deserialization of trusted data via XML and JSON transcoders under certain server configurations. A user with authenticated access to the server could send a malicious object to a cache configured to accept certain types of objects, achieving code execution and possible further attacks. Versions 9.0.3.Final, 9.1.7.Final, 8.2.10.Final, 9.2.2.Final, 9.3.0.Alpha1 are believed to be affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1131|2024-08-05T03:51:48.906Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1054|2024-08-05T03:44:11.950Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- 389-ds-base
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1054</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds memory read flaw was found in the way 389-ds-base handled certain LDAP search filters, affecting all versions including 1.4.x. A remote, unauthenticated attacker could potentially use this flaw to make ns-slapd crash via a specially crafted LDAP request, thus resulting in denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1054|2024-08-05T03:44:11.950Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1069|2024-08-05T03:51:47.337Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- openshift%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1069</link>
      <description>Red Hat OpenShift Enterprise version 3.7 is vulnerable to access control override for container network filesystems. An attacker could override the UserId and GroupId for GlusterFS and NFS to read and write any data on the network filesystem.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1069|2024-08-05T03:51:47.337Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1081|2024-08-05T03:51:48.685Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- moodle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1081</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Moodle 3.4 to 3.4.1, 3.3 to 3.3.4, 3.2 to 3.2.7, 3.1 to 3.1.10 and earlier unsupported versions. Unauthenticated users can trigger custom messages to admin via paypal enrol script. Paypal IPN callback script should only send error emails to admin after request origin was verified, otherwise admin email can be spammed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1081|2024-08-05T03:51:48.685Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10861|2024-08-05T07:46:47.425Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- ceph
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10861</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the way ceph mon handles user requests. Any authenticated ceph user having read access to ceph can delete, create ceph storage pools and corrupt snapshot images. Ceph branches master, mimic, luminous and jewel are believed to be affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10861|2024-08-05T07:46:47.425Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1082|2024-08-05T03:51:48.369Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- moodle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1082</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Moodle 3.4 to 3.4.1, and 3.3 to 3.3.4. If a user account using OAuth2 authentication method was once confirmed but later suspended, the user could still login to the site.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1082|2024-08-05T03:51:48.369Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1051|2024-08-05T03:44:11.805Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- resteasy
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1051</link>
      <description>It was found that the fix for CVE-2016-9606 in versions 3.0.22 and 3.1.2 was incomplete and Yaml unmarshalling in Resteasy is still possible via `Yaml.load()` in YamlProvider.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1051|2024-08-05T03:44:11.805Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1129|2024-08-05T03:51:48.711Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- ceph
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1129</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the way signature calculation was handled by cephx authentication protocol. An attacker having access to ceph cluster network who is able to alter the message payload was able to bypass signature checks done by cephx protocol. Ceph branches master, mimic, luminous and jewel are believed to be vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1129|2024-08-05T03:51:48.711Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1128|2024-08-05T03:51:48.733Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- ceph
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1128</link>
      <description>It was found that cephx authentication protocol did not verify ceph clients correctly and was vulnerable to replay attack. Any attacker having access to ceph cluster network who is able to sniff packets on network can use this vulnerability to authenticate with ceph service and perform actions allowed by ceph service. Ceph branches master, mimic, luminous and jewel are believed to be vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1128|2024-08-05T03:51:48.733Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1041|2024-08-05T03:44:11.948Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- jboss-remoting
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1041</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in the way RemoteMessageChannel, introduced in jboss-remoting versions 3.3.10, reads from an empty buffer. An attacker could use this flaw to cause denial of service via high CPU caused by an infinite loop.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1041|2024-08-05T03:44:11.948Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1059|2024-08-05T03:44:11.812Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- dpdk
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1059</link>
      <description>The DPDK vhost-user interface does not check to verify that all the requested guest physical range is mapped and contiguous when performing Guest Physical Addresses to Host Virtual Addresses translations. This may lead to a malicious guest exposing vhost-user backend process memory. All versions before 18.02.1 are vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1059|2024-08-05T03:44:11.812Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1048|2024-08-05T03:44:11.828Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- undertow%20as%20shipped%20in%20jboss%20eap%207.1.0.ga
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1048</link>
      <description>It was found that the AJP connector in undertow, as shipped in Jboss EAP 7.1.0.GA, does not use the ALLOW_ENCODED_SLASH option and thus allow the the slash / anti-slash characters encoded in the url which may lead to path traversal and result in the information disclosure of arbitrary local files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1048|2024-08-05T03:44:11.828Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1101|2024-08-05T03:51:48.446Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- ansible%20tower
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1101</link>
      <description>Ansible Tower before version 3.2.4 has a flaw in the management of system and organization administrators that allows for privilege escalation. System administrators that are members of organizations can have their passwords reset by organization administrators, allowing organization administrators access to the entire system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1101|2024-08-05T03:51:48.446Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1098|2024-08-05T03:51:48.502Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- etcd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1098</link>
      <description>A cross-site request forgery flaw was found in etcd 3.3.1 and earlier. An attacker can set up a website that tries to send a POST request to the etcd server and modify a key. Adding a key is done with PUT so it is theoretically safe (can't PUT from an HTML form or such) but POST allows creating in-order keys that an attacker can send.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1098|2024-08-05T03:51:48.502Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1099|2024-08-05T03:51:48.412Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- etcd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1099</link>
      <description>DNS rebinding vulnerability found in etcd 3.3.1 and earlier. An attacker can control his DNS records to direct to localhost, and trick the browser into sending requests to localhost (or any other address).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1099|2024-08-05T03:51:48.412Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
