<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Red Hat, Inc. -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/red%20hat%2C%20inc./all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Red Hat, Inc. -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:23:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1059|2024-09-17T00:46:47.514Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- dpdk
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1059</link>
      <description>The DPDK vhost-user interface does not check to verify that all the requested guest physical range is mapped and contiguous when performing Guest Physical Addresses to Host Virtual Addresses translations. This may lead to a malicious guest exposing vhost-user backend process memory. All versions before 18.02.1 are vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1059|2024-09-17T00:46:47.514Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1101|2024-09-17T01:45:32.582Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- ansible%20tower
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1101</link>
      <description>Ansible Tower before version 3.2.4 has a flaw in the management of system and organization administrators that allows for privilege escalation. System administrators that are members of organizations can have their passwords reset by organization administrators, allowing organization administrators access to the entire system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1101|2024-09-17T01:45:32.582Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1099|2024-09-17T00:36:24.817Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- etcd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1099</link>
      <description>DNS rebinding vulnerability found in etcd 3.3.1 and earlier. An attacker can control his DNS records to direct to localhost, and trick the browser into sending requests to localhost (or any other address).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1099|2024-09-17T00:36:24.817Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1129|2024-09-17T01:45:51.875Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- ceph
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1129</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the way signature calculation was handled by cephx authentication protocol. An attacker having access to ceph cluster network who is able to alter the message payload was able to bypass signature checks done by cephx protocol. Ceph branches master, mimic, luminous and jewel are believed to be vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1129|2024-09-17T01:45:51.875Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1054|2024-09-17T00:11:04.061Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- 389-ds-base
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1054</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds memory read flaw was found in the way 389-ds-base handled certain LDAP search filters, affecting all versions including 1.4.x. A remote, unauthenticated attacker could potentially use this flaw to make ns-slapd crash via a specially crafted LDAP request, thus resulting in denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1054|2024-09-17T00:11:04.061Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7555|2024-09-17T02:36:08.138Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- augeas
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7555</link>
      <description>Augeas versions up to and including 1.8.0 are vulnerable to heap-based buffer overflow due to improper handling of escaped strings. Attacker could send crafted strings that would cause the application using augeas to copy past the end of a buffer, leading to a crash or possible code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7555|2024-09-17T02:36:08.138Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
