<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Red Hat, Inc. -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/red%20hat%2C%20inc./all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Red Hat, Inc. -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 20:23:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10861|2024-09-16T16:28:46.914Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- ceph
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10861</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the way ceph mon handles user requests. Any authenticated ceph user having read access to ceph can delete, create ceph storage pools and corrupt snapshot images. Ceph branches master, mimic, luminous and jewel are believed to be affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10861|2024-09-16T16:28:46.914Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1104|2024-09-16T19:09:02.633Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- ansible%20tower
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1104</link>
      <description>Ansible Tower through version 3.2.3 has a vulnerability that allows users only with access to define variables for a job template to execute arbitrary code on the Tower server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1104|2024-09-16T19:09:02.633Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1081|2024-09-16T19:55:57.284Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- moodle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1081</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Moodle 3.4 to 3.4.1, 3.3 to 3.3.4, 3.2 to 3.2.7, 3.1 to 3.1.10 and earlier unsupported versions. Unauthenticated users can trigger custom messages to admin via paypal enrol script. Paypal IPN callback script should only send error emails to admin after request origin was verified, otherwise admin email can be spammed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1081|2024-09-16T19:55:57.284Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1049|2024-09-16T16:47:41.544Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- systemd
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1049</link>
      <description>In systemd prior to 234 a race condition exists between .mount and .automount units such that automount requests from kernel may not be serviced by systemd resulting in kernel holding the mountpoint and any processes that try to use said mount will hang. A race condition like this may lead to denial of service, until mount points are unmounted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1049|2024-09-16T16:47:41.544Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3813|2024-09-16T16:23:33.117Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- spice
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3813</link>
      <description>Spice, versions 0.5.2 through 0.14.1, are vulnerable to an out-of-bounds read due to an off-by-one error in memslot_get_virt. This may lead to a denial of service, or, in the worst case, code-execution by unauthenticated attackers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3813|2024-09-16T16:23:33.117Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-8629|2024-09-16T17:52:54.232Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- keycloak
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-8629</link>
      <description>Red Hat Keycloak before version 2.4.0 did not correctly check permissions when handling service account user deletion requests sent to the rest server. An attacker with service account authentication could use this flaw to bypass normal permissions and delete users in a separate realm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-8629|2024-09-16T17:52:54.232Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7523|2024-09-16T18:03:20.729Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- cygwin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7523</link>
      <description>Cygwin versions 1.7.2 up to and including 1.8.0 are vulnerable to buffer overflow vulnerability in wcsxfrm/wcsxfrm_l functions resulting into denial-of-service by crashing the process or potential hijack of the process running with administrative privileges triggered by specially crafted input string.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7523|2024-09-16T18:03:20.729Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12160|2024-09-16T18:48:51.709Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- keycloak
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12160</link>
      <description>It was found that Keycloak oauth would permit an authenticated resource to obtain an access/refresh token pair from the authentication server, permitting indefinite usage in the case of permission revocation. An attacker on an already compromised resource could use this flaw to grant himself continued permissions and possibly conduct further attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12160|2024-09-16T18:48:51.709Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1106|2024-09-16T16:18:44.131Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- packagekit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1106</link>
      <description>An authentication bypass flaw has been found in PackageKit before 1.1.10 that allows users without administrator privileges to install signed packages. A local attacker can use this vulnerability to install vulnerable packages to further compromise a system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1106|2024-09-16T16:18:44.131Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-15099|2024-09-16T16:43:27.924Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- postgresql
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-15099</link>
      <description>INSERT ... ON CONFLICT DO UPDATE commands in PostgreSQL 10.x before 10.1, 9.6.x before 9.6.6, and 9.5.x before 9.5.10 disclose table contents that the invoker lacks privilege to read. These exploits affect only tables where the attacker lacks full read access but has both INSERT and UPDATE privileges. Exploits bypass row level security policies and lack of SELECT privilege.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-15099|2024-09-16T16:43:27.924Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7559|2024-09-16T19:56:46.618Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- undertow
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7559</link>
      <description>In Undertow 2.x before 2.0.0.Alpha2, 1.4.x before 1.4.17.Final, and 1.3.x before 1.3.31.Final, it was found that the fix for CVE-2017-2666 was incomplete and invalid characters are still allowed in the query string and path parameters. This could be exploited, in conjunction with a proxy that also permitted the invalid characters but with a different interpretation, to inject data into the HTTP response. By manipulating the HTTP response the attacker could poison a web-cache, perform an XSS attack, or obtain sensitive information from requests other than their own.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7559|2024-09-16T19:56:46.618Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7557|2024-09-16T18:19:26.001Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- dnsdist
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7557</link>
      <description>dnsdist version 1.1.0 is vulnerable to a flaw in authentication mechanism for REST API potentially allowing CSRF attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7557|2024-09-16T18:19:26.001Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1082|2024-09-16T16:43:01.540Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- moodle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1082</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in Moodle 3.4 to 3.4.1, and 3.3 to 3.3.4. If a user account using OAuth2 authentication method was once confirmed but later suspended, the user could still login to the site.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1082|2024-09-16T16:43:01.540Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7536|2024-09-16T17:32:38.135Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- hibernate-validator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7536</link>
      <description>In Hibernate Validator 5.2.x before 5.2.5 final, 5.3.x, and 5.4.x, it was found that when the security manager's reflective permissions, which allows it to access the private members of the class, are granted to Hibernate Validator, a potential privilege escalation can occur. By allowing the calling code to access those private members without the permission an attacker may be able to validate an invalid instance and access the private member value via ConstraintViolation#getInvalidValue().</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7536|2024-09-16T17:32:38.135Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
