<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Red Hat, Inc. -- ceph</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/red%20hat%2C%20inc./ceph.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Red Hat, Inc. -- ceph</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 11:21:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10861|2024-08-05T07:46:47.425Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- ceph
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10861</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the way ceph mon handles user requests. Any authenticated ceph user having read access to ceph can delete, create ceph storage pools and corrupt snapshot images. Ceph branches master, mimic, luminous and jewel are believed to be affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10861|2024-08-05T07:46:47.425Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1129|2024-08-05T03:51:48.711Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- ceph
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1129</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the way signature calculation was handled by cephx authentication protocol. An attacker having access to ceph cluster network who is able to alter the message payload was able to bypass signature checks done by cephx protocol. Ceph branches master, mimic, luminous and jewel are believed to be vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1129|2024-08-05T03:51:48.711Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1128|2024-08-05T03:51:48.733Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- ceph
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1128</link>
      <description>It was found that cephx authentication protocol did not verify ceph clients correctly and was vulnerable to replay attack. Any attacker having access to ceph cluster network who is able to sniff packets on network can use this vulnerability to authenticate with ceph service and perform actions allowed by ceph service. Ceph branches master, mimic, luminous and jewel are believed to be vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1128|2024-08-05T03:51:48.733Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
