<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Red Hat, Inc. -- keycloak</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/red%20hat%2C%20inc./keycloak.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Red Hat, Inc. -- keycloak</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 22:22:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12160|2024-08-05T18:28:16.585Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- keycloak
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12160</link>
      <description>It was found that Keycloak oauth would permit an authenticated resource to obtain an access/refresh token pair from the authentication server, permitting indefinite usage in the case of permission revocation. An attacker on an already compromised resource could use this flaw to grant himself continued permissions and possibly conduct further attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12160|2024-08-05T18:28:16.585Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12161|2024-08-05T18:28:16.559Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- keycloak
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12161</link>
      <description>It was found that keycloak before 3.4.2 final would permit misuse of a client-side /etc/hosts entry to spoof a URL in a password reset request. An attacker could use this flaw to craft a malicious password reset request and gain a valid reset token, leading to information disclosure or further attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12161|2024-08-05T18:28:16.559Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12158|2024-08-05T18:28:16.496Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- keycloak
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12158</link>
      <description>It was found that Keycloak would accept a HOST header URL in the admin console and use it to determine web resource locations. An attacker could use this flaw against an authenticated user to attain reflected XSS via a malicious server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12158|2024-08-05T18:28:16.496Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12159|2024-08-05T18:28:16.484Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- keycloak
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12159</link>
      <description>It was found that the cookie used for CSRF prevention in Keycloak was not unique to each session. An attacker could use this flaw to gain access to an authenticated user session, leading to possible information disclosure or further attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12159|2024-08-05T18:28:16.484Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2585|2024-08-05T13:55:06.129Z -- red%20hat%2C%20inc. -- keycloak
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2585</link>
      <description>Red Hat Keycloak before version 2.5.1 has an implementation of HMAC verification for JWS tokens that uses a method that runs in non-constant time, potentially leaving the application vulnerable to timing attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2585|2024-08-05T13:55:06.129Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
