<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for Ministry of Agriculture, Forestry and Fisheries -- Electronic Delivery Check System (Ministry of Agriculture, Forestry and Fisheries The Agriculture and Rural Development Project Version) March, Heisei 31 era edition</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ministry%20of%20agriculture%2C%20forestry%20and%20fisheries/electronic%20delivery%20check%20system%20%28ministry%20of%20agriculture%2C%20forestry%20and%20fisheries%20the%20agriculture%20and%20rural%20development%20project%20version%29%20march%2C%20heisei%2031%20era%20edition.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for Ministry of Agriculture, Forestry and Fisheries -- Electronic Delivery Check System (Ministry of Agriculture, Forestry and Fisheries The Agriculture and Rural Development Project Version) March, Heisei 31 era edition</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 16:28:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-22380|2024-01-24T01:32:47.520Z -- Ministry of Agriculture, Forestry and Fisheries -- Electronic Delivery Check System (Ministry of Agriculture, Forestry and Fisheries The Agriculture and Rural Development Project Version) March, Heisei 31 era edition
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22380</link><description>Electronic Delivery Check System (Ministry of Agriculture, Forestry and Fisheries The Agriculture and Rural Development Project Version) March, Heisei 31 era edition Ver.14.0.001.002 and earlier improperly restricts XML external entity references (XXE). By processing a specially crafted XML file, arbitrary files on the system may be read by an attacker.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22380|2024-01-24T01:32:47.520Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 01:32:47 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>