<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Natus Medical Incorporated -- Natus</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/natus%20medical%20incorporated/natus.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Natus Medical Incorporated -- Natus</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 20:22:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2853|2024-08-05T14:09:16.810Z -- natus%20medical%20incorporated -- natus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2853</link>
      <description>An exploitable Code Execution vulnerability exists in the RequestForPatientInfoEEGfile functionality of Natus Xltek NeuroWorks 8. A specially crafted network packet can cause a stack buffer overflow resulting in arbitrary command execution. An attacker can send a malicious packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2853|2024-08-05T14:09:16.810Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2867|2024-08-05T14:09:17.280Z -- natus%20medical%20incorporated -- natus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2867</link>
      <description>An exploitable code execution vulnerability exists in the SavePatientMontage functionality of Natus Xltek NeuroWorks 8. A specially crafted network packet can cause a stack buffer overflow resulting in code execution. An attacker can a malicious packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2867|2024-08-05T14:09:17.280Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2861|2024-08-05T14:09:17.222Z -- natus%20medical%20incorporated -- natus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2861</link>
      <description>An exploitable Denial of Service vulnerability exists in the use of a return value in the NewProducerStream command in Natus Xltek NeuroWorks 8. A specially crafted network packet can cause an out of bounds read resulting in a denial of service. An attacker can send a malicious packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2861|2024-08-05T14:09:17.222Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2869|2024-08-05T14:09:17.353Z -- natus%20medical%20incorporated -- natus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2869</link>
      <description>An exploitable code execution vulnerability exists in the OpenProducer functionality of Natus Xltek NeuroWorks 8. A specially crafted network packet can cause a stack buffer overflow resulting in code execution. An attacker can send a malicious packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2869|2024-08-05T14:09:17.353Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2868|2024-08-05T14:09:17.464Z -- natus%20medical%20incorporated -- natus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2868</link>
      <description>An exploitable code execution vulnerability exists in the NewProducerStream functionality of Natus Xltek NeuroWorks 8. A specially crafted network packet can cause a stack buffer overflow resulting in code execution. An attacker can send a malicious packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2868|2024-08-05T14:09:17.464Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
