<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for ETIC Telecom -- Remote Access Server (RAS)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/etic%20telecom/remote%20access%20server%20%28ras%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for ETIC Telecom -- Remote Access Server (RAS)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 20:22:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41607|2024-08-03T12:49:43.447Z -- etic%20telecom -- remote%20access%20server%20%28ras%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41607</link>
      <description>All versions of ETIC Telecom Remote Access Server (RAS) 4.5.0 and prior’s application programmable interface (API) is vulnerable to directory traversal through several different methods. This could allow an attacker to read sensitive files from the server, including SSH private keys, passwords, scripts, python objects, database files, and more.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41607|2024-08-03T12:49:43.447Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40981|2024-08-03T12:28:42.952Z -- etic%20telecom -- remote%20access%20server%20%28ras%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40981</link>
      <description>All versions of ETIC Telecom Remote Access Server (RAS) 4.5.0 and prior is vulnerable to malicious file upload. An attacker could take advantage of this to store malicious files on the server, which could override sensitive and useful existing files on the filesystem, fill the hard disk to full capacity, or compromise the affected device or computers with administrator level privileges connected to the affected device.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40981|2024-08-03T12:28:42.952Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3703|2024-08-03T01:20:57.038Z -- etic%20telecom -- remote%20access%20server%20%28ras%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3703</link>
      <description>All versions of ETIC Telecom Remote Access Server (RAS) 4.5.0 and prior’s web portal is vulnerable to accepting malicious firmware packages that could provide a backdoor to an attacker and provide privilege escalation to the device.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3703|2024-08-03T01:20:57.038Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
