<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for sourcegraph -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sourcegraph/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for sourcegraph -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 20:23:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-46248|2024-09-05T17:34:41.209Z -- sourcegraph -- cody
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46248</link>
      <description>Cody is an artificial intelligence (AI) coding assistant. The Cody AI VSCode extension versions 0.10.0 through 0.14.0 are vulnerable to Remote Code Execution under certain conditions. An attacker in control of a malicious repository could modify the Cody configuration file `.vscode/cody.json` and overwrite Cody commands. If a user with the extension installed opens this malicious repository and runs a Cody command such as /explain or /doc, this could allow arbitrary code execution on the user's machine. The vulnerability is rated as critical severity, but with low exploitability. It requires the user to have a malicious repository loaded and execute the overwritten command in VS Code. The issue is exploitable regardless of the user blocking code execution on a repository through VS Code Workspace Trust. The issue was found during a regular 3rd party penetration test. The maintainers of Cody do not have evidence of open source repositories having malicious `.vscode/cody.json` files to exploit this vulnerability. The issue is fixed in version 0.14.1 of the Cody VSCode extension. In case users can't promptly upgrade, they should not open any untrusted repositories with the Cody extension loaded.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-46248|2024-09-05T17:34:41.209Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:11:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
