<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Nesote -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/nesote/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Nesote -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 17:22:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3624|2024-08-02T07:01:57.200Z -- nesote -- inout%20blockchain%20fiatexchanger
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3624</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Nesote Inout Blockchain FiatExchanger 3.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /index.php/coins/update_marketboxslider of the component POST Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument marketcurrency leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The identifier VDB-233577 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Nesote Inout Blockchain FiatExchanger 3.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei /index.php/coins/update_marketboxslider der Komponente POST Parameter Handler. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments marketcurrency mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3624|2024-08-02T07:01:57.200Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 17:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3682|2024-08-02T07:01:57.360Z -- nesote -- inout%20blockchain%20easypayments
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3682</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Nesote Inout Blockchain EasyPayments 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /index.php/payment/getcoinaddress of the component POST Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument coinid leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-234228. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Nesote Inout Blockchain EasyPayments 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei /index.php/payment/getcoinaddress der Komponente POST Parameter Handler. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments coinid mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3682|2024-08-02T07:01:57.360Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 16:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3685|2024-08-02T07:01:57.397Z -- nesote -- inout%20search%20engine%20ai%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3685</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Nesote Inout Search Engine AI Edition 1.1. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument page leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-234231. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Nesote Inout Search Engine AI Edition 1.1 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei /index.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments page mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3685|2024-08-02T07:01:57.397Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
