<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for prisma -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/prisma/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for prisma -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 21:21:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21414|2024-08-03T18:09:16.130Z -- prisma -- prisma
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21414</link>
      <description>Prisma is an open source ORM for Node.js &amp; TypeScript. As of today, we are not aware of any Prisma users or external consumers of the `@prisma/sdk` package who are affected by this security vulnerability. This issue may lead to remote code execution if a client of the library calls the vulnerable method with untrusted input. It only affects the `getPackedPackage` function and this function is not advertised and only used for tests &amp; building our CLI, no malicious code was found after checking our codebase.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21414|2024-08-03T18:09:16.130Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 00:45:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21415|2024-08-03T18:09:16.078Z -- prisma -- language-tools
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21415</link>
      <description>Prisma VS Code a VSCode extension for Prisma schema files. This is a Remote Code Execution Vulnerability that affects all versions of the Prisma VS Code extension older than 2.20.0. If a custom binary path for the Prisma format binary is set in VS Code Settings, for example by downloading a project that has a .vscode/settings.json file that sets a value for "prismaFmtBinPath". That custom binary is executed when auto-formatting is triggered by VS Code or when validation checks are triggered after each keypress on a *.prisma file. Fixed in versions 2.20.0 and 20.0.27. As a workaround users can either edit or delete the `.vscode/settings.json` file or check if the binary is malicious and delete it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21415|2024-08-03T18:09:16.078Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 16:50:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
