<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for MongoDB Inc. -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/mongodb%20inc./all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for MongoDB Inc. -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 21:21:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-20329|2024-08-03T17:37:23.756Z -- mongodb%20inc. -- mongodb%20go%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-20329</link>
      <description>Specific cstrings input may not be properly validated in the MongoDB Go Driver when marshalling Go objects into BSON. A malicious user could use a Go object with specific string to potentially inject additional fields into marshalled documents. This issue affects all MongoDB GO Drivers prior to and including 1.5.0.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-20329|2024-08-03T17:37:23.756Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-20326|2024-08-03T17:37:23.931Z -- mongodb%20inc. -- mongodb%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-20326</link>
      <description>A user authorized to performing a specific type of find query may trigger a denial of service. This issue affects MongoDB Server v4.4 versions prior to 4.4.4.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-20326|2024-08-03T17:37:23.931Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24272|2024-08-03T04:07:02.637Z -- mongodb%20inc. -- mongodb%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24272</link>
      <description>An authenticated user may trigger an invariant assertion during command dispatch due to incorrect validation on the $external database. This may result in mongod denial of service or server crash. This issue affects: MongoDB Inc. MongoDB Server v5.0 versions, prior to and including v5.0.6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24272|2024-08-03T04:07:02.637Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-20334|2024-08-03T17:37:23.920Z -- mongodb%20inc. -- mongodb%20compass
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-20334</link>
      <description>A malicious 3rd party with local access to the Windows machine where MongoDB Compass is installed can execute arbitrary software with the privileges of the user who is running MongoDB Compass. This issue affects: MongoDB Inc. MongoDB Compass 1.x version 1.3.0 on Windows and later versions; 1.x versions prior to 1.25.0 on Windows.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-20334|2024-08-03T17:37:23.920Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-20328|2024-08-03T17:37:24.117Z -- mongodb%20inc. -- mongo-java-driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-20328</link>
      <description>Specific versions of the Java driver that support client-side field level encryption (CSFLE) fail to perform correct host name verification on the KMS server’s certificate. This vulnerability in combination with a privileged network position active MITM attack could result in interception of traffic between the Java driver and the KMS service rendering Field Level Encryption ineffective. This issue was discovered during internal testing and affects all versions of the Java driver that support CSFLE. The Java async, Scala, and reactive streams drivers are not impacted. This vulnerability does not impact driver traffic payloads with CSFLE-supported key services originating from applications residing inside the AWS, GCP, and Azure network fabrics due to compensating controls in these environments. This issue does not impact driver workloads that don’t use Field Level Encryption.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-20328|2024-08-03T17:37:24.117Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-20331|2024-08-03T17:37:23.787Z -- mongodb%20inc. -- mongodb%20c%23%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-20331</link>
      <description>
Specific versions of the MongoDB C# Driver may erroneously publish events containing authentication-related data to a command listener configured by an application. The published events may contain security-sensitive data when commands such as "saslStart", "saslContinue", "isMaster", "createUser", and "updateUser" are executed. Without due care, an application may inadvertently expose this authenticated-related information, e.g., by writing it to a log file. This issue only arises if an application enables the command listener feature (this is not enabled by default). This issue affects the MongoDB C# Driver v2.12 versions prior to and including 2.12.1.




</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-20331|2024-08-03T17:37:23.787Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-20333|2024-08-03T17:37:23.864Z -- mongodb%20inc. -- mongodb%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-20333</link>
      <description>Sending specially crafted commands to a MongoDB Server may result in artificial log entries being generated or for log entries to be split. This issue affects MongoDB Server v3.6 versions prior to 3.6.20; MongoDB Server v4.0 versions prior to 4.0.21 and MongoDB Server v4.2 versions prior to 4.2.10.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-20333|2024-08-03T17:37:23.864Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-20327|2024-08-03T17:37:23.809Z -- mongodb%20inc. -- mongodb%20node.js%20driver%20mongodb-client-encryption%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-20327</link>
      <description>A specific version of the Node.js mongodb-client-encryption module does not perform correct validation of the KMS server’s certificate. This vulnerability in combination with a privileged network position active MITM attack could result in interception of traffic between the Node.js driver and the KMS service rendering client-side field level encryption (CSFLE) ineffective. This issue was discovered during internal testing and affects mongodb-client-encryption module version 1.2.0, which was available from 2021-Jan-29 and deprecated in the NPM Registry on 2021-Feb-04. This vulnerability does not impact driver traffic payloads with CSFLE-supported key services from applications residing inside the AWS, GCP, and Azure nework fabrics due to compensating controls in these environments. This issue does not impact driver workloads that don’t use Field Level Encryption. This issue affect MongoDB Node.js Driver mongodb-client-encryption module version 1.2.0


</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-20327|2024-08-03T17:37:23.809Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-20332|2024-08-03T17:37:23.892Z -- mongodb%20inc. -- mongodb%20rust%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-20332</link>
      <description>Specific MongoDB Rust Driver versions can include credentials used by the connection pool to authenticate connections in the monitoring event that is emitted when the pool is created. The user's logging infrastructure could then potentially ingest these events and unexpectedly leak the credentials. Note that such monitoring is not enabled by default. This issue affects MongoDB Rust Driver version 2.0.0-alpha, MongoDB Rust Driver version 2.0.0-alpha1 and MongoDB Rust Driver version 1.0.0 through to and including 1.2.1

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-20332|2024-08-03T17:37:23.892Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-20335|2024-08-03T17:37:23.802Z -- mongodb%20inc. -- mongodb%20ops%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-20335</link>
      <description>
For MongoDB Ops Manager versions prior to and including 4.2.24 with multiple OM application servers, that have SSL turned on for their MongoDB processes, the upgrade to MongoDB Ops Manager versions prior to and including 4.4.12 triggers a bug where Automation thinks SSL is being turned off, and can disable SSL temporarily for members of the cluster. This issue is temporary and eventually corrects itself after MongoDB Ops Manager instances have finished upgrading to MongoDB Ops Manager 4.4. In addition, customers must be running with clientCertificateMode=OPTIONAL / allowConnectionsWithoutCertificates=true to be impacted*.* Customers upgrading from Ops Manager 4.2.X to 4.2.24 and finally to Ops Manager 4.4.13+ are unaffected by this issue.



</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-20335|2024-08-03T17:37:23.802Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-20330|2024-08-03T17:37:23.911Z -- mongodb%20inc. -- mongodb%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-20330</link>
      <description>An attacker with basic CRUD permissions on a replicated collection can run the applyOps command with specially malformed oplog entries, resulting in a potential denial of service on secondaries. This issue affects MongoDB Server v4.0 versions prior to 4.0.27; MongoDB Server v4.2 versions prior to 4.2.16; MongoDB Server v4.4 versions prior to 4.4.9.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-20330|2024-08-03T17:37:23.911Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
