<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for MongoDB Inc. -- MongoDB Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/mongodb%20inc./mongodb%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for MongoDB Inc. -- MongoDB Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 20:22:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-32040|2024-08-15T17:07:34.494Z -- mongodb%20inc. -- mongodb%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-32040</link>
      <description>It may be possible to have an extremely long aggregation pipeline in conjunction with a specific stage/operator and cause a stack overflow due to the size of the stack frames used by that stage. If an attacker could cause such an aggregation to occur, they could maliciously crash MongoDB in a DoS attack. This vulnerability affects MongoDB Server v4.4 versions prior to and including 4.4.28, MongoDB Server v5.0 versions prior to 5.0.4 and MongoDB Server v4.2 versions prior to 4.2.16.

Workaround: &gt;= v4.2.16 users and all v4.4 users can add the --setParameter internalPipelineLengthLimit=50 instead of the default 1000 to mongod at startup to prevent a crash.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-32040|2024-08-15T17:07:34.494Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-32037|2024-08-15T17:09:26.403Z -- mongodb%20inc. -- mongodb%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-32037</link>
      <description>An authorized user may trigger an invariant which may result in denial of service or server exit if a relevant aggregation request is sent to a shard. Usually, the requests are sent via mongos and special privileges are required in order to know the address of the shards and to log in to the shards of an auth enabled environment. This issue affects MongoDB Server v5.0 versions prior to and including 5.0.2.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-32037|2024-08-15T17:09:26.403Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-20330|2024-08-15T17:08:47.259Z -- mongodb%20inc. -- mongodb%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-20330</link>
      <description>An attacker with basic CRUD permissions on a replicated collection can run the applyOps command with specially malformed oplog entries, resulting in a potential denial of service on secondaries. This issue affects MongoDB Server v4.0 versions prior to 4.0.27; MongoDB Server v4.2 versions prior to 4.2.16; MongoDB Server v4.4 versions prior to 4.4.9.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-20330|2024-08-15T17:08:47.259Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-20923|2024-08-15T17:19:26.516Z -- mongodb%20inc. -- mongodb%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-20923</link>
      <description>A user authorized to perform database queries may trigger denial of service by issuing specially crafted queries, which throw unhandled Javascript exceptions containing types intended to be scoped to the Javascript engine's internals. This issue affects MongoDB Server v4.0 versions prior to 4.0.7.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-20923|2024-08-15T17:19:26.516Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7929|2024-08-15T17:22:54.094Z -- mongodb%20inc. -- mongodb%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7929</link>
      <description>A user authorized to perform database queries may trigger denial of service by issuing specially crafted query contain a type of regex. This issue affects MongoDB Server v3.6 versions prior to 3.6.21 and MongoDB Server v4.0 versions prior to 4.0.20.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7929|2024-08-15T17:22:54.094Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
