<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for MongoDB Inc. -- MongoDB Ops Manager</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/mongodb%20inc./mongodb%20ops%20manager.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for MongoDB Inc. -- MongoDB Ops Manager</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 08:24:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-20335|2024-09-17T01:50:44.645Z -- mongodb%20inc. -- mongodb%20ops%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-20335</link>
      <description>For MongoDB Ops Manager versions prior to and including 4.2.24 with multiple OM application servers, that have SSL turned on for their MongoDB processes, the upgrade to MongoDB Ops Manager versions prior to and including 4.4.12 triggers a bug where Automation thinks SSL is being turned off, and can disable SSL temporarily for members of the cluster. This issue is temporary and eventually corrects itself after MongoDB Ops Manager instances have finished upgrading to MongoDB Ops Manager 4.4. In addition, customers must be running with clientCertificateMode=OPTIONAL / allowConnectionsWithoutCertificates=true to be impacted*.* Customers upgrading from Ops Manager 4.2.X to 4.2.24 and finally to Ops Manager 4.4.13+ are unaffected by this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-20335|2024-09-17T01:50:44.645Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 10:10:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7927|2024-09-17T02:01:37.645Z -- mongodb%20inc. -- mongodb%20ops%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7927</link>
      <description>Specially crafted API calls may allow an authenticated user who holds Organization Owner privilege to obtain an API key with Global Role privilege. This issue affects MongoDB Ops Manager v4.2 versions prior to and including 4.2.17, MongoDB Ops Manager v4.3 versions prior to and including 4.3.9 and MongoDB Ops Manager v4.4 versions prior to and including 4.4.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7927|2024-09-17T02:01:37.645Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 19:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
