<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Trend Micro -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/trend%20micro/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Trend Micro -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 04:23:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23120|2024-08-03T03:36:19.169Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20deep%20security%20agent%20for%20linux
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23120</link>
      <description>A code injection vulnerability in Trend Micro Deep Security and Cloud One - Workload Security Agent for Linux version 20 and below could allow an attacker to escalate privileges and run arbitrary code in the context of root. Please note: an attacker must first obtain access to the target agent in an un-activated and unconfigured state in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23120|2024-08-03T03:36:19.169Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 18:11:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23805|2024-08-03T03:51:45.989Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20worry-free%20business%20security
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23805</link>
      <description>A security out-of-bounds read information disclosure vulnerability in Trend Micro Worry-Free Business Security Server could allow a local attacker to send garbage data to a specific named pipe and crash the server. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23805|2024-08-03T03:51:45.989Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 22:32:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23119|2024-08-03T03:36:19.202Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20deep%20security%20agent%20for%20linux
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23119</link>
      <description>A directory traversal vulnerability in Trend Micro Deep Security and Cloud One - Workload Security Agent for Linux version 20 and below could allow an attacker to read arbitrary files from the file system. Please note: an attacker must first obtain compromised access to the target Deep Security Manager (DSM) or the target agent must be not yet activated or configured in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23119|2024-08-03T03:36:19.202Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 18:11:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
