<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Trend Micro -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/trend%20micro/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Trend Micro -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:22:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-24564|2024-08-04T15:19:08.922Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-24564</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read information disclosure vulnerabilities in Trend Micro Apex One may allow a local attacker to disclose sensitive information to an unprivileged account on vulnerable installations of the product. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target in order to exploit these vulnerabilities. The subs affected in this vulnerability makes it unique compared to similar CVEs such as CVE-2020-24565 and CVE-2020-25770.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-24564|2024-08-04T15:19:08.922Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 23:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8468|2024-08-04T10:03:44.778Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20officescan%2C%20trend%20micro%20apex%20one%2C%20trend%20micro%20worry-free%20business%20security%20%28wfbs%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8468</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Apex One (2019), OfficeScan XG and Worry-Free Business Security (9.0, 9.5, 10.0) agents are affected by a content validation escape vulnerability which could allow an attacker to manipulate certain agent client components. An attempted attack requires user authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8468|2024-08-04T10:03:44.778Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 00:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27015|2024-08-04T16:03:23.262Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20antivirus%20for%20mac%20%28consumer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27015</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Antivirus for Mac 2020 (Consumer) contains an Error Message Information Disclosure vulnerability that if exploited, could allow kernel pointers and debug messages to leak to userland. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27015|2024-08-04T16:03:23.262Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 23:45:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-15602|2024-08-04T13:22:29.985Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20security%20%28consumer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-15602</link>
      <description>An untrusted search path remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in the Trend Micro Secuity 2020 (v16.0.0.1146 and below) consumer family of products could allow an attacker to run arbitrary code on a vulnerable system. As the Trend Micro installer tries to load DLL files from its current directory, an arbitrary DLL could also be loaded with the same privileges as the installer if run as Administrator. User interaction is required to exploit the vulnerbaility in that the target must open a malicious directory or device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-15602|2024-08-04T13:22:29.985Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 19:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-36744|2024-08-04T01:01:59.187Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20security%20%28consumer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-36744</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Security (Consumer) 2021 and 2020 are vulnerable to a directory junction vulnerability which could allow an attacker to exploit the system to escalate privileges and create a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-36744|2024-08-04T01:01:59.187Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2021 11:37:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-28574|2024-08-04T16:40:59.630Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20worry-free%20business%20security
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-28574</link>
      <description>A unauthenticated path traversal arbitrary remote file deletion vulnerability in Trend Micro Worry-Free Business Security 10 SP1 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to exploit the vulnerability and modify or delete arbitrary files on the product's management console.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-28574|2024-08-04T16:40:59.630Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 18:45:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-25778|2024-08-04T15:40:36.913Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20antivirus%20for%20mac%20%28consumer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-25778</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Antivirus for Mac 2020 (Consumer) has a vulnerability in a specific kernel extension where an attacker could supply a kernel pointer and leak several bytes of memory. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-25778|2024-08-04T15:40:36.913Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 15:10:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43771|2024-08-04T04:03:08.683Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20antivirus%20for%20mac%202021
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43771</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Antivirus for Mac 2021 v11 (Consumer) is vulnerable to an improper access control privilege escalation vulnerability that could allow an attacker to establish a connection that could lead to full local privilege escalation within the application. Please note that an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43771|2024-08-04T04:03:08.683Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 11:18:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-42102|2024-08-04T03:22:25.977Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42102</link>
      <description>An uncontrolled search path element vulnerabilities in Trend Micro Apex One and Apex One as a Service agents could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-42102|2024-08-04T03:22:25.977Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 07:46:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-25775|2024-08-04T15:40:36.947Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20security%20%28consumer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-25775</link>
      <description>The Trend Micro Security 2020 (v16) consumer family of products is vulnerable to a security race condition arbitrary file deletion vulnerability that could allow an unprivileged user to manipulate the product's secure erase feature to delete files with a higher set of privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-25775|2024-08-04T15:40:36.947Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 23:30:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-15601|2024-08-04T13:22:30.378Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20deep%20security
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-15601</link>
      <description>If LDAP authentication is enabled, an LDAP authentication bypass vulnerability in Trend Micro Deep Security 10.x-12.x could allow an unauthenticated attacker with prior knowledge of the targeted organization to bypass manager authentication. Enabling multi-factor authentication prevents this attack. Installations using manager native authentication or SAML authentication are not impacted by this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-15601|2024-08-04T13:22:30.378Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 20:35:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8605|2024-08-04T10:03:46.260Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20interscan%20web%20security%20virtual%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8605</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Trend Micro InterScan Web Security Virtual Appliance 6.5 may allow remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8605|2024-08-04T10:03:46.260Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 22:45:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-28581|2024-08-04T16:40:59.456Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20interscan%20web%20security%20virtual%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-28581</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability in ModifyVLANItem of Trend Micro InterScan Web Security Virtual Appliance 6.5 SP2 could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to send specially crafted HTTP messages and execute arbitrary OS commands with elevated privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-28581|2024-08-04T16:40:59.456Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 18:45:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8606|2024-08-04T10:03:46.240Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20interscan%20web%20security%20virtual%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8606</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Trend Micro InterScan Web Security Virtual Appliance 6.5 may allow remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of Trend Micro InterScan Web Security Virtual Appliance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8606|2024-08-04T10:03:46.240Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 22:45:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-25772|2024-08-04T15:40:36.981Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-25772</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read information disclosure vulnerabilities in Trend Micro Apex One may allow a local attacker to disclose sensitive information to an unprivileged account on vulnerable installations of the product. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target in order to exploit these vulnerabilities. The subs affected in this vulnerability makes it unique compared to similar CVEs such as CVE-2020-24564 and CVE-2020-25771.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-25772|2024-08-04T15:40:36.981Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 23:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-28583|2024-08-04T16:40:59.251Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-28583</link>
      <description>An improper access control information disclosure vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One and OfficeScan XG SP1 could allow an unauthenticated user to connect to the product server and reveal version, build and patch information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-28583|2024-08-04T16:40:59.251Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 18:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-44021|2024-08-04T04:10:17.287Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20worry-free%20business%20security
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-44021</link>
      <description>An unnecessary privilege vulnerability in Trend Micro Worry-Free Business Security 10.0 SP1 could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability is similar to but not identical to CVE-2021-44019 and 44020.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-44021|2024-08-04T04:10:17.287Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 10:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-15604|2024-08-04T13:22:30.611Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20security%20%28consumer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-15604</link>
      <description>An incomplete SSL server certification validation vulnerability in the Trend Micro Security 2019 (v15) consumer family of products could allow an attacker to combine this vulnerability with another attack to trick an affected client into downloading a malicious update instead of the expected one. CWE-494: Update files are not properly verified.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-15604|2024-08-04T13:22:30.611Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 01:50:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27697|2024-08-04T16:18:45.678Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20security%20%28consumer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27697</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Security 2020 (Consumer) contains a vulnerability in the installer package that could be exploited by placing a malicious DLL in a non-protected location with high privileges (symlink attack) which can lead to obtaining administrative privileges during the installation of the product.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27697|2024-08-04T16:18:45.678Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 18:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-24558|2024-08-04T15:19:07.400Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-24558</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in an Trend Micro Apex One, Worry-Free Business Security 10.0 SP1 and Worry-Free Business Security Services dll may allow an attacker to manipulate it to cause an out-of-bounds read that crashes multiple processes in the product. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-24558|2024-08-04T15:19:07.400Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 18:55:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-25773|2024-08-04T15:40:36.970Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-25773</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One ServerMigrationTool component could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code on affected products. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must import a corrupted configuration file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-25773|2024-08-04T15:40:36.970Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 23:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27013|2024-08-04T16:03:23.260Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20antivirus%20for%20mac%20%28consumer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27013</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Antivirus for Mac 2020 (Consumer) contains a vulnerability in the product that occurs when a webserver is started that implements an API with several properties that can be read and written to allowing the attacker to gather and modify sensitive product and user data. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27013|2024-08-04T16:03:23.260Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 15:10:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-25770|2024-08-04T15:40:36.949Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-25770</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read information disclosure vulnerabilities in Trend Micro Apex One may allow a local attacker to disclose sensitive information to an unprivileged account on vulnerable installations of the product. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target in order to exploit these vulnerabilities. The subs affected in this vulnerability makes it unique compared to similar CVEs such as CVE-2020-24564 and CVE-2020-25771.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-25770|2024-08-04T15:40:36.949Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 23:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27019|2024-08-04T16:03:23.230Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20interscan%20messaging%20security%20virtual%20appliance%20%28imsva%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27019</link>
      <description>Trend Micro InterScan Messaging Security Virtual Appliance (IMSVA) 9.1 is vulnerable to an information disclosure vulnerability which could allow an attacker to access a specific database and key.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27019|2024-08-04T16:03:23.230Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 23:10:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-42012|2024-08-04T03:22:25.638Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42012</link>
      <description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One, Apex One as a Service and Worry-Free Business Security 10.0 SP1 could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-42012|2024-08-04T03:22:25.638Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 07:46:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-24560|2024-08-04T15:19:07.405Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20security%20%28consumer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-24560</link>
      <description>An incomplete SSL server certification validation vulnerability in the Trend Micro Security 2019 (v15) consumer family of products could allow an attacker to combine this vulnerability with another attack to trick an affected client into downloading a malicious update instead of the expected one. CWE-295: Improper server certificate verification in the communication with the update server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-24560|2024-08-04T15:19:07.405Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 01:50:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-28576|2024-08-04T16:40:59.867Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-28576</link>
      <description>An improper access control information disclosure vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One and OfficeScan XG SP1 could allow an unauthenticated user to connect to the product server and reveal version and build information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-28576|2024-08-04T16:40:59.867Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 18:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-28577|2024-08-04T16:40:59.382Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-28577</link>
      <description>An improper access control information disclosure vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One and OfficeScan XG SP1 could allow an unauthenticated user to connect to the product server and reveal server hostname and db names.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-28577|2024-08-04T16:40:59.382Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 18:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-36745|2024-08-04T01:01:59.288Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20serverprotect%20for%20storage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-36745</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Trend Micro ServerProtect for Storage 6.0, ServerProtect for EMC Celerra 5.8, ServerProtect for Network Appliance Filers 5.8, and ServerProtect for Microsoft Windows / Novell Netware 5.8 could allow a remote attacker to bypass authentication on affected installations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-36745|2024-08-04T01:01:59.288Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 10:21:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27018|2024-08-04T16:03:23.265Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20interscan%20messaging%20security%20virtual%20appliance%20%28imsva%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27018</link>
      <description>Trend Micro InterScan Messaging Security Virtual Appliance (IMSVA) 9.1 is vulnerable to a server side request forgery vulnerability which could allow an authenticated attacker to abuse the product's web server and grant access to web resources or parts of local files. An attacker must already have obtained authenticated privileges on the product to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27018|2024-08-04T16:03:23.265Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 23:10:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-24562|2024-08-04T15:19:07.370Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20officescan
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-24562</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Trend Micro OfficeScan XG SP1 on Microsoft Windows may allow an attacker to create a hard link to any file on the system, which then could be manipulated to gain a privilege escalation and code execution. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. This CVE is similar, but not identical to CVE-2020-24556.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-24562|2024-08-04T15:19:07.370Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 23:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-24561|2024-08-04T15:19:07.396Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20serverprotect%20for%20linux
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-24561</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability in Trend Micro ServerProtect for Linux 3.0 could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code on an affected system. An attacker must first obtain admin/root privileges on the SPLX console to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-24561|2024-08-04T15:19:07.396Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 20:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-42108|2024-08-04T03:22:25.952Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42108</link>
      <description>Unnecessary privilege vulnerabilities in the Web Console of Trend Micro Apex One, Apex One as a Service and Worry-Free Business Security 10.0 SP1 could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-42108|2024-08-04T03:22:25.952Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 07:46:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8467|2024-08-04T10:03:44.669Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20officescan%2C%20trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8467</link>
      <description>A migration tool component of Trend Micro Apex One (2019) and OfficeScan XG contains a vulnerability which could allow remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations (RCE). An attempted attack requires user authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8467|2024-08-04T10:03:44.669Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 00:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-15603|2024-08-04T13:22:30.145Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20security%20%28consumer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-15603</link>
      <description>An invalid memory read vulnerability in a Trend Micro Secuity 2020 (v16.0.0.1302 and below) consumer family of products' driver could allow an attacker to manipulate the specific driver to do a system call operation with an invalid address, resulting in a potential system crash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-15603|2024-08-04T13:22:30.145Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 19:15:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-42107|2024-08-04T03:22:25.899Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42107</link>
      <description>Unnecessary privilege vulnerabilities in Trend Micro Apex One, Apex One as a Service, Worry-Free Business Security 10.0 SP1 and Worry-Free Business Security Services could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability is similar to but not identical to CVE-2021-42104, 42105 and 42106.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-42107|2024-08-04T03:22:25.899Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 07:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8601|2024-08-04T10:03:46.282Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20vulnerability%20protection
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8601</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Vulnerability Protection 2.0 is affected by a vulnerability that could allow an attack to use the product installer to load other DLL files located in the same directory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8601|2024-08-04T10:03:46.282Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 22:50:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8464|2024-08-04T10:03:44.846Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20interscan%20web%20security%20virtual%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8464</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Trend Micro InterScan Web Security Virtual Appliance 6.5 SP2 could allow an attacker to send requests that appear to come from the localhost which could expose the product's admin interface to users who would not normally have access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8464|2024-08-04T10:03:44.846Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 21:05:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8603|2024-08-04T10:03:46.332Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20interscan%20web%20security%20virtual%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8603</link>
      <description>A cross-site scripting vulnerability (XSS) in Trend Micro InterScan Web Security Virtual Appliance 6.5 may allow a remote attacker to tamper with the web interface of affected installations. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8603|2024-08-04T10:03:46.332Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 22:45:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-44019|2024-08-04T04:10:17.188Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20worry-free%20business%20security
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-44019</link>
      <description>An unnecessary privilege vulnerability in Trend Micro Worry-Free Business Security 10.0 SP1 could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability is similar to but not identical to CVE-2021-44020 and 44021.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-44019|2024-08-04T04:10:17.188Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 10:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-42101|2024-08-04T03:22:25.786Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42101</link>
      <description>An uncontrolled search path element vulnerabilities in Trend Micro Apex One and Apex One as a Service could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability is similar but not identical to CVE-2021-42103.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-42101|2024-08-04T03:22:25.786Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 07:46:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8470|2024-08-04T10:03:44.846Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20officescan%2C%20trend%20micro%20apex%20one%2C%20trend%20micro%20worry-free%20business%20security%20%28wfbs%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8470</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Apex One (2019), OfficeScan XG and Worry-Free Business Security (9.0, 9.5, 10.0) server contains a vulnerable service DLL file that could allow an attacker to delete any file on the server with SYSTEM level privileges. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8470|2024-08-04T10:03:44.846Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 00:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-45442|2024-08-04T04:39:20.981Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20worry-free%20business%20security
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-45442</link>
      <description>A link following denial-of-service vulnerability in Trend Micro Worry-Free Business Security (on prem only) could allow a local attacker to overwrite arbitrary files in the context of SYSTEM. This is similar to, but not the same as CVE-2021-44024. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-45442|2024-08-04T04:39:20.981Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 15:51:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-42103|2024-08-04T03:22:25.872Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42103</link>
      <description>An uncontrolled search path element vulnerabilities in Trend Micro Apex One and Apex One as a Service could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability is similar but not identical to CVE-2021-42101.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-42103|2024-08-04T03:22:25.872Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 07:46:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-9489|2024-08-04T21:54:44.231Z -- trend%20micro -- apex%20one%2C%20officescan%2C%20worry-free%20business%20security
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-9489</link>
      <description>A directory traversal vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One, OfficeScan (versions XG and 11.0), and Worry-Free Business Security (versions 10.0, 9.5 and 9.0) could allow an attacker to modify arbitrary files on the affected product's management console.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-9489|2024-08-04T21:54:44.231Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 22:46:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8598|2024-08-04T10:03:45.801Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20officescan%2C%20trend%20micro%20apex%20one%2C%20trend%20micro%20worry-free%20business%20security%20%28wfbs%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8598</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Apex One (2019), OfficeScan XG and Worry-Free Business Security (9.0, 9.5, 10.0) server contains a vulnerable service DLL file that could allow a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code on affected installations with SYSTEM level privileges. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8598|2024-08-04T10:03:45.801Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 00:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-45441|2024-08-04T04:39:20.691Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-45441</link>
      <description>A origin validation error vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One (on-prem and SaaS) could allow a local attacker drop and manipulate a specially crafted file to issue commands over a certain pipe and elevate to a higher level of privileges. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-45441|2024-08-04T04:39:20.691Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 15:51:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-9491|2024-08-04T21:54:44.137Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20anti-threat%20toolkit%20%28attk%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-9491</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Anti-Threat Toolkit (ATTK) versions 1.62.0.1218 and below have a vulnerability that may allow an attacker to place malicious files in the same directory, potentially leading to arbitrary remote code execution (RCE) when executed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-9491|2024-08-04T21:54:44.137Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 18:35:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-25771|2024-08-04T15:40:36.947Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-25771</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read information disclosure vulnerabilities in Trend Micro Apex One may allow a local attacker to disclose sensitive information to an unprivileged account on vulnerable installations of the product. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target in order to exploit these vulnerabilities. The subs affected in this vulnerability makes it unique compared to similar CVEs such as CVE-2020-24564 and CVE-2020-25770.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-25771|2024-08-04T15:40:36.947Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 23:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-9488|2024-08-04T21:54:44.150Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20deep%20security
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-9488</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Deep Security Manager (10.x, 11.x) and Vulnerability Protection (2.0) are vulnerable to a XML External Entity Attack. However, for the attack to be possible, the attacker must have root/admin access to a protected host which is authorized to communicate with the Deep Security Manager (DSM).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-9488|2024-08-04T21:54:44.150Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 18:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-36741|2024-08-04T01:01:59.373Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-36741</link>
      <description>An improper input validation vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One, Apex One as a Service, OfficeScan XG, and Worry-Free Business Security 10.0 SP1 allows a remote attached to upload arbitrary files on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to logon to the product�s management console in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-36741|2024-08-04T01:01:59.373Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 19:23:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8600|2024-08-04T10:03:46.241Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20worry-free%20business%20security%20%28wfbs%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8600</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Worry-Free Business Security (9.0, 9.5, 10.0) is affected by a directory traversal vulnerability that could allow an attacker to manipulate a key file to bypass authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8600|2024-08-04T10:03:46.241Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 00:30:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8466|2024-08-04T10:03:44.800Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20interscan%20web%20security%20virtual%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8466</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability in Trend Micro InterScan Web Security Virtual Appliance 6.5 SP2, with the improved password hashing method enabled, could allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute certain commands by providing a manipulated password.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8466|2024-08-04T10:03:44.800Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 21:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-24565|2024-08-04T15:19:07.757Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-24565</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read information disclosure vulnerabilities in Trend Micro Apex One may allow a local attacker to disclose sensitive information to an unprivileged account on vulnerable installations of the product. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target in order to exploit these vulnerabilities. The subs affected in this vulnerability makes it unique compared to similar CVEs such as CVE-2020-24564 and CVE-2020-25770.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-24565|2024-08-04T15:19:07.757Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 23:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-28578|2024-08-04T16:40:59.453Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20interscan%20web%20security%20virtual%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-28578</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Trend Micro InterScan Web Security Virtual Appliance 6.5 SP2 could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to send a specially crafted HTTP message and achieve remote code execution with elevated privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-28578|2024-08-04T16:40:59.453Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 18:45:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-25779|2024-08-04T15:40:36.956Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20antivirus%20for%20mac%20%28consumer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-25779</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Antivirus for Mac 2020 (Consumer) has a vulnerability in which a Internationalized Domain Name homograph attack (Puny-code) could be used to add a malicious website to the approved websites list of Trend Micro Antivirus for Mac to bypass the web threat protection feature.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-25779|2024-08-04T15:40:36.956Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-9492|2024-08-04T21:54:44.041Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20officescan
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-9492</link>
      <description>A DLL side-loading vulnerability in Trend Micro OfficeScan 11.0 SP1 and XG could allow an authenticated attacker to gain code execution and terminate the product's process - disabling endpoint protection. The attacker must have already gained authentication and have local access to the vulnerable system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-9492|2024-08-04T21:54:44.041Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 13:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-24563|2024-08-04T15:19:07.401Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-24563</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One may allow a local attacker to manipulate the process of the security agent unload option (if configured), which then could be manipulated to gain a privilege escalation and code execution. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-24563|2024-08-04T15:19:07.401Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 23:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27016|2024-08-04T16:03:23.191Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20interscan%20messaging%20security%20virtual%20appliance%20%28imsva%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27016</link>
      <description>Trend Micro InterScan Messaging Security Virtual Appliance (IMSVA) 9.1 is vulnerable to a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability which could allow an attacker to modify policy rules by tricking an authenticated administrator into accessing an attacker-controlled web page. An attacker must already have obtained product administrator/root privileges to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27016|2024-08-04T16:03:23.191Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 23:10:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27693|2024-08-04T16:18:45.678Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20interscan%20messaging%20security%20virtual%20appliance%20%28imsva%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27693</link>
      <description>Trend Micro InterScan Messaging Security Virtual Appliance (IMSVA) 9.1 stores administrative passwords using a hash that is considered outdated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27693|2024-08-04T16:18:45.678Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 23:10:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-42104|2024-08-04T03:22:25.988Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42104</link>
      <description>Unnecessary privilege vulnerabilities in Trend Micro Apex One, Apex One as a Service, Worry-Free Business Security 10.0 SP1 and Worry-Free Business Security Services could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability is similar to but not identical to CVE-2021-42105, 42106 and 42107.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-42104|2024-08-04T03:22:25.988Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 07:46:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-42105|2024-08-04T03:22:25.842Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42105</link>
      <description>Unnecessary privilege vulnerabilities in Trend Micro Apex One, Apex One as a Service, Worry-Free Business Security 10.0 SP1 and Worry-Free Business Security Services could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability is similar to but not identical to CVE-2021-42104, 42106 and 42107.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-42105|2024-08-04T03:22:25.842Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 07:46:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-28582|2024-08-04T16:40:59.354Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-28582</link>
      <description>An improper access control information disclosure vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One and OfficeScan XG SP1 could allow an unauthenticated user to connect to the product server and reveal number of managed agents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-28582|2024-08-04T16:40:59.354Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 18:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-25774|2024-08-04T15:40:36.979Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-25774</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One ServerMigrationTool component could allow an attacker to trigger an out-of-bounds red information disclosure which would disclose sensitive information to an unprivileged account. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-25774|2024-08-04T15:40:36.979Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 23:30:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8465|2024-08-04T10:03:44.874Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20interscan%20web%20security%20virtual%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8465</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Trend Micro InterScan Web Security Virtual Appliance 6.5 SP2 could allow an attacker to manipulate system updates using a combination of CSRF bypass (CVE-2020-8461) and authentication bypass (CVE-2020-8464) to execute code as user root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8465|2024-08-04T10:03:44.874Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 21:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27696|2024-08-04T16:18:45.580Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20security%20%28consumer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27696</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Security 2020 (Consumer) contains a vulnerability in the installer package that could be exploited by placing a specific Windows system directory which can lead to obtaining administrative privileges during the installation of the product.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27696|2024-08-04T16:18:45.580Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 18:45:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-24557|2024-08-04T15:19:07.575Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-24557</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One and Worry-Free Business Security 10.0 SP1 on Microsoft Windows may allow an attacker to manipulate a particular product folder to disable the security temporarily, abuse a specific Windows function and attain privilege escalation. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. Please note that version 1909 (OS Build 18363.719) of Microsoft Windows 10 mitigates hard links, but previous versions are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-24557|2024-08-04T15:19:07.575Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 18:55:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43772|2024-08-04T04:03:08.811Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20security%202021%20%28consumer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43772</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Security 2021 v17.0 (Consumer) contains a vulnerability that allows files inside the protected folder to be modified without any detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43772|2024-08-04T04:03:08.811Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 10:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-28579|2024-08-04T16:40:59.158Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20interscan%20web%20security%20virtual%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-28579</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Trend Micro InterScan Web Security Virtual Appliance 6.5 SP2 could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to send a specially crafted HTTP message and achieve remote code execution with elevated privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-28579|2024-08-04T16:40:59.158Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 18:45:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27694|2024-08-04T16:18:45.774Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20interscan%20messaging%20security%20virtual%20appliance%20%28imsva%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27694</link>
      <description>Trend Micro InterScan Messaging Security Virtual Appliance (IMSVA) 9.1 has updated a specific critical library that may vulnerable to attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27694|2024-08-04T16:18:45.774Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 23:10:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8463|2024-08-04T10:03:44.801Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20interscan%20web%20security%20virtual%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8463</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Trend Micro InterScan Web Security Virtual Appliance 6.5 SP2 could allow an attacker to bypass a global authorization check for anonymous users by manipulating request paths.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8463|2024-08-04T10:03:44.801Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 21:05:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-44020|2024-08-04T04:10:17.310Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20worry-free%20business%20security
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-44020</link>
      <description>An unnecessary privilege vulnerability in Trend Micro Worry-Free Business Security 10.0 SP1 could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability is similar to but not identical to CVE-2021-44019 and 44021.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-44020|2024-08-04T04:10:17.310Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 10:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27695|2024-08-04T16:18:45.580Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20security%20%28consumer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27695</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Security 2020 (Consumer) contains a vulnerability in the installer package that could be exploited by placing a malicious DLL in a local directory which can lead to obtaining administrative privileges during the installation of the product.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27695|2024-08-04T16:18:45.580Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 18:45:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-42011|2024-08-04T03:22:25.709Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42011</link>
      <description>An incorrect permission assignment vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One and Apex One as a Service could allow a local attacker to load a DLL with escalated privileges on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-42011|2024-08-04T03:22:25.709Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 07:46:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-28572|2024-08-04T16:40:59.599Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-28572</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One could allow an unprivileged user to abuse the product installer to reinstall the agent with additional malicious code in the context of a higher privilege.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-28572|2024-08-04T16:40:59.599Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 18:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-44022|2024-08-04T04:10:17.161Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-44022</link>
      <description>A reachable assertion vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One could allow an attacker to crash the program on affected installations, leading to a denial-of-service (DoS). Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-44022|2024-08-04T04:10:17.161Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 10:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8599|2024-08-04T10:03:46.134Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20officescan%2C%20trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8599</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Apex One (2019) and OfficeScan XG server contain a vulnerable EXE file that could allow a remote attacker to write arbitrary data to an arbitrary path on affected installations and bypass ROOT login. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8599|2024-08-04T10:03:46.134Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 00:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-44023|2024-08-04T04:10:17.277Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20security%20%28consumer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-44023</link>
      <description>A link following denial-of-service (DoS) vulnerability in the Trend Micro Security (Consumer) 2021 familiy of products could allow an attacker to abuse the PC Health Checkup feature of the product to create symlinks that would allow modification of files which could lead to a denial-of-service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-44023|2024-08-04T04:10:17.277Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 02:28:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27010|2024-08-04T16:03:23.183Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20interscan%20web%20security%20virtual%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27010</link>
      <description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Trend Micro InterScan Web Security Virtual Appliance 6.5 SP2 could allow an attacker to tamper with the web interface of the product in a manner separate from the similar CVE-2020-8462.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27010|2024-08-04T16:03:23.183Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 21:05:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-9490|2024-08-04T21:54:44.101Z -- trend%20micro -- interscan%20web%20security%20virtual%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-9490</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Trend Micro InterScan Web Security Virtual Appliance version 6.5 SP2 could allow an non-authorized user to disclose administrative credentials. An attacker must be an authenticated user in order to exploit the vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-9490|2024-08-04T21:54:44.101Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 22:46:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-44024|2024-08-04T04:10:17.189Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-44024</link>
      <description>A link following denial-of-service vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One (on-prem and SaaS) and Trend Micro Worry-Free Business Security (10.0 SP1 and Services) could allow a local attacker to overwrite arbitrary files in the context of SYSTEM. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-44024|2024-08-04T04:10:17.189Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 15:51:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27014|2024-08-04T16:03:23.197Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20antivirus%20for%20mac%20%28consumer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27014</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Antivirus for Mac 2020 (Consumer) contains a race condition vulnerability in the Web Threat Protection Blocklist component, that if exploited, could allow an attacker to case a kernel panic or crash.\n\n\r\nAn attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27014|2024-08-04T16:03:23.197Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 23:45:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-28575|2024-08-04T16:40:58.911Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20serverprotect%20for%20linux
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-28575</link>
      <description>A heap-based buffer overflow privilege escalation vulnerability in Trend Micro ServerProtect for Linux 3.0 may allow an attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-28575|2024-08-04T16:40:58.911Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 18:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-42106|2024-08-04T03:22:25.939Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42106</link>
      <description>Unnecessary privilege vulnerabilities in Trend Micro Apex One, Apex One as a Service, Worry-Free Business Security 10.0 SP1 and Worry-Free Business Security Services could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability is similar to but not identical to CVE-2021-42104, 42105 and 42107.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-42106|2024-08-04T03:22:25.939Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 07:46:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-28580|2024-08-04T16:40:59.935Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20interscan%20web%20security%20virtual%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-28580</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability in AddVLANItem of Trend Micro InterScan Web Security Virtual Appliance 6.5 SP2 could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to send specially crafted HTTP messages and execute arbitrary OS commands with elevated privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-28580|2024-08-04T16:40:59.935Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 18:45:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-45231|2024-08-04T04:39:20.384Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-45231</link>
      <description>A link following privilege escalation vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One (on-prem and SaaS) and Trend Micro Worry-Free Business Security (10.0 SP1 and Services) could allow a local attacker to create a specially crafted file with arbitrary content which could grant local privilege escalation on the affected system. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-45231|2024-08-04T04:39:20.384Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 15:51:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-28573|2024-08-04T16:40:59.551Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-28573</link>
      <description>An improper access control information disclosure vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One and OfficeScan XG SP1 could allow an unauthenticated user to connect to the product server and reveal the total agents managed by the server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-28573|2024-08-04T16:40:59.551Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 18:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8607|2024-08-04T10:03:46.363Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8607</link>
      <description>An input validation vulnerability found in multiple Trend Micro products utilizing a particular version of a specific rootkit protection driver could allow an attacker in user-mode with administrator permissions to abuse the driver to modify a kernel address that may cause a system crash or potentially lead to code execution in kernel mode. An attacker must already have obtained administrator access on the target machine (either legitimately or via a separate unrelated attack) to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8607|2024-08-04T10:03:46.363Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 14:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-36742|2024-08-04T01:01:59.398Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-36742</link>
      <description>A improper input validation vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One, Apex One as a Service, OfficeScan XG and Worry-Free Business Security 10.0 SP1 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-36742|2024-08-04T01:01:59.398Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 19:23:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-25777|2024-08-04T15:40:36.936Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20antivirus%20for%20mac%20%28consumer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-25777</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Antivirus for Mac 2020 (Consumer) is vulnerable to a specific kernel extension request attack where an attacker could bypass the Web Threat Protection feature of the product. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-25777|2024-08-04T15:40:36.936Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 15:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-15605|2024-08-04T13:22:30.177Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20vulnerability%20protection
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-15605</link>
      <description>If LDAP authentication is enabled, an LDAP authentication bypass vulnerability in Trend Micro Vulnerability Protection 2.0 SP2 could allow an unauthenticated attacker with prior knowledge of the targeted organization to bypass manager authentication. Enabling multi-factor authentication prevents this attack. Installations using manager native authentication or SAML authentication are not impacted by this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-15605|2024-08-04T13:22:30.177Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 20:35:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8462|2024-08-04T10:03:44.665Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20interscan%20web%20security%20virtual%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8462</link>
      <description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Trend Micro InterScan Web Security Virtual Appliance 6.5 SP2 could allow an attacker to tamper with the web interface of the product.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8462|2024-08-04T10:03:44.665Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 21:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8469|2024-08-04T10:03:45.524Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20password%20manager%20for%20windows
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8469</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Password Manager for Windows version 5.0 is affected by a DLL hijacking vulnerability would could potentially allow an attacker privleged escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8469|2024-08-04T10:03:45.524Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 23:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-24559|2024-08-04T15:19:07.401Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-24559</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One, Worry-Free Business Security 10.0 SP1 and Worry-Free Business Security Services on macOS may allow an attacker to manipulate a certain binary to load and run a script from a user-writable folder, which then would allow them to execute arbitrary code as root. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-24559|2024-08-04T15:19:07.401Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 18:55:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27017|2024-08-04T16:03:23.261Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20interscan%20messaging%20security%20virtual%20appliance%20%28imsva%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27017</link>
      <description>Trend Micro InterScan Messaging Security Virtual Appliance (IMSVA) 9.1 is vulnerable to an XML External Entity Processing (XXE) vulnerability which could allow an authenticated administrator to read arbitrary local files. An attacker must already have obtained product administrator/root privileges to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27017|2024-08-04T16:03:23.261Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 23:10:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8604|2024-08-04T10:03:46.361Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20interscan%20web%20security%20virtual%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8604</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Trend Micro InterScan Web Security Virtual Appliance 6.5 may allow remote attackers to disclose sensitive informatoin on affected installations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8604|2024-08-04T10:03:46.361Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 22:45:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8602|2024-08-04T10:03:46.269Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20deep%20security
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8602</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the management consoles of Trend Micro Deep Security 10.0-12.0 and Trend Micro Vulnerability Protection 2.0 SP2 may allow an authenticated attacker with full control privileges to bypass file integrity checks, leading to remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8602|2024-08-04T10:03:46.269Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 20:35:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-25776|2024-08-04T15:40:36.983Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20antivirus%20for%20mac%20%28consumer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-25776</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Antivirus for Mac 2020 (Consumer) is vulnerable to a symbolic link privilege escalation attack where an attacker could exploit a critical file on the system to escalate their privileges. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-25776|2024-08-04T15:40:36.983Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 22:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-24556|2024-08-04T15:12:09.086Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-24556</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One, OfficeScan XG SP1, Worry-Free Business Security 10 SP1 and Worry-Free Business Security Services on Microsoft Windows may allow an attacker to create a hard link to any file on the system, which then could be manipulated to gain a privilege escalation and code execution. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. Please note that version 1909 (OS Build 18363.719) of Microsoft Windows 10 mitigates hard links, but previous versions are affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-24556|2024-08-04T15:12:09.086Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 18:55:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-45440|2024-08-04T04:39:20.966Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-45440</link>
      <description>A unnecessary privilege vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One and Trend Micro Worry-Free Business Security 10.0 SP1 (on-prem versions only) could allow a local attacker to abuse an impersonation privilege and elevate to a higher level of privileges. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-45440|2024-08-04T04:39:20.966Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 15:51:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8461|2024-08-04T10:03:44.691Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20interscan%20web%20security%20virtual%20appliance
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8461</link>
      <description>A CSRF protection bypass vulnerability in Trend Micro InterScan Web Security Virtual Appliance 6.5 SP2 could allow an attacker to get a victim's browser to send a specifically encoded request without requiring a valid CSRF token.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8461|2024-08-04T10:03:44.691Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 21:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
