<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Trend Micro -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/trend%20micro/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Trend Micro -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 17:21:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41749|2024-08-03T12:49:43.934Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41749</link>
      <description>An origin validation error vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One agents could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41749|2024-08-03T12:49:43.934Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40144|2024-08-03T12:14:39.823Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40144</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One and Trend Micro Apex One as a Service could allow an attacker to bypass the product's login authentication by falsifying request parameters on affected installations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40144|2024-08-03T12:14:39.823Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40139|2024-08-03T12:14:39.635Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40139</link>
      <description>Improper validation of some components used by the rollback mechanism in Trend Micro Apex One and Trend Micro Apex One as a Service clients could allow a Apex One server administrator to instruct affected clients to download an unverified rollback package, which could lead to remote code execution. Please note: an attacker must first obtain Apex One server administration console access in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40139|2024-08-03T12:14:39.635Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 18:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41744|2024-08-03T12:49:43.722Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41744</link>
      <description>A Time-of-Check Time-Of-Use vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One Vulnerability Protection integrated component could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges and turn a specific working directory into a mount point on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41744|2024-08-03T12:49:43.722Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-33158|2024-08-03T08:01:19.490Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20vpn%20proxy%20one%20pro%20%28consumer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-33158</link>
      <description>Trend Micro VPN Proxy Pro version 5.2.1026 and below contains a vulnerability involving some overly permissive folders in a key directory which could allow a local attacker to obtain privilege escalation on an affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-33158|2024-08-03T08:01:19.490Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 23:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41747|2024-08-03T12:49:43.590Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41747</link>
      <description>An improper certification validation vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One agents could allow a local attacker to load a DLL file with system service privileges on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41747|2024-08-03T12:49:43.590Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-37348|2024-08-03T10:29:20.699Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20security%20%28consumer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-37348</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Security 2021 and 2022 (Consumer) is vulnerable to an Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability that could allow an attacker to read sensitive information from other memory locations and cause a crash on an affected machine. This vulnerability is similar to, but not the same as CVE-2022-37347.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-37348|2024-08-03T10:29:20.699Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 18:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30687|2024-08-03T06:56:13.447Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20maximum%20security
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30687</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Maximum Security 2022 is vulnerable to a link following vulnerability that could allow a low privileged local user to manipulate the product's secure erase feature to delete arbitrary files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30687|2024-08-03T06:56:13.447Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 23:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30703|2024-08-03T06:56:13.820Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20security%20%28consumer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30703</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Security 2021 and 2022 (Consumer) is vulnerable to an exposed dangerous method vulnerability that could allow an attacker to obtain access to leaked kernel addresses and disclose sensitive information. This vulnerability could also potentially be chained for privilege escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30703|2024-08-03T06:56:13.820Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 20:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36336|2024-08-03T10:00:04.319Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36336</link>
      <description>A link following vulnerability in the scanning function of Trend Micro Apex One and Worry-Free Business Security agents could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations. The resolution for this issue has been deployed automatically via ActiveUpdate to customers in an updated Spyware pattern. Customers who are up-to-date on detection patterns are not required to take any additional steps to mitigate this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36336|2024-08-03T10:00:04.319Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 23:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-27883|2024-08-03T05:41:10.659Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20antivirus%20for%20mac
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27883</link>
      <description>A link following vulnerability in Trend Micro Antivirus for Mac 11.5 could allow an attacker to create a specially-crafted file as a symlink that can lead to privilege escalation. Please note that an attacker must at least have low-level privileges on the system to attempt to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-27883|2024-08-03T05:41:10.659Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 00:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40707|2024-08-03T12:21:46.562Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20deep%20security
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40707</link>
      <description>An Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in Trend Micro Deep Security 20 and Cloud One - Workload Security Agent for Windows could allow a local attacker to disclose sensitive information on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit these vulnerabilities. This vulnerability is similar to, but not identical to CVE-2022-40708.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40707|2024-08-03T12:21:46.562Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 21:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41745|2024-08-03T12:49:43.818Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41745</link>
      <description>An Out-of-Bounds access vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One could allow a local attacker to create a specially crafted message to cause memory corruption on a certain service process which could lead to local privilege escalation on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41745|2024-08-03T12:49:43.818Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30702|2024-08-03T06:56:13.714Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20security%20%28consumer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30702</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Security 2022 and 2021 (Consumer) is vulnerable to an Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure vulnerability that could allow an attacker to disclose sensitive information on an affected machine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30702|2024-08-03T06:56:13.714Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 20:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30701|2024-08-03T06:56:13.781Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30701</link>
      <description>An uncontrolled search path element vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One and Apex One as a Service could allow a local attacker to craft a special configuration file to load an untrusted library with escalated privileges on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30701|2024-08-03T06:56:13.781Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 23:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24680|2024-08-03T04:20:49.145Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24680</link>
      <description>A security link following local privilege escalation vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One, Trend Micro Apex One as a Service, Trend Micro Worry-Free Business Security 10.0 SP1 and Trend Micro Worry-Free Business Security Services agents could allow a local attacker to create a mount point and leverage this for arbitrary folder deletion, leading to escalated privileges on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24680|2024-08-03T04:20:49.145Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 02:45:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-25331|2024-08-03T04:36:06.923Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20serverprotect%20for%20storage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-25331</link>
      <description>Uncaught exceptions that can be generated in Trend Micro ServerProtection 6.0/5.8 Information Server could allow a remote attacker to crash the process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-25331|2024-08-03T04:36:06.923Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 02:45:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26337|2024-08-03T05:03:32.878Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20password%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26337</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Password Manager (Consumer) installer version 5.0.0.1262 and below is vulnerable to an Uncontrolled Search Path Element vulnerability that could allow an attacker to use a specially crafted file to exploit the vulnerability and escalate local privileges on the affected machine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26337|2024-08-03T05:03:32.878Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 21:55:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23120|2024-08-03T03:36:19.169Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20deep%20security%20agent%20for%20linux
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23120</link>
      <description>A code injection vulnerability in Trend Micro Deep Security and Cloud One - Workload Security Agent for Linux version 20 and below could allow an attacker to escalate privileges and run arbitrary code in the context of root. Please note: an attacker must first obtain access to the target agent in an un-activated and unconfigured state in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23120|2024-08-03T03:36:19.169Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 18:11:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40709|2024-08-03T12:21:46.453Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20deep%20security
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40709</link>
      <description>An Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in Trend Micro Deep Security 20 and Cloud One - Workload Security Agent for Windows could allow a local attacker to disclose sensitive information on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit these vulnerabilities. This vulnerability is similar to, but not identical to CVE-2022-40707 and 40708.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40709|2024-08-03T12:21:46.453Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 21:10:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24671|2024-08-03T04:20:49.102Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20antivirus%20for%20mac
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24671</link>
      <description>A link following privilege escalation vulnerability in Trend Micro Antivirus for Max 11.0.2150 and below could allow a local attacker to modify a file during the update process and escalate their privileges. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24671|2024-08-03T04:20:49.102Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 02:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24679|2024-08-03T04:20:50.339Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24679</link>
      <description>A security link following local privilege escalation vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One, Trend Micro Apex One as a Service, Trend Micro Worry-Free Business Security 10.0 SP1 and Trend Micro Worry-Free Business Security Services agents could allow a local attacker to create an writable folder in an arbitrary location and escalate privileges affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24679|2024-08-03T04:20:50.339Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 02:45:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-25329|2024-08-03T04:36:06.803Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20serverprotect%20for%20storage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-25329</link>
      <description>Trend Micro ServerProtect 6.0/5.8 Information Server uses a static credential to perform authentication when a specific command is typed in the console. An unauthenticated remote attacker with access to the Information Server could exploit this to register to the server and perform authenticated actions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-25329|2024-08-03T04:36:06.803Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 02:45:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41746|2024-08-03T12:49:43.755Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41746</link>
      <description>A forced browsing vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One could allow an attacker with access to the Apex One console on affected installations to escalate privileges and modify certain agent groupings. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to log onto the Apex One web console in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41746|2024-08-03T12:49:43.755Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40980|2024-08-03T12:28:43.107Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20mobile%20security%20for%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40980</link>
      <description>A potential unathenticated file deletion vulnerabilty on Trend Micro Mobile Security for Enterprise 9.8 SP5 could allow an attacker with access to the Management Server to delete files. This issue was resolved in 9.8 SP5 Critical Patch 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40980|2024-08-03T12:28:43.107Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 18:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-35234|2024-08-03T09:29:17.571Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20security%28consumer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-35234</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Security 2021 and 2022 (Consumer) is vulnerable to an Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability that could allow an attacker to read sensitive information from other memory locations and cause a crash on an affected machine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-35234|2024-08-03T09:29:17.571Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 23:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40142|2024-08-03T12:14:39.779Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40142</link>
      <description>A security link following local privilege escalation vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One and Trend Micro Apex One as a Service agents could allow a local attacker to create a writable folder in an arbitrary location and escalate privileges on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40142|2024-08-03T12:14:39.779Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 18:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-34893|2024-08-03T09:22:10.646Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20security%20%28consumer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34893</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Security 2022 (consumer) has a link following vulnerability where an attacker with lower privileges could manipulate a mountpoint which could lead to escalation of privilege on an affected machine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-34893|2024-08-03T09:22:10.646Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 18:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30700|2024-08-03T06:56:13.806Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30700</link>
      <description>An incorrect permission assignment vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One and Apex One as a Service could allow a local attacker to load a DLL with escalated privileges on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30700|2024-08-03T06:56:13.806Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 23:25:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23805|2024-08-03T03:51:45.989Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20worry-free%20business%20security
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23805</link>
      <description>A security out-of-bounds read information disclosure vulnerability in Trend Micro Worry-Free Business Security Server could allow a local attacker to send garbage data to a specific named pipe and crash the server. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23805|2024-08-03T03:51:45.989Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 22:32:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23119|2024-08-03T03:36:19.202Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20deep%20security%20agent%20for%20linux
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23119</link>
      <description>A directory traversal vulnerability in Trend Micro Deep Security and Cloud One - Workload Security Agent for Linux version 20 and below could allow an attacker to read arbitrary files from the file system. Please note: an attacker must first obtain compromised access to the target Deep Security Manager (DSM) or the target agent must be not yet activated or configured in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23119|2024-08-03T03:36:19.202Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 18:11:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38764|2024-08-03T11:02:14.601Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20housecall%20%28consumer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38764</link>
      <description>A vulnerability on Trend Micro HouseCall version 1.62.1.1133 and below could allow a local attacker to escalate privlieges due to an overly permissive folder om the product installer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38764|2024-08-03T11:02:14.601Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 18:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30523|2024-08-03T06:48:36.384Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20password%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30523</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Password Manager (Consumer) version 5.0.0.1266 and below is vulnerable to a Link Following Privilege Escalation Vulnerability that could allow a low privileged local attacker to delete the contents of an arbitrary folder as SYSTEM which can then be used for privilege escalation on the affected machine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30523|2024-08-03T06:48:36.384Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 14:45:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40143|2024-08-03T12:14:39.963Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40143</link>
      <description>A link following local privilege escalation vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One and Trend Micro Apex One as a Service servers could allow a local attacker to abuse an insecure directory that could allow a low-privileged user to run arbitrary code with elevated privileges. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40143|2024-08-03T12:14:39.963Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 18:01:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26319|2024-08-03T05:03:32.227Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20portable%20security
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26319</link>
      <description>An installer search patch element vulnerability in Trend Micro Portable Security 3.0 Pro, 3.0 and 2.0 could allow a local attacker to place an arbitrarily generated DLL file in an installer folder to elevate local privileges. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26319|2024-08-03T05:03:32.227Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 21:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40710|2024-08-03T12:21:46.609Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20deep%20security
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40710</link>
      <description>A link following vulnerability in Trend Micro Deep Security 20 and Cloud One - Workload Security Agent for Windows could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40710|2024-08-03T12:21:46.609Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 21:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28394|2024-08-03T05:56:15.184Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20password%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28394</link>
      <description>EOL Product CVE - Installer of Trend Micro Password Manager (Consumer) versions 3.7.0.1223 and below provided by Trend Micro Incorporated contains an issue with the DLL search path, which may lead to insecurely loading Dynamic Link Libraries (CWE-427). Please note that this was reported on an EOL version of the product, and users are advised to upgrade to the latest supported version (5.x).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28394|2024-08-03T05:56:15.184Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 23:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40708|2024-08-03T12:21:46.401Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20deep%20security
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40708</link>
      <description>An Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in Trend Micro Deep Security 20 and Cloud One - Workload Security Agent for Windows could allow a local attacker to disclose sensitive information on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit these vulnerabilities. This vulnerability is similar to, but not identical to CVE-2022-40707.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40708|2024-08-03T12:21:46.401Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 21:10:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-25330|2024-08-03T04:36:06.908Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20serverprotect%20for%20storage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-25330</link>
      <description>Integer overflow conditions that exist in Trend Micro ServerProtect 6.0/5.8 Information Server could allow a remote attacker to crash the process or achieve remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-25330|2024-08-03T04:36:06.908Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 02:45:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26871|2024-08-03T05:18:38.023Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20central
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26871</link>
      <description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex Central could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to upload an arbitrary file which could lead to remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26871|2024-08-03T05:18:38.023Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 20:45:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40141|2024-08-03T12:14:39.954Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40141</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One and Apex One as a Service could allow an attacker to intercept and decode certain communication strings that may contain some identification attributes of a particular Apex One server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40141|2024-08-03T12:14:39.954Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 18:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41748|2024-08-03T12:49:44.167Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41748</link>
      <description>A registry permissions vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One Data Loss Prevention (DLP) module could allow a local attacker with administrative credentials to bypass certain elements of the product's anti-tampering mechanisms on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain administrative credentials on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41748|2024-08-03T12:49:44.167Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24678|2024-08-03T04:20:49.099Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24678</link>
      <description>An security agent resource exhaustion denial-of-service vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One, Trend Micro Apex One as a Service, Trend Micro Worry-Free Business Security 10.0 SP1 and Trend Micro Worry-Free Business Security Services agents could allow an attacker to flood a temporary log location and consume all disk space on affected installations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24678|2024-08-03T04:20:49.099Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 02:45:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40140|2024-08-03T12:14:39.803Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40140</link>
      <description>An origin validation error vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One and Apex One as a Service could allow a local attacker to cause a denial-of-service on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40140|2024-08-03T12:14:39.803Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 18:01:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-37347|2024-08-03T10:29:20.949Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20security%20%28consumer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-37347</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Security 2021 and 2022 (Consumer) is vulnerable to an Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability that could allow an attacker to read sensitive information from other memory locations and cause a crash on an affected machine. This vulnerability is similar to, but not the same as CVE-2022-35234.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-37347|2024-08-03T10:29:20.949Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 18:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
