<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Trend Micro -- Trend Micro Password Manager</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/trend%20micro/trend%20micro%20password%20manager.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Trend Micro -- Trend Micro Password Manager</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 12:25:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26337|2024-08-03T05:03:32.878Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20password%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26337</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Password Manager (Consumer) installer version 5.0.0.1262 and below is vulnerable to an Uncontrolled Search Path Element vulnerability that could allow an attacker to use a specially crafted file to exploit the vulnerability and escalate local privileges on the affected machine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26337|2024-08-03T05:03:32.878Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 21:55:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30523|2024-08-03T06:48:36.384Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20password%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30523</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Password Manager (Consumer) version 5.0.0.1266 and below is vulnerable to a Link Following Privilege Escalation Vulnerability that could allow a low privileged local attacker to delete the contents of an arbitrary folder as SYSTEM which can then be used for privilege escalation on the affected machine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30523|2024-08-03T06:48:36.384Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 14:45:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28394|2024-08-03T05:56:15.184Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20password%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28394</link>
      <description>EOL Product CVE - Installer of Trend Micro Password Manager (Consumer) versions 3.7.0.1223 and below provided by Trend Micro Incorporated contains an issue with the DLL search path, which may lead to insecurely loading Dynamic Link Libraries (CWE-427). Please note that this was reported on an EOL version of the product, and users are advised to upgrade to the latest supported version (5.x).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28394|2024-08-03T05:56:15.184Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 23:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
