<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Trend Micro -- Trend Micro Apex One</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/trend%20micro/trend%20micro%20apex%20one.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Trend Micro -- Trend Micro Apex One</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 12:25:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36336|2024-08-03T10:00:04.319Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36336</link>
      <description>A link following vulnerability in the scanning function of Trend Micro Apex One and Worry-Free Business Security agents could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations. The resolution for this issue has been deployed automatically via ActiveUpdate to customers in an updated Spyware pattern. Customers who are up-to-date on detection patterns are not required to take any additional steps to mitigate this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36336|2024-08-03T10:00:04.319Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 23:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30701|2024-08-03T06:56:13.781Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30701</link>
      <description>An uncontrolled search path element vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One and Apex One as a Service could allow a local attacker to craft a special configuration file to load an untrusted library with escalated privileges on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30701|2024-08-03T06:56:13.781Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 23:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24680|2024-08-03T04:20:49.145Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24680</link>
      <description>A security link following local privilege escalation vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One, Trend Micro Apex One as a Service, Trend Micro Worry-Free Business Security 10.0 SP1 and Trend Micro Worry-Free Business Security Services agents could allow a local attacker to create a mount point and leverage this for arbitrary folder deletion, leading to escalated privileges on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24680|2024-08-03T04:20:49.145Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 02:45:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24679|2024-08-03T04:20:50.339Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24679</link>
      <description>A security link following local privilege escalation vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One, Trend Micro Apex One as a Service, Trend Micro Worry-Free Business Security 10.0 SP1 and Trend Micro Worry-Free Business Security Services agents could allow a local attacker to create an writable folder in an arbitrary location and escalate privileges affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24679|2024-08-03T04:20:50.339Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 02:45:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30700|2024-08-03T06:56:13.806Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30700</link>
      <description>An incorrect permission assignment vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One and Apex One as a Service could allow a local attacker to load a DLL with escalated privileges on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30700|2024-08-03T06:56:13.806Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 23:25:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24678|2024-08-03T04:20:49.099Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24678</link>
      <description>An security agent resource exhaustion denial-of-service vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One, Trend Micro Apex One as a Service, Trend Micro Worry-Free Business Security 10.0 SP1 and Trend Micro Worry-Free Business Security Services agents could allow an attacker to flood a temporary log location and consume all disk space on affected installations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24678|2024-08-03T04:20:49.099Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 02:45:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
