<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Trend Micro -- Trend Micro Security (Consumer)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/trend%20micro/trend%20micro%20security%20%28consumer%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Trend Micro -- Trend Micro Security (Consumer)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:23:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-15602|2024-08-04T13:22:29.985Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20security%20%28consumer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-15602</link>
      <description>An untrusted search path remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in the Trend Micro Secuity 2020 (v16.0.0.1146 and below) consumer family of products could allow an attacker to run arbitrary code on a vulnerable system. As the Trend Micro installer tries to load DLL files from its current directory, an arbitrary DLL could also be loaded with the same privileges as the installer if run as Administrator. User interaction is required to exploit the vulnerbaility in that the target must open a malicious directory or device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-15602|2024-08-04T13:22:29.985Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 19:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-36744|2024-08-04T01:01:59.187Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20security%20%28consumer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-36744</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Security (Consumer) 2021 and 2020 are vulnerable to a directory junction vulnerability which could allow an attacker to exploit the system to escalate privileges and create a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-36744|2024-08-04T01:01:59.187Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2021 11:37:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-25775|2024-08-04T15:40:36.947Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20security%20%28consumer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-25775</link>
      <description>The Trend Micro Security 2020 (v16) consumer family of products is vulnerable to a security race condition arbitrary file deletion vulnerability that could allow an unprivileged user to manipulate the product's secure erase feature to delete files with a higher set of privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-25775|2024-08-04T15:40:36.947Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 23:30:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-15604|2024-08-04T13:22:30.611Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20security%20%28consumer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-15604</link>
      <description>An incomplete SSL server certification validation vulnerability in the Trend Micro Security 2019 (v15) consumer family of products could allow an attacker to combine this vulnerability with another attack to trick an affected client into downloading a malicious update instead of the expected one. CWE-494: Update files are not properly verified.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-15604|2024-08-04T13:22:30.611Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 01:50:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27697|2024-08-04T16:18:45.678Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20security%20%28consumer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27697</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Security 2020 (Consumer) contains a vulnerability in the installer package that could be exploited by placing a malicious DLL in a non-protected location with high privileges (symlink attack) which can lead to obtaining administrative privileges during the installation of the product.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27697|2024-08-04T16:18:45.678Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 18:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-24560|2024-08-04T15:19:07.405Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20security%20%28consumer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-24560</link>
      <description>An incomplete SSL server certification validation vulnerability in the Trend Micro Security 2019 (v15) consumer family of products could allow an attacker to combine this vulnerability with another attack to trick an affected client into downloading a malicious update instead of the expected one. CWE-295: Improper server certificate verification in the communication with the update server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-24560|2024-08-04T15:19:07.405Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 01:50:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-15603|2024-08-04T13:22:30.145Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20security%20%28consumer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-15603</link>
      <description>An invalid memory read vulnerability in a Trend Micro Secuity 2020 (v16.0.0.1302 and below) consumer family of products' driver could allow an attacker to manipulate the specific driver to do a system call operation with an invalid address, resulting in a potential system crash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-15603|2024-08-04T13:22:30.145Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 19:15:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27696|2024-08-04T16:18:45.580Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20security%20%28consumer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27696</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Security 2020 (Consumer) contains a vulnerability in the installer package that could be exploited by placing a specific Windows system directory which can lead to obtaining administrative privileges during the installation of the product.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27696|2024-08-04T16:18:45.580Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 18:45:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-27695|2024-08-04T16:18:45.580Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20security%20%28consumer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-27695</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Security 2020 (Consumer) contains a vulnerability in the installer package that could be exploited by placing a malicious DLL in a local directory which can lead to obtaining administrative privileges during the installation of the product.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-27695|2024-08-04T16:18:45.580Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 18:45:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-44023|2024-08-04T04:10:17.277Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20security%20%28consumer%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-44023</link>
      <description>A link following denial-of-service (DoS) vulnerability in the Trend Micro Security (Consumer) 2021 familiy of products could allow an attacker to abuse the PC Health Checkup feature of the product to create symlinks that would allow modification of files which could lead to a denial-of-service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-44023|2024-08-04T04:10:17.277Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 02:28:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
