<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Trend Micro -- Trend Micro Apex One</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/trend%20micro/trend%20micro%20apex%20one.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Trend Micro -- Trend Micro Apex One</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 21:21:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25235|2024-08-03T19:56:11.080Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25235</link>
      <description>An improper access control vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One (on-prem and SaaS) and OfficeScan XG SP1 could allow an unauthenticated user to obtain information about a content inspection configuration file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25235|2024-08-03T19:56:11.080Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 19:36:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41749|2024-08-03T12:49:43.934Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41749</link>
      <description>An origin validation error vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One agents could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41749|2024-08-03T12:49:43.934Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40144|2024-08-03T12:14:39.823Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40144</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One and Trend Micro Apex One as a Service could allow an attacker to bypass the product's login authentication by falsifying request parameters on affected installations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40144|2024-08-03T12:14:39.823Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25249|2024-08-03T19:56:11.053Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25249</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds write information disclosure vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One (on-prem and SaaS), OfficeScan XG SP1, and Worry-Free Business Security (10.0 SP1 and Services) could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25249|2024-08-03T19:56:11.053Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 19:36:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40139|2024-08-03T12:14:39.635Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40139</link>
      <description>Improper validation of some components used by the rollback mechanism in Trend Micro Apex One and Trend Micro Apex One as a Service clients could allow a Apex One server administrator to instruct affected clients to download an unverified rollback package, which could lead to remote code execution. Please note: an attacker must first obtain Apex One server administration console access in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40139|2024-08-03T12:14:39.635Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 18:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41744|2024-08-03T12:49:43.722Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41744</link>
      <description>A Time-of-Check Time-Of-Use vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One Vulnerability Protection integrated component could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges and turn a specific working directory into a mount point on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41744|2024-08-03T12:49:43.722Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25241|2024-08-03T19:56:11.098Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25241</link>
      <description>A server-side request forgery (SSRF) information disclosure vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One and Worry-Free Business Security 10.0 SP1 could allow an unauthenticated user to locate online agents via a sweep.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25241|2024-08-03T19:56:11.098Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 19:36:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41747|2024-08-03T12:49:43.590Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41747</link>
      <description>An improper certification validation vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One agents could allow a local attacker to load a DLL file with system service privileges on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41747|2024-08-03T12:49:43.590Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36336|2024-08-03T10:00:04.319Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36336</link>
      <description>A link following vulnerability in the scanning function of Trend Micro Apex One and Worry-Free Business Security agents could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations. The resolution for this issue has been deployed automatically via ActiveUpdate to customers in an updated Spyware pattern. Customers who are up-to-date on detection patterns are not required to take any additional steps to mitigate this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36336|2024-08-03T10:00:04.319Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 23:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25242|2024-08-03T19:56:11.063Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25242</link>
      <description>An improper access control vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One (on-prem and SaaS), OfficeScan XG SP1, and Worry-Free Business Security 10.0 SP1 could allow an unauthenticated user to obtain version and build information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25242|2024-08-03T19:56:11.063Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 19:36:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41745|2024-08-03T12:49:43.818Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41745</link>
      <description>An Out-of-Bounds access vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One could allow a local attacker to create a specially crafted message to cause memory corruption on a certain service process which could lead to local privilege escalation on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41745|2024-08-03T12:49:43.818Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25232|2024-08-03T19:56:11.106Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25232</link>
      <description>An improper access control vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One (on-prem and SaaS) and OfficeScan XG SP1 could allow an unauthenticated user to obtain information about the SQL database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25232|2024-08-03T19:56:11.106Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 19:36:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30701|2024-08-03T06:56:13.781Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30701</link>
      <description>An uncontrolled search path element vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One and Apex One as a Service could allow a local attacker to craft a special configuration file to load an untrusted library with escalated privileges on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30701|2024-08-03T06:56:13.781Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 23:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24680|2024-08-03T04:20:49.145Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24680</link>
      <description>A security link following local privilege escalation vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One, Trend Micro Apex One as a Service, Trend Micro Worry-Free Business Security 10.0 SP1 and Trend Micro Worry-Free Business Security Services agents could allow a local attacker to create a mount point and leverage this for arbitrary folder deletion, leading to escalated privileges on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24680|2024-08-03T04:20:49.145Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 02:45:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25237|2024-08-03T19:56:11.041Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25237</link>
      <description>An improper access control vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One (on-prem) could allow an unauthenticated user to obtain information about the managing port used by agents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25237|2024-08-03T19:56:11.041Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 19:36:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25233|2024-08-03T19:56:11.094Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25233</link>
      <description>An improper access control vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One (on-prem and SaaS), OfficeScan XG SP1, and Worry-Free Business Security 10.0 SP1 could allow an unauthenticated user to obtain information about a specific configuration download file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25233|2024-08-03T19:56:11.094Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 19:36:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25246|2024-08-03T19:56:11.043Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25246</link>
      <description>An improper access control information disclosure vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One, Apex One as a Service, OfficeScan XG SP1, and Worry-Free Business Security could allow an unauthenticated user to create a bogus agent on an affected server that could be used then make valid configuration queries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25246|2024-08-03T19:56:11.043Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 19:36:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24679|2024-08-03T04:20:50.339Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24679</link>
      <description>A security link following local privilege escalation vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One, Trend Micro Apex One as a Service, Trend Micro Worry-Free Business Security 10.0 SP1 and Trend Micro Worry-Free Business Security Services agents could allow a local attacker to create an writable folder in an arbitrary location and escalate privileges affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24679|2024-08-03T04:20:50.339Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 02:45:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41746|2024-08-03T12:49:43.755Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41746</link>
      <description>A forced browsing vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One could allow an attacker with access to the Apex One console on affected installations to escalate privileges and modify certain agent groupings. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to log onto the Apex One web console in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41746|2024-08-03T12:49:43.755Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25239|2024-08-03T19:56:11.075Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25239</link>
      <description>An improper access control vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One (on-prem), OfficeScan XG SP1, and Worry-Free Business Security 10.0 SP1 could allow an unauthenticated user to obtain information about x86 agent hotfixes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25239|2024-08-03T19:56:11.075Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 19:36:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40142|2024-08-03T12:14:39.779Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40142</link>
      <description>A security link following local privilege escalation vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One and Trend Micro Apex One as a Service agents could allow a local attacker to create a writable folder in an arbitrary location and escalate privileges on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40142|2024-08-03T12:14:39.779Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 18:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3848|2024-08-03T17:09:09.607Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3848</link>
      <description>An arbitrary file creation by privilege escalation vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One, Apex One as a Service, Worry-Free Business Security 10.0 SP1, and Worry-Free Business Security Services could allow a local attacker to create an arbitrary file with higher privileges that could lead to a denial-of-service (DoS) on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3848|2024-08-03T17:09:09.607Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 09:50:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25250|2024-08-03T19:56:11.087Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25250</link>
      <description>An improper access control vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One, Trend Micro Apex One as a Service and OfficeScan XG SP1 on a sensitive file could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25250|2024-08-03T19:56:11.087Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 12:35:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25231|2024-08-03T19:56:11.054Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25231</link>
      <description>An improper access control vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One (on-prem and SaaS), OfficeScan XG SP1, and Worry-Free Business Security 10.0 SP1 could allow an unauthenticated user to obtain information about a specific hotfix history file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25231|2024-08-03T19:56:11.054Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 19:36:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-30700|2024-08-03T06:56:13.806Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-30700</link>
      <description>An incorrect permission assignment vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One and Apex One as a Service could allow a local attacker to load a DLL with escalated privileges on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-30700|2024-08-03T06:56:13.806Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 23:25:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25228|2024-08-03T19:56:11.064Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25228</link>
      <description>An improper access control vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One (on-prem and SaaS), OfficeScan XG SP1, and Worry-Free Business Security 10.0 SP1 could allow an unauthenticated user to obtain information about hotfix history.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25228|2024-08-03T19:56:11.064Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 19:36:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-23139|2024-08-03T18:58:26.372Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23139</link>
      <description>A null pointer vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One and Worry-Free Business Security 10.0 SP1 could allow an attacker to crash the CGI program on affected installations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-23139|2024-08-03T18:58:26.372Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 07:46:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25248|2024-08-03T19:56:11.069Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25248</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds read information disclosure vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One (on-prem and SaaS), OfficeScan XG SP1, and Worry-Free Business Security (10.0 SP1 and Services) could allow an attacker to disclose sensitive information about a named pipe. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25248|2024-08-03T19:56:11.069Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 19:36:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40143|2024-08-03T12:14:39.963Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40143</link>
      <description>A link following local privilege escalation vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One and Trend Micro Apex One as a Service servers could allow a local attacker to abuse an insecure directory that could allow a low-privileged user to run arbitrary code with elevated privileges. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40143|2024-08-03T12:14:39.963Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 18:01:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25253|2024-08-03T19:56:11.086Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25253</link>
      <description>An improper access control vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One, Trend Micro Apex One as a Service and OfficeScan XG SP1 on a resource used by the service could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25253|2024-08-03T19:56:11.086Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 12:53:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25230|2024-08-03T19:56:11.074Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25230</link>
      <description>An improper access control vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One (on-prem and SaaS) and OfficeScan XG SP1 could allow an unauthenticated user to obtain information about the contents of a scan connection exception file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25230|2024-08-03T19:56:11.074Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 19:36:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25234|2024-08-03T19:56:11.062Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25234</link>
      <description>An improper access control vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One (on-prem and SaaS), OfficeScan XG SP1, and Worry-Free Business Security 10.0 SP1 could allow an unauthenticated user to obtain information about a specific notification configuration file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25234|2024-08-03T19:56:11.062Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 19:36:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25243|2024-08-03T19:56:11.085Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25243</link>
      <description>An improper access control vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One (on-prem and SaaS), OfficeScan XG SP1, and Worry-Free Business Security 10.0 SP1 could allow an unauthenticated user to obtain patch level information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25243|2024-08-03T19:56:11.085Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 19:36:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25229|2024-08-03T19:56:11.014Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25229</link>
      <description>An improper access control vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One (on-prem and SaaS) and OfficeScan XG SP1 could allow an unauthenticated user to obtain information about the database server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25229|2024-08-03T19:56:11.014Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 19:36:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40141|2024-08-03T12:14:39.954Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40141</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One and Apex One as a Service could allow an attacker to intercept and decode certain communication strings that may contain some identification attributes of a particular Apex One server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40141|2024-08-03T12:14:39.954Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 18:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25240|2024-08-03T19:56:11.074Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25240</link>
      <description>An improper access control vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One (on-prem and SaaS), OfficeScan XG SP1, and Worry-Free Business Security 10.0 SP1 could allow an unauthenticated user to obtain x64 agent hofitx information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25240|2024-08-03T19:56:11.074Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 19:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41748|2024-08-03T12:49:44.167Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41748</link>
      <description>A registry permissions vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One Data Loss Prevention (DLP) module could allow a local attacker with administrative credentials to bypass certain elements of the product's anti-tampering mechanisms on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain administrative credentials on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41748|2024-08-03T12:49:44.167Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24678|2024-08-03T04:20:49.099Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24678</link>
      <description>An security agent resource exhaustion denial-of-service vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One, Trend Micro Apex One as a Service, Trend Micro Worry-Free Business Security 10.0 SP1 and Trend Micro Worry-Free Business Security Services agents could allow an attacker to flood a temporary log location and consume all disk space on affected installations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24678|2024-08-03T04:20:49.099Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 02:45:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40140|2024-08-03T12:14:39.803Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20apex%20one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40140</link>
      <description>An origin validation error vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One and Apex One as a Service could allow a local attacker to cause a denial-of-service on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40140|2024-08-03T12:14:39.803Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 18:01:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
