<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Trend Micro -- Trend Micro OfficeScan</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/trend%20micro/trend%20micro%20officescan.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Trend Micro -- Trend Micro OfficeScan</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:23:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-15364|2024-08-05T09:54:02.358Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20officescan
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-15364</link>
      <description>A Named Pipe Request Processing Out-of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure vulnerability in Trend Micro OfficeScan XG (12.0) could allow a local attacker to disclose sensitive information on vulnerable installations. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit the vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-15364|2024-08-05T09:54:02.358Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14087|2024-08-05T19:13:41.655Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20officescan
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14087</link>
      <description>A Host Header Injection vulnerability in Trend Micro OfficeScan XG (12.0) may allow an attacker to spoof a particular Host header, allowing the attacker to render arbitrary links that point to a malicious website with poisoned Host header webpages.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14087|2024-08-05T19:13:41.655Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10359|2024-08-05T07:39:08.076Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20officescan
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10359</link>
      <description>A pool corruption privilege escalation vulnerability in Trend Micro OfficeScan 11.0 SP1 and XG could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on vulnerable installations due to a flaw within the processing of IOCTL 0x220078 in the TMWFP driver. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10359|2024-08-05T07:39:08.076Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10506|2024-08-05T07:39:07.685Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20officescan
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10506</link>
      <description>A out-of-bounds read information disclosure vulnerability in Trend Micro OfficeScan 11.0 SP1 and XG could allow a local attacker to disclose sensitive information on vulnerable installations due to a flaw within the processing of IOCTL 0x220004 by the TMWFP driver. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10506|2024-08-05T07:39:07.685Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14084|2024-08-05T19:13:41.570Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20officescan
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14084</link>
      <description>A potential Man-in-the-Middle (MitM) attack vulnerability in Trend Micro OfficeScan 11.0 and XG may allow attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14084|2024-08-05T19:13:41.570Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14089|2024-08-05T19:13:41.934Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20officescan
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14089</link>
      <description>An Unauthorized Memory Corruption vulnerability in Trend Micro OfficeScan 11.0 and XG may allow remote unauthenticated users who can access the OfficeScan server to target cgiShowClientAdm.exe and cause memory corruption issues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14089|2024-08-05T19:13:41.934Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14083|2024-08-05T19:13:41.699Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20officescan
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14083</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Trend Micro OfficeScan 11.0 and XG allows remote unauthenticated users who can access the system to download the OfficeScan encryption file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14083|2024-08-05T19:13:41.699Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10507|2024-08-05T07:39:08.272Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20officescan
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10507</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Trend Micro OfficeScan 11.0 SP1 and XG could allow a attacker to take a series of steps to bypass or render the OfficeScan Unauthorized Change Prevention inoperable on vulnerable installations. An attacker must already have administrator privileges in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10507|2024-08-05T07:39:08.272Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-11394|2024-08-05T18:05:30.605Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20officescan
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-11394</link>
      <description>Proxy command injection vulnerability in Trend Micro OfficeScan 11 and XG (12) allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations. The specific flaw can be exploited by parsing the T parameter within Proxy.php. Formerly ZDI-CAN-4544.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-11394|2024-08-05T18:05:30.605Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10505|2024-08-05T07:39:07.668Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20officescan
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10505</link>
      <description>A pool corruption privilege escalation vulnerability in Trend Micro OfficeScan 11.0 SP1 and XG could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on vulnerable installations due to a flaw within the processing of IOCTL 0x220008 in the TMWFP driver. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10505|2024-08-05T07:39:07.668Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10358|2024-08-05T07:39:07.401Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20officescan
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10358</link>
      <description>A pool corruption privilege escalation vulnerability in Trend Micro OfficeScan 11.0 SP1 and XG could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on vulnerable installations due to a flaw within the processing of IOCTL 0x2200B4 in the TMWFP driver. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10358|2024-08-05T07:39:07.401Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14085|2024-08-05T19:13:41.709Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20officescan
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14085</link>
      <description>Information disclosure vulnerabilities in Trend Micro OfficeScan 11.0 and XG may allow unauthenticated users who can access the OfficeScan server to query the network's NT domain or the PHP version and modules.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14085|2024-08-05T19:13:41.709Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10509|2024-08-05T07:39:08.300Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20officescan
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10509</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Trend Micro OfficeScan 11.0 SP1 and XG could allow a attacker to exploit it via a Browser Refresh attack on vulnerable installations. An attacker must be using a AD logon user account in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10509|2024-08-05T07:39:08.300Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14088|2024-08-05T19:13:41.767Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20officescan
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14088</link>
      <description>Memory Corruption Privilege Escalation vulnerabilities in Trend Micro OfficeScan 11.0 and XG allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code and escalate privileges to resources normally reserved for the kernel on vulnerable installations by exploiting tmwfp.sys. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit the vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14088|2024-08-05T19:13:41.767Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18331|2024-08-05T11:08:21.430Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20officescan
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18331</link>
      <description>A Trend Micro OfficeScan XG weak file permissions vulnerability on a particular folder for a particular group may allow an attacker to alter the files, which could lead to other exploits on vulnerable installations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18331|2024-08-05T11:08:21.430Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10508|2024-08-05T07:39:07.712Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20officescan
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10508</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Trend Micro OfficeScan 11.0 SP1 and XG could allow a attacker to use a specially crafted URL to elevate account permissions on vulnerable installations. An attacker must already have at least guest privileges in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10508|2024-08-05T07:39:07.712Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18332|2024-08-05T11:08:21.697Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20officescan
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18332</link>
      <description>A Trend Micro OfficeScan XG weak file permissions vulnerability may allow an attacker to potentially manipulate permissions on some key files to modify other files and folders on vulnerable installations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18332|2024-08-05T11:08:21.697Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-11393|2024-08-05T18:05:30.604Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20officescan
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-11393</link>
      <description>Proxy command injection vulnerability in Trend Micro OfficeScan 11 and XG (12) allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations. The specific flaw can be exploited by parsing the tr parameter within Proxy.php. Formerly ZDI-CAN-4543.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-11393|2024-08-05T18:05:30.604Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18187|2024-08-05T01:47:13.639Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20officescan
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18187</link>
      <description>Trend Micro OfficeScan versions 11.0 and XG (12.0) could be exploited by an attacker utilizing a directory traversal vulnerability to extract files from an arbitrary zip file to a specific folder on the OfficeScan server, which could potentially lead to remote code execution (RCE). The remote process execution is bound to a web service account, which depending on the web platform used may have restricted permissions. An attempted attack requires user authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18187|2024-08-05T01:47:13.639Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 19:28:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14086|2024-08-05T19:13:41.878Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20officescan
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14086</link>
      <description>Pre-authorization Start Remote Process vulnerabilities in Trend Micro OfficeScan 11.0 and XG may allow unauthenticated users who can access the OfficeScan server to start the fcgiOfcDDA.exe executable or cause a potential INI corruption, which may cause the server disk space to be consumed with dump files from continuous HTTP requests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14086|2024-08-05T19:13:41.878Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
