<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Trend Micro -- Trend Micro Antivirus for Mac</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/trend%20micro/trend%20micro%20antivirus%20for%20mac.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Trend Micro -- Trend Micro Antivirus for Mac</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:22:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25227|2024-08-03T19:56:11.062Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20antivirus%20for%20mac
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25227</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Antivirus for Mac 2021 (Consumer) is vulnerable to a memory exhaustion vulnerability that could lead to disabling all the scanning functionality within the application. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability - i.e. the attacker must already have access to the target system (either legitimately or via another exploit).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25227|2024-08-03T19:56:11.062Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 19:36:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-27883|2024-08-03T05:41:10.659Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20antivirus%20for%20mac
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27883</link>
      <description>A link following vulnerability in Trend Micro Antivirus for Mac 11.5 could allow an attacker to create a specially-crafted file as a symlink that can lead to privilege escalation. Please note that an attacker must at least have low-level privileges on the system to attempt to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-27883|2024-08-03T05:41:10.659Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 00:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24671|2024-08-03T04:20:49.102Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20antivirus%20for%20mac
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24671</link>
      <description>A link following privilege escalation vulnerability in Trend Micro Antivirus for Max 11.0.2150 and below could allow a local attacker to modify a file during the update process and escalate their privileges. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24671|2024-08-03T04:20:49.102Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 02:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28648|2024-08-03T21:47:33.215Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20antivirus%20for%20mac
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28648</link>
      <description>Trend Micro Antivirus for Mac 2020 v10.5 and 2021 v11 (Consumer) is vulnerable to an improper access control privilege escalation vulnerability that could allow an attacker to establish a connection that could lead to full local privilege escalation within the application. Please note that an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28648|2024-08-03T21:47:33.215Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 21:21:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
