<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Trend Micro -- Trend Micro Deep Security</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/trend%20micro/trend%20micro%20deep%20security.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Trend Micro -- Trend Micro Deep Security</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 23:23:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40707|2024-08-03T12:21:46.562Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20deep%20security
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40707</link>
      <description>An Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in Trend Micro Deep Security 20 and Cloud One - Workload Security Agent for Windows could allow a local attacker to disclose sensitive information on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit these vulnerabilities. This vulnerability is similar to, but not identical to CVE-2022-40708.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40707|2024-08-03T12:21:46.562Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 21:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40709|2024-08-03T12:21:46.453Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20deep%20security
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40709</link>
      <description>An Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in Trend Micro Deep Security 20 and Cloud One - Workload Security Agent for Windows could allow a local attacker to disclose sensitive information on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit these vulnerabilities. This vulnerability is similar to, but not identical to CVE-2022-40707 and 40708.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40709|2024-08-03T12:21:46.453Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 21:10:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40710|2024-08-03T12:21:46.609Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20deep%20security
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40710</link>
      <description>A link following vulnerability in Trend Micro Deep Security 20 and Cloud One - Workload Security Agent for Windows could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40710|2024-08-03T12:21:46.609Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 21:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40708|2024-08-03T12:21:46.401Z -- trend%20micro -- trend%20micro%20deep%20security
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40708</link>
      <description>An Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in Trend Micro Deep Security 20 and Cloud One - Workload Security Agent for Windows could allow a local attacker to disclose sensitive information on affected installations. Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit these vulnerabilities. This vulnerability is similar to, but not identical to CVE-2022-40707.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40708|2024-08-03T12:21:46.401Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 21:10:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
