<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Sage -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sage/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Sage -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 18:24:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7390|2024-08-04T09:25:49.122Z -- sage -- x3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7390</link>
      <description>Sage X3 Stored XSS Vulnerability on ‘Edit’ Page of User Profile. An authenticated user can pass XSS strings the "First Name," "Last Name," and "Email Address" fields of this web application component. Updates are available for on-premises versions of Version 12 (components shipped with Syracuse 12.10.0 and later) of Sage X3. Other on-premises versions of Sage X3 are unaffected or unsupported by the vendor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7390|2024-08-04T09:25:49.122Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7389|2024-08-04T09:25:49.087Z -- sage -- x3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7389</link>
      <description>Sage X3 System CHAINE Variable Script Command Injection. An authenticated user with developer access can pass OS commands via this variable used by the web application. Note, this developer configuration should not be deployed in production.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7389|2024-08-04T09:25:49.087Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7388|2024-08-04T09:25:49.034Z -- sage -- x3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7388</link>
      <description>Sage X3 Unauthenticated Remote Command Execution (RCE) as SYSTEM in AdxDSrv.exe component. By editing the client side authentication request, an attacker can bypass credential validation. While exploiting this does require knowledge of the installation path, that information can be learned by exploiting CVE-2020-7387. This issue was fixed in AdxAdmin 93.2.53, which ships with updates for on-premises versions of Sage X3 including Version 9 (components shipped with Syracuse 9.22.7.2 and later), Sage X3 HR &amp; Payroll Version 9 (those components that ship with Syracuse 9.24.1.3), Version 11 (components shipped with Syracuse 11.25.2.6 and later), and Version 12 (components shipped with Syracuse 12.10.2.8 and later) of Sage X3. Other on-premises versions of Sage X3 are unsupported by the vendor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7388|2024-08-04T09:25:49.034Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-7387|2024-08-04T09:25:49.086Z -- sage -- x3
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-7387</link>
      <description>Sage X3 Installation Pathname Disclosure. A specially crafted packet can elicit a response from the AdxDSrv.exe component that reveals the installation directory of the product. Note that this vulnerability can be combined with CVE-2020-7388 to achieve full RCE. This issue was fixed in AdxAdmin 93.2.53, which ships with updates for on-premises versions of Sage X3 Version 9 (components shipped with Syracuse 9.22.7.2 and later), Sage X3 HR &amp; Payroll Version 9 (those components that ship with Syracuse 9.24.1.3), Version 11 (components shipped with Syracuse 11.25.2.6 and later), and Version 12 (components shipped with Syracuse 12.10.2.8 and later) of Sage X3. Other on-premises versions of Sage X3 are unsupported by the vendor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-7387|2024-08-04T09:25:49.086Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
