<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Vivotek -- CC8160</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/vivotek/cc8160.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Vivotek -- CC8160</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 17:22:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7440|2024-08-03T16:31:04.256Z -- vivotek -- cc8160
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7440</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in Vivotek CC8160 VVTK-0100d. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function getenv of the file upload_file.cgi. The manipulation of the argument QUERY_STRING leads to command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The identifier VDB-273525 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the affected release tree is end-of-life.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Vivotek CC8160 VVTK-0100d ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es betrifft die Funktion getenv der Datei upload_file.cgi. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments QUERY_STRING mit unbekannten Daten kann eine command injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7440|2024-08-03T16:31:04.256Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 16:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7439|2024-08-03T16:00:07.798Z -- vivotek -- cc8160
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7439</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in Vivotek CC8160 VVTK-0100d and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function read of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument Content-Length leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273524. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the affected release tree is end-of-life.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Vivotek CC8160 VVTK-0100d gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei geht es um die Funktion read der Komponente httpd. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments Content-Length mit unbekannten Daten kann eine stack-based buffer overflow-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7439|2024-08-03T16:00:07.798Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 16:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
