<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for gssapi -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/gssapi/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for gssapi -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25563|2023-02-14T17:35:08.172Z -- gssapi -- gss-ntlmssp
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-25563</link>
      <description>GSS-NTLMSSP is a mechglue plugin for the GSSAPI library that implements NTLM authentication. Prior to version 1.2.0, multiple out-of-bounds reads when decoding NTLM fields can trigger a denial of service. A 32-bit integer overflow condition can lead to incorrect checks of consistency of length of internal buffers. Although most applications will error out before accepting a singe input buffer of 4GB in length this could theoretically happen. This vulnerability can be triggered via the main `gss_accept_sec_context` entry point if the application allows tokens greater than 4GB in length. This can lead to a large, up to 65KB, out-of-bounds read which could cause a denial-of-service if it reads from unmapped memory. Version 1.2.0 contains a patch for the out-of-bounds reads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25563|2023-02-14T17:35:08.172Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 17:35:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25565|2023-02-14T17:35:41.222Z -- gssapi -- gss-ntlmssp
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-25565</link>
      <description>GSS-NTLMSSP is a mechglue plugin for the GSSAPI library that implements NTLM authentication. Prior to version 1.2.0, an incorrect free when decoding target information can trigger a denial of service. The error condition incorrectly assumes the `cb` and `sh` buffers contain a copy of the data that needs to be freed. However, that is not the case. This vulnerability can be triggered via the main `gss_accept_sec_context` entry point. This will likely trigger an assertion failure in `free`, causing a denial-of-service. This issue is fixed in version 1.2.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25565|2023-02-14T17:35:41.222Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 17:35:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25564|2023-02-14T17:35:26.294Z -- gssapi -- gss-ntlmssp
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-25564</link>
      <description>GSS-NTLMSSP is a mechglue plugin for the GSSAPI library that implements NTLM authentication. Prior to version 1.2.0, memory corruption can be triggered when decoding UTF16 strings. The variable `outlen` was not initialized and could cause writing a zero to an arbitrary place in memory if `ntlm_str_convert()` were to fail, which would leave `outlen` uninitialized. This can lead to a denial of service if the write hits unmapped memory or randomly corrupts a byte in the application memory space. This vulnerability can trigger an out-of-bounds write, leading to memory corruption. This vulnerability can be triggered via the main `gss_accept_sec_context` entry point. This issue is fixed in version 1.2.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25564|2023-02-14T17:35:26.294Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 17:35:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25567|2023-02-14T17:35:59.571Z -- gssapi -- gss-ntlmssp
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-25567</link>
      <description>GSS-NTLMSSP, a mechglue plugin for the GSSAPI library that implements NTLM authentication, has an out-of-bounds read when decoding target information prior to version 1.2.0. The length of the `av_pair` is not checked properly for two of the elements which can trigger an out-of-bound read. The out-of-bounds read can be triggered via the main `gss_accept_sec_context` entry point and could cause a denial-of-service if the memory is unmapped. The issue is fixed in version 1.2.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25567|2023-02-14T17:35:59.571Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 17:35:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25566|2023-02-14T17:35:48.482Z -- gssapi -- gss-ntlmssp
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-25566</link>
      <description>GSS-NTLMSSP is a mechglue plugin for the GSSAPI library that implements NTLM authentication. Prior to version 1.2.0, a memory leak can be triggered when parsing usernames which can trigger a denial-of-service. The domain portion of a username may be overridden causing an allocated memory area the size of the domain name to be leaked. An attacker can leak memory via the main `gss_accept_sec_context` entry point, potentially causing a denial-of-service. This issue is fixed in version 1.2.0.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25566|2023-02-14T17:35:48.482Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 17:35:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
