<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Bentley -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/bentley/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Bentley -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 16:24:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28302|2024-08-03T05:48:37.939Z -- bentley -- microstation%20connect
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28302</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Bentley MicroStation CONNECT 10.16.02.34. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of IFC files. Crafted data in an IFC file can trigger a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-16446.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28302|2024-08-03T05:48:37.939Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28313|2024-08-03T05:48:37.890Z -- bentley -- microstation%20connect
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28313</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Bentley MicroStation CONNECT 10.16.02.034. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of 3DS files. Crafted data in a 3DS file can trigger a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-16343.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28313|2024-08-03T05:48:37.890Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28317|2024-08-03T05:48:37.970Z -- bentley -- microstation%20connect
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28317</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Bentley MicroStation CONNECT 10.16.02.34. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of IFC files. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of memory prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-16369.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28317|2024-08-03T05:48:37.970Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28312|2024-08-03T05:48:37.910Z -- bentley -- microstation%20connect
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28312</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Bentley MicroStation CONNECT 10.16.02.034. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of 3DS files. Crafted data in a 3DS file can trigger a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-16342.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28312|2024-08-03T05:48:37.910Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28308|2024-08-03T05:48:38.040Z -- bentley -- view
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28308</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Bentley View 10.16.02.022. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of 3DS files. Crafted data in a 3DS file can trigger a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-16307.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28308|2024-08-03T05:48:38.040Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28311|2024-08-03T05:48:37.943Z -- bentley -- microstation%20connect
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28311</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Bentley MicroStation CONNECT 10.16.02.034. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DXF files. Crafted data in a DXF file can trigger a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-16341.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28311|2024-08-03T05:48:37.943Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28310|2024-08-03T05:48:37.895Z -- bentley -- microstation%20connect
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28310</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Bentley MicroStation CONNECT 10.16.02.034. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of SKP files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-16339.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28310|2024-08-03T05:48:37.895Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28318|2024-08-03T05:48:37.934Z -- bentley -- microstation%20connect
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28318</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Bentley MicroStation CONNECT 10.16.02.34. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of IFC files. Crafted data in an IFC file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-16379.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28318|2024-08-03T05:48:37.934Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28643|2024-08-03T05:56:16.386Z -- bentley -- microstation%20connect
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28643</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Bentley MicroStation CONNECT 10.16.02.34. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DGN files. Crafted data in a DGN file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-16468.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28643|2024-08-03T05:56:16.386Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28315|2024-08-03T05:48:38.094Z -- bentley -- microstation%20connect
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28315</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Bentley MicroStation CONNECT 10.16.02.34. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of IFC files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-16367.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28315|2024-08-03T05:48:38.094Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28641|2024-08-03T05:56:16.399Z -- bentley -- microstation%20connect
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28641</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Bentley MicroStation CONNECT 10.16.02.34. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of IFC files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-16390.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28641|2024-08-03T05:56:16.399Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28314|2024-08-03T05:48:38.086Z -- bentley -- microstation%20connect
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28314</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Bentley MicroStation CONNECT 10.16.02.34. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of IFC files. Crafted data in an IFC file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-16332.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28314|2024-08-03T05:48:38.086Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28642|2024-08-03T05:56:16.416Z -- bentley -- microstation%20connect
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28642</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Bentley MicroStation CONNECT 10.16.02.34. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DGN files. Crafted data in a DGN file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-16424.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28642|2024-08-03T05:56:16.416Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28306|2024-08-03T05:48:37.947Z -- bentley -- microstation%20connect
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28306</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Bentley MicroStation CONNECT 10.16.02.034. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of OBJ files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-16174.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28306|2024-08-03T05:48:37.947Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28305|2024-08-03T05:48:37.887Z -- bentley -- microstation%20connect
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28305</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Bentley MicroStation CONNECT 10.16.02.034. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of OBJ files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-16172.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28305|2024-08-03T05:48:37.887Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28316|2024-08-03T05:48:38.031Z -- bentley -- microstation%20connect
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28316</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Bentley MicroStation CONNECT 10.16.02.34. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of IFC files. Crafted data in an IFC file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-16368.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28316|2024-08-03T05:48:38.031Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28304|2024-08-03T05:48:38.170Z -- bentley -- microstation%20connect
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28304</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Bentley MicroStation CONNECT 10.16.02.034. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of OBJ files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-16171.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28304|2024-08-03T05:48:38.170Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28301|2024-08-03T05:48:37.951Z -- bentley -- microstation%20connect
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28301</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Bentley MicroStation CONNECT 10.16.02.34. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of IFC files. Crafted data in an IFC file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-16392.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28301|2024-08-03T05:48:37.951Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28307|2024-08-03T05:48:38.032Z -- bentley -- view
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28307</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Bentley View 10.16.02.022. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DXF files. Crafted data in a DXF file can trigger a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-16306.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28307|2024-08-03T05:48:38.032Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28319|2024-08-03T05:48:38.041Z -- bentley -- microstation%20connect
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28319</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Bentley MicroStation CONNECT 10.16.02.034. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of 3DM files. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of memory prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-16340.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28319|2024-08-03T05:48:38.041Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28309|2024-08-03T05:48:37.977Z -- bentley -- view
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28309</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Bentley View 10.16.02.022. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of 3DS files. Crafted data in a 3DS file can trigger a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-16308.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28309|2024-08-03T05:48:37.977Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28320|2024-08-03T05:48:37.883Z -- bentley -- view
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28320</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Bentley View 10.16.02.022. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of 3DM files. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of memory prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-16282.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28320|2024-08-03T05:48:37.883Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28647|2024-08-03T05:56:16.439Z -- bentley -- microstation%20connect
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28647</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Bentley MicroStation CONNECT 10.16.2.034. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of IFC files. Crafted data in an IFC file can trigger a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-16573.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28647|2024-08-03T05:56:16.439Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28303|2024-08-03T05:48:37.694Z -- bentley -- view
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28303</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Bentley View 10.16.02.022. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of SKP files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-16280.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28303|2024-08-03T05:48:37.694Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28646|2024-08-03T05:56:16.352Z -- bentley -- microstation%20connect
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28646</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Bentley MicroStation CONNECT 10.16.2.034. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of IFC files. Crafted data in an IFC file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-16570.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28646|2024-08-03T05:56:16.352Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28645|2024-08-03T05:56:16.408Z -- bentley -- microstation%20connect
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28645</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Bentley MicroStation CONNECT 10.16.02.34. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DGN files. Crafted data in a DGN file can trigger a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-16470.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28645|2024-08-03T05:56:16.408Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28644|2024-08-03T05:56:16.301Z -- bentley -- microstation%20connect
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28644</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Bentley MicroStation CONNECT 10.16.02.34. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DGN files. Crafted data in a DGN file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-16469.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28644|2024-08-03T05:56:16.301Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-28300|2024-08-03T05:48:37.922Z -- bentley -- microstation
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28300</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Bentley MicroStation 10.16.02.034 CONNECT. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JP2 images. Crafted data in a JP2 file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-16202.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-28300|2024-08-03T05:48:37.922Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-43653|2024-08-03T13:40:06.143Z -- bentley -- view</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43653</link>
      <description>Bentley View SKP File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Bentley View. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of SKP files. Crafted data in an SKP file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19084.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-43653|2024-08-03T13:40:06.143Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-43656|2024-08-03T13:40:05.639Z -- bentley -- view</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43656</link>
      <description>Bentley View FBX File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Bentley View. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of FBX files. Crafted data in an FBX file can trigger a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18492.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-43656|2024-08-03T13:40:05.639Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:55:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-43652|2024-08-03T13:40:06.413Z -- bentley -- view</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43652</link>
      <description>Bentley View SKP File Parsing Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Bentley View. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of SKP files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18981.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-43652|2024-08-03T13:40:06.413Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-43655|2024-08-03T13:40:06.024Z -- bentley -- view</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43655</link>
      <description>Bentley View FBX File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Bentley View. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of FBX files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18491.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-43655|2024-08-03T13:40:06.024Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-43651|2024-08-03T13:40:05.691Z -- bentley -- view</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43651</link>
      <description>Bentley View SKP File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Bentley View. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of SKP files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18960.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-43651|2024-08-03T13:40:05.691Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44430|2024-06-04T17:19:35.843Z -- bentley -- view</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-44430</link>
      <description>Bentley View SKP File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Bentley View. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of SKP files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19067.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44430|2024-06-04T17:19:35.843Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-44430|2024-08-02T20:07:33.102Z -- bentley -- view</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44430</link>
      <description>Bentley View SKP File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Bentley View. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of SKP files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19067.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-44430|2024-08-02T20:07:33.102Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
