<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Bentley -- ContextCapture</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/bentley/contextcapture.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Bentley -- ContextCapture</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 19:19:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34985|2024-08-04T00:26:55.784Z -- bentley -- contextcapture
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34985</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Bentley ContextCapture 10.18.0.232. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of OBJ files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14785.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34985|2024-08-04T00:26:55.784Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 21:44:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34984|2024-08-04T00:26:55.671Z -- bentley -- contextcapture
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34984</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Bentley ContextCapture 10.18.0.232. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the parsing of OBJ files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14784.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34984|2024-08-04T00:26:55.671Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 21:44:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
