<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Crestron -- Crestron AirMedia, Barco WePresent, Extron ShareLink, Teq AV IT WIPS710, SHARP PN-L703WA, Optoma WPS-Pro, Blackbox HD WPS, InFocus LiteShow3, and InFocus LiteShow4.</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/crestron/crestron%20airmedia%2C%20barco%20wepresent%2C%20extron%20sharelink%2C%20teq%20av%20it%20wips710%2C%20sharp%20pn-l703wa%2C%20optoma%20wps-pro%2C%20blackbox%20hd%20wps%2C%20infocus%20liteshow3%2C%20and%20infocus%20liteshow4..rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Crestron -- Crestron AirMedia, Barco WePresent, Extron ShareLink, Teq AV IT WIPS710, SHARP PN-L703WA, Optoma WPS-Pro, Blackbox HD WPS, InFocus LiteShow3, and InFocus LiteShow4.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 20:23:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3929|2024-08-04T19:26:27.549Z -- crestron -- crestron%20airmedia%2C%20barco%20wepresent%2C%20extron%20sharelink%2C%20teq%20av%20it%20wips710%2C%20sharp%20pn-l703wa%2C%20optoma%20wps-pro%2C%20blackbox%20hd%20wps%2C%20infocus%20liteshow3%2C%20and%20infocus%20liteshow4.
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3929</link>
      <description>The Crestron AM-100 firmware 1.6.0.2, Crestron AM-101 firmware 2.7.0.1, Barco wePresent WiPG-1000P firmware 2.3.0.10, Barco wePresent WiPG-1600W before firmware 2.4.1.19, Extron ShareLink 200/250 firmware 2.0.3.4, Teq AV IT WIPS710 firmware 1.1.0.7, SHARP PN-L703WA firmware 1.4.2.3, Optoma WPS-Pro firmware 1.0.0.5, Blackbox HD WPS firmware 1.0.0.5, InFocus LiteShow3 firmware 1.0.16, and InFocus LiteShow4 2.0.0.7 are vulnerable to command injection via the file_transfer.cgi HTTP endpoint. A remote, unauthenticated attacker can use this vulnerability to execute operating system commands as root.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3929|2024-08-04T19:26:27.549Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 20:21:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-3930|2024-08-04T19:26:27.743Z -- crestron -- crestron%20airmedia%2C%20barco%20wepresent%2C%20extron%20sharelink%2C%20teq%20av%20it%20wips710%2C%20sharp%20pn-l703wa%2C%20optoma%20wps-pro%2C%20blackbox%20hd%20wps%2C%20infocus%20liteshow3%2C%20and%20infocus%20liteshow4.
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-3930</link>
      <description>The Crestron AM-100 firmware 1.6.0.2, Crestron AM-101 firmware 2.7.0.1, Barco wePresent WiPG-1000P firmware 2.3.0.10, Barco wePresent WiPG-1600W before firmware 2.4.1.19, Extron ShareLink 200/250 firmware 2.0.3.4, Teq AV IT WIPS710 firmware 1.1.0.7, SHARP PN-L703WA firmware 1.4.2.3, Optoma WPS-Pro firmware 1.0.0.5, Blackbox HD WPS firmware 1.0.0.5, InFocus LiteShow3 firmware 1.0.16, and InFocus LiteShow4 2.0.0.7 are vulnerable to a stack buffer overflow in libAwgCgi.so's PARSERtoCHAR function. A remote, unauthenticated attacker can use this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code as root via a crafted request to the return.cgi endpoint.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-3930|2024-08-04T19:26:27.743Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 20:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
