<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for openenclave -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/openenclave/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for openenclave -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 17:22:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-15224|2024-08-04T13:08:22.881Z -- openenclave -- openenclave
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-15224</link>
      <description>In Open Enclave before version 0.12.0, an information disclosure vulnerability exists when an enclave application using the syscalls provided by the sockets.edl is loaded by a malicious host application. An attacker who successfully exploited the vulnerability could read privileged data from the enclave heap across trust boundaries. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would have to log on to an affected system and run a specially crafted application. The vulnerability would not allow an attacker to elevate user rights directly, but it could be used to obtain information otherwise considered confidential in an enclave, which could be used in further compromises. The issue has been addressed in version 0.12.0 and the current master branch. Users will need to to recompile their applications against the patched libraries to be protected from this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-15224|2024-08-04T13:08:22.881Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 18:35:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-15107|2024-08-04T13:08:21.928Z -- openenclave -- openenclave
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-15107</link>
      <description>In openenclave before 0.10.0, enclaves that use x87 FPU operations are vulnerable to tampering by a malicious host application. By violating the Linux System V Application Binary Interface (ABI) for such operations, a host app can compromise the execution integrity of some x87 FPU operations in an enclave. Depending on the FPU control configuration of the enclave app and whether the operations are used in secret-dependent execution paths, this vulnerability may also be used to mount a side-channel attack on the enclave. This has been fixed in 0.10.0 and the current master branch. Users will need to recompile their applications against the patched libraries to be protected from this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-15107|2024-08-04T13:08:21.928Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 21:21:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
