<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Gnome -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/gnome/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Gnome -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 08:24:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-1010238|2024-08-05T03:07:18.524Z -- gnome -- pango
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-1010238</link>
      <description>Gnome Pango 1.42 and later is affected by: Buffer Overflow. The impact is: The heap based buffer overflow can be used to get code execution. The component is: function name: pango_log2vis_get_embedding_levels, assignment of nchars and the loop condition. The attack vector is: Bug can be used when application pass invalid utf-8 strings to functions like pango_itemize.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-1010238|2024-08-05T03:07:18.524Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2019 16:42:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-25085|2024-08-05T03:00:18.977Z -- gnome -- gvdb
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25085</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in GNOME gvdb. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function gvdb_table_write_contents_async of the file gvdb-builder.c. The manipulation leads to use after free. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The name of the patch is d83587b2a364eb9a9a53be7e6a708074e252de14. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier VDB-216789 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in GNOME gvdb ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist die Funktion gvdb_table_write_contents_async der Datei gvdb-builder.c. Dank Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine use after free-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Patch wird als d83587b2a364eb9a9a53be7e6a708074e252de14 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-25085|2024-08-05T03:00:18.977Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 06:58:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
