<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Artica PFMS -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/artica%20pfms/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Artica PFMS -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 20:23:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-24518|2024-08-02T10:56:04.392Z -- artica%20pfms -- pandora%20fms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24518</link>
      <description>A Cross-site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Pandora FMS allows an attacker to force authenticated users to send a request to a web application they are currently authenticated against. This issue affects Pandora FMS version 767 and earlier versions on all platforms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-24518|2024-08-02T10:56:04.392Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 10:41:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-24514|2024-08-02T10:56:04.297Z -- artica%20pfms -- pandora%20fms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24514</link>
      <description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Visual Console Module of Pandora FMS could be used to hijack admin users session cookie values, carry out phishing attacks, etc. This issue affects Pandora FMS v767 version and prior versions on all platforms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-24514|2024-08-02T10:56:04.297Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 13:02:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0828|2024-08-02T05:24:34.587Z -- artica%20pfms -- pandora%20fms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0828</link>
      <description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Syslog Section of Pandora FMS allows attacker to cause that users cookie value will be transferred to the attackers users server. This issue affects Pandora FMS v767 version and prior versions on all platforms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0828|2024-08-02T05:24:34.587Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 10:44:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-24516|2024-08-02T10:56:04.230Z -- artica%20pfms -- pandora%20fms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24516</link>
      <description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Pandora FMS Special Days component allows an attacker to use it to steal  the session cookie value of admin users easily with little user interaction. This issue affects Pandora FMS v767 version and prior versions on all platforms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-24516|2024-08-02T10:56:04.230Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 13:03:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2807|2024-08-02T06:33:05.503Z -- artica%20pfms -- pandora%20fms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2807</link>
      <description>Authentication Bypass by Spoofing vulnerability in the password reset process of Pandora FMS allows an unauthenticated attacker to initiate a password reset process for any user account without proper authentication. This issue affects PandoraFMS v771 and prior versions on all platforms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2807|2024-08-02T06:33:05.503Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 11:10:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-24517|2024-08-02T10:56:04.228Z -- artica%20pfms -- pandora%20fms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24517</link>
      <description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in the Pandora FMS File Manager component, allows an attacker to make make use of this issue ( unrestricted file upload ) to execute arbitrary system commands. This issue affects Pandora FMS v767 version and prior versions on all platforms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-24517|2024-08-02T10:56:04.228Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 13:05:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-24515|2024-08-02T10:56:04.284Z -- artica%20pfms -- pandora%20fms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24515</link>
      <description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in API checker of Pandora FMS. Application does not have a check on the URL scheme used while retrieving API URL. Rather than validating the http/https scheme, the application allows other scheme such as file, which could allow a malicious user to fetch internal file content. This issue affects Pandora FMS v767 version and prior versions on all platforms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-24515|2024-08-02T10:56:04.284Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 12:59:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
