<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for Nsasoft -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/nsasoft/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for Nsasoft -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 22:02:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-1184|2024-02-02T13:00:06.720Z -- Nsasoft -- Network Sleuth
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1184</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Nsasoft Network Sleuth 3.0.0.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Registration Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252674 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in Nsasoft Network Sleuth 3.0.0.0 ausgemacht. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Komponente Registration Handler. Durch Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine denial of service-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff muss lokal passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1184|2024-02-02T13:00:06.720Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 13:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1185|2024-02-02T15:31:03.441Z -- Nsasoft -- NBMonitor Network Bandwidth Monitor
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1185</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Nsasoft NBMonitor Network Bandwidth Monitor 1.6.5.0. This affects an unknown part of the component Registration Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252675. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Nsasoft NBMonitor Network Bandwidth Monitor 1.6.5.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Komponente Registration Handler. Mittels dem Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine denial of service-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff muss lokal erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1185|2024-02-02T15:31:03.441Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 15:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0771|2024-01-21T23:00:07.048Z -- Nsasoft -- Product Key Explorer
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0771</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Nsasoft Product Key Explorer 4.0.9 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Registration Handler. The manipulation of the argument Name/Key leads to memory corruption. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-251671. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Nsasoft Product Key Explorer 4.0.9 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Komponente Registration Handler. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments Name/Key mit unbekannten Daten kann eine memory corruption-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff muss lokal angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0771|2024-01-21T23:00:07.048Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 23:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0772|2024-01-21T23:31:04.097Z -- Nsasoft -- ShareAlarmPro
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0772</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Nsasoft ShareAlarmPro 2.1.4 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Registration Handler. The manipulation of the argument Name/Key leads to memory corruption. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-251672. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Nsasoft ShareAlarmPro 2.1.4 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Komponente Registration Handler. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments Name/Key mit unbekannten Daten kann eine memory corruption-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff muss lokal passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0772|2024-01-21T23:31:04.097Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 23:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>