<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Lenovo Group Ltd. -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/lenovo%20group%20ltd./all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Lenovo Group Ltd. -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 21:42:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-9066|2024-09-16T17:14:32.440Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- lenovo%20xclarity%20administrator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9066</link>
      <description>In Lenovo xClarity Administrator versions earlier than 2.1.0, an authenticated LXCA user can, under specific circumstances, inject additional parameters into a specific web API call which can result in privileged command execution within LXCA's underlying operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-9066|2024-09-16T17:14:32.440Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3776|2024-09-16T16:38:02.181Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- help%20mobile%20android%20app
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3776</link>
      <description>Lenovo Help Android mobile app versions earlier than 6.1.2.0327 allowed information to be transmitted over an HTTP channel, permitting others observing the channel to potentially see this information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3776|2024-09-16T16:38:02.181Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3742|2024-09-16T19:51:52.104Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- lenovo%20connect2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3742</link>
      <description>In Lenovo Connect2 versions earlier than 4.2.5.4885 for Windows and 4.2.5.3071 for Android, when an ad-hoc connection is made between two systems for the purpose of sharing files, the password for this ad-hoc connection will be stored in a user-readable location. An attacker with read access to the user's contents could connect to the Connect2 hotspot and see the contents of files while they are being transferred between the two systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3742|2024-09-16T19:51:52.104Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-9063|2024-09-16T20:12:36.388Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- lenovo%20system%20update
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9063</link>
      <description>MapDrv (C:\Program Files\Lenovo\System Update\mapdrv.exe) In Lenovo System Update versions earlier than 5.07.0072 contains a local vulnerability where an attacker entering very large user ID or password can overrun the program's buffer, causing undefined behaviors, such as execution of arbitrary code. No additional privilege is granted to the attacker beyond what is already possessed to run MapDrv.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-9063|2024-09-16T20:12:36.388Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3756|2024-09-16T19:36:23.552Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- thinkpad%20active%20protection%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3756</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation vulnerability was identified in Lenovo Active Protection System for ThinkPad systems versions earlier than 1.82.0.17. An attacker with local privileges could execute code with administrative privileges via an unquoted service path.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3756|2024-09-16T19:36:23.552Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-9065|2024-09-16T17:28:39.870Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- lenovo%20xclarity%20administrator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9065</link>
      <description>In Lenovo xClarity Administrator versions earlier than 2.1.0, an attacker that gains access to the underlying LXCA file system user may be able to retrieve a credential store containing the service processor user names and passwords for servers previously managed by that LXCA instance, and potentially decrypt those credentials more easily than intended.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-9065|2024-09-16T17:28:39.870Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-9070|2024-09-16T19:09:48.146Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- lenovo%20smart%20assistant
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9070</link>
      <description>For the Lenovo Smart Assistant Android app versions earlier than 12.1.82, an attacker with physical access to the smart speaker can, by pressing a specific button sequence, enter factory test mode and enable a web service intended for testing the device. As with most test modes, this provides extra privileges, including changing settings and running code. Lenovo Smart Assistant is an Amazon Alexa-enabled smart speaker developed by Lenovo.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-9070|2024-09-16T19:09:48.146Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3774|2024-09-16T16:48:19.094Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- imm2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3774</link>
      <description>A stack overflow vulnerability was discovered within the web administration service in Integrated Management Module 2 (IMM2) earlier than version 4.70 used in some Lenovo servers and earlier than version 6.60 used in some IBM servers. An attacker providing a crafted user ID and password combination can cause a portion of the authentication routine to overflow its stack, resulting in stack corruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3774|2024-09-16T16:48:19.094Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3759|2024-09-16T19:19:06.707Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- service%20framework%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3759</link>
      <description>The Lenovo Service Framework Android application accepts some responses from the server without proper validation. This exposes the application to man-in-the-middle attacks leading to possible remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3759|2024-09-16T19:19:06.707Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3753|2024-09-16T20:47:47.220Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- desktop%20and%20notebook%20bios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3753</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in some Lenovo products that use UEFI (BIOS) code developed by American Megatrends, Inc. (AMI). With this vulnerability, conditions exist where an attacker with administrative privileges or physical access to a system may be able to run specially crafted code that can allow them to bypass system protections such as Device Guard and Hyper-V.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3753|2024-09-16T20:47:47.220Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-9064|2024-09-16T19:04:25.593Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- lenovo%20xclarity%20administrator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9064</link>
      <description>In Lenovo xClarity Administrator versions earlier than 2.1.0, an authenticated LXCA user may abuse a web API debug call to retrieve the credentials for the System Manager user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-9064|2024-09-16T19:04:25.593Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3748|2024-09-16T18:55:20.530Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- lenovo%20vibe%20and%20lenovo%20china-only%20moto%20mobile%20phones
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3748</link>
      <description>On Lenovo VIBE mobile phones, improper access controls on the nac_server component can be abused in conjunction with CVE-2017-3749 and CVE-2017-3750 to elevate privileges to the root user (commonly known as 'rooting' or "jail breaking" a device).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3748|2024-09-16T18:55:20.530Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3754|2024-09-16T18:12:56.349Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- lenovo%20notebook%20bios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3754</link>
      <description>Some Lenovo brand notebook systems do not have write protections properly configured in the system BIOS. This could enable an attacker with physical or administrative access to a system to be able to flash the BIOS with an arbitrary image and potentially run malicious BIOS code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3754|2024-09-16T18:12:56.349Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-16098|2024-09-16T16:32:37.513Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- various%20thinkpad%20products
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-16098</link>
      <description>In some Lenovo ThinkPads, an unquoted search path vulnerability was found in various versions of the Synaptics Pointing Device driver which could allow unauthorized code execution as a low privilege user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-16098|2024-09-16T16:32:37.513Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3762|2024-09-16T16:24:14.952Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- lenovo%20fingerprint%20manager%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3762</link>
      <description>Sensitive data stored by Lenovo Fingerprint Manager Pro, version 8.01.86 and earlier, including users' Windows logon credentials and fingerprint data, is encrypted using a weak algorithm, contains a hard-coded password, and is accessible to all users with local non-administrative access to the system in which it is installed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3762|2024-09-16T16:24:14.952Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
