<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Lenovo Group Ltd. -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/lenovo%20group%20ltd./all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Lenovo Group Ltd. -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 18:24:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3760|2024-08-05T14:39:40.446Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- service%20framework%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3760</link>
      <description>The Lenovo Service Framework Android application uses a set of nonsecure credentials when performing integrity verification of downloaded applications and/or data. This exposes the application to man-in-the-middle attacks leading to possible remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3760|2024-08-05T14:39:40.446Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-9066|2024-08-05T07:10:47.468Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- lenovo%20xclarity%20administrator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9066</link>
      <description>In Lenovo xClarity Administrator versions earlier than 2.1.0, an authenticated LXCA user can, under specific circumstances, inject additional parameters into a specific web API call which can result in privileged command execution within LXCA's underlying operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-9066|2024-08-05T07:10:47.468Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3767|2024-08-05T14:39:40.326Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- realtek%20audio%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3767</link>
      <description>A local privilege escalation vulnerability was identified in the Realtek audio driver versions prior to 6.0.1.8224 in some Lenovo ThinkPad products. An attacker with local privileges could execute code with administrative privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3767|2024-08-05T14:39:40.326Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3762|2024-08-05T14:39:40.562Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- lenovo%20fingerprint%20manager%20pro
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3762</link>
      <description>Sensitive data stored by Lenovo Fingerprint Manager Pro, version 8.01.86 and earlier, including users' Windows logon credentials and fingerprint data, is encrypted using a weak algorithm, contains a hard-coded password, and is accessible to all users with local non-administrative access to the system in which it is installed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3762|2024-08-05T14:39:40.562Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3774|2024-08-05T14:39:40.967Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- imm2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3774</link>
      <description>A stack overflow vulnerability was discovered within the web administration service in Integrated Management Module 2 (IMM2) earlier than version 4.70 used in some Lenovo servers and earlier than version 6.60 used in some IBM servers. An attacker providing a crafted user ID and password combination can cause a portion of the authentication routine to overflow its stack, resulting in stack corruption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3774|2024-08-05T14:39:40.967Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3751|2024-08-05T14:39:40.626Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- thinkpad%20compact%20usb%20keyboard%20with%20trackpoint%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3751</link>
      <description>An unquoted service path vulnerability was identified in the driver for the ThinkPad Compact USB Keyboard with TrackPoint versions earlier than 1.5.5.0. This could allow an attacker with local privileges to execute code with administrative privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3751|2024-08-05T14:39:40.626Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3756|2024-08-05T14:39:39.640Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- thinkpad%20active%20protection%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3756</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation vulnerability was identified in Lenovo Active Protection System for ThinkPad systems versions earlier than 1.82.0.17. An attacker with local privileges could execute code with administrative privileges via an unquoted service path.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3756|2024-08-05T14:39:39.640Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3742|2024-08-05T14:39:40.707Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- lenovo%20connect2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3742</link>
      <description>In Lenovo Connect2 versions earlier than 4.2.5.4885 for Windows and 4.2.5.3071 for Android, when an ad-hoc connection is made between two systems for the purpose of sharing files, the password for this ad-hoc connection will be stored in a user-readable location. An attacker with read access to the user's contents could connect to the Connect2 hotspot and see the contents of files while they are being transferred between the two systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3742|2024-08-05T14:39:40.707Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3763|2024-08-05T14:39:41.044Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- lenovo%20xclarity%20administrator%20%28lxca%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3763</link>
      <description>An attacker who obtains access to the location where the LXCA file system is stored may be able to access credentials of local LXCA accounts in LXCA versions earlier than 1.3.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3763|2024-08-05T14:39:41.044Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3746|2024-08-05T14:39:41.081Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- thinkpad%20usb%203.0%20ethernet%20adapter%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3746</link>
      <description>ThinkPad USB 3.0 Ethernet Adapter (part number 4X90E51405) driver, various versions, was found to contain a privilege escalation vulnerability that could allow a local user to execute arbitrary code with administrative or system level privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3746|2024-08-05T14:39:41.081Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-9070|2024-08-05T07:17:50.627Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- lenovo%20smart%20assistant
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9070</link>
      <description>For the Lenovo Smart Assistant Android app versions earlier than 12.1.82, an attacker with physical access to the smart speaker can, by pressing a specific button sequence, enter factory test mode and enable a web service intended for testing the device. As with most test modes, this provides extra privileges, including changing settings and running code. Lenovo Smart Assistant is an Amazon Alexa-enabled smart speaker developed by Lenovo.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-9070|2024-08-05T07:17:50.627Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3752|2024-08-05T14:39:41.295Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- lenovo%20and%20ibm%20switch%20products
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3752</link>
      <description>An industry-wide vulnerability has been identified in the implementation of the Open Shortest Path First (OSPF) routing protocol used on some Lenovo switches. Exploitation of these implementation flaws may result in attackers being able to erase or alter the routing tables of one or many routers, switches, or other devices that support OSPF within a routing domain.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3752|2024-08-05T14:39:41.295Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-16098|2024-08-05T10:17:38.214Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- various%20thinkpad%20products
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-16098</link>
      <description>In some Lenovo ThinkPads, an unquoted search path vulnerability was found in various versions of the Synaptics Pointing Device driver which could allow unauthorized code execution as a low privilege user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-16098|2024-08-05T10:17:38.214Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3758|2024-08-05T14:39:40.738Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- service%20framework%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3758</link>
      <description>Improper access controls on several Android components in the Lenovo Service Framework application can be exploited to enable remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3758|2024-08-05T14:39:40.738Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-9067|2024-08-05T07:17:50.327Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- lenovo%20help%20android%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9067</link>
      <description>The Lenovo Help Android app versions earlier than 6.1.2.0327 had insufficient access control for some functions which, if exploited, could have led to exposure of approximately 400 email addresses and 8,500 IMEI.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-9067|2024-08-05T07:17:50.327Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3776|2024-08-05T14:39:41.081Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- help%20mobile%20android%20app
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3776</link>
      <description>Lenovo Help Android mobile app versions earlier than 6.1.2.0327 allowed information to be transmitted over an HTTP channel, permitting others observing the channel to potentially see this information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3776|2024-08-05T14:39:41.081Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3749|2024-08-05T14:39:41.080Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- lenovo%20vibe%20and%20lenovo%20china-only%20moto%20mobile%20phones
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3749</link>
      <description>On Lenovo VIBE mobile phones, the Idea Friend Android application allows private data to be backed up and restored via Android Debug Bridge, which allows tampering leading to privilege escalation in conjunction with CVE-2017-3748 and CVE-2017-3750.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3749|2024-08-05T14:39:41.080Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3741|2024-08-05T14:39:40.937Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- power%20management%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3741</link>
      <description>In the Lenovo Power Management driver before 1.67.12.24, a local user may alter the trackpoint's firmware and stop the trackpoint from functioning correctly. This issue only affects ThinkPad X1 Carbon 5th generation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3741|2024-08-05T14:39:40.937Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3747|2024-08-05T14:39:41.074Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- lenovo%20nerve%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3747</link>
      <description>Privilege escalation vulnerability in Lenovo Nerve Center for Windows 10 on Desktop systems (Lenovo Nerve Center for notebook systems is not affected) that could allow an attacker with local privileges on a system to alter registry keys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3747|2024-08-05T14:39:41.074Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3771|2024-08-05T14:39:40.932Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- e95%2C%20thinkcentre%20m710s%2Fm710t
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3771</link>
      <description>System boot process is not adequately secured In Lenovo E95 and ThinkCentre M710s/M710t because systems were shipped from factory without completing BIOS/UEFI initialization process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3771|2024-08-05T14:39:40.932Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3765|2024-08-05T14:39:41.059Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- enterprise%20network%20operating%20system%20affecting%20lenovo%20and%20ibm%20rackswitch%20and%20bladecenter%20products
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3765</link>
      <description>In Enterprise Networking Operating System (ENOS) in Lenovo and IBM RackSwitch and BladeCenter products, an authentication bypass known as "HP Backdoor" was discovered during a Lenovo security audit in the serial console, Telnet, SSH, and Web interfaces. This bypass mechanism can be accessed when performing local authentication under specific circumstances. If exploited, admin-level access to the switch is granted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3765|2024-08-05T14:39:41.059Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3770|2024-08-05T14:39:39.676Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- lenovo%20xclarity%20administrator%20%28lxca%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3770</link>
      <description>Privilege escalation vulnerability in LXCA versions earlier than 1.3.2 where an authenticated user may be able to abuse certain web interface functionality to execute privileged commands within the underlying LXCA operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3770|2024-08-05T14:39:39.676Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3740|2024-08-05T14:39:40.912Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- active%20protection%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3740</link>
      <description>In Lenovo Active Protection System before 1.82.0.14, an attacker with local privileges could send commands to the system's embedded controller, which could cause a denial of service attack on the system or the ability to alter hardware functionality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3740|2024-08-05T14:39:40.912Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3759|2024-08-05T14:39:40.715Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- service%20framework%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3759</link>
      <description>The Lenovo Service Framework Android application accepts some responses from the server without proper validation. This exposes the application to man-in-the-middle attacks leading to possible remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3759|2024-08-05T14:39:40.715Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-9065|2024-08-05T07:10:47.362Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- lenovo%20xclarity%20administrator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9065</link>
      <description>In Lenovo xClarity Administrator versions earlier than 2.1.0, an attacker that gains access to the underlying LXCA file system user may be able to retrieve a credential store containing the service processor user names and passwords for servers previously managed by that LXCA instance, and potentially decrypt those credentials more easily than intended.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-9065|2024-08-05T07:10:47.362Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3753|2024-08-05T14:39:39.608Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- desktop%20and%20notebook%20bios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3753</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in some Lenovo products that use UEFI (BIOS) code developed by American Megatrends, Inc. (AMI). With this vulnerability, conditions exist where an attacker with administrative privileges or physical access to a system may be able to run specially crafted code that can allow them to bypass system protections such as Device Guard and Hyper-V.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3753|2024-08-05T14:39:39.608Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3750|2024-08-05T14:39:40.389Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- lenovo%20vibe%20and%20lenovo%20china-only%20moto%20mobile%20phones
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3750</link>
      <description>On Lenovo VIBE mobile phones, the Lenovo Security Android application allows private data to be backed up and restored via Android Debug Bridge, which allows tampering leading to privilege escalation in conjunction with CVE-2017-3748 and CVE-2017-3749.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3750|2024-08-05T14:39:40.389Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3754|2024-08-05T14:39:40.296Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- lenovo%20notebook%20bios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3754</link>
      <description>Some Lenovo brand notebook systems do not have write protections properly configured in the system BIOS. This could enable an attacker with physical or administrative access to a system to be able to flash the BIOS with an arbitrary image and potentially run malicious BIOS code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3754|2024-08-05T14:39:40.296Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3743|2024-08-05T14:39:40.750Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- toolscenter
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3743</link>
      <description>If multiple users are concurrently logged into a single system where one user is sending a command via the Lenovo ToolsCenter Advanced Settings Utility (ASU), UpdateXpress System Pack Installer (UXSPI) or Dynamic System Analysis (DSA) to a second machine, the other users may be able to see the user ID and clear text password that were used to access the second machine during the time the command is processing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3743|2024-08-05T14:39:40.750Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3745|2024-08-05T14:39:41.321Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- xclarity%20administrator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3745</link>
      <description>In Lenovo XClarity Administrator (LXCA) before 1.3.0, if service data is downloaded from LXCA, a non-administrative user may have access to password information for users that have previously authenticated to the LXCA's internal LDAP server, including administrative accounts and service accounts with administrative privileges. This is an issue only for users who have used local authentication with LXCA and not remote authentication against external LDAP or ADFS servers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3745|2024-08-05T14:39:41.321Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-9068|2024-08-05T07:17:50.331Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- system%20x%20imm2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9068</link>
      <description>The IMM2 First Failure Data Capture function collects management module logs and diagnostic information when a hardware error is detected. This information is made available for download through an SFTP server hosted on the IMM2 management network interface. In versions earlier than 4.90 for Lenovo System x and earlier than 6.80 for IBM System x, the credentials to access the SFTP server are hard-coded and described in the IMM2 documentation, allowing an attacker with management network access to obtain the collected FFDC data. After applying the update, the IMM2 will create random SFTP credentials for use with OneCLI.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-9068|2024-08-05T07:17:50.331Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-9063|2024-08-05T07:10:47.364Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- lenovo%20system%20update
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9063</link>
      <description>MapDrv (C:\Program Files\Lenovo\System Update\mapdrv.exe) In Lenovo System Update versions earlier than 5.07.0072 contains a local vulnerability where an attacker entering very large user ID or password can overrun the program's buffer, causing undefined behaviors, such as execution of arbitrary code. No additional privilege is granted to the attacker beyond what is already possessed to run MapDrv.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-9063|2024-08-05T07:10:47.364Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3757|2024-08-05T14:39:39.686Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- lenovo%20elantech%20touchpad%20driver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3757</link>
      <description>An unquoted service path vulnerability was identified in the driver for the ElanTech Touchpad, various versions, used on some Lenovo brand notebooks (not ThinkPads). This could allow an attacker with local privileges to execute code with administrative privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3757|2024-08-05T14:39:39.686Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3744|2024-08-05T14:39:41.051Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- lenovo%20system%20x%20imm2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3744</link>
      <description>In the IMM2 firmware of Lenovo System x servers, remote commands issued by LXCA or other utilities may be captured in the First Failure Data Capture (FFDC) service log if the service log is generated when that remote command is running. Captured command data may contain clear text login information. Authorized users that can capture and export FFDC service log data may have access to these remote commands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3744|2024-08-05T14:39:41.051Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3775|2024-08-05T14:39:39.687Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- some%20lenovo%20flex%20system%20and%20lenovo%20system%20x%20products
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3775</link>
      <description>Some Lenovo System x server BIOS/UEFI versions, when Secure Boot mode is enabled by a system administrator, do not properly authenticate signed code before booting it. As a result, an attacker with physical access to the system could boot unsigned code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3775|2024-08-05T14:39:39.687Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3768|2024-08-05T14:39:41.107Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- integrated%20management%20module%202%20%28imm2%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3768</link>
      <description>An unprivileged attacker with connectivity to the IMM2 could cause a denial of service attack on the IMM2 (Versions earlier than 4.4 for Lenovo System x and earlier than 6.4 for IBM System x). Flooding the IMM2 with a high volume of authentication failures via the Common Information Model (CIM) used by LXCA and OneCLI and other tools can exhaust available system memory which can cause the IMM2 to reboot itself until the requests cease.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3768|2024-08-05T14:39:41.107Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-9064|2024-08-05T07:10:47.368Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- lenovo%20xclarity%20administrator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9064</link>
      <description>In Lenovo xClarity Administrator versions earlier than 2.1.0, an authenticated LXCA user may abuse a web API debug call to retrieve the credentials for the System Manager user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-9064|2024-08-05T07:10:47.368Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3748|2024-08-05T14:39:39.676Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- lenovo%20vibe%20and%20lenovo%20china-only%20moto%20mobile%20phones
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3748</link>
      <description>On Lenovo VIBE mobile phones, improper access controls on the nac_server component can be abused in conjunction with CVE-2017-3749 and CVE-2017-3750 to elevate privileges to the root user (commonly known as 'rooting' or "jail breaking" a device).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3748|2024-08-05T14:39:39.676Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3761|2024-08-05T14:39:41.039Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- service%20framework%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3761</link>
      <description>The Lenovo Service Framework Android application executes some system commands without proper sanitization of external input. In certain cases, this could lead to command injection which, in turn, could lead to remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3761|2024-08-05T14:39:41.039Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-9062|2024-08-05T07:10:47.415Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- some%20lenovo%20thinkpads
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9062</link>
      <description>In some Lenovo ThinkPad products, one BIOS region is not properly included in the checks, allowing injection of arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-9062|2024-08-05T07:10:47.415Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3764|2024-08-05T14:39:40.402Z -- lenovo%20group%20ltd. -- xclarity%20administrator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3764</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was identified in Lenovo XClarity Administrator (LXCA) before 1.4.0 where LXCA user account names may be exposed to unauthenticated users with access to the LXCA web user interface. No password information of the user accounts is exposed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3764|2024-08-05T14:39:40.402Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
