<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for QDocs -- Smart School Management System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/qdocs/smart%20school%20management%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for QDocs -- Smart School Management System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 19:21:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8784|2024-09-13T18:31:09.898Z -- qdocs -- smart%20school%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8784</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in QDocs Smart School Management System 7.0.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /user/chat/mynewuser of the component Chat. The manipulation of the argument users[] with the input 1'+AND+(SELECT+3220+FROM+(SELECT(SLEEP(5)))ZNun)+AND+'WwBM'%3d'WwBM as part of POST Request Parameter leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 7.0.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.
In QDocs Smart School Management System 7.0.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei /user/chat/mynewuser der Komponente Chat. Durch Manipulation des Arguments users[] mit der Eingabe 1'+AND+(SELECT+3220+FROM+(SELECT(SLEEP(5)))ZNun)+AND+'WwBM'%3d'WwBM durch POST Request Parameter kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 7.0.1 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8784|2024-09-13T18:31:09.898Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 18:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
