<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for matrix-org -- matrix-js-sdk</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/matrix-org/matrix-js-sdk.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for matrix-org -- matrix-js-sdk</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 18:24:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29529|2024-08-02T14:14:38.965Z -- matrix-org -- matrix-js-sdk
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29529</link>
      <description>matrix-js-sdk is the Matrix Client-Server SDK for JavaScript and TypeScript. An attacker present in a room where an MSC3401 group call is taking place can eavesdrop on the video and audio of participants using matrix-js-sdk, without their knowledge. To affected matrix-js-sdk users, the attacker will not appear to be participating in the call. This attack is possible because matrix-js-sdk's group call implementation accepts incoming direct calls from other users, even if they have not yet declared intent to participate in the group call, as a means of resolving a race condition in call setup. Affected versions do not restrict access to the user's outbound media in this case. Legacy 1:1 calls are unaffected. This is fixed in matrix-js-sdk 24.1.0. As a workaround, users may hold group calls in private rooms where only the exact users who are expected to participate in the call are present.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29529|2024-08-02T14:14:38.965Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 18:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28427|2024-08-02T12:38:25.414Z -- matrix-org -- matrix-js-sdk
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28427</link>
      <description>matrix-js-sdk is a Matrix messaging protocol Client-Server SDK for JavaScript. In versions prior to 24.0.0 events sent with special strings in key places can temporarily disrupt or impede the matrix-js-sdk from functioning properly, potentially impacting the consumer's ability to process data safely. Note that the matrix-js-sdk can appear to be operating normally but be excluding or corrupting runtime data presented to the consumer. This vulnerability is distinct from GHSA-rfv9-x7hh-xc32 which covers a similar issue. The issue has been patched in matrix-js-sdk 24.0.0 and users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28427|2024-08-02T12:38:25.414Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 20:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
