<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for matrix-org -- matrix-react-sdk</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/matrix-org/matrix-react-sdk.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for matrix-org -- matrix-react-sdk</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 18:25:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28103|2024-08-02T12:30:24.072Z -- matrix-org -- matrix-react-sdk
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28103</link>
      <description>matrix-react-sdk is a Matrix chat protocol SDK for React Javascript. In certain configurations, data sent by remote servers containing special strings in key locations could cause modifications of the `Object.prototype`, disrupting matrix-react-sdk functionality, causing denial of service and potentially affecting program logic. This is fixed in matrix-react-sdk 3.69.0 and users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability. Note this advisory is distinct from GHSA-2x9c-qwgf-94xr which refers to a similar issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28103|2024-08-02T12:30:24.072Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 20:37:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-30609|2024-08-02T14:28:51.679Z -- matrix-org -- matrix-react-sdk
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30609</link>
      <description>matrix-react-sdk is a react-based SDK for inserting a Matrix chat/VoIP client into a web page. Prior to version 3.71.0, plain text messages containing HTML tags are rendered as HTML in the search results. To exploit this, an attacker needs to trick a user into searching for a specific message containing an HTML injection payload. No cross-site scripting attack is possible due to the hardcoded content security policy. Version 3.71.0 of the SDK patches over the issue. As a workaround, restarting the client will clear the HTML injection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-30609|2024-08-02T14:28:51.679Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 20:58:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37259|2024-08-02T17:09:33.537Z -- matrix-org -- matrix-react-sdk
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37259</link>
      <description>matrix-react-sdk is a react-based SDK for inserting a Matrix chat/voip client into a web page. The Export Chat feature includes certain attacker-controlled elements in the generated document without sufficient escaping, leading to stored Cross site scripting (XSS). Since the Export Chat feature generates a separate document, an attacker can only inject code run from the `null` origin, restricting the impact. However, the attacker can still potentially use the XSS to leak message contents. A malicious homeserver is a potential attacker since the affected inputs are controllable server-side. This issue has been addressed in commit `22fcd34c60` which is included in release version 3.76.0. Users are advised to upgrade. The only known workaround for this issue is to disable or to not use the Export Chat feature.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37259|2024-08-02T17:09:33.537Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 16:59:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
