<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for matrix-org -- synapse</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/matrix-org/synapse.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for matrix-org -- synapse</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:23:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41281|2024-08-04T03:08:31.942Z -- matrix-org -- synapse
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41281</link>
      <description>Synapse is a package for Matrix homeservers written in Python 3/Twisted. Prior to version 1.47.1, Synapse instances with the media repository enabled can be tricked into downloading a file from a remote server into an arbitrary directory. No authentication is required for the affected endpoint. The last 2 directories and file name of the path are chosen randomly by Synapse and cannot be controlled by an attacker, which limits the impact. Homeservers with the media repository disabled are unaffected. Homeservers with a federation whitelist are also unaffected, since Synapse will check the remote hostname, including the trailing `../`s, against the whitelist. Server administrators should upgrade to 1.47.1 or later. Server administrators using a reverse proxy could, at the expense of losing media functionality, may block the certain endpoints as a workaround. Alternatively, non-containerized deployments can be adapted to use the hardened systemd config.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41281|2024-08-04T03:08:31.942Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 19:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39163|2024-08-04T01:58:18.227Z -- matrix-org -- synapse
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39163</link>
      <description>Matrix is an ecosystem for open federated Instant Messaging and Voice over IP. In versions 1.41.0 and prior, unauthorised users can access the name, avatar, topic and number of members of a room if they know the ID of the room. This vulnerability is limited to homeservers where the vulnerable homeserver is in the room and untrusted users are permitted to create groups (communities). By default, only homeserver administrators can create groups. However, homeserver administrators can already access this information in the database or using the admin API. As a result, only homeservers where the configuration setting `enable_group_creation` has been set to `true` are impacted. Server administrators should upgrade to 1.41.1 or higher to patch the vulnerability. There are two potential workarounds. Server administrators can set `enable_group_creation` to `false` in their homeserver configuration (this is the default value) to prevent creation of groups by non-administrators. Administrators that are using a reverse proxy could, with partial loss of group functionality, block the endpoints `/_matrix/client/r0/groups/{group_id}/rooms` and `/_matrix/client/unstable/groups/{group_id}/rooms`.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39163|2024-08-04T01:58:18.227Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 16:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39164|2024-08-04T01:58:18.118Z -- matrix-org -- synapse
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39164</link>
      <description>Matrix is an ecosystem for open federated Instant Messaging and Voice over IP. In versions 1.41.0 and prior, unauthorised users can access the membership (list of members, with their display names) of a room if they know the ID of the room. The vulnerability is limited to rooms with `shared` history visibility. Furthermore, the unauthorised user must be using an account on a vulnerable homeserver that is in the room. Server administrators should upgrade to 1.41.1 or later in order to receive the patch. One workaround is available. Administrators of servers that use a reverse proxy could, with potentially unacceptable loss of functionality, block the endpoints: `/_matrix/client/r0/rooms/{room_id}/members` with `at` query parameter, and `/_matrix/client/unstable/rooms/{room_id}/members` with `at` query parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39164|2024-08-04T01:58:18.118Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 16:20:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26257|2024-08-04T15:56:03.561Z -- matrix-org -- synapse
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26257</link>
      <description>Matrix is an ecosystem for open federated Instant Messaging and VoIP. Synapse is a reference "homeserver" implementation of Matrix. A malicious or poorly-implemented homeserver can inject malformed events into a room by specifying a different room id in the path of a `/send_join`, `/send_leave`, `/invite` or `/exchange_third_party_invite` request. This can lead to a denial of service in which future events will not be correctly sent to other servers over federation. This affects any server which accepts federation requests from untrusted servers. The Matrix Synapse reference implementation before version 1.23.1 the implementation is vulnerable to this injection attack. Issue is fixed in version 1.23.1. As a workaround homeserver administrators could limit access to the federation API to trusted servers (for example via `federation_domain_whitelist`).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26257|2024-08-04T15:56:03.561Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 18:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
