<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for matrix-org -- synapse</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/matrix-org/synapse.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for matrix-org -- synapse</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 23:21:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32682|2024-08-02T15:25:36.434Z -- matrix-org -- synapse
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32682</link>
      <description>Synapse is a Matrix protocol homeserver written in Python with the Twisted framework. In affected versions it may be possible for a deactivated user to login when using uncommon configurations. This only applies if any of the following are true: 1. JSON Web Tokens are enabled for login via the `jwt_config.enabled` configuration setting. 2. The local password database is enabled via the `password_config.enabled` and `password_config.localdb_enabled` configuration settings *and* a user's password is updated via an admin API after a user is deactivated. Note that the local password database is enabled by default, but it is uncommon to set a user's password after they've been deactivated. Installations that are configured to only allow login via Single Sign-On (SSO) via CAS, SAML or OpenID Connect (OIDC); or via an external password provider (e.g. LDAP) are not affected. If not using JSON Web Tokens, ensure that deactivated users do not have a password set. This issue has been addressed in version 1.85.0. Users are advised to upgrade.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32682|2024-08-02T15:25:36.434Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 18:20:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-43796|2024-08-02T19:52:11.374Z -- matrix-org -- synapse
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43796</link>
      <description>Synapse is an open-source Matrix homeserver Prior to versions 1.95.1 and 1.96.0rc1, cached device information of remote users can be queried from Synapse. This can be used to enumerate the remote users known to a homeserver. System administrators are encouraged to upgrade to Synapse 1.95.1 or 1.96.0rc1 to receive a patch. As a workaround, the `federation_domain_whitelist` can be used to limit federation traffic with a homeserver.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-43796|2024-08-02T19:52:11.374Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 16:52:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32323|2024-08-02T15:10:24.899Z -- matrix-org -- synapse
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32323</link>
      <description>Synapse is an open-source Matrix homeserver written and maintained by the Matrix.org Foundation. A malicious user on a Synapse homeserver X with permission to create certain state events can disable outbound federation from X to an arbitrary homeserver Y. Synapse instances with federation disabled are not affected. In versions of Synapse up to and including 1.73, Synapse did not limit the size of `invite_room_state`, meaning that it was possible to create an arbitrarily large invite event. Synapse 1.74 refuses to create oversized `invite_room_state` fields. Server operators should upgrade to Synapse 1.74 or newer urgently.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32323|2024-08-02T15:10:24.899Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 13:32:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41335|2024-08-02T19:01:35.279Z -- matrix-org -- synapse
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41335</link>
      <description>Synapse is an open-source Matrix homeserver written and maintained by the Matrix.org Foundation. When users update their passwords, the new credentials may be briefly held in the server database. While this doesn't grant the server any added capabilities—it already learns the users' passwords as part of the authentication process—it does disrupt the expectation that passwords won't be stored in the database. As a result, these passwords could inadvertently be captured in database backups for a longer duration. These temporarily stored passwords are automatically erased after a 48-hour window. This issue has been addressed in version 1.93.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41335|2024-08-02T19:01:35.279Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 20:51:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-45129|2024-08-02T20:14:19.828Z -- matrix-org -- synapse
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45129</link>
      <description>Synapse is an open-source Matrix homeserver written and maintained by the Matrix.org Foundation. Prior to version 1.94.0, a malicious server ACL event can impact performance temporarily or permanently leading to a persistent denial of service. Homeservers running on a closed federation (which presumably do not need to use server ACLs) are not affected. Server administrators are advised to upgrade to Synapse 1.94.0 or later. As a workaround, rooms with malicious server ACL events can be purged and blocked using the admin API.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-45129|2024-08-02T20:14:19.828Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 17:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-32683|2024-08-02T15:25:36.588Z -- matrix-org -- synapse
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32683</link>
      <description>Synapse is a Matrix protocol homeserver written in Python with the Twisted framework. A discovered oEmbed or image URL can bypass the `url_preview_url_blacklist` setting potentially allowing server side request forgery or bypassing network policies. Impact is limited to IP addresses allowed by the `url_preview_ip_range_blacklist` setting (by default this only allows public IPs) and by the limited information returned to the client: 1. For discovered oEmbed URLs, any non-JSON response or a JSON response which includes non-oEmbed information is discarded. 2. For discovered image URLs, any non-image response is discarded. Systems which have URL preview disabled (via the `url_preview_enabled` setting) or have not configured a `url_preview_url_blacklist` are not affected. This issue has been addressed in version 1.85.0. Users are advised to upgrade. User unable to upgrade may also disable URL previews.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-32683|2024-08-02T15:25:36.588Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 18:24:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42453|2024-08-02T19:23:38.904Z -- matrix-org -- synapse
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42453</link>
      <description>Synapse is an open-source Matrix homeserver written and maintained by the Matrix.org Foundation. Users were able to forge read receipts for any event (if they knew the room ID and event ID). Note that the users were not able to view the events, but simply mark it as read. This could be confusing as clients will show the event as read by the user, even if they are not in the room. This issue has been patched in version 1.93.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42453|2024-08-02T19:23:38.904Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 20:49:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
