<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for matrix-org -- vodozemac</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/matrix-org/vodozemac.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for matrix-org -- vodozemac</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 18:24:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-40640|2024-07-17T17:27:15.586Z -- matrix-org -- vodozemac
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40640</link>
      <description>vodozemac is an open source implementation of Olm and Megolm in pure Rust.  Versions before 0.7.0 of vodozemac use a non-constant time base64 implementation for importing key material for Megolm group sessions and `PkDecryption` Ed25519 secret keys. This flaw might allow an attacker to infer some information about the secret key material through a side-channel attack. The use of a non-constant time base64 implementation might allow an attacker to observe timing variations in the encoding and decoding operations of the secret key material. This could potentially provide insights into the underlying secret key material. The impact of this vulnerability is considered low because exploiting the attacker is required to have access to high precision timing measurements, as well as repeated access to the base64 encoding or decoding processes.  Additionally, the estimated leakage amount is bounded and low according to the referenced paper. This has been patched in commit 734b6c6948d4b2bdee3dd8b4efa591d93a61d272 which has been included in release version 0.7.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-40640|2024-07-17T17:27:15.586Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 17:27:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34063|2024-06-04T17:41:34.387Z -- matrix-org -- vodozemac</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-34063</link>
      <description>vodozemac is an implementation of Olm and Megolm in pure Rust. Versions 0.5.0 and 0.5.1 of vodozemac have degraded secret zeroization capabilities, due to changes in third-party cryptographic dependencies (the Dalek crates), which moved secret zeroization capabilities behind a feature flag and defaulted this feature to off. The degraded zeroization capabilities could result in the production of more memory copies of encryption secrets and secrets could linger in memory longer than necessary. This marginally increases the risk of sensitive data exposure. This issue has been addressed in version 0.6.0 and users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34063|2024-06-04T17:41:34.387Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 09:52:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
