<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Secure Systems Engineering -- Connaisseur</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/secure%20systems%20engineering/connaisseur.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Secure Systems Engineering -- Connaisseur</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 15:23:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7279|2024-09-02T14:00:06.559Z -- secure%20systems%20engineering -- connaisseur
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7279</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Secure Systems Engineering Connaisseur up to 3.3.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file connaisseur/res/targets_schema.json of the component Delegation Name Handler. The manipulation leads to inefficient regular expression complexity. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. Upgrading to version 3.3.1 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is 524b73ff7306707f6d3a4d1e86401479bca91b02. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.
In Secure Systems Engineering Connaisseur bis 3.3.0 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle gefunden. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei connaisseur/res/targets_schema.json der Komponente Delegation Name Handler. Durch die Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine inefficient regular expression complexity-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Das Ausnutzen gilt als schwierig. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 3.3.1 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als 524b73ff7306707f6d3a4d1e86401479bca91b02 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7279|2024-09-02T14:00:06.559Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 14:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
