<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for OnShift -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/onshift/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for OnShift -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:23:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-25101|2024-08-05T03:00:19.286Z -- onshift -- turbogears
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25101</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in OnShift TurboGears 1.0.11.10. This affects an unknown part of the file turbogears/controllers.py of the component HTTP Header Handler. The manipulation leads to http response splitting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 1.0.11.11 is able to address this issue. The patch is named f68bbaba47f4474e1da553aa51564a73e1d92a84. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-220059.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in OnShift TurboGears 1.0.11.10 entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei turbogears/controllers.py der Komponente HTTP Header Handler. Durch Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine http response splitting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 1.0.11.11 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als f68bbaba47f4474e1da553aa51564a73e1d92a84 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-25101|2024-08-05T03:00:19.286Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 07:57:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
