<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for NREL -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/nrel/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for NREL -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 19:19:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2015-10080|2024-07-18T15:25:28.544Z -- nrel -- api-umbrella-web
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-10080</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in NREL api-umbrella-web 0.7.1. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the component Admin Data Table Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 0.8.0 is able to address this issue. The patch is named f53a9fb87e10c457f0f3dd4f2af24d3b2f21b3ca. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-221487.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in NREL api-umbrella-web 0.7.1 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Komponente Admin Data Table Handler. Mit der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 0.8.0 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als f53a9fb87e10c457f0f3dd4f2af24d3b2f21b3ca bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2015-10080|2024-07-18T15:25:28.544Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 09:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
