<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for IBM -- BigFix Platform</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ibm/bigfix%20platform.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for IBM -- BigFix Platform</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 13:23:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1475|2024-08-05T03:59:39.164Z -- ibm -- bigfix%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1475</link>
      <description>IBM BigFix Platform 9.2 and 9.5 uses an inadequate account lockout setting that could allow a remote attacker to brute force account credentials. IBM X-Force ID: 140756.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1475|2024-08-05T03:59:39.164Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1473|2024-08-05T03:59:39.090Z -- ibm -- bigfix%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1473</link>
      <description>IBM BigFix Platform 9.2 and 9.5 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session. IBM X-Force ID: 140691.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1473|2024-08-05T03:59:39.090Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1474|2024-08-05T03:59:39.064Z -- ibm -- bigfix%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1474</link>
      <description>IBM BigFix Platform 9.2.0 through 9.2.14 and 9.5 through 9.5.9 is vulnerable to HTTP response splitting attacks, caused by improper validation of user-supplied input. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to inject arbitrary HTTP headers and cause the server to return a split response, once the URL is clicked. This would allow the attacker to perform further attacks, such as Web cache poisoning or cross-site scripting, and possibly obtain sensitive information. IBM X-force ID: 140692.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1474|2024-08-05T03:59:39.064Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1480|2024-08-05T03:59:39.142Z -- ibm -- bigfix%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1480</link>
      <description>IBM BigFix Platform 9.2.0 through 9.2.14 and 9.5 through 9.5.9 does not set the 'HttpOnly' attribute on authorization tokens or session cookies. If a Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability also existed attackers may be able to get the cookie values via malicious JavaScript and then hijack the user session. IBM X-Force ID: 140762.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1480|2024-08-05T03:59:39.142Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1600|2024-08-05T04:07:43.845Z -- ibm -- bigfix%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1600</link>
      <description>IBM BigFix Platform 9.2 and 9.5 transmits sensitive or security-critical data in clear text in a communication channel that can be sniffed by unauthorized actors. IBM X-Force ID: 143745.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1600|2024-08-05T04:07:43.845Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1481|2024-08-05T03:59:39.053Z -- ibm -- bigfix%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1481</link>
      <description>IBM BigFix Platform 9.2.0 through 9.2.14 and 9.5 through 9.5.9 stores sensitive information in URL parameters. This may lead to information disclosure if unauthorized parties have access to the URLs via server logs, referrer header or browser history. IBM X-Force ID: 140763.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1481|2024-08-05T03:59:39.053Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1478|2024-08-05T03:59:39.145Z -- ibm -- bigfix%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1478</link>
      <description>IBM BigFix Platform 9.2.0 through 9.2.14 and 9.5 through 9.5.9 could allow a remote attacker to hijack the clicking action of the victim. By persuading a victim to visit a malicious Web site, a remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to hijack the victim's click actions and possibly launch further attacks against the victim. IBM X-Force ID: 140760.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1478|2024-08-05T03:59:39.145Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1476|2024-08-05T03:59:39.158Z -- ibm -- bigfix%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1476</link>
      <description>IBM BigFix Platform 9.2.0 through 9.2.14 and 9.5 through 9.5.9 discloses sensitive information to unauthorized users. The information can be used to mount further attacks on the system. IBM X-Force ID: 140757.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1476|2024-08-05T03:59:39.158Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1484|2024-08-05T03:59:39.100Z -- ibm -- bigfix%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1484</link>
      <description>IBM BigFix Platform 9.2.0 through 9.2.14 and 9.5 through 9.5.9 does not set the secure attribute on authorization tokens or session cookies. Attackers may be able to get the cookie values by sending a http:// link to a user or by planting this link in a site the user goes to. The cookie will be sent to the insecure link and the attacker can then obtain the cookie value by snooping the traffic. IBM X-Force ID: 140969.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1484|2024-08-05T03:59:39.100Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1485|2024-08-05T03:59:39.086Z -- ibm -- bigfix%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1485</link>
      <description>IBM BigFix Platform 9.2.0 through 9.2.14 and 9.5 through 9.5.9 does not renew a session variable after a successful authentication which could lead to session fixation/hijacking vulnerability. This could force a user to utilize a cookie that may be known to an attacker. IBM X-Force ID: 140970.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1485|2024-08-05T03:59:39.086Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2005|2024-08-05T04:14:39.683Z -- ibm -- bigfix%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2005</link>
      <description>IBM BigFix Platform 9.2 and 9.5 stores potentially sensitive information in process memory that could be read by a local attacker with elevated permissions. IBM X-Force ID: 155007</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2005|2024-08-05T04:14:39.683Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1479|2024-08-05T03:59:39.098Z -- ibm -- bigfix%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1479</link>
      <description>IBM BigFix Platform 9.2 and 9.5 is vulnerable to cross-site request forgery which could allow an attacker to execute malicious and unauthorized actions transmitted from a user that the website trusts. IBM X-Force ID: 140761.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1479|2024-08-05T03:59:39.098Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
