<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for IBM -- BigFix family</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ibm/bigfix%20family.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for IBM -- BigFix family</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 22:22:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-1223|2024-08-05T13:25:17.478Z -- ibm -- bigfix%20family
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-1223</link>
      <description>IBM Tivoli Endpoint Manager could allow a remote attacker to conduct phishing attacks, using an open redirect attack. By persuading a victim to visit a specially-crafted Web site, a remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to spoof the URL displayed to redirect a user to a malicious Web site that would appear to be trusted. This could allow the attacker to obtain highly sensitive information or conduct further attacks against the victim. IBM X-Force ID: 123902.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-1223|2024-08-05T13:25:17.478Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-1224|2024-08-05T13:25:17.464Z -- ibm -- bigfix%20family
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-1224</link>
      <description>IBM Tivoli Endpoint Manager uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt highly sensitive information. IBM X-Force ID: 123903.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-1224|2024-08-05T13:25:17.464Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-1219|2024-08-05T13:25:17.451Z -- ibm -- bigfix%20family
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-1219</link>
      <description>IBM Tivoli Endpoint Manager is vulnerable to a XML External Entity Injection (XXE) attack when processing XML data. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to expose sensitive information or consume memory resources. IBM X-Force ID: 123859.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-1219|2024-08-05T13:25:17.451Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-1218|2024-08-05T13:25:17.627Z -- ibm -- bigfix%20family
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-1218</link>
      <description>IBM Tivoli Endpoint Manager is vulnerable to cross-site request forgery which could allow an attacker to execute malicious and unauthorized actions transmitted from a user that the website trusts. IBM X-Force ID: 123858.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-1218|2024-08-05T13:25:17.627Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-1203|2024-08-05T13:25:17.424Z -- ibm -- bigfix%20family
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-1203</link>
      <description>IBM Tivoli Endpoint Manager (for Lifecycle/Power/Patch) Platform and Applications is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session. IBM X-Force ID: 123678.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-1203|2024-08-05T13:25:17.424Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-1229|2024-08-05T13:25:17.578Z -- ibm -- bigfix%20family
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-1229</link>
      <description>IBM Tivoli Endpoint Manager (IBM BigFix 9.2 and 9.5) could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information, caused by the failure to properly enable HTTP Strict Transport Security. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to obtain sensitive information using man in the middle techniques. IBM X-Force ID: 123908.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-1229|2024-08-05T13:25:17.578Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
