<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for IBM -- Cloud Orchestrator</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ibm/cloud%20orchestrator.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for IBM -- Cloud Orchestrator</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:23:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-4396|2024-08-04T19:33:38.213Z -- ibm -- cloud%20orchestrator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-4396</link>
      <description>IBM Cloud Orchestrator 2.4 through 2.4.0.5 and 2.5 through 2.5.0.9 is vulnerable to HTTP response splitting attacks, caused by improper validation of user-supplied input. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to inject arbitrary HTTP headers and cause the server to return a split response, once the URL is clicked. This would allow the attacker to perform further attacks, such as Web cache poisoning or cross-site scripting, and possibly obtain sensitive information. IBM X-Force ID: 162236.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-4396|2024-08-04T19:33:38.213Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-4394|2024-08-04T19:33:37.927Z -- ibm -- cloud%20orchestrator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-4394</link>
      <description>IBM Cloud Orchestrator 2.4 through 2.4.0.5 and 2.5 through 2.5.0.9 contain APIs that could be used by a local user to send email. IBM X-Force ID: 162232.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-4394|2024-08-04T19:33:37.927Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-4395|2024-08-04T19:33:37.981Z -- ibm -- cloud%20orchestrator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-4395</link>
      <description>IBM Cloud Orchestrator 2.4 through 2.4.0.5 and 2.5 through 2.5.0.9 could allow a local user to obtain sensitive information from temporary script files. IBM X-Force ID: 162333.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-4395|2024-08-04T19:33:37.981Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-4459|2024-08-04T19:33:38.278Z -- ibm -- cloud%20orchestrator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-4459</link>
      <description>IBM Cloud Orchestrator and IBM Cloud Orchestrator Enterprise 2.5 through 2.5.0.9 and 2.4 through 2.4.0.5 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session. IBM X-Force ID: 163656.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-4459|2024-08-04T19:33:38.278Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-4461|2024-08-04T19:33:38.203Z -- ibm -- cloud%20orchestrator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-4461</link>
      <description>IBM Cloud Orchestrator 2.4 through 2.4.0.5 and 2.5 through 2.5.0.9 is vulnerable to HTTP Response Splitting caused by improper caching of content. This would allow the attacker to perform further attacks, such as Web Cache poisoning, cross-site scripting and possibly obtain sensitive information. IBM X-Force ID: 163682.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-4461|2024-08-04T19:33:38.203Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-4400|2024-08-04T19:33:37.972Z -- ibm -- cloud%20orchestrator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-4400</link>
      <description>IBM Cloud Orchestrator 2.4 through 2.4.0.5 and 2.5 through 2.5.0.9 could allow a remote attacker to traverse directories on the system. An attacker could send a specially-crafted URL request containing "dot dot" sequences (/../) to view arbitrary files on the system. IBM X-Force ID: 162261.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-4400|2024-08-04T19:33:37.972Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-4399|2024-08-04T19:33:38.449Z -- ibm -- cloud%20orchestrator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-4399</link>
      <description>IBM Cloud Orchestrator 2.4 through 2.4.0.5 and 2.5 through 2.5.0.9 uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt highly sensitive information. IBM X-Force ID: 162260.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-4399|2024-08-04T19:33:38.449Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-4398|2024-08-04T19:33:38.214Z -- ibm -- cloud%20orchestrator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-4398</link>
      <description>IBM Cloud Orchestrator and IBM Cloud Orchestrator Enterprise 2.5 through 2.5.0.9 and 2.4 through 2.4.0.5 could allow a local user to obtain sensitive information from SessionManagement cookies. IBM X-Force ID: 162259.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-4398|2024-08-04T19:33:38.214Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-4397|2024-08-04T19:33:38.291Z -- ibm -- cloud%20orchestrator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-4397</link>
      <description>IBM Cloud Orchestrator and IBM Cloud Orchestrator Enterprise 2.5 through 2.5.0.9 and 2.4 through 2.4.0.5 stores sensitive information in URL parameters. This may lead to information disclosure if unauthorized parties have access to the URLs via server logs, referrer header or browser history. IBM X-Force ID: 162239</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-4397|2024-08-04T19:33:38.291Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
