<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for IBM -- Curam SPM</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ibm/curam%20spm.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for IBM -- Curam SPM</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 20:22:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4775|2024-08-04T08:14:58.013Z -- ibm -- curam%20spm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4775</link>
      <description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability may impact IBM Curam Social Program Management 7.0.9 and 7.0.10. This vulnerability allows attackers to inject malicious scripts into web applications for the purpose of running unwanted actions on the end user's device, restricted to a single location. IBM X-Force ID: 189153.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4775|2024-08-04T08:14:58.013Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4942|2024-08-04T08:14:59.166Z -- ibm -- curam%20spm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4942</link>
      <description>IBM Curam Social Program Management 7.0.9 and 7.0.11 is vulnerable to cross-site request forgery which could allow an attacker to execute malicious and unauthorized actions transmitted from a user that the website trusts. IBM X-Force ID: 191942.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4942|2024-08-04T08:14:59.166Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4772|2024-08-04T08:14:58.933Z -- ibm -- curam%20spm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4772</link>
      <description>An XML External Entity Injection (XXE) vulnerability may impact IBM Curam Social Program Management 7.0.9 and 7.0.10. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to expose sensitive information, denial of service, server side request forgery or consume memory resources. IBM X-Force ID: 189150.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4772|2024-08-04T08:14:58.933Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4780|2024-08-04T08:14:58.970Z -- ibm -- curam%20spm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4780</link>
      <description>OOTB build scripts does not set the secure attribute on session cookie which may impact IBM Curam Social Program Management 7.0.9 and 7.0,10. The purpose of the 'secure' attribute is to prevent cookies from being observed by unauthorized parties. IBM X-Force ID: 189158.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4780|2024-08-04T08:14:58.970Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4778|2024-08-04T08:14:59.257Z -- ibm -- curam%20spm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4778</link>
      <description>IBM Curam Social Program Management 7.0.9 and 7.0.10 uses MD5 algorithm for hashing token in a single instance which less safe than default SHA-256 cryptographic algorithm used throughout the Cúram application. IBM X-Force ID: 189156.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4778|2024-08-04T08:14:59.257Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4774|2024-08-04T08:14:59.404Z -- ibm -- curam%20spm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4774</link>
      <description>An XPath vulnerability may impact IBM Curam Social Program Management 7.0.9 and 7.0.10, caused by the improper handling of user-supplied input. By sending a specially-crafted input, a remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to obtain unauthorized access or reveal sensitive information such as XML document structure and content. IBM X-Force ID: 189152.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4774|2024-08-04T08:14:59.404Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4773|2024-08-04T08:14:58.631Z -- ibm -- curam%20spm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4773</link>
      <description>A cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability may impact IBM Curam Social Program Management 7.0.9 and 7.0.10, which is an attack that forces a user to execute unwanted actions on the web application while they are currently authenticated. This applies to a single server class only, with no impact to remainder of web application. IBM X-Force ID: 189151.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4773|2024-08-04T08:14:58.631Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4781|2024-08-04T08:14:59.002Z -- ibm -- curam%20spm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4781</link>
      <description>An improper input validation before calling java readLine() method may impact IBM Curam Social Program Management 7.0.9 and 7.0.10, which could result in a denial of service. IBM X-Force ID: 189159.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4781|2024-08-04T08:14:59.002Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4776|2024-08-04T08:14:57.793Z -- ibm -- curam%20spm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4776</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability may impact IBM Curam Social Program Management 7.0.9 and 7.0.10, which could allow a remote attacker to traverse directories on the system. An attacker could send a specially-crafted file path in URL request to view arbitrary files on the system. IBM X-Force ID: 189154.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4776|2024-08-04T08:14:57.793Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4779|2024-08-04T08:14:58.980Z -- ibm -- curam%20spm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4779</link>
      <description>A HTTP Verb Tampering vulnerability may impact IBM Curam Social Program Management 7.0.9 and 7.0.10. By sending a specially-crafted request, an attacker could exploit this vulnerability to bypass security access controls. IBM X-Force ID: 189156.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4779|2024-08-04T08:14:58.980Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
