<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for IBM -- Planning Analytics</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ibm/planning%20analytics.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for IBM -- Planning Analytics</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 19:20:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-4612|2024-09-16T17:15:17.474Z -- ibm -- planning%20analytics
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-4612</link>
      <description>IBM Planning Analytics 2.0 is vulnerable to malicious file upload in the My Account Portal. Attackers can make use of this weakness and upload malicious executable files into the system and it can be sent to victim for performing further attacks. IBM X-Force ID: 168523.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-4612|2024-09-16T17:15:17.474Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 22:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4645|2024-09-16T17:08:03.138Z -- ibm -- planning%20analytics
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4645</link>
      <description>IBM Planning Analytics Local 2.0.0 through 2.0.9.1 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session. IBM X-Force ID: 185717.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4645|2024-09-16T17:08:03.138Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 14:05:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-4611|2024-09-16T18:33:37.269Z -- ibm -- planning%20analytics
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-4611</link>
      <description>IBM Planning Analytics 2.0 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session. IBM X-Force ID: 168519.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-4611|2024-09-16T18:33:37.269Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 22:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-4613|2024-09-16T17:33:04.222Z -- ibm -- planning%20analytics
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-4613</link>
      <description>IBM Planning Analytics 2.0 is vulnerable to cross-site request forgery which could allow an attacker to execute malicious and unauthorized actions transmitted from a user that the website trusts. IBM X-Force ID: 168524.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-4613|2024-09-16T17:33:04.222Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 15:20:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4644|2024-09-16T16:53:00.771Z -- ibm -- planning%20analytics
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4644</link>
      <description>IBM Planning Analytics Local 2.0.0 through 2.0.9.1 could allow a remote attacker to hijack the clicking action of the victim. By persuading a victim to visit a malicious Web site, a remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to hijack the victim's click actions and possibly launch further attacks against the victim. IBM X-Force ID: 185716.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4644|2024-09-16T16:53:00.771Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 14:05:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4653|2024-09-16T16:17:49.998Z -- ibm -- planning%20analytics
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4653</link>
      <description>IBM Planning Analytics 2.0 could allow a remote attacker to conduct phishing attacks, using an open redirect attack. By persuading a victim to visit a specially-crafted Web site, a remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to spoof the URL displayed to redirect a user to a malicious Web site that would appear to be trusted. This could allow the attacker to obtain highly sensitive information or conduct further attacks against the victim.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4653|2024-09-16T16:17:49.998Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 12:35:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22308|2024-09-16T18:13:10.537Z -- ibm -- planning%20analytics
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22308</link>
      <description>IBM Planning Analytics 2.0 is vulnerable to a Remote File Include (RFI) attack. User input could be passed into file include commands and the web application could be tricked into including remote files with malicious code. IBM X-Force ID: 216891.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22308|2024-09-16T18:13:10.537Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 18:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
