<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for IBM -- Rational Collaborative Lifecycle Management</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ibm/rational%20collaborative%20lifecycle%20management.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for IBM -- Rational Collaborative Lifecycle Management</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 18:24:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1658|2024-09-16T16:14:06.764Z -- ibm -- rational%20collaborative%20lifecycle%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1658</link>
      <description>IBM Jazz Foundation (IBM Rational Collaborative Lifecycle Management 5.0 through 6.0.6) is vulnerable to HTTP header injection, caused by improper validation of input. By persuading a victim to visit a specially-crafted Web page, a remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to inject arbitrary HTTP headers, which will allow the attacker to conduct various attacks against the vulnerable system, including cross-site scripting, cache poisoning or session hijacking. IBM X-Force ID: 144884.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1658|2024-09-16T16:14:06.764Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-4250|2024-09-16T17:28:19.282Z -- ibm -- rational%20collaborative%20lifecycle%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-4250</link>
      <description>IBM Jazz Foundation products (IBM Rational Collaborative Lifecycle Management 6.0 through 6.0.6.1) is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session. IBM X-Force ID: 159648.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-4250|2024-09-16T17:28:19.282Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 13:45:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-1237|2024-09-16T16:37:58.397Z -- ibm -- rational%20collaborative%20lifecycle%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-1237</link>
      <description>IBM Jazz based applications are vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session. IBM X-Force ID: 124355.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-1237|2024-09-16T16:37:58.397Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-1365|2024-09-16T17:54:32.885Z -- ibm -- rational%20collaborative%20lifecycle%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-1365</link>
      <description>IBM Team Concert (RTC including IBM Rational Collaborative Lifecycle Management 4.0, 5.0., and 6.0) is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session. IBM X-force ID: 126858.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-1365|2024-09-16T17:54:32.885Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-29713|2024-09-16T16:32:30.155Z -- ibm -- rational%20collaborative%20lifecycle%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-29713</link>
      <description>IBM Jazz Team Server products are vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-29713|2024-09-16T16:32:30.155Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 16:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-20346|2024-09-16T16:12:46.143Z -- ibm -- rational%20collaborative%20lifecycle%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-20346</link>
      <description>IBM Jazz Foundation and IBM Engineering products are vulnerable to server-side request forgery (SSRF). This may allow an authenticated attacker to send unauthorized requests from the system, potentially leading to network enumeration or facilitating other attacks. IBM X-Force ID: 194595.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-20346|2024-09-16T16:12:46.143Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 20:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-1281|2024-09-16T16:38:07.993Z -- ibm -- rational%20collaborative%20lifecycle%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-1281</link>
      <description>IBM Rational Quality Manager and IBM Rational Collaborative Lifecycle Management 5.0 through 5.0.2 and 6.0 through 6.0.5 are vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session. IBM X-Force ID: 124759.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-1281|2024-09-16T16:38:07.993Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1688|2024-09-16T16:58:12.505Z -- ibm -- rational%20collaborative%20lifecycle%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1688</link>
      <description>IBM Jazz Foundation (IBM Rational Collaborative Lifecycle Management 5.0 through 6.0.6) is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session. IBM X-Force ID: 145509.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1688|2024-09-16T16:58:12.505Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1762|2024-09-16T17:33:37.367Z -- ibm -- rational%20collaborative%20lifecycle%20management
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1762</link>
      <description>IBM Rational Collaborative Lifecycle Management 5.0 through 5.0.2 and 6.0 through 6.0.6 are vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session. IBM X-Force ID: 148616.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1762|2024-09-16T17:33:37.367Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
