<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for IBM -- Rational Team Concert</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ibm/rational%20team%20concert.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for IBM -- Rational Team Concert</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 18:24:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-1113|2024-09-17T04:09:11.479Z -- ibm -- rational%20team%20concert
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-1113</link>
      <description>IBM Rational Team Concert (RTC) 4.0, 5.0 and 6.0 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session. IBM X-Force ID: 121151.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-1113|2024-09-17T04:09:11.479Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-20351|2024-09-17T00:10:34.504Z -- ibm -- rational%20team%20concert
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-20351</link>
      <description>IBM Engineering products are vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session. IBM X-Force ID: 194708.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-20351|2024-09-17T00:10:34.504Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 19:05:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-20504|2024-09-17T00:46:59.724Z -- ibm -- rational%20team%20concert
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-20504</link>
      <description>IBM Jazz Foundation Products are vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session. IBM X-Force ID: 198231.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-20504|2024-09-17T00:46:59.724Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 16:45:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1606|2024-09-17T00:46:10.633Z -- ibm -- rational%20team%20concert
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1606</link>
      <description>IBM Jazz based applications (IBM Rational Collaborative Lifecycle Management 5.0 through 5.02 and 6.0 through 6.0.6, IBM Rational DOORS Next Generation 5.0 through 5.02 and 6.0 through 6.0.6, IBM Rational Engineering Lifecycle Manager 5.0 through 5.02 and 6.0 through 6.0.6, IBM Rational Quality Manager 5.0 through 5.02 and 6.0 through 6.0.6, IBM Rational Rhapsody Design Manager 5.0 through 5.02 and 6.0 through 6.0.6, IBM Rational Software Architect Design Manager 5.0 through 5.02 and 6.0 through 6.0.1, IBM Rational Team Concert 5.0 through 5.02 and 6.0 through 6.0.6) could allow an authenticated user to obtain sensitive information from an error message that could be used in further attacks against the system. IBM X-Force ID: 143796.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1606|2024-09-17T00:46:10.633Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1694|2024-09-17T00:40:43.367Z -- ibm -- rational%20team%20concert
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1694</link>
      <description>IBM Jazz applications (IBM Rational Collaborative Lifecycle Management 5.0 through 5.02 and 6.0 through 6.0.6, IBM Rational DOORS Next Generation 5.0 through 5.02 and 6.0 through 6.0.6, IBM Rational Engineering Lifecycle Manager 5.0 through 5.02 and 6.0 through 6.0.6, IBM Rational Quality Manager 5.0 through 5.02 and 6.0 through 6.0.6, IBM Rational Rhapsody Design Manager 5.0 through 5.02 and 6.0 through 6.0.6, IBM Rational Software Architect Design Manager 5.0 through 5.02 and 6.0 through 6.0.1, IBM Rational Team Concert 5.0 through 5.02 and 6.0 through 6.0.6) could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information, caused by the failure to properly enable HTTP Strict Transport Security. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to obtain sensitive information using man in the middle techniques. IBM X-Force ID: 145609.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1694|2024-09-17T00:40:43.367Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-4747|2024-09-17T01:36:43.856Z -- ibm -- rational%20team%20concert
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-4747</link>
      <description>IBM Team Concert (RTC) is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session. IBM X-Force ID: 172887.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-4747|2024-09-17T01:36:43.856Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 15:05:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-9746|2024-09-17T02:57:21.831Z -- ibm -- rational%20team%20concert
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-9746</link>
      <description>IBM Team Concert (RTC) 4.0, 5.0 and 6.0 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session. IBM X-Force ID: 119821.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-9746|2024-09-17T02:57:21.831Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-29673|2024-09-17T00:45:51.739Z -- ibm -- rational%20team%20concert
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-29673</link>
      <description>IBM Jazz Team Server products are vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session. IBM X-Force ID: 199482.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-29673|2024-09-17T00:45:51.739Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 16:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4697|2024-09-17T03:34:13.410Z -- ibm -- rational%20team%20concert
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4697</link>
      <description>IBM Jazz Foundation products are vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session. IBM X-Force ID: 186790.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4697|2024-09-17T03:34:13.410Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 20:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1407|2024-09-17T03:33:05.708Z -- ibm -- rational%20team%20concert
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1407</link>
      <description>IBM Rational Team Concert 5.0 through 5.0.2 and 6.0 through 6.0.5 are vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session. IBM X-Force ID: 138445.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1407|2024-09-17T03:33:05.708Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-1700|2024-09-17T03:48:55.534Z -- ibm -- rational%20team%20concert
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-1700</link>
      <description>IBM Jazz Team Server affecting the following IBM Rational Products: Collaborative Lifecycle Management (CLM), Rational DOORS Next Generation (RDNG), Rational Engineering Lifecycle Manager (RELM), Rational Team Concert (RTC), Rational Quality Manager (RQM), Rational Rhapsody Design Manager (Rhapsody DM), and Rational Software Architect (RSA DM) could allow an authenticated user to cause a denial of service due to incorrect authorization for resource intensive scenarios. IBM X-Force ID: 134392.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-1700|2024-09-17T03:48:55.534Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1983|2024-09-17T01:31:51.060Z -- ibm -- rational%20team%20concert
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1983</link>
      <description>IBM Rational Team Concert 5.0 through 6.0.6 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session. IBM X-Force ID: 154136.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1983|2024-09-17T01:31:51.060Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
