<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for IBM -- Robotic Process Automation with Automation Anywhere</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ibm/robotic%20process%20automation%20with%20automation%20anywhere.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for IBM -- Robotic Process Automation with Automation Anywhere</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 17:23:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1877|2024-08-05T04:14:38.723Z -- ibm -- robotic%20process%20automation%20with%20automation%20anywhere
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1877</link>
      <description>IBM Robotic Process Automation with Automation Anywhere 11 could store highly sensitive information in the form of unencrypted passwords that would be available to a local user. IBM X-Force ID: 151713.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1877|2024-08-05T04:14:38.723Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1514|2024-08-05T04:07:42.906Z -- ibm -- robotic%20process%20automation%20with%20automation%20anywhere
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1514</link>
      <description>IBM Robotic Process Automation with Automation Anywhere 10.0 is vulnerable to cross-site request forgery which could allow an attacker to execute malicious and unauthorized actions transmitted from a user that the website trusts. IBM X-Force ID: 141622.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1514|2024-08-05T04:07:42.906Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-2006|2024-08-05T04:14:39.579Z -- ibm -- robotic%20process%20automation%20with%20automation%20anywhere
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-2006</link>
      <description>IBM Robotic Process Automation with Automation Anywhere 11 could allow a remote attacker to traverse directories on the system. An attacker could send a specially-crafted URL request containing "dot dot" sequences (/../) to upload arbitrary files to the system. IBM X-Force ID: 155008.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-2006|2024-08-05T04:14:39.579Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1547|2024-08-05T04:07:43.779Z -- ibm -- robotic%20process%20automation%20with%20automation%20anywhere
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1547</link>
      <description>IBM Robotic Process Automation with Automation Anywhere 10.0 could allow a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code on the system, caused by improper output encoding in an CSV export. By persuading a victim to download the CSV export, to open it in Microsoft Excel and to confirm the two security questions, an attacker could exploit this vulnerability to run any command or program on the victim's machine. IBM X-Force ID: 142651.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1547|2024-08-05T04:07:43.779Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1795|2024-08-05T04:14:38.394Z -- ibm -- robotic%20process%20automation%20with%20automation%20anywhere
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1795</link>
      <description>IBM Robotic Process Automation with Automation Anywhere Enterprise 10 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session. IBM X-Force ID: 149073.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1795|2024-08-05T04:14:38.394Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1552|2024-08-05T04:07:43.396Z -- ibm -- robotic%20process%20automation%20with%20automation%20anywhere
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1552</link>
      <description>IBM Robotic Process Automation with Automation Anywhere 10.0 and 11.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code on the system, caused by a missing restriction in which file types can be uploaded to the control room. By uploading a malicious file and tricking a victim to run it, an attacker could exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code on the system. IBM X-Force ID: 142889.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1552|2024-08-05T04:07:43.396Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1812|2024-08-05T04:14:38.525Z -- ibm -- robotic%20process%20automation%20with%20automation%20anywhere
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1812</link>
      <description>IBM Robotic Process Automation with Automation Anywhere Enterprise 10 is vulnerable to persistent cross-site scripting, caused by missing escaping of a database field. An attacker that has access to the Control Room database could exploit this vulnerability to execute script in a victim's web browser within the security context of the hosting Web site, once victim opens a certain page in Control Room. IBM X-Force ID: 149883.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1812|2024-08-05T04:14:38.525Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1876|2024-08-05T04:14:38.537Z -- ibm -- robotic%20process%20automation%20with%20automation%20anywhere
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1876</link>
      <description>IBM Robotic Process Automation with Automation Anywhere 11 could under certain cases, display the password in a Control Room log file after installation. IBM X-Force ID: 151707.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1876|2024-08-05T04:14:38.537Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1878|2024-08-05T04:14:38.757Z -- ibm -- robotic%20process%20automation%20with%20automation%20anywhere
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1878</link>
      <description>IBM Robotic Process Automation with Automation Anywhere 11 could disclose sensitive information in a web request that could aid in future attacks against the system. IBM X-Force ID: 151714.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1878|2024-08-05T04:14:38.757Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-1751|2024-08-05T13:39:32.280Z -- ibm -- robotic%20process%20automation%20with%20automation%20anywhere
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-1751</link>
      <description>IBM Robotic Process Automation with Automation Anywhere 10.0.0 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session. IBM X-Force ID: 135546.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-1751|2024-08-05T13:39:32.280Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1908|2024-08-05T04:14:38.776Z -- ibm -- robotic%20process%20automation%20with%20automation%20anywhere
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1908</link>
      <description>IBM Robotic Process Automation with Automation Anywhere 11 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session. IBM X-Force ID: 152671.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1908|2024-08-05T04:14:38.776Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
