<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for IBM -- Security Access Manager</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ibm/security%20access%20manager.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for IBM -- Security Access Manager</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 09:23:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-1474|2024-09-17T01:06:25.459Z -- ibm -- security%20access%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-1474</link>
      <description>IBM Security Access Manager Appliance 7.0.0, 8.0.0 through 8.0.1.6, and 9.0.0 through 9.0.3.1 discloses sensitive information to unauthorized users. The information can be used to mount further attacks on the system. IBM X-Force ID: 128606.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-1474|2024-09-17T01:06:25.459Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-4153|2024-09-17T00:50:37.050Z -- ibm -- security%20access%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-4153</link>
      <description>IBM Security Access Manager 9.0.1 through 9.0.6 could allow a remote attacker to conduct phishing attacks, using an open redirect attack. By persuading a victim to visit a specially-crafted Web site, a remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to spoof the URL displayed to redirect a user to a malicious Web site that would appear to be trusted. This could allow the attacker to obtain highly sensitive information or conduct further attacks against the victim. IBM X-Force ID: 158517.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-4153|2024-09-17T00:50:37.050Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 15:45:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-1478|2024-09-17T00:56:40.475Z -- ibm -- security%20access%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-1478</link>
      <description>IBM Security Access Manager Appliance 9.0.0 allows web pages to be stored locally which can be read by another user on the system. IBM X-Force ID: 128613.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-1478|2024-09-17T00:56:40.475Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-4145|2024-09-17T02:31:05.131Z -- ibm -- security%20access%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-4145</link>
      <description>IBM Security Access Manager 9.0.1 through 9.0.6 could reveal highly sensitive in specialized conditions to a local user which could be used in further attacks against the system. IBM X-Force ID: 158400.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-4145|2024-09-17T02:31:05.131Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 15:45:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-4150|2024-09-17T00:56:34.677Z -- ibm -- security%20access%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-4150</link>
      <description>IBM Security Access Manager 9.0.1 through 9.0.6 does not validate, or incorrectly validates, a certificate which could allow an attacker to spoof a trusted entity by using a man-in-the-middle (MITM) attack. IBM X-Force ID: 158510.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-4150|2024-09-17T00:56:34.677Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 15:45:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-1534|2024-09-17T00:05:31.546Z -- ibm -- security%20access%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-1534</link>
      <description>IBM Security Access Manager Appliance 8.0.0 and 9.0.0 could allow a remote attacker to conduct phishing attacks, using an open redirect attack. By persuading a victim to visit a specially-crafted Web site, a remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to spoof the URL displayed to redirect a user to a malicious Web site that would appear to be trusted. This could allow the attacker to obtain highly sensitive information or conduct further attacks against the victim. IBM X-Force ID: 130676.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-1534|2024-09-17T00:05:31.546Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-4036|2024-09-17T01:41:17.545Z -- ibm -- security%20access%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-4036</link>
      <description>IBM Security Access Manager Appliance could allow unauthenticated attacker to cause a denial of service in the reverse proxy component. IBM X-Force ID: 156159.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-4036|2024-09-17T01:41:17.545Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 16:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-1453|2024-09-17T02:01:14.772Z -- ibm -- security%20access%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-1453</link>
      <description>IBM Security Access Manager Appliance 9.0.3 could allow a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the system. By sending a specially-crafted request, an attacker could exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary commands on the system. IBM X-Force ID: 128372.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-1453|2024-09-17T02:01:14.772Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-1459|2024-09-17T00:07:01.089Z -- ibm -- security%20access%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-1459</link>
      <description>IBM Security Access Manager Appliance 8.0.0 and 9.0.0 specifies permissions for a security-critical resource in a way that allows that resource to be read or modified by unintended actors. IBM X-Force ID: 128378.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-1459|2024-09-17T00:07:01.089Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
