<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for IBM -- Security Identity Governance and Intelligence</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ibm/security%20identity%20governance%20and%20intelligence.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for IBM -- Security Identity Governance and Intelligence</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 20:22:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-1396|2024-08-05T13:32:30.135Z -- ibm -- security%20identity%20governance%20and%20intelligence
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-1396</link>
      <description>IBM Security Identity Governance Virtual Appliance 5.2 through 5.2.3.2 specifies permissions for a security-critical resource in a way that allows that resource to be read or modified by unintended actors. IBM X-Force ID: 127342.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-1396|2024-08-05T13:32:30.135Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-1368|2024-08-05T13:32:29.426Z -- ibm -- security%20identity%20governance%20and%20intelligence
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-1368</link>
      <description>IBM Security Identity Governance Virtual Appliance 5.2 through 5.2.3.2 does not set the secure attribute on authorization tokens or session cookies. Attackers may be able to get the cookie values by sending a http:// link to a user or by planting this link in a site the user goes to. The cookie will be sent to the insecure link and the attacker can then obtain the cookie value by snooping the traffic. IBM X-Force ID: 126861.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-1368|2024-08-05T13:32:29.426Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-1409|2024-08-05T13:32:30.286Z -- ibm -- security%20identity%20governance%20and%20intelligence
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-1409</link>
      <description>IBM Security Identity Governance Virtual Appliance 5.2 through 5.2.3.2 discloses sensitive information to unauthorized users. The information can be used to mount further attacks on the system. IBM X-Force ID: 127396.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-1409|2024-08-05T13:32:30.286Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-1367|2024-08-05T13:32:29.666Z -- ibm -- security%20identity%20governance%20and%20intelligence
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-1367</link>
      <description>IBM Security Identity Governance and Intelligence Virtual Appliance 5.2 through 5.2.3.2 stores sensitive information in URL parameters. This may lead to information disclosure if unauthorized parties have access to the URLs via server logs, referrer header or browser history. IBM X-Force ID: 126860.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-1367|2024-08-05T13:32:29.666Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-1412|2024-08-05T13:32:30.227Z -- ibm -- security%20identity%20governance%20and%20intelligence
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-1412</link>
      <description>IBM Security Identity Governance Virtual Appliance 5.2 through 5.2.3.2 generates an error message that includes sensitive information about its environment, users, or associated data. IBM X-Force ID: 127400.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-1412|2024-08-05T13:32:30.227Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-1411|2024-08-05T13:32:29.854Z -- ibm -- security%20identity%20governance%20and%20intelligence
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-1411</link>
      <description>IBM Security Identity Governance Virtual Appliance 5.2 through 5.2.3.2 does not require that users should have strong passwords by default, which makes it easier for attackers to compromise user accounts. IBM X-Force ID: 127399.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-1411|2024-08-05T13:32:29.854Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-1755|2024-08-05T13:39:32.311Z -- ibm -- security%20identity%20governance%20and%20intelligence
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-1755</link>
      <description>IBM Security Identity Governance Virtual Appliance 5.2 through 5.2.3.2 could allow a local attacker to inject commands into malicious files that could be executed by the administrator. IBM X-Force ID: 135855.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-1755|2024-08-05T13:39:32.311Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1944|2024-08-05T04:14:39.618Z -- ibm -- security%20identity%20governance%20and%20intelligence
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1944</link>
      <description>IBM Security Identity Governance and Intelligence 5.2 through 5.2.4.1 Virtual Appliance contains hard-coded credentials, such as a password or cryptographic key, which it uses for its own inbound authentication, outbound communication to external components, or encryption of internal data. IBM X-Force ID: 153386.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1944|2024-08-05T04:14:39.618Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1948|2024-08-05T04:14:39.586Z -- ibm -- security%20identity%20governance%20and%20intelligence
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1948</link>
      <description>IBM Security Identity Governance and Intelligence 5.2 through 5.2.4.1 Virtual Appliance does not set the secure attribute on authorization tokens or session cookies. Attackers may be able to get the cookie values by sending a http:// link to a user or by planting this link in a site the user goes to. The cookie will be sent to the insecure link and the attacker can then obtain the cookie value by snooping the traffic. IBM X-Force ID: 153428.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1948|2024-08-05T04:14:39.586Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1949|2024-08-05T04:14:39.582Z -- ibm -- security%20identity%20governance%20and%20intelligence
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1949</link>
      <description>IBM Security Identity Governance and Intelligence 5.2 through 5.2.4.1 Virtual Appliance discloses sensitive information to unauthorized users. The information can be used to mount further attacks on the system. IBM X-Force ID: 153429.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1949|2024-08-05T04:14:39.582Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1950|2024-08-05T04:14:39.523Z -- ibm -- security%20identity%20governance%20and%20intelligence
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1950</link>
      <description>IBM Security Identity Governance and Intelligence 5.2 through 5.2.4.1 Virtual Appliance generates an error message that includes sensitive information about its environment, users, or associated data which could be used in further attacks against the system. IBM X-Force ID: 153430.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1950|2024-08-05T04:14:39.523Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-1366|2024-08-05T13:32:29.637Z -- ibm -- security%20identity%20governance%20and%20intelligence
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-1366</link>
      <description>IBM Security Identity Governance Virtual Appliance 5.2 through 5.2.3.2 uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt highly sensitive information. IBM X-Force ID: 126859.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-1366|2024-08-05T13:32:29.637Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1947|2024-08-05T04:14:39.515Z -- ibm -- security%20identity%20governance%20and%20intelligence
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1947</link>
      <description>IBM Security Identity Governance and Intelligence 5.2 through 5.2.4.1 Virtual Appliance is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session. IBM X-Force ID: 153427.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1947|2024-08-05T04:14:39.515Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1756|2024-08-05T04:07:44.309Z -- ibm -- security%20identity%20governance%20and%20intelligence
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1756</link>
      <description>IBM Security Identity Governance and Intelligence 5.2.3.2 and 5.2.4 is vulnerable to SQL injection. A remote attacker could send specially-crafted SQL statements, which could allow the attacker to view, information in the back-end database. IBM X-Force ID: 148599.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1756|2024-08-05T04:07:44.309Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-1395|2024-08-05T13:32:29.672Z -- ibm -- security%20identity%20governance%20and%20intelligence
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-1395</link>
      <description>IBM Security Identity Governance and Intelligence Virtual Appliance 5.2 through 5.2.3.2 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information, caused by the failure to properly enable HTTP Strict Transport Security. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to obtain sensitive information using man in the middle techniques. IBM X-Force ID: 127341.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-1395|2024-08-05T13:32:29.672Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1945|2024-08-05T04:14:39.462Z -- ibm -- security%20identity%20governance%20and%20intelligence
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1945</link>
      <description>IBM Security Identity Governance and Intelligence 5.2 through 5.2.4.1 Virtual Appliance could allow a remote attacker to hijack the clicking action of the victim. By persuading a victim to visit a malicious Web site, a remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to hijack the victim's click actions and possibly launch further attacks against the victim. IBM X-Force ID: 153387.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1945|2024-08-05T04:14:39.462Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1757|2024-08-05T04:07:44.386Z -- ibm -- security%20identity%20governance%20and%20intelligence
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1757</link>
      <description>IBM Security Identity Governance and Intelligence 5.2.3.2 and 5.2.4 could allow an attacker to obtain sensitive information due to missing authentication in IGI for the survey application. IBM X-Force ID: 148601.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1757|2024-08-05T04:07:44.386Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1946|2024-08-05T04:14:39.394Z -- ibm -- security%20identity%20governance%20and%20intelligence
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1946</link>
      <description>IBM Security Identity Governance and Intelligence 5.2 through 5.2.4.1 Virtual Appliance supports interaction between multiple actors and allows those actors to negotiate which algorithm should be used as a protection mechanism such as encryption or authentication, but it does not select the strongest algorithm that is available to both parties. IBM X-Force ID: 153388.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1946|2024-08-05T04:14:39.394Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
