<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for IBM -- Security Access Manager</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ibm/security%20access%20manager.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for IBM -- Security Access Manager</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:22:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-1473|2024-08-05T13:32:29.637Z -- ibm -- security%20access%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-1473</link>
      <description>IBM Security Access Manager Appliance 8.0.0 through 8.0.1.6 and 9.0.0 through 9.0.3.1 uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt highly sensitive information. IBM X-Force ID: 128605.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-1473|2024-08-05T13:32:29.637Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-1534|2024-08-05T13:32:29.662Z -- ibm -- security%20access%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-1534</link>
      <description>IBM Security Access Manager Appliance 8.0.0 and 9.0.0 could allow a remote attacker to conduct phishing attacks, using an open redirect attack. By persuading a victim to visit a specially-crafted Web site, a remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to spoof the URL displayed to redirect a user to a malicious Web site that would appear to be trusted. This could allow the attacker to obtain highly sensitive information or conduct further attacks against the victim. IBM X-Force ID: 130676.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-1534|2024-08-05T13:32:29.662Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1443|2024-08-05T03:59:39.129Z -- ibm -- security%20access%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1443</link>
      <description>An XML parsing vulnerability affects IBM SAML-based single sign-on (SSO) systems (IBM Security Access Manager 9.0.0 - 9.0.4 and IBM Tivoli Federated Identity Manager 6.2 - 6.0.2.) This vulnerability can allow an attacker with authenticated access to trick SAML systems into authenticating as a different user without knowledge of the victim users password. IBM X-Force ID: 139754.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1443|2024-08-05T03:59:39.129Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-1474|2024-08-05T13:32:29.829Z -- ibm -- security%20access%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-1474</link>
      <description>IBM Security Access Manager Appliance 7.0.0, 8.0.0 through 8.0.1.6, and 9.0.0 through 9.0.3.1 discloses sensitive information to unauthorized users. The information can be used to mount further attacks on the system. IBM X-Force ID: 128606.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-1474|2024-08-05T13:32:29.829Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-1476|2024-08-05T13:32:29.799Z -- ibm -- security%20access%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-1476</link>
      <description>IBM Security Access Manager Appliance 7.0.0, 8.0.0 through 8.0.1.6, and 9.0.0 through 9.0.3.1 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information, caused by the failure to properly enable HTTP Strict Transport Security. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to obtain sensitive information using man in the middle techniques. IBM X-Force ID: 128610.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-1476|2024-08-05T13:32:29.799Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-1533|2024-08-05T13:32:30.277Z -- ibm -- security%20access%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-1533</link>
      <description>IBM Security Access Manager Appliance 9.0.3 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session. IBM X-Force ID: 130675.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-1533|2024-08-05T13:32:30.277Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-1478|2024-08-05T13:32:29.676Z -- ibm -- security%20access%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-1478</link>
      <description>IBM Security Access Manager Appliance 9.0.0 allows web pages to be stored locally which can be read by another user on the system. IBM X-Force ID: 128613.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-1478|2024-08-05T13:32:29.676Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-1453|2024-08-05T13:32:29.617Z -- ibm -- security%20access%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-1453</link>
      <description>IBM Security Access Manager Appliance 9.0.3 could allow a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the system. By sending a specially-crafted request, an attacker could exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary commands on the system. IBM X-Force ID: 128372.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-1453|2024-08-05T13:32:29.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-1480|2024-08-05T13:32:30.276Z -- ibm -- security%20access%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-1480</link>
      <description>IBM Security Access Manager Appliance 8.0.0 through 8.0.1.6, and 9.0.0 through 9.0.3.1 stores potentially sensitive information in log files that could be read by a remote user. IBM X-Force ID: 128617.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-1480|2024-08-05T13:32:30.276Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-1477|2024-08-05T13:32:30.256Z -- ibm -- security%20access%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-1477</link>
      <description>IBM Security Access Manager Appliance 9.0.3 is vulnerable to a XML External Entity Injection (XXE) attack when processing XML data. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to expose sensitive information or consume memory resources. IBM X-Force ID: 128612.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-1477|2024-08-05T13:32:30.256Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-1459|2024-08-05T13:32:30.257Z -- ibm -- security%20access%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-1459</link>
      <description>IBM Security Access Manager Appliance 8.0.0 and 9.0.0 specifies permissions for a security-critical resource in a way that allows that resource to be read or modified by unintended actors. IBM X-Force ID: 128378.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-1459|2024-08-05T13:32:30.257Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
