<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for IBM -- Security Directory Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ibm/security%20directory%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for IBM -- Security Directory Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 20:23:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-4539|2024-08-04T19:40:47.350Z -- ibm -- security%20directory%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-4539</link>
      <description>IBM Security Directory Server 6.4.0 does not properly neutralize special elements that are used in XML, allowing attackers to modify the syntax, content, or commands of the XML before it is processed by an end system. IBM X-Force ID: 165812.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-4539|2024-08-04T19:40:47.350Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-4562|2024-08-04T19:40:48.248Z -- ibm -- security%20directory%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-4562</link>
      <description>IBM Security Directory Server 6.4.0 stores sensitive information in URLs. This may lead to information disclosure if unauthorized parties have access to the URLs via server logs, referer header or browser history. IBM X-Force ID: 166623.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-4562|2024-08-04T19:40:48.248Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-4550|2024-08-04T19:40:47.603Z -- ibm -- security%20directory%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-4550</link>
      <description>IBM Security Directory Server 6.4.0 is deployed with active debugging code that can create unintended entry points. IBM X-Force ID: 165952.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-4550|2024-08-04T19:40:47.603Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-4540|2024-08-04T19:40:47.299Z -- ibm -- security%20directory%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-4540</link>
      <description>IBM Security Directory Server 6.4.0 uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt highly sensitive information. IBM X-Force ID: 165813.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-4540|2024-08-04T19:40:47.299Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-4551|2024-08-04T19:40:47.363Z -- ibm -- security%20directory%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-4551</link>
      <description>IBM Security Directory Server 6.4.0 does not perform an authentication check for a critical resource or functionality allowing anonymous users access to protected areas. IBM X-Force ID: 165953.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-4551|2024-08-04T19:40:47.363Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-4541|2024-08-04T19:40:47.604Z -- ibm -- security%20directory%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-4541</link>
      <description>IBM Security Directory Server 6.4.0 uses incomplete blacklisting for input validation which allows attackers to bypass application controls resulting in direct impact to the system and data integrity. IBM X-Force ID: 165814.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-4541|2024-08-04T19:40:47.604Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-4542|2024-08-04T19:40:47.608Z -- ibm -- security%20directory%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-4542</link>
      <description>IBM Security Directory Server 6.4.0 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session. IBM X-Force ID: 165815.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-4542|2024-08-04T19:40:47.608Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-4520|2024-08-04T19:40:47.255Z -- ibm -- security%20directory%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-4520</link>
      <description>IBM Security Directory Server 6.4.0 uses an inadequate account lockout setting that could allow a remote attacker to brute force account credentials. IBM X-Force ID: 165178.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-4520|2024-08-04T19:40:47.255Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-4549|2024-08-04T19:40:48.734Z -- ibm -- security%20directory%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-4549</link>
      <description>IBM Security Directory Server 6.4.0 discloses sensitive information to unauthorized users. The information can be used to mount further attacks on the system. IBM X-Force ID: 165951.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-4549|2024-08-04T19:40:48.734Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-4547|2024-08-04T19:40:47.465Z -- ibm -- security%20directory%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-4547</link>
      <description>IBM Security Directory Server 6.4.0 generates an error message that includes sensitive information about its environment, users, or associated data. IBM X-Force ID: 165949.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-4547|2024-08-04T19:40:47.465Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-4538|2024-08-04T19:40:47.373Z -- ibm -- security%20directory%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-4538</link>
      <description>IBM Security Directory Server 6.4.0 could allow a remote attacker to conduct phishing attacks, using an open redirect attack. By persuading a victim to visit a specially-crafted Web site, a remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to spoof the URL displayed to redirect a user to a malicious Web site that would appear to be trusted. This could allow the attacker to obtain highly sensitive information or conduct further attacks against the victim. IBM X-Force ID: 165660.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-4538|2024-08-04T19:40:47.373Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-4548|2024-08-04T19:40:47.557Z -- ibm -- security%20directory%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-4548</link>
      <description>IBM Security Directory Server 6.4.0 could allow a remote attacker to hijack the clicking action of the victim. By persuading a victim to visit a malicious Web site, a remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to hijack the victim's click actions and possibly launch further attacks against the victim. IBM X-Force ID: 165950.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-4548|2024-08-04T19:40:47.557Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-4563|2024-08-04T19:40:47.613Z -- ibm -- security%20directory%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-4563</link>
      <description>IBM Security Directory Server 6.4.0 does not set the secure attribute on authorization tokens or session cookies. Attackers may be able to get the cookie values by sending a http:// link to a user or by planting this link in a site the user goes to. The cookie will be sent to the insecure link and the attacker can then obtain the cookie value by snooping the traffic. IBM X-Force ID: 166624.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-4563|2024-08-04T19:40:47.613Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
