<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for IBM -- Spectrum Protect Server</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ibm/spectrum%20protect%20server.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for IBM -- Spectrum Protect Server</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 08:24:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22394|2024-08-03T03:14:55.124Z -- ibm -- spectrum%20protect%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22394</link>
      <description>The IBM Spectrum Protect 8.1.14.000 server could allow a remote attacker to bypass security restrictions, caused by improper enforcement of access controls. By signing in, an attacker could exploit this vulnerability to bypass security and gain unauthorized administrator or node access to the vulnerable server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22394|2024-08-03T03:14:55.124Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22485|2024-08-03T03:14:55.375Z -- ibm -- spectrum%20protect%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22485</link>
      <description>In some cases, an unsuccessful attempt to log into IBM Spectrum Protect Operations Center 8.1.0.000 through 8.1.14.000 does not cause the administrator's invalid sign-on count to be incremented on the IBM Spectrum Protect Server. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability using brute force techniques to gain unauthorized administrative access to the IBM Spectrum Protect Server. IBM X-Force ID: 226325.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22485|2024-08-03T03:14:55.375Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22487|2024-08-03T03:14:55.322Z -- ibm -- spectrum%20protect%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22487</link>
      <description>An IBM Spectrum Protect storage agent could allow a remote attacker to perform a brute force attack by allowing unlimited attempts to login to the storage agent without locking the administrative ID. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability using brute force techniques to gain unauthorized administrative access to both the IBM Spectrum Protect storage agent and the IBM Spectrum Protect Server 8.1.0.000 through 8.1.14 with which it communicates. IBM X-Force ID: 226326.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22487|2024-08-03T03:14:55.322Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22496|2024-08-03T03:14:55.267Z -- ibm -- spectrum%20protect%20server
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22496</link>
      <description>While a user account for the IBM Spectrum Protect Server 8.1.0.000 through 8.1.14 is being established, it may be configured to use SESSIONSECURITY=TRANSITIONAL. While in this mode, it may be susceptible to an offline dictionary attack. IBM X-Force ID: 226942.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22496|2024-08-03T03:14:55.267Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
