<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for IBM -- Spectrum Protect Operations Center</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ibm/spectrum%20protect%20operations%20center.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for IBM -- Spectrum Protect Operations Center</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 23:24:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4956|2024-09-17T00:25:43.022Z -- ibm -- spectrum%20protect%20operations%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4956</link>
      <description>IBM Spectrum Protect Operations Center 7.1 and 8.1 is vulnerable to a denial of service, caused by a RPC that allows certain cache values to be set and dumped to a file. By setting a grossly large cache value and dumping that cached value to a file multiple times, a remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to cause the consumption of all memory resources. IBM X-Force ID: 192156.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4956|2024-09-17T00:25:43.022Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 15:05:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4955|2024-09-17T02:31:23.322Z -- ibm -- spectrum%20protect%20operations%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4955</link>
      <description>IBM Spectrum Protect Operations Center 7.1 and 8.1could allow a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code on the system, caused by improper parameter validation. By creating an unspecified servlet request with specially crafted input parameters, an attacker could exploit this vulnerability to load a malicious .dll with elevated privileges. IBM X-Force ID: 192155.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4955|2024-09-17T02:31:23.322Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 15:05:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4693|2024-09-17T03:07:44.052Z -- ibm -- spectrum%20protect%20operations%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4693</link>
      <description>IBM Spectrum Protect Operations Center 7.1.0.000 through 7.1.10 and 8.1.0.000 through 8.1.9 may allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code on the system, caused by improper validation of data prior to export. IBM X-Force ID: 186782.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4693|2024-09-17T03:07:44.052Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 18:25:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4771|2024-09-17T02:00:53.424Z -- ibm -- spectrum%20protect%20operations%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4771</link>
      <description>IBM Spectrum Protect Operations Center 8.1.0.000 through 8.1.10.and 7.1.0.000 through 7.1.11 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information, caused by improper authentication of a websocket endpoint. By using known tools to subscribe to the websocket event stream, an attacker could exploit this vulnerability to obtain sensitive information. IBM X-Force ID: 188993.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4771|2024-09-17T02:00:53.424Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 16:55:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4954|2024-09-17T01:21:33.577Z -- ibm -- spectrum%20protect%20operations%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4954</link>
      <description>IBM Spectrum Protect Operations Center 7.1 and 8.1 could allow a remote attacker to bypass authentication restrictions, caused by improper session validation . By using the configuration panel to obtain a valid session using an attacker controlled IBM Spectrum Protect server, an attacker could exploit this vulnerability to bypass authentication and gain access to a limited number of debug functions, such as logging levels. IBM X-Force ID: 192153.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4954|2024-09-17T01:21:33.577Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 15:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38901|2024-09-17T00:40:53.077Z -- ibm -- spectrum%20protect%20operations%20center
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38901</link>
      <description>IBM Spectrum Protect Operations Center 7.1, under special configurations, could allow a local user to obtain highly sensitive information. IBM X-Force ID: 209610.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38901|2024-09-17T00:40:53.077Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 18:35:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
