<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for IBM -- Spectrum Protect Plus</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ibm/spectrum%20protect%20plus.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for IBM -- Spectrum Protect Plus</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 04:23:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22472|2024-08-03T03:14:55.311Z -- ibm -- spectrum%20protect%20plus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22472</link>
      <description>IBM Spectrum Protect Plus Container Backup and Restore (10.1.5 through 10.1.10.2 for Kubernetes and 10.1.7 through 10.1.10.2 for Red Hat OpenShift) could allow a remote attacker to bypass IBM Spectrum Protect Plus role based access control restrictions, caused by improper disclosure of session information. By retrieving the logs of a container an attacker could exploit this vulnerability to bypass login security of the IBM Spectrum Protect Plus server and gain unauthorized access based on the permissions of the IBM Spectrum Protect Plus user to the vulnerable Spectrum Protect Plus server software. IBM X-Force ID: 225340.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22472|2024-08-03T03:14:55.311Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-22396|2024-08-03T03:14:55.198Z -- ibm -- spectrum%20protect%20plus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22396</link>
      <description>Credentials are printed in clear text in the IBM Spectrum Protect Plus 10.1.0.0 through 10.1.9.3 virgo log file in certain cases. Credentials could be the remote vSnap, offload targets, or VADP credentials depending on the operation performed. Credentials that are using API key or certificate are not printed. IBM X-Force ID: 222231.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-22396|2024-08-03T03:14:55.198Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
