<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for IBM -- Spectrum Scale</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ibm/spectrum%20scale.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for IBM -- Spectrum Scale</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 14:22:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1431|2024-09-17T00:26:35.956Z -- ibm -- spectrum%20scale
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1431</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in GSKit affects IBM Spectrum Scale 4.1.1, 4.2.0, 4.2.1, 4.2.3, and 5.0.0 that could allow a local attacker to obtain control of the Spectrum Scale daemon and to access and modify files in the Spectrum Scale file system, and possibly to obtain administrator privileges on the node. IBM X-Force ID: 139240.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1431|2024-09-17T00:26:35.956Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1782|2024-09-17T02:41:39.089Z -- ibm -- spectrum%20scale
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1782</link>
      <description>IBM GPFS (IBM Spectrum Scale 5.0.1.0 and 5.0.1.1) allows a local, unprivileged user to cause a kernel panic on a node running GPFS by accessing a file that is stored on a GPFS file system with mmap, or by executing a crafted file stored on a GPFS file system. IBM X-Force ID: 148805.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1782|2024-09-17T02:41:39.089Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4357|2024-09-17T02:11:27.796Z -- ibm -- spectrum%20scale
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4357</link>
      <description>IBM Spectrum Scale 5.0.0.0 through 5.0.4.4 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when a detailed technical error message is returned in the browser. This information could be used in further attacks against the system. IBM X-Force ID: 178761.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4357|2024-09-17T02:11:27.796Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 13:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4889|2024-09-17T02:20:39.274Z -- ibm -- spectrum%20scale
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4889</link>
      <description>IBM Spectrum Scale 5.0.0 through 5.0.5.4 and 5.1.0 could allow a local user to poison log files which could impact support and development efforts. IBM X-Force ID: 190971.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4889|2024-09-17T02:20:39.274Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 14:25:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4358|2024-09-17T02:58:21.823Z -- ibm -- spectrum%20scale
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4358</link>
      <description>IBM Spectrum Scale 5.0.0.0 through 5.0.4.4 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session. IBM X-Force ID: 178762.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4358|2024-09-17T02:58:21.823Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 13:15:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4891|2024-09-17T00:16:08.376Z -- ibm -- spectrum%20scale
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4891</link>
      <description>IBM Spectrum Scale 5.0.0 through 5.0.5.5 and 5.1.0 through 5.1.0.2 uses an inadequate account lockout setting that could allow a local user er to brute force Rest API account credentials. IBM X-Force ID: 190974.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4891|2024-09-17T00:16:08.376Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 13:55:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4491|2024-09-17T00:46:13.362Z -- ibm -- spectrum%20scale
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4491</link>
      <description>IBM Spectrum Scale V4.2.0.0 through V4.2.3.22 and V5.0.0.0 through V5.0.5 could allow a local attacker to cause a denial of service by sending a large number of RPC requests to the mmfsd daemon which would cause the service to crash. IBM X-Force ID: 181991.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4491|2024-09-17T00:46:13.362Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 14:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4749|2024-09-17T01:11:47.263Z -- ibm -- spectrum%20scale
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4749</link>
      <description>IBM Spectrum Scale 5.0.0 through 5.0.5.2 does not set the secure attribute on authorization tokens or session cookies. Attackers may be able to get the cookie values by sending a http:// link to a user or by planting this link in a site the user goes to. The cookie will be sent to the insecure link and the attacker can then obtain the cookie value by snooping the traffic. IBM X-Force ID: 188518.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4749|2024-09-17T01:11:47.263Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 14:15:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4350|2024-09-17T00:06:12.764Z -- ibm -- spectrum%20scale
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4350</link>
      <description>IBM Spectrum Scale 5.0.0.0 through 5.0.4.4 uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt highly sensitive information. IBM X-Force ID: 178424.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4350|2024-09-17T00:06:12.764Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 13:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4411|2024-09-17T02:12:04.316Z -- ibm -- spectrum%20scale
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4411</link>
      <description>The Spectrum Scale 4.2.0.0 through 4.2.3.21 and 5.0.0.0 through 5.0.4.3 file system component is affected by a denial of service vulnerability in its kernel module that could allow an attacker to cause a denial of service condition on the affected system. To exploit this vulnerability, a local attacker could invoke a subset of ioctls on the Spectrum Scale device with non-valid arguments. This could allow the attacker to crash the kernel. IBM X-Force ID: 179986.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4411|2024-09-17T02:12:04.316Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 13:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4755|2024-09-17T02:52:54.469Z -- ibm -- spectrum%20scale
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4755</link>
      <description>IBM Spectrum Scale 5.0.0 through 5.0.5.2 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session. IBM X-Force ID: 188595.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4755|2024-09-17T02:52:54.469Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 14:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
