<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Samsung -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/samsung/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Samsung -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 16:24:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3877|2024-08-05T04:57:24.407Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3877</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the credentials handler of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250-Firmware version 0.20.17. The strncpy overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 160 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "directory" value in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3877|2024-08-05T04:57:24.407Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3894|2024-08-05T04:57:24.476Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3894</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the /cameras/XXXX/clips handler of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250-Firmware version 0.20.17. The strncpy call overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 52 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "startTime" value in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3894|2024-08-05T04:57:24.476Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3874|2024-08-05T04:57:24.422Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3874</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the credentials handler of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250-Firmware version 0.20.17. The strncpy overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 32 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "accessKey" value in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3874|2024-08-05T04:57:24.422Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3863|2024-08-05T04:57:24.367Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3863</link>
      <description>On Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 devices with firmware version 0.20.17, the video-core process incorrectly extracts fields from a user-controlled JSON payload, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. An attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability. A strcpy overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 40 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "user" value in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3863|2024-08-05T04:57:24.367Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3872|2024-08-05T04:57:24.206Z -- samsung -- samsung
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3872</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the credentials handler of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 - Firmware version 0.20.17. The video-core process incorrectly extracts the videoHostUrl field from a user-controlled JSON payload, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. An attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3872|2024-08-05T04:57:24.206Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3916|2024-08-05T04:57:24.315Z -- samsung -- samsung
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3916</link>
      <description>An exploitable stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the retrieval of database fields in the video-core HTTP server of the Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 - Firmware version 0.20.17. The strcpy call overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 136 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long 'directory' value in order to exploit this vulnerability. An attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3916|2024-08-05T04:57:24.315Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10499|2024-08-05T07:39:07.725Z -- samsung -- samsung%20galaxy%20apps
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10499</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Samsung Galaxy Apps Fixed in version 6.4.0.15. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of URLs. The issue lies in the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can allow arbitrary JavaScript to execute. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to install applications under the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-5330.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10499|2024-08-05T07:39:07.725Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3895|2024-08-05T04:57:24.469Z -- samsung -- samsung
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3895</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the /cameras/XXXX/clips handler of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 Firmware version 0.20.17. The strncpy call overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 52 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long 'endTime' value in order to exploit this vulnerability. An attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3895|2024-08-05T04:57:24.469Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3915|2024-08-05T04:57:24.396Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3915</link>
      <description>An exploitable stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the retrieval of database fields in the video-core HTTP server of the Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 - Firmware version 0.20.17. The strcpy call overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 64 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "bucket" value in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3915|2024-08-05T04:57:24.396Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3906|2024-08-05T04:57:24.450Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3906</link>
      <description>An exploitable stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the retrieval of a database field in video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub. The video-core process insecurely extracts the shard.videoHostURL field from its SQLite database, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. An attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3906|2024-08-05T04:57:24.450Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3902|2024-08-05T04:57:24.149Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3902</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the camera "replace" feature of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 devices with firmware version 0.20.17. The video-core process incorrectly extracts the URL field from a user-controlled JSON payload, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. An attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3902|2024-08-05T04:57:24.149Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3865|2024-08-05T04:57:24.343Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3865</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the Samsung WifiScan handler of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 - Firmware version 0.20.17. The strcpy overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 40 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "cameraIp" value in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3865|2024-08-05T04:57:24.343Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3896|2024-08-05T04:57:24.414Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3896</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the /cameras/XXXX/clips handler of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub with Firmware version 0.20.17. The video-core process incorrectly extracts fields from a user-controlled JSON payload, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. The strncpy call overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 52 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "correlationId" value in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3896|2024-08-05T04:57:24.414Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3875|2024-08-05T04:57:24.522Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3875</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the credentials handler of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250-Firmware version 0.20.17. The video-core process incorrectly extracts fields from a user-controlled JSON payload, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. The strncpy overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 2,000 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "sessionToken" value in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3875|2024-08-05T04:57:24.522Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3905|2024-08-05T04:57:24.098Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3905</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the camera "create" feature of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 devices with firmware version 0.20.17. The video-core process incorrectly extracts the "state" field from a user-controlled JSON payload, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. An attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3905|2024-08-05T04:57:24.098Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3908|2024-08-05T04:57:24.393Z -- samsung -- samsung
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3908</link>
      <description>An exploitable vulnerability exists in the REST parser of video-core's HTTP server of the Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250-Firmware version 0.20.17. The video-core process incorrectly handles pipelined HTTP requests, which allows successive requests to overwrite the previously parsed HTTP method, URL and body. With the implementation of the on_body callback, defined by sub_41734, an attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3908|2024-08-05T04:57:24.393Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11614|2024-08-05T08:17:07.793Z -- samsung -- samsung%20members
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11614</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to escalate privileges on vulnerable installations of Samsung Members Fixed in version 2.4.25. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of Intents. The issue lies in the ability to send an Intent that would not otherwise be reachable. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges to resources normally protected from the application. Was ZDI-CAN-5361.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11614|2024-08-05T08:17:07.793Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3878|2024-08-05T04:57:24.465Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3878</link>
      <description>Multiple exploitable buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the credentials handler of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 devices with firmware version 0.20.17. The video-core process incorrectly extracts fields from a user-controlled JSON payload, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. A strncpy overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 16 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "region" value in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3878|2024-08-05T04:57:24.465Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3864|2024-08-05T04:57:24.206Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3864</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the Samsung WifiScan handler of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 - Firmware version 0.20.17. The strcpy overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 40 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "password" value in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3864|2024-08-05T04:57:24.206Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3880|2024-08-05T04:57:24.247Z -- samsung -- samsung
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3880</link>
      <description>An exploitable stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the database 'find-by-cameraId' functionality of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 - Firmware version 0.20.17. The video-core process incorrectly handles existing records inside its SQLite database, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. An attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3880|2024-08-05T04:57:24.247Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3911|2024-08-05T04:57:24.449Z -- samsung -- samsung
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3911</link>
      <description>An exploitable HTTP header injection vulnerability exists in the remote servers of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 - Firmware version 0.20.17. The hubCore process listens on port 39500 and relays any unauthenticated message to SmartThings' remote servers, which insecurely handle JSON messages, leading to partially controlled requests generated toward the internal video-core process. An attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3911|2024-08-05T04:57:24.449Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3918|2024-08-05T04:57:24.445Z -- samsung -- samsung
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3918</link>
      <description>An exploitable vulnerability exists in the remote servers of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 - Firmware version 0.20.17. The hubCore process listens on port 39500 and relays any unauthenticated messages to SmartThings' remote servers, which incorrectly handle camera IDs for the 'sync' operation, leading to arbitrary deletion of cameras. An attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3918|2024-08-05T04:57:24.445Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3925|2024-08-05T04:57:24.493Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3925</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the remote video-host communication of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 devices with firmware version 0.20.17. The video-core process insecurely parses the AWSELB cookie while communicating with remote video-host servers, leading to a buffer overflow on the heap. An attacker able to impersonate the remote HTTP servers could trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3925|2024-08-05T04:57:24.493Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10501|2024-08-05T07:39:08.068Z -- samsung -- samsung%20notes
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10501</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on vulnerable installations of Samsung Notes Fixed in version 2.0.02.31. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of ZIP files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges to resources normally protected from the application. Was ZDI-CAN-5358.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10501|2024-08-05T07:39:08.068Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3927|2024-08-05T04:57:24.426Z -- samsung -- samsung
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3927</link>
      <description>An exploitable information disclosure vulnerability exists in the crash handler of the hubCore binary of the Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 - Firmware version 0.20.17. When hubCore crashes, Google Breakpad is used to record minidumps, which are sent over an insecure HTTPS connection to the backtrace.io service, leading to the exposure of sensitive data. An attacker can impersonate the remote backtrace.io server in order to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3927|2024-08-05T04:57:24.426Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3873|2024-08-05T04:57:24.254Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3873</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the credentials handler of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250-Firmware version 0.20.17. The strncpy overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 128 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "secretKey" value in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3873|2024-08-05T04:57:24.254Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3919|2024-08-05T04:57:24.449Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3919</link>
      <description>An exploitable stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the retrieval of database fields in video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 devices with firmware version 0.20.17. The video-core process insecurely extracts the fields from the "clips" table of its SQLite database, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. An attacker can send a series of HTTP requests to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3919|2024-08-05T04:57:24.449Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10496|2024-08-05T07:39:08.019Z -- samsung -- samsung%20internet%20browser
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10496</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Samsung Internet Browser Fixed in version 6.4.0.15. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the handling of TypedArray objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code under the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-5326.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10496|2024-08-05T07:39:08.019Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3914|2024-08-05T04:57:24.484Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3914</link>
      <description>An exploitable stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the retrieval of database fields in the video-core HTTP server of the Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 - Firmware version 0.20.17. The strcpy call overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 2000 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "sessionToken" value in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3914|2024-08-05T04:57:24.484Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3897|2024-08-05T04:57:24.335Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3897</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the /cameras/XXXX/clips handler of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub with Firmware version 0.20.17. The video-core process incorrectly extracts fields from a user-controlled JSON payload, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. The strncpy call overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 52 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "callbackUrl" value in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3897|2024-08-05T04:57:24.335Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3867|2024-08-05T04:57:24.110Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3867</link>
      <description>An exploitable stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the samsungWifiScan callback notification of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 devices with firmware version 0.20.17. The video-core process incorrectly handles the answer received from a smart camera, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. An attacker can send a series of HTTP requests to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3867|2024-08-05T04:57:24.110Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10500|2024-08-05T07:39:07.919Z -- samsung -- samsung%20galaxy%20apps
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10500</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on vulnerable installations of Samsung Galaxy Apps Fixed in version 6.4.0.15. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of push messages. The issue lies in the ability to start an activity with controlled arguments. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges to resources normally protected from the application. Was ZDI-CAN-5331.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10500|2024-08-05T07:39:07.919Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3904|2024-08-05T04:57:24.467Z -- samsung -- samsung
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3904</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the camera 'update' feature of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 - Firmware version 0.20.17. The video-core process incorrectly extracts fields from a user-controlled JSON payload, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. An attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3904|2024-08-05T04:57:24.467Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3917|2024-08-05T04:57:24.596Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3917</link>
      <description>On Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 devices with firmware version 0.20.17, the video-core process insecurely extracts the fields from the "shard" table of its SQLite database, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. An attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability. The strcpy call overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 16 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "region" value in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3917|2024-08-05T04:57:24.596Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10502|2024-08-05T07:39:07.944Z -- samsung -- samsung%20galaxy%20apps
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10502</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on vulnerable installations of Samsung Galaxy Apps Fixed in version 4.2.18.2. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of a staging mode. The issue lies in the ability to change the configuration based on the presence of a file in an user-controlled location. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges to resources normally protected from the application. Was ZDI-CAN-5359.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10502|2024-08-05T07:39:07.944Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3866|2024-08-05T04:57:24.143Z -- samsung -- samsung
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3866</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the samsungWifiScan handler of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 - Firmware version 0.20.17. The video-core process incorrectly extracts fields from a user-controlled JSON payload, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. The strcpy at [8] overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 40 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long 'callbackUrl' value in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3866|2024-08-05T04:57:24.143Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-14318|2024-08-05T09:21:41.618Z -- samsung -- samsung%20galaxy%20s8
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-14318</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Samsung Galaxy S8 G950FXXU1AQL5. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must have their cellular radios enabled. The specific flaw exists within the handling of IPCP headers. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length, stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code under the context of the baseband processor. Was ZDI-CAN-5368.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-14318|2024-08-05T09:21:41.618Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3218|2024-08-05T14:16:28.240Z -- samsung -- magician
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3218</link>
      <description>Samsung Magician 5.0 fails to validate TLS certificates for HTTPS software update traffic. Prior to version 5.0, Samsung Magician uses HTTP for software updates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3218|2024-08-05T14:16:28.240Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10498|2024-08-05T07:39:07.683Z -- samsung -- samsung%20email
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10498</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose sensitive information on vulnerable installations of Samsung Email Fixed in version 5.0.02.16. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of file:/// URIs. The issue lies in the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can allow for reading arbitrary files. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to escalate privileges. Was ZDI-CAN-5329.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10498|2024-08-05T07:39:07.683Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3856|2024-08-05T04:57:24.030Z -- samsung -- samsung
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3856</link>
      <description>An exploitable vulnerability exists in the smart cameras RTSP configuration of the Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 - Firmware version 0.20.17. The device incorrectly handles spaces in the URL field, leading to an arbitrary operating system command injection. An attacker can send a series of HTTP requests to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3856|2024-08-05T04:57:24.030Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3912|2024-08-05T04:57:24.448Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3912</link>
      <description>On Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 devices with firmware version 0.20.17, the video-core process insecurely extracts the fields from the "shard" table of its SQLite database, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. The strcpy call overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 128 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "secretKey" value in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3912|2024-08-05T04:57:24.448Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3879|2024-08-05T04:57:24.397Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3879</link>
      <description>An exploitable JSON injection vulnerability exists in the credentials handler of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 devices with firmware version 0.20.17. The video-core process incorrectly parses the user-controlled JSON payload, leading to a JSON injection which in turn leads to a SQL injection in the video-core database. An attacker can send a series of HTTP requests to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3879|2024-08-05T04:57:24.397Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10497|2024-08-05T07:39:08.259Z -- samsung -- samsung%20email
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10497</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on vulnerable installations of Samsung Email Fixed in version 5.0.02.16. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of EML files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can allow arbitrary JavaScript to execute. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges to resources normally protected from the application. Was ZDI-CAN-5328.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10497|2024-08-05T07:39:08.259Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3876|2024-08-05T04:57:24.417Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3876</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the credentials handler of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250-Firmware version 0.20.17. The strncpy overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 64 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "bucket" value in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3876|2024-08-05T04:57:24.417Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32670|2024-08-02T02:13:40.331Z -- samsung -- galaxy%20smarttag2</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32670</link>
      <description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor in Samsung Galaxy SmartTag2 prior to 0.20.04 allows attackes to potentially identify the tag's location by scanning the BLE adversting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32670|2024-08-02T02:13:40.331Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:20:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32670|2024-07-10T03:35:29.150Z -- samsung -- galaxy%20smarttag2</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32670</link>
      <description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor in Samsung Galaxy SmartTag2 prior to 0.20.04 allows attackes to potentially identify the tag's location by scanning the BLE adversting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32670|2024-07-10T03:35:29.150Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:20:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32670|2024-07-11T19:11:16.215Z -- samsung -- galaxy%20smarttag2</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32670</link>
      <description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor in Samsung Galaxy SmartTag2 prior to 0.20.04 allows attackes to potentially identify the tag's location by scanning the BLE adversting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32670|2024-07-11T19:11:16.215Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:20:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
