<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Samsung -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/samsung/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Samsung -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:22:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6741|2024-08-04T20:31:04.219Z -- samsung -- galaxy%20s9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6741</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Samsung Galaxy S9 prior to January 2019 Security Update (SMR-JAN-2019 - SVE-2018-13467). User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must connect to a wireless network. The specific flaw exists within the captive portal. By manipulating HTML, an attacker can force a page redirection. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7476.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6741|2024-08-04T20:31:04.219Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 18:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8860|2024-08-04T10:12:10.942Z -- samsung -- galaxy%20s10
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8860</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Samsung Galaxy S10 Firmware G973FXXS3ASJA, O(8.x), P(9.0), Q(10.0) devices with Exynos chipsets. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must answer a phone call. The specific flaw exists within the Call Control Setup messages. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length, stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the baseband processor. Was ZDI-CAN-9658.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8860|2024-08-04T10:12:10.942Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 00:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-42114|2024-08-04T03:22:25.781Z -- samsung -- samsung%20ddr4_sdram
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42114</link>
      <description>Modern DRAM devices (PC-DDR4, LPDDR4X) are affected by a vulnerability in their internal Target Row Refresh (TRR) mitigation against Rowhammer attacks. Novel non-uniform Rowhammer access patterns, consisting of aggressors with different frequencies, phases, and amplitudes allow triggering bit flips on affected memory modules using our Blacksmith fuzzer. The patterns generated by Blacksmith were able to trigger bitflips on all 40 PC-DDR4 DRAM devices in our test pool, which cover the three major DRAM manufacturers: Samsung, SK Hynix, and Micron. This means that, even when chips advertised as Rowhammer-free are used, attackers may still be able to exploit Rowhammer. For example, this enables privilege-escalation attacks against the kernel or binaries such as the sudo binary, and also triggering bit flips in RSA-2048 keys (e.g., SSH keys) to gain cross-tenant virtual-machine access. We can confirm that DRAM devices acquired in July 2020 with DRAM chips from all three major DRAM vendors (Samsung, SK Hynix, Micron) are affected by this vulnerability. For more details, please refer to our publication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-42114|2024-08-04T03:22:25.781Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6740|2024-08-04T20:31:04.226Z -- samsung -- galaxy%20s9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6740</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Samsung Galaxy S9 prior to January 2019 Security Update (SMR-JAN-2019 - SVE-2018-13467). User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file. The specific flaw exists within the ASN.1 parser. When parsing ASN.1 strings, the process does not properly validate the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7472.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6740|2024-08-04T20:31:04.226Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 18:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6744|2024-08-04T20:31:04.254Z -- samsung -- knox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6744</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Samsung Knox 1.2.02.39 on Samsung Galaxy S9 build G9600ZHS3ARL1 Secure Folder. An attacker must first obtain physical access to the device in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaws exists within the the handling of the lock screen for Secure Folder. The issue results from the lack of proper validation that a user has correctly authenticated. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose the contents of the secure container. Was ZDI-CAN-7381.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6744|2024-08-04T20:31:04.254Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 19:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6335|2024-08-04T20:16:24.812Z -- samsung -- laser%20printers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6335</link>
      <description>A potential security vulnerability has been identified with Samsung Laser Printers. This vulnerability could potentially be exploited to create a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6335|2024-08-04T20:16:24.812Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:34:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6742|2024-08-04T20:31:04.245Z -- samsung -- galaxy%20s9
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6742</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Samsung Galaxy S9 prior to 1.4.20.2. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of the GameServiceReceiver update mechanism. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-7477.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6742|2024-08-04T20:31:04.245Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 18:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9061|2024-08-04T10:19:19.812Z -- samsung -- sth-eth-200
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9061</link>
      <description>Z-Wave devices using Silicon Labs 500 and 700 series chipsets, including but not likely limited to the SiLabs UZB-7 version 7.00, ZooZ ZST10 version 6.04, Aeon Labs ZW090-A version 3.95, and Samsung STH-ETH-200 version 6.04, are susceptible to denial of service via malformed routing messages.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9061|2024-08-04T10:19:19.812Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-8899|2024-08-04T10:12:10.997Z -- samsung -- android%20os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-8899</link>
      <description>There is a buffer overwrite vulnerability in the Quram qmg library of Samsung's Android OS versions O(8.x), P(9.0) and Q(10.0). An unauthenticated, unauthorized attacker sending a specially crafted MMS to a vulnerable phone can trigger a heap-based buffer overflow in the Quram image codec leading to an arbitrary remote code execution (RCE) without any user interaction. The Samsung ID is SVE-2020-16747.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-8899|2024-08-04T10:12:10.997Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32670|2024-07-11T19:11:16.215Z -- samsung -- galaxy%20smarttag2</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32670</link>
      <description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor in Samsung Galaxy SmartTag2 prior to 0.20.04 allows attackes to potentially identify the tag's location by scanning the BLE adversting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32670|2024-07-11T19:11:16.215Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:20:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32670|2024-07-10T03:35:29.150Z -- samsung -- galaxy%20smarttag2</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32670</link>
      <description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor in Samsung Galaxy SmartTag2 prior to 0.20.04 allows attackes to potentially identify the tag's location by scanning the BLE adversting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32670|2024-07-10T03:35:29.150Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:20:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32670|2024-08-02T02:13:40.331Z -- samsung -- galaxy%20smarttag2</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32670</link>
      <description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor in Samsung Galaxy SmartTag2 prior to 0.20.04 allows attackes to potentially identify the tag's location by scanning the BLE adversting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32670|2024-08-02T02:13:40.331Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:20:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
