<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Samsung -- Samsung</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/samsung/samsung.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Samsung -- Samsung</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:22:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3872|2024-08-05T04:57:24.206Z -- samsung -- samsung
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3872</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the credentials handler of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 - Firmware version 0.20.17. The video-core process incorrectly extracts the videoHostUrl field from a user-controlled JSON payload, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. An attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3872|2024-08-05T04:57:24.206Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3916|2024-08-05T04:57:24.315Z -- samsung -- samsung
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3916</link>
      <description>An exploitable stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the retrieval of database fields in the video-core HTTP server of the Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 - Firmware version 0.20.17. The strcpy call overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 136 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long 'directory' value in order to exploit this vulnerability. An attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3916|2024-08-05T04:57:24.315Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3895|2024-08-05T04:57:24.469Z -- samsung -- samsung
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3895</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the /cameras/XXXX/clips handler of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 Firmware version 0.20.17. The strncpy call overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 52 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long 'endTime' value in order to exploit this vulnerability. An attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3895|2024-08-05T04:57:24.469Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3908|2024-08-05T04:57:24.393Z -- samsung -- samsung
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3908</link>
      <description>An exploitable vulnerability exists in the REST parser of video-core's HTTP server of the Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250-Firmware version 0.20.17. The video-core process incorrectly handles pipelined HTTP requests, which allows successive requests to overwrite the previously parsed HTTP method, URL and body. With the implementation of the on_body callback, defined by sub_41734, an attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3908|2024-08-05T04:57:24.393Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3880|2024-08-05T04:57:24.247Z -- samsung -- samsung
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3880</link>
      <description>An exploitable stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the database 'find-by-cameraId' functionality of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 - Firmware version 0.20.17. The video-core process incorrectly handles existing records inside its SQLite database, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. An attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3880|2024-08-05T04:57:24.247Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3911|2024-08-05T04:57:24.449Z -- samsung -- samsung
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3911</link>
      <description>An exploitable HTTP header injection vulnerability exists in the remote servers of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 - Firmware version 0.20.17. The hubCore process listens on port 39500 and relays any unauthenticated message to SmartThings' remote servers, which insecurely handle JSON messages, leading to partially controlled requests generated toward the internal video-core process. An attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3911|2024-08-05T04:57:24.449Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3918|2024-08-05T04:57:24.445Z -- samsung -- samsung
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3918</link>
      <description>An exploitable vulnerability exists in the remote servers of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 - Firmware version 0.20.17. The hubCore process listens on port 39500 and relays any unauthenticated messages to SmartThings' remote servers, which incorrectly handle camera IDs for the 'sync' operation, leading to arbitrary deletion of cameras. An attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3918|2024-08-05T04:57:24.445Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3927|2024-08-05T04:57:24.426Z -- samsung -- samsung
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3927</link>
      <description>An exploitable information disclosure vulnerability exists in the crash handler of the hubCore binary of the Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 - Firmware version 0.20.17. When hubCore crashes, Google Breakpad is used to record minidumps, which are sent over an insecure HTTPS connection to the backtrace.io service, leading to the exposure of sensitive data. An attacker can impersonate the remote backtrace.io server in order to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3927|2024-08-05T04:57:24.426Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3904|2024-08-05T04:57:24.467Z -- samsung -- samsung
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3904</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the camera 'update' feature of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 - Firmware version 0.20.17. The video-core process incorrectly extracts fields from a user-controlled JSON payload, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. An attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3904|2024-08-05T04:57:24.467Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3866|2024-08-05T04:57:24.143Z -- samsung -- samsung
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3866</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the samsungWifiScan handler of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 - Firmware version 0.20.17. The video-core process incorrectly extracts fields from a user-controlled JSON payload, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. The strcpy at [8] overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 40 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long 'callbackUrl' value in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3866|2024-08-05T04:57:24.143Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3856|2024-08-05T04:57:24.030Z -- samsung -- samsung
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3856</link>
      <description>An exploitable vulnerability exists in the smart cameras RTSP configuration of the Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 - Firmware version 0.20.17. The device incorrectly handles spaces in the URL field, leading to an arbitrary operating system command injection. An attacker can send a series of HTTP requests to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3856|2024-08-05T04:57:24.030Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
