<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Samsung -- SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/samsung/smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Samsung -- SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:23:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3877|2024-08-05T04:57:24.407Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3877</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the credentials handler of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250-Firmware version 0.20.17. The strncpy overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 160 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "directory" value in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3877|2024-08-05T04:57:24.407Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3894|2024-08-05T04:57:24.476Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3894</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the /cameras/XXXX/clips handler of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250-Firmware version 0.20.17. The strncpy call overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 52 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "startTime" value in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3894|2024-08-05T04:57:24.476Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3874|2024-08-05T04:57:24.422Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3874</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the credentials handler of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250-Firmware version 0.20.17. The strncpy overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 32 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "accessKey" value in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3874|2024-08-05T04:57:24.422Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3863|2024-08-05T04:57:24.367Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3863</link>
      <description>On Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 devices with firmware version 0.20.17, the video-core process incorrectly extracts fields from a user-controlled JSON payload, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. An attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability. A strcpy overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 40 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "user" value in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3863|2024-08-05T04:57:24.367Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3915|2024-08-05T04:57:24.396Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3915</link>
      <description>An exploitable stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the retrieval of database fields in the video-core HTTP server of the Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 - Firmware version 0.20.17. The strcpy call overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 64 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "bucket" value in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3915|2024-08-05T04:57:24.396Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3906|2024-08-05T04:57:24.450Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3906</link>
      <description>An exploitable stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the retrieval of a database field in video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub. The video-core process insecurely extracts the shard.videoHostURL field from its SQLite database, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. An attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3906|2024-08-05T04:57:24.450Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3902|2024-08-05T04:57:24.149Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3902</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the camera "replace" feature of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 devices with firmware version 0.20.17. The video-core process incorrectly extracts the URL field from a user-controlled JSON payload, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. An attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3902|2024-08-05T04:57:24.149Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3865|2024-08-05T04:57:24.343Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3865</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the Samsung WifiScan handler of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 - Firmware version 0.20.17. The strcpy overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 40 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "cameraIp" value in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3865|2024-08-05T04:57:24.343Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3896|2024-08-05T04:57:24.414Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3896</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the /cameras/XXXX/clips handler of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub with Firmware version 0.20.17. The video-core process incorrectly extracts fields from a user-controlled JSON payload, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. The strncpy call overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 52 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "correlationId" value in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3896|2024-08-05T04:57:24.414Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3875|2024-08-05T04:57:24.522Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3875</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the credentials handler of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250-Firmware version 0.20.17. The video-core process incorrectly extracts fields from a user-controlled JSON payload, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. The strncpy overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 2,000 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "sessionToken" value in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3875|2024-08-05T04:57:24.522Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3905|2024-08-05T04:57:24.098Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3905</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the camera "create" feature of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 devices with firmware version 0.20.17. The video-core process incorrectly extracts the "state" field from a user-controlled JSON payload, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. An attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3905|2024-08-05T04:57:24.098Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3878|2024-08-05T04:57:24.465Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3878</link>
      <description>Multiple exploitable buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the credentials handler of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 devices with firmware version 0.20.17. The video-core process incorrectly extracts fields from a user-controlled JSON payload, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. A strncpy overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 16 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "region" value in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3878|2024-08-05T04:57:24.465Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3864|2024-08-05T04:57:24.206Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3864</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the Samsung WifiScan handler of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 - Firmware version 0.20.17. The strcpy overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 40 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "password" value in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3864|2024-08-05T04:57:24.206Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3925|2024-08-05T04:57:24.493Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3925</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the remote video-host communication of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 devices with firmware version 0.20.17. The video-core process insecurely parses the AWSELB cookie while communicating with remote video-host servers, leading to a buffer overflow on the heap. An attacker able to impersonate the remote HTTP servers could trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3925|2024-08-05T04:57:24.493Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3873|2024-08-05T04:57:24.254Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3873</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the credentials handler of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250-Firmware version 0.20.17. The strncpy overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 128 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "secretKey" value in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3873|2024-08-05T04:57:24.254Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3919|2024-08-05T04:57:24.449Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3919</link>
      <description>An exploitable stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the retrieval of database fields in video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 devices with firmware version 0.20.17. The video-core process insecurely extracts the fields from the "clips" table of its SQLite database, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. An attacker can send a series of HTTP requests to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3919|2024-08-05T04:57:24.449Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3914|2024-08-05T04:57:24.484Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3914</link>
      <description>An exploitable stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the retrieval of database fields in the video-core HTTP server of the Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 - Firmware version 0.20.17. The strcpy call overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 2000 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "sessionToken" value in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3914|2024-08-05T04:57:24.484Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3897|2024-08-05T04:57:24.335Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3897</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in the /cameras/XXXX/clips handler of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub with Firmware version 0.20.17. The video-core process incorrectly extracts fields from a user-controlled JSON payload, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. The strncpy call overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 52 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "callbackUrl" value in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3897|2024-08-05T04:57:24.335Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3867|2024-08-05T04:57:24.110Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3867</link>
      <description>An exploitable stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the samsungWifiScan callback notification of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 devices with firmware version 0.20.17. The video-core process incorrectly handles the answer received from a smart camera, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. An attacker can send a series of HTTP requests to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3867|2024-08-05T04:57:24.110Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3917|2024-08-05T04:57:24.596Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3917</link>
      <description>On Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 devices with firmware version 0.20.17, the video-core process insecurely extracts the fields from the "shard" table of its SQLite database, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. An attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability. The strcpy call overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 16 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "region" value in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3917|2024-08-05T04:57:24.596Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3912|2024-08-05T04:57:24.448Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3912</link>
      <description>On Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 devices with firmware version 0.20.17, the video-core process insecurely extracts the fields from the "shard" table of its SQLite database, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. The strcpy call overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 128 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "secretKey" value in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3912|2024-08-05T04:57:24.448Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3879|2024-08-05T04:57:24.397Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3879</link>
      <description>An exploitable JSON injection vulnerability exists in the credentials handler of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 devices with firmware version 0.20.17. The video-core process incorrectly parses the user-controlled JSON payload, leading to a JSON injection which in turn leads to a SQL injection in the video-core database. An attacker can send a series of HTTP requests to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3879|2024-08-05T04:57:24.397Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3876|2024-08-05T04:57:24.417Z -- samsung -- smartthings%20hub%20sth-eth-250
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3876</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the credentials handler of video-core's HTTP server of Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250-Firmware version 0.20.17. The strncpy overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 64 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "bucket" value in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3876|2024-08-05T04:57:24.417Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
