<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for thimpress -- LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/thimpress/learnpress%20%E2%80%93%20wordpress%20lms%20plugin.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for thimpress -- LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 22:02:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-1463|2024-04-09T18:59:12.301Z -- thimpress -- LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1463</link><description>The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Course, Lesson, and Quiz title and content in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.6.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with LP Instructor-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1463|2024-04-09T18:59:12.301Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:59:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1289|2024-04-09T18:58:31.705Z -- thimpress -- LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1289</link><description>The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.6.3 due to missing validation on a user controlled key when looking up order information. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers to obtain information on orders placed by other users and guests, which can be leveraged to sign up for paid courses that were purchased by guests. Emails of other users are also exposed.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1289|2024-04-09T18:58:31.705Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:58:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4277|2024-05-10T09:32:08.904Z -- thimpress -- LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4277</link><description>The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘layout_html’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.6.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4277|2024-05-10T09:32:08.904Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 09:32:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4397|2024-05-09T20:03:41.532Z -- thimpress -- LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4397</link><description>The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'save_post_materials' function in versions up to, and including, 4.2.6.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Instructor-level permissions and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4397|2024-05-09T20:03:41.532Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 20:03:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4434|2024-05-10T08:32:33.463Z -- thimpress -- LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4434</link><description>The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘term_id’ parameter in versions up to, and including, 4.2.6.5 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4434|2024-05-10T08:32:33.463Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 08:32:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4971|2024-05-22T05:32:46.886Z -- thimpress -- LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4971</link><description>The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.6.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4971|2024-05-22T05:32:46.886Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 05:32:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4444|2024-05-10T08:32:34.579Z -- thimpress -- LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4444</link><description>The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to bypass to user registration in versions up to, and including, 4.2.6.5. This is due to missing checks in the 'create_account' function in the checkout. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to register as the default role on the site, even if registration is disabled.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4444|2024-05-10T08:32:34.579Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 08:32:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3560|2024-04-19T01:57:09.385Z -- thimpress -- LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3560</link><description>The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the _id value in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.6.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3560|2024-04-19T01:57:09.385Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 01:57:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2115|2024-04-05T07:34:35.847Z -- thimpress -- LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2115</link><description>The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the filter_users functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to elevate their privileges to that of a teacher via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2115|2024-04-05T07:34:35.847Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 07:34:35 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>