<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Larvata Digital Technology Co. Ltd. -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/larvata%20digital%20technology%20co.%20ltd./all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Larvata Digital Technology Co. Ltd. -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 06:24:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-37212|2024-08-04T01:16:03.908Z -- larvata%20digital%20technology%20co.%20ltd. -- flygo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-37212</link>
      <description>The bulletin function of Flygo contains Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability. After being authenticated as a general user, remote attackers can manipulate the bulletin ID in specific Url parameters and access and modify bulletin particular content.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-37212|2024-08-04T01:16:03.908Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-37211|2024-08-04T01:16:04.048Z -- larvata%20digital%20technology%20co.%20ltd. -- flygo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-37211</link>
      <description>The bulletin function of Flygo does not filter special characters while a new announcement is added. Remoter attackers can use the vulnerability with general user’s credential to inject JavaScript and execute stored XSS attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-37211|2024-08-04T01:16:04.048Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-37214|2024-08-04T01:16:03.817Z -- larvata%20digital%20technology%20co.%20ltd. -- flygo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-37214</link>
      <description>The employee management page of Flygo contains Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability. After being authenticated as a general user, remote attackers can manipulate the employee ID in specific parameters to arbitrary access employee's data, modify it, and then obtain administrator privilege and execute arbitrary command.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-37214|2024-08-04T01:16:03.817Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-37215|2024-08-04T01:16:03.383Z -- larvata%20digital%20technology%20co.%20ltd. -- flygo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-37215</link>
      <description>The employee management page of Flygo contains an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability. After being authenticated as a general user, remote attacker can manipulate the user data and then over-write another employee’s user data by specifying that employee’s ID in the API parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-37215|2024-08-04T01:16:03.383Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-37213|2024-08-04T01:16:03.210Z -- larvata%20digital%20technology%20co.%20ltd. -- flygo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-37213</link>
      <description>The check-in record page of Flygo contains Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability. After being authenticated as a general user, remote attackers can manipulate the employee ID and date in specific parameters to access particular employee’s check-in record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-37213|2024-08-04T01:16:03.210Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
