<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for stacklok -- minder</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/stacklok/minder.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for stacklok -- minder</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 20:23:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-35185|2024-06-06T19:17:43.766Z -- stacklok -- minder
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-35185</link>
      <description>Minder is a software supply chain security platform. Prior to version 0.0.49, the Minder REST ingester is vulnerable to a denial of service attack via an attacker-controlled REST endpoint that can crash the Minder server. The REST ingester allows users to interact with REST endpoints to fetch data for rule evaluation. When fetching data with the REST ingester, Minder sends a request to an endpoint and will use the data from the body of the response as the data to evaluate against a certain rule. If the response is sufficiently large, it can drain memory on the machine and crash the Minder server. The attacker can control the remote REST endpoints that Minder sends requests to, and they can configure the remote REST endpoints to return responses with large bodies. They would then instruct Minder to send a request to their configured endpoint that would return the large response which would crash the Minder server. Version 0.0.49 fixes this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-35185|2024-06-06T19:17:43.766Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 15:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-35194|2024-05-20T20:44:10.562Z -- stacklok -- minder</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-35194</link>
      <description>Minder is a software supply chain security platform. Prior to version 0.0.50, Minder engine is susceptible to a denial of service from memory exhaustion that can be triggered from maliciously created templates. Minder engine uses templating to generate strings for various use cases such as URLs, messages for pull requests, descriptions for advisories. In some cases can the user control both the template and the params for it, and in a subset of these cases, Minder reads the generated template entirely into memory. When Minders templating meets both of these conditions, an attacker is able to generate large enough templates that Minder will exhaust memory and crash. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.0.50.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-35194|2024-05-20T20:44:10.562Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 20:44:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
