<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for labring -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/labring/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for labring -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 23:21:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50253|2024-08-02T22:16:46.099Z -- labring -- laf
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50253</link>
      <description>Laf is a cloud development platform. In the Laf version design, the log uses communication with k8s to quickly retrieve logs from the container without the need for additional storage. However, in version 1.0.0-beta.13 and prior, this interface does not verify the permissions of the pod, which allows authenticated users to obtain any pod logs under the same namespace through this method, thereby obtaining sensitive information printed in the logs. As of time of publication, no known patched versions exist.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50253|2024-08-02T22:16:46.099Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 16:45:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33190|2024-08-02T15:39:35.773Z -- labring -- sealos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33190</link>
      <description>Sealos is an open source cloud operating system distribution based on the Kubernetes kernel. In versions of Sealos prior to 4.2.1-rc4 an improper configuration of role based access control (RBAC) permissions resulted in an attacker being able to obtain cluster control permissions, which could control the entire cluster deployed with Sealos, as well as hundreds of pods and other resources within the cluster. This issue has been addressed in version 4.2.1-rc4. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33190|2024-08-02T15:39:35.773Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 17:27:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-48225|2024-08-02T21:23:39.023Z -- labring -- laf
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48225</link>
      <description>Laf is a cloud development platform. Prior to version 1.0.0-beta.13, the control of LAF app enV is not strict enough, and in certain scenarios of privatization environment, it may lead to sensitive information leakage in secret and configmap. In ES6 syntax, if an obj directly references another obj, the name of the obj itself will be used as the key, and the entire object structure will be integrated intact. When constructing the deployment instance of the app, env was found from the database and directly inserted into the template, resulting in controllability here. Sensitive information in the secret and configmap can be read through the k8s envFrom field. In a privatization environment, when `namespaceConf. fixed` is marked, it may lead to the leakage of sensitive information in the system. As of time of publication, it is unclear whether any patches or workarounds exist.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-48225|2024-08-02T21:23:39.023Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 20:33:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-36815|2024-08-02T17:01:09.546Z -- labring -- sealos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36815</link>
      <description>Sealos is a Cloud Operating System designed for managing cloud-native applications. In version 4.2.0 and prior, there is a permission flaw in the Sealos billing system, which allows users to control the recharge resource account `sealos[.] io/v1/Payment`, resulting in the ability to recharge any amount of 1 renminbi (RMB). The charging interface may expose resource information. The namespace of this custom resource would be user's control and may have permission to correct it. It is not clear whether a fix exists.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-36815|2024-08-02T17:01:09.546Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 17:44:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
