<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for labring -- sealos</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/labring/sealos.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for labring -- sealos</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 22:22:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33190|2024-08-02T15:39:35.773Z -- labring -- sealos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33190</link>
      <description>Sealos is an open source cloud operating system distribution based on the Kubernetes kernel. In versions of Sealos prior to 4.2.1-rc4 an improper configuration of role based access control (RBAC) permissions resulted in an attacker being able to obtain cluster control permissions, which could control the entire cluster deployed with Sealos, as well as hundreds of pods and other resources within the cluster. This issue has been addressed in version 4.2.1-rc4. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33190|2024-08-02T15:39:35.773Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 17:27:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-36815|2024-08-02T17:01:09.546Z -- labring -- sealos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36815</link>
      <description>Sealos is a Cloud Operating System designed for managing cloud-native applications. In version 4.2.0 and prior, there is a permission flaw in the Sealos billing system, which allows users to control the recharge resource account `sealos[.] io/v1/Payment`, resulting in the ability to recharge any amount of 1 renminbi (RMB). The charging interface may expose resource information. The namespace of this custom resource would be user's control and may have permission to correct it. It is not clear whether a fix exists.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-36815|2024-08-02T17:01:09.546Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 17:44:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
