<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for solidusio -- solidus</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/solidusio/solidus.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for solidusio -- solidus</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 09:23:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43805|2024-08-04T04:03:08.816Z -- solidusio -- solidus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43805</link>
      <description>Solidus is a free, open-source ecommerce platform built on Rails. Versions of Solidus prior to 3.1.4, 3.0.4, and 2.11.13 have a denial of service vulnerability that could be exploited during a guest checkout. The regular expression used to validate a guest order's email was subject to exponential backtracking through a fragment like `a.a.` Versions 3.1.4, 3.0.4, and 2.11.13 have been patched to use a different regular expression. The maintainers added a check for email addresses that are no longer valid that will print information about any affected orders that exist. If a prompt upgrade is not an option, a workaround is available. It is possible to edit the file `config/application.rb` manually (with code provided by the maintainers in the GitHub Security Advisory) to check email validity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43805|2024-08-04T04:03:08.816Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 17:25:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-43846|2024-08-04T04:10:16.776Z -- solidusio -- solidus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43846</link>
      <description>`solidus_frontend` is the cart and storefront for the Solidus e-commerce project. Versions of `solidus_frontend` prior to 3.1.5, 3.0.5, and 2.11.14 contain a cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability that allows a malicious site to add an item to the user's cart without their knowledge. Versions 3.1.5, 3.0.5, and 2.11.14 contain a patch for this issue. The patch adds CSRF token verification to the "Add to cart" action. Adding forgery protection to a form that missed it can have some side effects. Other CSRF protection strategies as well as a workaround involving modifcation to config/application.rb` are available. More details on these mitigations are available in the GitHub Security Advisory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-43846|2024-08-04T04:10:16.776Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 21:30:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
