<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for NTP Project -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ntp%20project/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for NTP Project -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:23:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-1551|2024-08-05T23:02:12.002Z -- ntp%20project -- ntp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-1551</link>
      <description>ntpd in NTP 4.2.8p3 and NTPsec a5fb34b9cc89b92a8fef2f459004865c93bb7f92 relies on the underlying operating system to protect it from requests that impersonate reference clocks. Because reference clocks are treated like other peers and stored in the same structure, any packet with a source ip address of a reference clock (127.127.1.1 for example) that reaches the receive() function will match that reference clock's peer record and will be treated as a trusted peer. Any system that lacks the typical martian packet filtering which would block these packets is in danger of having its time controlled by an attacker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-1551|2024-08-05T23:02:12.002Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-1548|2024-08-05T23:02:11.744Z -- ntp%20project -- ntp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-1548</link>
      <description>An attacker can spoof a packet from a legitimate ntpd server with an origin timestamp that matches the peer-&gt;dst timestamp recorded for that server. After making this switch, the client in NTP 4.2.8p4 and earlier and NTPSec aa48d001683e5b791a743ec9c575aaf7d867a2b0c will reject all future legitimate server responses. It is possible to force the victim client to move time after the mode has been changed. ntpq gives no indication that the mode has been switched.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-1548|2024-08-05T23:02:11.744Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-1549|2024-08-05T23:02:12.001Z -- ntp%20project -- ntp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-1549</link>
      <description>A malicious authenticated peer can create arbitrarily-many ephemeral associations in order to win the clock selection algorithm in ntpd in NTP 4.2.8p4 and earlier and NTPsec 3e160db8dc248a0bcb053b56a80167dc742d2b74 and a5fb34b9cc89b92a8fef2f459004865c93bb7f92 and modify a victim's clock.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-1549|2024-08-05T23:02:12.001Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-1547|2024-08-05T23:02:11.962Z -- ntp%20project -- ntp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-1547</link>
      <description>An off-path attacker can cause a preemptible client association to be demobilized in NTP 4.2.8p4 and earlier and NTPSec a5fb34b9cc89b92a8fef2f459004865c93bb7f92 by sending a crypto NAK packet to a victim client with a spoofed source address of an existing associated peer. This is true even if authentication is enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-1547|2024-08-05T23:02:11.962Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-1550|2024-08-05T23:02:11.957Z -- ntp%20project -- ntp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-1550</link>
      <description>An exploitable vulnerability exists in the message authentication functionality of libntp in ntp 4.2.8p4 and NTPSec a5fb34b9cc89b92a8fef2f459004865c93bb7f92. An attacker can send a series of crafted messages to attempt to recover the message digest key.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-1550|2024-08-05T23:02:11.957Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
