<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for JTEKT ELECTRONICS CORPORATION -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/jtekt%20electronics%20corporation/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for JTEKT ELECTRONICS CORPORATION -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 20:23:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22349|2024-08-02T10:07:06.106Z -- jtekt%20electronics%20corporation -- screen%20creator%20advance%202
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22349</link>
      <description>Out-of-bound read vulnerability exists in Screen Creator Advance 2 Ver.0.1.1.4 Build01 and earlier because the end of data cannot be verified when processing screen management information. Having a user of Screen Creator Advance 2 to open a specially crafted project file may lead to information disclosure and/or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22349|2024-08-02T10:07:06.106Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22424|2024-08-02T10:07:06.596Z -- jtekt%20electronics%20corporation -- kostac%20plc%20programming%20software%20%28former%20name%3A%20koyo%20plc%20programming%20software%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22424</link>
      <description>Use-after-free vulnerability exists in Kostac PLC Programming Software (Former name: Koyo PLC Programming Software) Version 1.6.9.0 and earlier. With the abnormal value given as the maximum number of columns for the PLC program, the process accesses the freed memory. As a result, opening a specially crafted project file may lead to information disclosure and/or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22424|2024-08-02T10:07:06.596Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22421|2024-08-02T10:07:06.743Z -- jtekt%20electronics%20corporation -- kostac%20plc%20programming%20software%20%28former%20name%3A%20koyo%20plc%20programming%20software%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22421</link>
      <description>Out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in Kostac PLC Programming Software (Former name: Koyo PLC Programming Software) Version 1.6.9.0 and earlier. The insufficient buffer size for the PLC program instructions leads to out-of-bounds read. As a result, opening a specially crafted project file may lead to information disclosure and/or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22421|2024-08-02T10:07:06.743Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41375|2024-08-02T19:01:35.311Z -- jtekt%20electronics%20corporation -- kostac%20plc%20programming%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41375</link>
      <description>Use after free vulnerability exists in Kostac PLC Programming Software Version 1.6.11.0. Arbitrary code may be executed by having a user open a specially crafted project file which was saved using Kostac PLC Programming Software Version 1.6.9.0 and earlier because the issue exists in parsing of KPP project files. The vendor states that Kostac PLC Programming Software Version 1.6.10.0 or later implements the function which prevents a project file alteration. Therefore, to mitigate the impact of these vulnerabilities, a project file which was saved using Kostac PLC Programming Software Version 1.6.9.0 and earlier needs to be saved again using Kostac PLC Programming Software Version 1.6.10.0 or later.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41375|2024-08-02T19:01:35.311Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 08:49:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22419|2024-08-02T10:07:06.597Z -- jtekt%20electronics%20corporation -- kostac%20plc%20programming%20software%20%28former%20name%3A%20koyo%20plc%20programming%20software%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22419</link>
      <description>Out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in Kostac PLC Programming Software (Former name: Koyo PLC Programming Software) Version 1.6.9.0 and earlier. When processing a comment block in stage information, the end of data cannot be verified and out-of-bounds read occurs. As a result, opening a specially crafted project file may lead to information disclosure and/or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22419|2024-08-02T10:07:06.597Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41963|2024-08-02T19:09:49.464Z -- jtekt%20electronics%20corporation -- gc-a22w-cw
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41963</link>
      <description>Denial-of-service (DoS) vulnerability exists in FTP service of HMI GC-A2 series. If a remote unauthenticated attacker sends a specially crafted packets to specific ports, a denial-of-service (DoS) condition may occur.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41963|2024-08-02T19:09:49.464Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 09:16:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25755|2024-08-02T11:32:12.283Z -- jtekt%20electronics%20corporation -- screen%20creator%20advance%202
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25755</link>
      <description>Screen Creator Advance 2 Ver.0.1.1.4 Build01A and earlier is vulnerable to improper restriction of operations within the bounds of a memory buffer (CWE-119) due to improper check of its data size when processing a project file. If a user of Screen Creator Advance 2 opens a specially crafted project file, information may be disclosed and/or arbitrary code may be executed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25755|2024-08-02T11:32:12.283Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42506|2024-08-02T19:23:38.898Z -- jtekt%20electronics%20corporation -- onsinview2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42506</link>
      <description>Improper restriction of operations within the bounds of a memory buffer issue exists in OnSinView2 versions 2.0.1 and earlier. If this vulnerability is exploited, information may be disclosed or arbitrary code may be executed by having a user open a specially crafted OnSinView2 project file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42506|2024-08-02T19:23:38.898Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 22:32:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22360|2024-08-02T10:07:06.586Z -- jtekt%20electronics%20corporation -- screen%20creator%20advance%202
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22360</link>
      <description>Use-after free vulnerability exists in Screen Creator Advance 2 Ver.0.1.1.4 Build01 and earlier due to lack of error handling process even when an error was detected. Having a user of Screen Creator Advance 2 to open a specially crafted project file may lead to information disclosure and/or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22360|2024-08-02T10:07:06.586Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22353|2024-08-02T10:07:06.031Z -- jtekt%20electronics%20corporation -- screen%20creator%20advance%202
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22353</link>
      <description>Out-of-bound read vulnerability exists in Screen Creator Advance 2 Ver.0.1.1.4 Build01 and earlier because the end of data cannot be verified when processing control management information. Having a user of Screen Creator Advance 2 to open a specially crafted project file may lead to information disclosure and/or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22353|2024-08-02T10:07:06.031Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22347|2024-08-02T10:07:06.047Z -- jtekt%20electronics%20corporation -- screen%20creator%20advance%202
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22347</link>
      <description>Out-of-bound read vulnerability exists in Screen Creator Advance 2 Ver.0.1.1.4 Build01 and earlier because the end of data cannot be verified when processing file structure information. Having a user of Screen Creator Advance 2 to open a specially crafted project file may lead to information disclosure and/or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22347|2024-08-02T10:07:06.047Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41374|2024-08-02T19:01:35.076Z -- jtekt%20electronics%20corporation -- kostac%20plc%20programming%20software
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41374</link>
      <description>Double free issue exists in Kostac PLC Programming Software Version 1.6.11.0 and earlier. Arbitrary code may be executed by having a user open a specially crafted project file which was saved using Kostac PLC Programming Software Version 1.6.9.0 and earlier because the issue exists in parsing of KPP project files. The vendor states that Kostac PLC Programming Software Version 1.6.10.0 or later implements the function which prevents a project file alteration. Therefore, to mitigate the impact of these vulnerabilities, a project file which was saved using Kostac PLC Programming Software Version 1.6.9.0 and earlier needs to be saved again using Kostac PLC Programming Software Version 1.6.10.0 or later.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41374|2024-08-02T19:01:35.076Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 08:49:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22346|2024-08-02T10:07:06.425Z -- jtekt%20electronics%20corporation -- screen%20creator%20advance%202
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22346</link>
      <description>Out-of-bound read vulnerability exists in Screen Creator Advance 2 Ver.0.1.1.4 Build01 and earlier because the end of data cannot be verified when processing template information. Having a user of Screen Creator Advance 2 to open a specially crafted project file may lead to information disclosure and/or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22346|2024-08-02T10:07:06.425Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22350|2024-08-02T10:07:06.255Z -- jtekt%20electronics%20corporation -- screen%20creator%20advance%202
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22350</link>
      <description>Out-of-bound read vulnerability exists in Screen Creator Advance 2 Ver.0.1.1.4 Build01 and earlier because the end of data cannot be verified when processing parts management information. Having a user of Screen Creator Advance 2 to open a specially crafted project file may lead to information disclosure and/or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22350|2024-08-02T10:07:06.255Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22345|2024-08-02T10:07:06.462Z -- jtekt%20electronics%20corporation -- screen%20creator%20advance%202
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22345</link>
      <description>Out-of-bound write vulnerability exists in Screen Creator Advance 2 Ver.0.1.1.4 Build01 and earlier due to lack of error handling process when out of specification errors are detected. Having a user of Screen Creator Advance 2 to open a specially crafted project file may lead to information disclosure and/or arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22345|2024-08-02T10:07:06.462Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-42507|2024-08-02T19:23:39.368Z -- jtekt%20electronics%20corporation -- onsinview2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42507</link>
      <description>Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in OnSinView2 versions 2.0.1 and earlier. If this vulnerability is exploited, information may be disclosed or arbitrary code may be executed by having a user open a specially crafted OnSinView2 project file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-42507|2024-08-02T19:23:39.368Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 22:33:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
