<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Softing -- edgeConnector Siemens</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/softing/edgeconnector%20siemens.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Softing -- edgeConnector Siemens</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27334|2024-06-04T17:24:56.955Z -- softing -- edgeconnector%20siemens
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27334</link>
      <description>Softing edgeConnector Siemens ConditionRefresh Resource Exhaustion Denial-of-Service Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to create a denial-of-service condition on affected installations of Softing edgeConnector Siemens. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of OPC UA ConditionRefresh requests. By sending a large number of requests, an attacker can consume all available resources on the server. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to create a denial-of-service condition on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-20498.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27334|2024-06-04T17:24:56.955Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27336|2024-06-04T17:24:42.930Z -- softing -- edgeconnector%20siemens
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-27336</link>
      <description>Softing edgeConnector Siemens OPC UA Server Null Pointer Dereference Denial-of-Service Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to create a denial-of-service condition on affected installations of Softing edgeConnector Siemens. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of OPC client certificates. The issue results from dereferencing a NULL pointer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to create a denial-of-service condition on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-20508.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27336|2024-06-04T17:24:42.930Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:55:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
