<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Eclipse -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/eclipse/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Eclipse -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 16:24:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3592|2024-08-02T07:01:56.716Z -- eclipse -- mosquitto
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3592</link>
      <description>In Mosquitto before 2.0.16, a memory leak occurs when clients send v5 CONNECT packets with a will message that contains invalid property types.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3592|2024-08-02T07:01:56.716Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 19:01:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0809|2024-08-02T05:24:34.509Z -- eclipse -- mosquitto
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0809</link>
      <description>In Mosquitto before 2.0.16, excessive memory is allocated based on malicious initial packets that are not CONNECT packets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0809|2024-08-02T05:24:34.509Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 18:56:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26048|2024-08-02T11:39:06.487Z -- eclipse -- jetty.project
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26048</link>
      <description>Jetty is a java based web server and servlet engine. In affected versions servlets with multipart support (e.g. annotated with `@MultipartConfig`) that call `HttpServletRequest.getParameter()` or `HttpServletRequest.getParts()` may cause `OutOfMemoryError` when the client sends a multipart request with a part that has a name but no filename and very large content. This happens even with the default settings of `fileSizeThreshold=0` which should stream the whole part content to disk. An attacker client may send a large multipart request and cause the server to throw `OutOfMemoryError`. However, the server may be able to recover after the `OutOfMemoryError` and continue its service -- although it may take some time. This issue has been patched in versions 9.4.51, 10.0.14, and 11.0.14. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade may set the multipart parameter `maxRequestSize` which must be set to a non-negative value, so the whole multipart content is limited (although still read into memory).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26048|2024-08-02T11:39:06.487Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 20:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26049|2024-08-02T11:39:06.483Z -- eclipse -- jetty.project
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26049</link>
      <description>Jetty is a java based web server and servlet engine. Nonstandard cookie parsing in Jetty may allow an attacker to smuggle cookies within other cookies, or otherwise perform unintended behavior by tampering with the cookie parsing mechanism. If Jetty sees a cookie VALUE that starts with `"` (double quote), it will continue to read the cookie string until it sees a closing quote -- even if a semicolon is encountered. So, a cookie header such as: `DISPLAY_LANGUAGE="b; JSESSIONID=1337; c=d"` will be parsed as one cookie, with the name DISPLAY_LANGUAGE and a value of b; JSESSIONID=1337; c=d instead of 3 separate cookies. This has security implications because if, say, JSESSIONID is an HttpOnly cookie, and the DISPLAY_LANGUAGE cookie value is rendered on the page, an attacker can smuggle the JSESSIONID cookie into the DISPLAY_LANGUAGE cookie and thereby exfiltrate it. This is significant when an intermediary is enacting some policy based on cookies, so a smuggled cookie can bypass that policy yet still be seen by the Jetty server or its logging system. This issue has been addressed in versions 9.4.51, 10.0.14, 11.0.14, and 12.0.0.beta0 and users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26049|2024-08-02T11:39:06.483Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 20:35:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5632|2024-08-02T08:07:32.289Z -- eclipse -- mosquitto
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5632</link>
      <description>In Eclipse Mosquito before and including 2.0.5, establishing a connection to the mosquitto server without sending data causes the EPOLLOUT event to be added, which results excessive CPU consumption. This could be used by a malicious actor to perform denial of service type attack. This issue is fixed in 2.0.6


</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5632|2024-08-02T08:07:32.289Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 08:34:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
