<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Eclipse -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/eclipse/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Eclipse -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 22:23:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-36479|2024-09-25T15:04:37.795Z -- eclipse -- jetty.project
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36479</link>
      <description>Eclipse Jetty Canonical Repository is the canonical repository for the Jetty project. Users of the CgiServlet with a very specific command structure may have the wrong command executed. If a user sends a request to a org.eclipse.jetty.servlets.CGI Servlet for a binary with a space in its name, the servlet will escape the command by wrapping it in quotation marks. This wrapped command, plus an optional command prefix, will then be executed through a call to Runtime.exec. If the original binary name provided by the user contains a quotation mark followed by a space, the resulting command line will contain multiple tokens instead of one. This issue was patched in version 9.4.52, 10.0.16, 11.0.16 and 12.0.0-beta2.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-36479|2024-09-25T15:04:37.795Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 18:37:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40167|2024-09-25T18:50:08.203Z -- eclipse -- jetty.project
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40167</link>
      <description>Jetty is a Java based web server and servlet engine. Prior to versions 9.4.52, 10.0.16, 11.0.16, and 12.0.1, Jetty accepts the `+` character proceeding the content-length value in a HTTP/1 header field.  This is more permissive than allowed by the RFC and other servers routinely reject such requests with 400 responses.  There is no known exploit scenario, but it is conceivable that request smuggling could result if jetty is used in combination with a server that does not close the connection after sending such a 400 response. Versions 9.4.52, 10.0.16, 11.0.16, and 12.0.1 contain a patch for this issue. There is no workaround as there is no known exploit scenario.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40167|2024-09-25T18:50:08.203Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 19:37:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
