<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for nik00726 -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/nik00726/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for nik00726 -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 21:22:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2184|2024-08-02T06:12:20.608Z -- nik00726 -- wp%20responsive%20tabs%20horizontal%20vertical%20and%20accordion%20tabs
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2184</link>
      <description>The WP Responsive Tabs horizontal vertical and accordion Tabs plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the search_term parameter in versions up to, and including, 1.1.15 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2184|2024-08-02T06:12:20.608Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 05:33:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2710|2024-08-02T06:33:05.238Z -- nik00726 -- video%20carousel%20slider%20with%20lightbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2710</link>
      <description>The video carousel slider with lightbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the search_term parameter in versions up to, and including, 1.0.22  due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2710|2024-08-02T06:33:05.238Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 02:04:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2708|2024-08-02T06:33:04.314Z -- nik00726 -- video%20gallery
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2708</link>
      <description>The Video Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘search_term’ parameter in versions up to, and including, 1.0.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2708|2024-08-02T06:33:04.314Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 02:04:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6527|2024-08-02T08:35:14.198Z -- nik00726 -- email%20subscription%20popup
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6527</link>
      <description>The Email Subscription Popup plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the HTTP_REFERER header in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.18 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6527|2024-08-02T08:35:14.198Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 04:32:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2120|2024-08-02T06:12:20.449Z -- nik00726 -- thumbnail%20carousel%20slider
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2120</link>
      <description>The Thumbnail carousel slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the search_term parameter in versions up to, and including, 1.1.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2120|2024-08-02T06:12:20.449Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 01:57:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2402|2024-08-02T06:19:15.113Z -- nik00726 -- photo%20gallery%20slideshow%20%26%20masonry%20tiled%20gallery
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2402</link>
      <description>The Photo Gallery Slideshow &amp; Masonry Tiled Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the search_term parameter in versions up to, and including, 1.0.13 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2402|2024-08-02T06:19:15.113Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 05:33:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2119|2024-08-02T06:12:20.469Z -- nik00726 -- responsive%20filterable%20portfolio
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2119</link>
      <description>The Responsive Filterable Portfolio plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the search_term parameter in versions up to, and including, 1.0.19 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2119|2024-08-02T06:12:20.469Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 01:57:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5821|2024-08-02T08:14:24.765Z -- nik00726 -- thumbnail%20carousel%20slider
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5821</link>
      <description>The Thumbnail carousel slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in version 1.0. This is due to missing nonce validation on the deleteselected function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete sliders in bulk via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5821|2024-08-02T08:14:24.765Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 11:28:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5531|2024-08-02T07:59:44.836Z -- nik00726 -- thumbnail%20slider%20with%20lightbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5531</link>
      <description>The Thumbnail Slider With Lightbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the delete functionality. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete image lightboxes via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5531|2024-08-02T07:59:44.836Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 05:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5621|2024-08-02T08:07:32.416Z -- nik00726 -- thumbnail%20slider%20with%20lightbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5621</link>
      <description>The Thumbnail Slider With Lightbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Image Title field in versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5621|2024-08-02T08:07:32.416Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 07:31:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5945|2024-08-02T08:14:25.123Z -- nik00726 -- video%20carousel%20slider%20with%20lightbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5945</link>
      <description>The video carousel slider with lightbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in version 1.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the responsive_video_gallery_with_lightbox_video_management_func() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete videos hosted from the video slider via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5945|2024-08-02T08:14:25.123Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 12:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5820|2024-08-02T08:14:24.659Z -- nik00726 -- thumbnail%20slider%20with%20lightbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5820</link>
      <description>The Thumbnail Slider With Lightbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in version 1.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the addedit functionality. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5820|2024-08-02T08:14:24.659Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 11:28:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2289|2024-08-02T06:19:14.772Z -- nik00726 -- wordpress%20vertical%20image%20slider%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2289</link>
      <description>The wordpress vertical image slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘search_term’ parameter in versions up to, and including, 1.2.16 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2289|2024-08-02T06:19:14.772Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 05:33:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2604|2024-08-02T06:26:09.903Z -- nik00726 -- team%20circle%20image%20slider%20with%20lightbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2604</link>
      <description>The Team Circle Image Slider With Lightbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘search_term’ parameter in versions up to, and including, 1.0.17 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2604|2024-08-02T06:26:09.903Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 05:33:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
