<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for nik00726 -- Thumbnail Slider With Lightbox</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/nik00726/thumbnail%20slider%20with%20lightbox.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for nik00726 -- Thumbnail Slider With Lightbox</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 22:23:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5531|2024-08-02T07:59:44.836Z -- nik00726 -- thumbnail%20slider%20with%20lightbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5531</link>
      <description>The Thumbnail Slider With Lightbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the delete functionality. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete image lightboxes via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5531|2024-08-02T07:59:44.836Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 05:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5621|2024-08-02T08:07:32.416Z -- nik00726 -- thumbnail%20slider%20with%20lightbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5621</link>
      <description>The Thumbnail Slider With Lightbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Image Title field in versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5621|2024-08-02T08:07:32.416Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 07:31:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5820|2024-08-02T08:14:24.659Z -- nik00726 -- thumbnail%20slider%20with%20lightbox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5820</link>
      <description>The Thumbnail Slider With Lightbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in version 1.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the addedit functionality. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5820|2024-08-02T08:14:24.659Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 11:28:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
