<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for bluemark -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/bluemark/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for bluemark -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29156|2023-07-11T08:42:03.909Z -- bluemark -- ds230
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-29156</link>
      <description>DroneScout ds230 Remote ID receiver from BlueMark Innovations is affected by an information loss vulnerability through traffic injection.
An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by injecting, at the right times, spoofed Open Drone ID (ODID) messages which force the DroneScout ds230 Remote ID receiver to drop real Remote ID (RID) information and, instead, generate and transmit JSON encoded MQTT messages containing crafted RID information. Consequently, the MQTT broker, typically operated by a system integrator, will have no access to the drones’ real RID information.

This issue affects DroneScout ds230 in default configuration from firmware version 20211210-1627 through 20230329-1042.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29156|2023-07-11T08:42:03.909Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 08:42:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31191|2023-07-11T08:45:14.541Z -- bluemark -- ds230
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-31191</link>
      <description>DroneScout ds230 Remote ID receiver from BlueMark Innovations is affected by an information loss vulnerability through traffic injection.

An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by injecting, on carefully selected channels, high power spoofed Open Drone ID (ODID) messages which force the DroneScout ds230 Remote ID receiver to drop real Remote ID (RID) information and, instead, generate and transmit JSON encoded MQTT messages containing crafted RID information. Consequently, the MQTT broker, typically operated by a system integrator, will have no access to the drones’ real RID information.

This issue affects the adjacent channel suppression algorithm present in DroneScout ds230 firmware from version 20211210-1627 through 20230329-1042.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31191|2023-07-11T08:45:14.541Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 08:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-31190|2023-07-11T08:43:25.187Z -- bluemark -- ds230
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-31190</link>
      <description>DroneScout ds230 Remote ID receiver from BlueMark Innovations is affected by an Improper Authentication vulnerability during the firmware update procedure.

Specifically, the firmware update procedure ignores and does not check the validity of the TLS certificate of the HTTPS endpoint from which the firmware update package (.tar.bz2 file) is downloaded.
An attacker with the ability to put himself in a Man-in-the-Middle situation (e.g., DNS poisoning, ARP poisoning, control of a node on the route to the endpoint, etc.) can trick the DroneScout ds230 to install a crafted malicious firmware update containing arbitrary files (e.g., executable and configuration) and gain administrative (root) privileges on the underlying Linux operating system.
This issue affects DroneScout ds230 firmware from version 20211210-1627 through 20230329-1042.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-31190|2023-07-11T08:43:25.187Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 08:43:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
