<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Huawei -- CloudEngine 12800</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/huawei/cloudengine%2012800.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Huawei -- CloudEngine 12800</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 16:23:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9102|2024-08-04T10:19:19.813Z -- huawei -- cloudengine%2012800
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9102</link>
      <description>There is a information leak vulnerability in some Huawei products, and it could allow a local attacker to get information. The vulnerability is due to the improper management of the username. An attacker with the ability to access the device and cause the username information leak. Affected product versions include: CloudEngine 12800 versions V200R002C50SPC800, V200R003C00SPC810, V200R005C00SPC800, V200R005C10SPC800, V200R019C00SPC800; CloudEngine 5800 versions V200R002C50SPC800, V200R003C00SPC810, V200R005C00SPC800, V200R005C10SPC800, V200R019C00SPC800; CloudEngine 6800 versions V200R002C50SPC800, V200R003C00SPC810, V200R005C00SPC800, V200R005C10SPC800, V200R005C20SPC800, V200R019C00SPC800; CloudEngine 7800 versions V200R002C50SPC800, V200R003C00SPC810, V200R005C00SPC800, V200R005C10SPC800, V200R019C00SPC800</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9102|2024-08-04T10:19:19.813Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 22:59:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9094|2024-08-04T10:19:19.790Z -- huawei -- cloudengine%2012800
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9094</link>
      <description>There is an out of bound read vulnerability in some verisons of Huawei CloudEngine product. A module does not deal with specific message properly. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious packet. This can lead to denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9094|2024-08-04T10:19:19.790Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 17:28:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9124|2024-08-04T10:19:19.917Z -- huawei -- cloudengine%2012800
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9124</link>
      <description>There is a memory leak vulnerability in some versions of Huawei CloudEngine product. An unauthenticated, remote attacker may exploit this vulnerability by sending specific message to the affected product. Due to not release the allocated memory properly, successful exploit may cause memory leak.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9124|2024-08-04T10:19:19.917Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 17:17:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-9207|2024-08-04T10:19:19.931Z -- huawei -- cloudengine%2012800
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9207</link>
      <description>There is an improper authentication vulnerability in some verisons of Huawei CloudEngine product. A module does not verify the input file properly. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability by crafting malicious files to bypass current verification mechanism. This can compromise normal service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-9207|2024-08-04T10:19:19.931Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 17:57:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1870|2024-08-04T06:53:58.990Z -- huawei -- cloudengine%2012800
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1870</link>
      <description>There is a denial of service vulnerability in some Huawei products. Due to improper memory management, memory leakage may occur in some special cases. Attackers can perform a series of operations to exploit this vulnerability. Successful exploit may cause a denial of service. Affected product versions include: CloudEngine 12800 versions V200R019C00SPC800; CloudEngine 5800 versions V200R019C00SPC800; CloudEngine 6800 versions V200R005C20SPC800, V200R019C00SPC800; CloudEngine 7800 versions V200R019C00SPC800; NE40E versions V800R011C00SPC200, V800R011C00SPC300, V800R011C10SPC100; NE40E-F versions V800R011C00SPC200, V800R011C10SPC100; NE40E-M versions V800R011C00SPC200, V800R011C10SPC100.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1870|2024-08-04T06:53:58.990Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 19:13:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
