<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Huawei -- Honor V10</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/huawei/honor%20v10.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Huawei -- Honor V10</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 15:22:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1806|2024-08-04T06:46:30.950Z -- huawei -- honor%20v10
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1806</link>
      <description>Huawei Honor V10 smartphones with versions earlier than 10.0.0.156(C00E156R2P4) has three out of bounds vulnerabilities. Certain driver program does not sufficiently validate certain parameters received, that would lead to several bytes out of bound read. Successful exploit may cause information disclosure or service abnormal. This is 3 out of 3 out of bounds vulnerabilities found. Different than CVE-2020-1804 and CVE-2020-1805.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1806|2024-08-04T06:46:30.950Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 14:52:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1804|2024-08-04T06:46:30.926Z -- huawei -- honor%20v10
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1804</link>
      <description>Huawei Honor V10 smartphones with versions earlier than 10.0.0.156(C00E156R2P4) has three out of bounds vulnerabilities. Certain driver program does not sufficiently validate certain parameters received, that would lead to several bytes out of bound read. Successful exploit may cause information disclosure or service abnormal. This is 1 out of 3 out of bounds vulnerabilities found. Different than CVE-2020-1805 and CVE-2020-1806.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1804|2024-08-04T06:46:30.926Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 14:48:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1805|2024-08-04T06:46:30.907Z -- huawei -- honor%20v10
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1805</link>
      <description>Huawei Honor V10 smartphones with versions earlier than 10.0.0.156(C00E156R2P4) has three out of bounds vulnerabilities. Certain driver program does not sufficiently validate certain parameters received, that would lead to several bytes out of bound read. Successful exploit may cause information disclosure or service abnormal. This is 2 out of 3 out of bounds vulnerabilities found. Different than CVE-2020-1804 and CVE-2020-1806.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1805|2024-08-04T06:46:30.907Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 14:50:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
