<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Huawei -- NIP6800</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/huawei/nip6800.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Huawei -- NIP6800</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 07:20:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1828|2024-08-04T06:46:30.955Z -- huawei -- nip6800
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1828</link>
      <description>Huawei NIP6800 versions V500R001C30, V500R001C60SPC500, and V500R005C00; and Secospace USG6600 and USG9500 versions V500R001C30SPC200, V500R001C30SPC600, V500R001C60SPC500, and V500R005C00 have an input validation vulnerability where the IPSec module does not validate a field in a specific message. Attackers can send specific message to cause out-of-bound read, compromising normal service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1828|2024-08-04T06:46:30.955Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 19:49:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1829|2024-08-04T06:46:31.029Z -- huawei -- nip6800
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1829</link>
      <description>Huawei NIP6800 versions V500R001C30 and V500R001C60SPC500; and Secospace USG6600 and USG9500 versions V500R001C30SPC200, V500R001C30SPC600, and V500R001C60SPC500 have a vulnerability that the IPSec module handles a message improperly. Attackers can send specific message to cause double free memory. This may compromise normal service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1829|2024-08-04T06:46:31.029Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 20:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1814|2024-08-04T06:46:30.897Z -- huawei -- nip6800
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1814</link>
      <description>Huawei NIP6800 versions V500R001C30, V500R001C60SPC500, and V500R005C00; Secospace USG6600 and USG9500 versions V500R001C30SPC200, V500R001C30SPC600, V500R001C60SPC500, and V500R005C00 have a Dangling pointer dereference vulnerability. An authenticated attacker may do some special operations in the affected products in some special scenarios to exploit the vulnerability. Due to improper race conditions of different operations, successful exploit will lead to Dangling pointer dereference, causing some service abnormal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1814|2024-08-04T06:46:30.897Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 01:53:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1816|2024-08-04T06:46:30.940Z -- huawei -- nip6800
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1816</link>
      <description>Huawei NIP6800 versions V500R001C30, V500R001C60SPC500, and V500R005C00; Secospace USG6600 and USG9500 versions V500R001C30SPC200, V500R001C30SPC600, V500R001C60SPC500, and V500R005C00 have a Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability. Due to improper processing of specific IPSEC packets, remote attackers can send constructed IPSEC packets to affected devices to exploit this vulnerability. Successful exploit could cause the IPSec function of the affected device abnormal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1816|2024-08-04T06:46:30.940Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 23:24:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1858|2024-08-04T06:53:58.976Z -- huawei -- nip6800
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1858</link>
      <description>Huawei products NIP6800 versions V500R001C30, V500R001C60SPC500, and V500R005C00SPC100; Secospace USG6600 versions V500R001C30SPC600, V500R001C60SPC500, and V500R005C00SPC100; and USG9500 versions V500R001C30SPC600, V500R001C60SPC500, and V500R005C00SPC100 have a denial of service vulnerability. Attackers need to perform a series of operations in a special scenario to exploit this vulnerability. Successful exploit may cause the new connections can't be established, result in a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1858|2024-08-04T06:53:58.976Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 19:30:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1830|2024-08-04T06:46:30.948Z -- huawei -- nip6800
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1830</link>
      <description>Huawei NIP6800 versions V500R001C30, V500R001C60SPC500, and V500R005C00; Secospace USG6600 and USG9500 versions V500R001C30SPC200, V500R001C30SPC600, V500R001C60SPC500, and V500R005C00 have a vulnerability that a memory management error exists when IPSec Module handing a specific message. This causes 1 byte out-of-bound read, compromising normal service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1830|2024-08-04T06:46:30.948Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 23:35:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1827|2024-08-04T06:46:30.916Z -- huawei -- nip6800
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1827</link>
      <description>Huawei NIP6800 versions V500R001C30, V500R001C60SPC500, and V500R005C00SPC100; and Secospace USG6600 and USG9500 versions V500R001C30SPC200, V500R001C30SPC600, V500R001C60SPC500, and V500R005C00SPC100 have an information leakage vulnerability. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by sending specific request packets to affected devices. Successful exploit may lead to information leakage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1827|2024-08-04T06:46:30.916Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 20:38:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1815|2024-08-04T06:46:30.981Z -- huawei -- nip6800
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1815</link>
      <description>Huawei NIP6800 versions V500R001C30, V500R001C60SPC500, and V500R005C00; Secospace USG6600 and USG9500 versions V500R001C30SPC200, V500R001C30SPC600, V500R001C60SPC500, and V500R005C00 have a memory leak vulnerability. The software does not sufficiently track and release allocated memory while parse certain message, the attacker sends the message continuously that could consume remaining memory. Successful exploit could cause memory exhaust.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1815|2024-08-04T06:46:30.981Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 23:18:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1857|2024-08-04T06:53:58.616Z -- huawei -- nip6800
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1857</link>
      <description>Huawei NIP6800 versions V500R001C30, V500R001C60SPC500, and V500R005C00SPC100; and Secospace USG6600 and USG9500 versions V500R001C30SPC200, V500R001C30SPC600, V500R001C60SPC500, and V500R005C00SPC100 have an information leakage vulnerability. Due to improper processing of some data, a local authenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability through a series of operations. Successful exploitation may cause information leakage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1857|2024-08-04T06:53:58.616Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 20:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
