<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for engelsystem -- engelsystem</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/engelsystem/engelsystem.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for engelsystem -- engelsystem</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-45152|2023-10-16T23:34:28.735Z -- engelsystem -- engelsystem
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-45152</link>
      <description>Engelsystem is a shift planning system for chaos events. A Blind SSRF in the "Import schedule" functionality makes it possible to perform a port scan against the local environment. This vulnerability has been fixed in commit ee7d30b33. If a patch cannot be deployed, operators should ensure that no HTTP(s) services listen on localhost and/or systems only reachable from the host running the engelsystem software. If such services are necessary, they should utilize additional authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-45152|2023-10-16T23:34:28.735Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 23:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-45659|2023-10-16T23:32:57.929Z -- engelsystem -- engelsystem
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-45659</link>
      <description>Engelsystem is a shift planning system for chaos events.  If a users' password is compromised and an attacker gained access to a users' account, i.e., logged in and obtained a session, an attackers' session is not terminated if the users' account password is reset. This vulnerability has been fixed in the commit `dbb089315ff3d`. Users are advised to update their installations. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-45659|2023-10-16T23:32:57.929Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 23:32:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50924|2023-12-22T20:37:47.224Z -- engelsystem -- engelsystem
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50924</link>
      <description>Englesystem is a shift planning system for chaos events. Engelsystem prior to v3.4.1 performed insufficient validation of user supplied data for the DECT number, mobile number, and work-log comment fields. The values of those fields would be displayed in corresponding log overviews, allowing the injection and execution of Javascript code in another user's context. This vulnerability enables an authenticated user to inject Javascript into other user's sessions. The injected JS will be executed during normal usage of the system when viewing, e.g., overview pages. This issue has been fixed in version 3.4.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50924|2023-12-22T20:37:47.224Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 20:37:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
