<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for MariaDB -- MariaDB</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/mariadb/mariadb.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for MariaDB -- MariaDB</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 15:22:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24048|2024-08-03T03:59:23.650Z -- mariadb -- mariadb
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24048</link>
      <description>MariaDB CONNECT Storage Engine Stack-based Buffer Overflow Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of MariaDB. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the processing of SQL queries. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-16191.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24048|2024-08-03T03:59:23.650Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 19:51:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24052|2024-08-03T03:59:23.548Z -- mariadb -- mariadb
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24052</link>
      <description>MariaDB CONNECT Storage Engine Heap-based Buffer Overflow Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of MariaDB. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the processing of SQL queries. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-16190.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24052|2024-08-03T03:59:23.548Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 19:51:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24050|2024-08-03T03:59:23.684Z -- mariadb -- mariadb
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24050</link>
      <description>MariaDB CONNECT Storage Engine Use-After-Free Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of MariaDB. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the processing of SQL queries. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-16207.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24050|2024-08-03T03:59:23.684Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 19:51:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24051|2024-08-03T03:59:23.659Z -- mariadb -- mariadb
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24051</link>
      <description>MariaDB CONNECT Storage Engine Format String Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of MariaDB. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the processing of SQL queries. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it as a format specifier. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-16193.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24051|2024-08-03T03:59:23.659Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 19:51:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
