<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SolarWinds -- Web Help Desk</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/solarwinds/web%20help%20desk.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SolarWinds -- Web Help Desk</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 10:23:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35243|2024-08-04T00:33:51.244Z -- solarwinds -- web%20help%20desk
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35243</link>
      <description>The HTTP PUT and DELETE methods were enabled in the Web Help Desk web server (12.7.7 and earlier), allowing users to execute dangerous HTTP requests. The HTTP PUT method is normally used to upload data that is saved on the server with a user-supplied URL. While the DELETE method requests that the origin server removes the association between the target resource and its current functionality. Improper use of these methods may lead to a loss of integrity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35243|2024-08-04T00:33:51.244Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35251|2024-08-04T00:33:51.272Z -- solarwinds -- web%20help%20desk
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35251</link>
      <description>Sensitive information could be displayed when a detailed technical error message is posted. This information could disclose environmental details about the Web Help Desk installation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35251|2024-08-04T00:33:51.272Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-35232|2024-08-04T00:33:51.242Z -- solarwinds -- web%20help%20desk
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35232</link>
      <description>Hard coded credentials discovered in SolarWinds Web Help Desk product. Through these credentials, the attacker with local access to the Web Help Desk host machine allows to execute arbitrary HQL queries against the database and leverage the vulnerability to steal the password hashes of the users or insert arbitrary data into the database.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-35232|2024-08-04T00:33:51.242Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
