<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for yt-dlp -- yt-dlp</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/yt-dlp/yt-dlp.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for yt-dlp -- yt-dlp</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 19:19:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38519|2024-07-24T18:21:58.650Z -- yt-dlp -- yt-dlp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38519</link>
      <description>`yt-dlp` and `youtube-dl` are command-line audio/video downloaders. Prior to the fixed versions, `yt-dlp` and `youtube-dl` do not limit the extensions of downloaded files, which could lead to arbitrary filenames being created in the download folder (and path traversal on Windows). Since `yt-dlp` and `youtube-dl` also read config from the working directory (and on Windows executables will be executed from the `yt-dlp` or `youtube-dl` directory), this could lead to arbitrary code being executed.




`yt-dlp` version 2024.07.01 fixes this issue by whitelisting the allowed extensions. `youtube-dl` fixes this issue in commit `d42a222` on the `master` branch and in nightly builds tagged 2024-07-03 or later. This might mean some very uncommon extensions might not get downloaded, however it will also limit the possible exploitation surface. In addition to upgrading, have `.%(ext)s` at the end of the output template and make sure the user trusts the websites that they are downloading from. Also, make sure to never download to a directory within PATH or other sensitive locations like one's user directory, `system32`, or other binaries locations. For users who are not able to upgrade, keep the default output template (`-o "%(title)s [%(id)s].%(ext)s`); make sure the extension of the media to download is a common video/audio/sub/... one; try to avoid the generic extractor; and/or use `--ignore-config --config-location ...` to not load config from common locations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-38519|2024-07-24T18:21:58.650Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 13:47:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22423|2024-06-04T17:52:45.637Z -- yt-dlp -- yt-dlp</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22423</link>
      <description>yt-dlp is a youtube-dl fork with additional features and fixes. The patch that addressed CVE-2023-40581 attempted to prevent RCE when using `--exec` with `%q` by replacing double quotes with two double quotes. However, this escaping is not sufficient, and still allows expansion of environment variables. Support for output template expansion in `--exec`, along with this vulnerable behavior, was added to `yt-dlp` in version 2021.04.11. yt-dlp version 2024.04.09 fixes this issue by properly escaping `%`. It replaces them with `%%cd:~,%`, a variable that expands to nothing, leaving only the leading percent. It is recommended to upgrade yt-dlp to version 2024.04.09 as soon as possible. Also, always be careful when using `--exec`, because while this specific vulnerability has been patched, using unvalidated input in shell commands is inherently dangerous. For Windows users who are not able to upgrade, avoid using any output template expansion in `--exec` other than `{}` (filepath); if expansion in `--exec` is needed, verify the fields you are using do not contain `"`, `|` or `&amp;`; and/or instead of using `--exec`, write the info json and load the fields from it instead.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22423|2024-06-04T17:52:45.637Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 17:22:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38519|2024-07-02T13:47:36.399Z -- yt-dlp -- yt-dlp</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38519</link>
      <description>`yt-dlp` is a command-line audio/video downloader. Prior to version 2024.07.01, `yt-dlp` does not limit the extensions of downloaded files, which could lead to aribitrary filenames being created in the download folder (and path traversal on Windows). Since `yt-dlp` also reads config from the working directory (and on Windows executables will be executed from the yt-dlp directory) this could lead to arbitrary code being executed. `yt-dlp` version 2024.07.01 fixes this issue by whitelisting the allowed extensions. This might mean some very uncommon extensions might not get downloaded, however it will also limit the possible exploitation surface. In addition to upgrading, have `.%(ext)s` at the end of the output template and make sure the user trusts the websites that they are downloading from. Also, make sure to never download to a directory within PATH or other sensitive locations like one's user directory, `system32`, or other binaries locations. For users who are not able to upgrade, keep the default output template (`-o "%(title)s [%(id)s].%(ext)s`); make sure the extension of the media to download is a common video/audio/sub/... one; try to avoid the generic extractor; and/or use `--ignore-config --config-location ...` to not load config from common locations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-38519|2024-07-02T13:47:36.399Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 13:47:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
