<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for redis -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/redis/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for redis -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 19:20:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28856|2024-08-02T13:51:38.912Z -- redis -- redis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28856</link>
      <description>Redis is an open source, in-memory database that persists on disk. Authenticated users can use the `HINCRBYFLOAT` command to create an invalid hash field that will crash Redis on access in affected versions. This issue has been addressed in in versions 7.0.11, 6.2.12, and 6.0.19. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28856|2024-08-02T13:51:38.912Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 20:50:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41053|2024-08-02T18:46:11.704Z -- redis -- redis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41053</link>
      <description>Redis is an in-memory database that persists on disk. Redis does not correctly identify keys accessed by `SORT_RO` and as a result may grant users executing this command access to keys that are not explicitly authorized by the ACL configuration. The problem exists in Redis 7.0 or newer and has been fixed in Redis 7.0.13 and 7.2.1. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41053|2024-08-02T18:46:11.704Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 20:22:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41056|2024-08-02T18:46:11.706Z -- redis -- redis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41056</link>
      <description>Redis is an in-memory database that persists on disk. Redis incorrectly handles resizing of memory buffers which can result in integer overflow that leads to heap overflow and potential remote code execution. This issue has been patched in version 7.0.15 and 7.2.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41056|2024-08-02T18:46:11.706Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 15:59:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-36824|2024-08-02T17:01:09.772Z -- redis -- redis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36824</link>
      <description>Redis is an in-memory database that persists on disk. In Redit 7.0 prior to 7.0.12, extracting key names from a command and a list of arguments may, in some cases, trigger a heap overflow and result in reading random heap memory, heap corruption and potentially remote code execution. Several scenarios that may lead to authenticated users executing a specially crafted `COMMAND GETKEYS` or `COMMAND GETKEYSANDFLAGS`and authenticated users who were set with ACL rules that match key names, executing a specially crafted command that refers to a variadic list of key names. The vulnerability is patched in Redis 7.0.12.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-36824|2024-08-02T17:01:09.772Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 16:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28425|2024-08-02T12:38:25.331Z -- redis -- redis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28425</link>
      <description>Redis is an in-memory database that persists on disk. Starting in version 7.0.8 and prior to version 7.0.10, authenticated users can use the MSETNX command to trigger a runtime assertion and termination of the Redis server process. The problem is fixed in Redis version 7.0.10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28425|2024-08-02T12:38:25.331Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 19:03:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22458|2024-08-02T10:13:48.522Z -- redis -- redis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22458</link>
      <description>Redis is an in-memory database that persists on disk. Authenticated users can issue a `HRANDFIELD` or `ZRANDMEMBER` command with specially crafted arguments to trigger a denial-of-service by crashing Redis with an assertion failure. This problem affects Redis versions 6.2 or newer up to but not including 6.2.9 as well as versions 7.0 up to but not including 7.0.8. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22458|2024-08-02T10:13:48.522Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 18:19:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-25155|2024-08-02T11:18:36.023Z -- redis -- redis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25155</link>
      <description>Redis is an in-memory database that persists on disk. Authenticated users issuing specially crafted `SRANDMEMBER`, `ZRANDMEMBER`, and `HRANDFIELD` commands can trigger an integer overflow, resulting in a runtime assertion and termination of the Redis server process. This problem affects all Redis versions. Patches were released in Redis version(s) 6.0.18, 6.2.11 and 7.0.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-25155|2024-08-02T11:18:36.023Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 03:01:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
