<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Sustainsys -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sustainsys/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Sustainsys -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 11:20:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5261|2024-08-04T08:22:09.101Z -- sustainsys -- saml2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5261</link>
      <description>Saml2 Authentication services for ASP.NET (NuGet package Sustainsys.Saml2) greater than 2.0.0, and less than version 2.5.0 has a faulty implementation of Token Replay Detection. Token Replay Detection is an important defence in depth measure for Single Sign On solutions. The 2.5.0 version is patched. Note that version 1.0.1 is not affected. It has a correct Token Replay Implementation and is safe to use. Saml2 Authentication services for ASP.NET (NuGet package Sustainsys.Saml2) greater than 2.0.0, and less than version 2.5.0 have a faulty implementation of Token Replay Detection. Token Replay Detection is an important defense measure for Single Sign On solutions. The 2.5.0 version is patched. Note that version 1.0.1 and prior versions are not affected. These versions have a correct Token Replay Implementation and are safe to use.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5261|2024-08-04T08:22:09.101Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 01:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5268|2024-08-04T08:22:09.027Z -- sustainsys -- saml2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5268</link>
      <description>In Saml2 Authentication Services for ASP.NET versions before 1.0.2, and between 2.0.0 and 2.6.0, there is a vulnerability in how tokens are validated in some cases. Saml2 tokens are usually used as bearer tokens - a caller that presents a token is assumed to be the subject of the token. There is also support in the Saml2 protocol for issuing tokens that is tied to a subject through other means, e.g. holder-of-key where possession of a private key must be proved. The Sustainsys.Saml2 library incorrectly treats all incoming tokens as bearer tokens, even though they have another subject confirmation method specified. This could be used by an attacker that could get access to Saml2 tokens with another subject confirmation method than bearer. The attacker could then use such a token to create a log in session. This vulnerability is patched in versions 1.0.2 and 2.7.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5268|2024-08-04T08:22:09.027Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 15:30:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
