<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Talos -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/talos/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Talos -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:21:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3884|2024-09-16T21:02:27.961Z -- talos -- erpnext
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3884</link>
      <description>An exploitable SQL injection vulnerability exists in the authenticated part of ERPNext v10.1.6. Specially crafted web requests can cause SQL injections resulting in data compromise. The sort_by and start parameter can be used to perform an SQL injection attack. An attacker can use a browser to trigger these vulnerabilities, and no special tools are required.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3884|2024-09-16T21:02:27.961Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12112|2024-09-16T19:25:48.209Z -- talos -- cpp-ethereum
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12112</link>
      <description>An exploitable improper authorization vulnerability exists in admin_addPeer API of cpp-ethereum's JSON-RPC (commit 4e1015743b95821849d001618a7ce82c7c073768). A JSON request can cause an access to the restricted functionality resulting in authorization bypass. An attacker can send JSON to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12112|2024-09-16T19:25:48.209Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3885|2024-09-16T22:20:49.348Z -- talos -- erpnext
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3885</link>
      <description>An exploitable SQL injection vulnerability exists in the authenticated part of ERPNext v10.1.6. Specially crafted web requests can cause SQL injections resulting in data compromise. The order_by parameter can be used to perform an SQL injection attack. An attacker can use a browser to trigger these vulnerabilities, and no special tools are required.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3885|2024-09-16T22:20:49.348Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3840|2024-09-16T16:18:39.378Z -- talos -- pixar%20renderman
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3840</link>
      <description>A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the Pixar Renderman IT Display Service 21.6 (0x67). The vulnerability is present in the parsing of a network packet without proper validation of the packet. The data read by the application is not validated, and its use can lead to a null pointer dereference. The IT application is opened by a user and then listens for a connection on port 4001. An attacker can deliver an attack once the application has been opened.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3840|2024-09-16T16:18:39.378Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14462|2024-09-16T17:53:02.932Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14462</link>
      <description>An exploitable access control vulnerability exists in the data, program, and function file permissions functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a read or write operation resulting in disclosure of sensitive information, modification of settings, or modification of ladder logic. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability. Required Keyswitch State: REMOTE or PROG (also RUN for some) Description: Allows an attacker to enable SNMP, Modbus, DNP, and any other features in the channel configuration. Also allows attackers to change network parameters, such as IP address, name server, and domain name.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14462|2024-09-16T17:53:02.932Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14469|2024-09-16T17:48:19.444Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14469</link>
      <description>An exploitable access control vulnerability exists in the data, program, and function file permissions functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a read or write operation resulting in disclosure of sensitive information, modification of settings, or modification of ladder logic. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability. Required Keyswitch State: REMOTE or PROG Associated Fault Code: 0028 Fault Type: Non-User Description: Values 0x01 and 0x02 are invalid values for the user fault routine. By writing directly to the file it is possible to set these values. When this is done and the device is moved into a run state, a fault is triggered. NOTE: This is not possible through RSLogix.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14469|2024-09-16T17:48:19.444Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12092|2024-09-16T19:56:47.572Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12092</link>
      <description>An exploitable file write vulnerability exists in the memory module functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a file write resulting in a new program being written to the memory module. An attacker can send an unauthenticated packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12092|2024-09-16T19:56:47.572Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4054|2024-09-16T17:07:50.912Z -- talos -- pixar%20renderman
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4054</link>
      <description>A local privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the install helper tool of the Mac OS X version of Pixar Renderman, version 22.2.0. A user with local access can use this vulnerability to escalate their privileges to root. An attacker would need local access to the machine to successfully exploit this flaw.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4054|2024-09-16T17:07:50.912Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2858|2024-09-16T16:18:16.697Z -- talos -- natus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2858</link>
      <description>An exploitable denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the traversal of lists functionality of Natus Xltek NeuroWorks 8. A specially crafted network packet can cause an out-of-bounds read, resulting in a denial of service. An attacker can send a malicious packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2858|2024-09-16T16:18:16.697Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3841|2024-09-16T17:13:56.374Z -- talos -- pixar%20renderman
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3841</link>
      <description>A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the Pixar Renderman IT Display Service 21.6 (0x69). The vulnerability is present in the parsing of a network packet without proper validation of the packet. The data read-in is not validated, and its use can lead to a null pointer dereference. The IT application is opened by a user and then listens for a connection on port 4001. An attacker can deliver an attack once the application has been opened.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3841|2024-09-16T17:13:56.374Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12126|2024-09-16T16:53:59.341Z -- talos -- moxa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12126</link>
      <description>An exploitable cross-site request forgery vulnerability exists in the web server functionality of Moxa EDR-810 V4.1 build 17030317. A specially crafted HTTP packet can cause cross-site request forgery. An attacker can create malicious HTML to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12126|2024-09-16T16:53:59.341Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4038|2024-09-16T22:09:06.930Z -- talos -- atlantis%20word%20processor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4038</link>
      <description>An exploitable arbitrary write vulnerability exists in the open document format parser of the Atlantis Word Processor, version 3.2.7.2, while trying to null-terminate a string. A specially crafted document can allow an attacker to pass an untrusted value as a length to a constructor. This constructor will miscalculate a length and then use it to calculate the position to write a null byte. This can allow an attacker to corrupt memory, which can result in code execution under the context of the application. An attacker must convince a victim to open a specially crafted document in order to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4038|2024-09-16T22:09:06.930Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12130|2024-09-16T22:34:55.599Z -- talos -- tinysvcmdns
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12130</link>
      <description>An exploitable NULL pointer dereference vulnerability exists in the tinysvcmdns library version 2017-11-05. A specially crafted packet can make the library dereference a NULL pointer leading to a server crash and denial of service. An attacker needs to send a DNS query to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12130|2024-09-16T22:34:55.599Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14434|2024-09-16T22:45:13.801Z -- talos -- moxa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14434</link>
      <description>An exploitable command injection vulnerability exists in the web server functionality of Moxa EDR-810 V4.1 build 17030317. A specially crafted HTTP POST can cause a privilege escalation resulting in root shell. An attacker can inject OS commands into the remoteNetmask0= parameter in the "/goform/net\_Web\_get_value" uri to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14434|2024-09-16T22:45:13.801Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-8717|2024-09-16T17:09:11.126Z -- talos -- moxa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-8717</link>
      <description>An exploitable Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability exists in the Moxa AWK-3131A Wireless Access Point running firmware 1.1. The device operating system contains an undocumented, privileged (root) account with hard-coded credentials, giving attackers full control of affected devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-8717|2024-09-16T17:09:11.126Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-8390|2024-09-16T18:19:03.280Z -- talos -- hopper
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-8390</link>
      <description>An exploitable out of bounds write vulnerability exists in the parsing of ELF Section Headers of Hopper Disassembler 3.11.20. A specially crafted ELF file can cause attacker controlled pointer arithmetic resulting in a partially controlled out of bounds write. An attacker can craft an ELF file with specific section headers to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-8390|2024-09-16T18:19:03.280Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12128|2024-09-16T20:59:00.866Z -- talos -- moxa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12128</link>
      <description>An exploitable information disclosure vulnerability exists in the Server Agent functionality of Moxa EDR-810 V4.1 build 17030317. A specially crafted TCP packet can cause information disclosure. An attacker can send a crafted TCP packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12128|2024-09-16T20:59:00.866Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3952|2024-09-16T17:28:50.687Z -- talos -- nordvpn
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3952</link>
      <description>An exploitable code execution vulnerability exists in the connect functionality of NordVPN 6.14.28.0. A specially crafted configuration file can cause a privilege escalation, resulting in the execution of arbitrary commands with system privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3952|2024-09-16T17:28:50.687Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3888|2024-09-16T17:48:05.089Z -- talos -- computerinsel%20photoline
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3888</link>
      <description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the PCX-parsing functionality of Computerinsel Photoline 20.53. A specially crafted PCX image processed via the application can lead to an out-of-bounds write, overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker can deliver a PCX image to trigger this vulnerability and gain code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3888|2024-09-16T17:48:05.089Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2871|2024-09-16T20:47:04.590Z -- talos -- foscam
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2871</link>
      <description>Insufficient security checks exist in the recovery procedure used by the Foscam C1 Indoor HD Camera running application firmware 2.52.2.43. An attacker who is in the same subnetwork of the camera or has remote administrator access can fully compromise the device by performing a firmware recovery using a custom image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2871|2024-09-16T20:47:04.590Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5015|2024-09-16T19:04:24.135Z -- talos -- pixar%20renderman
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5015</link>
      <description>A local privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the Mac OS X version of Pixar Renderman 22.3.0's Install Helper helper tool. A user with local access can use this vulnerability to escalate their privileges to root. An attacker would need local access to the machine for a successful exploit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5015|2024-09-16T19:04:24.135Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3862|2024-09-16T21:07:49.129Z -- talos -- computerinsel%20photoline
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3862</link>
      <description>A specially crafted TIFF image processed via the application can lead to an out-of-bounds write, overwriting</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3862|2024-09-16T21:07:49.129Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3887|2024-09-16T17:58:29.770Z -- talos -- computerinsel%20photoline
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3887</link>
      <description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the PCX-parsing functionality of Computerinsel Photoline 20.53. A specially crafted PCX image processed via the application can lead to an out-of-bounds write, overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker can deliver a PCX image to trigger this vulnerability and gain code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3887|2024-09-16T17:58:29.770Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14472|2024-09-16T16:12:37.038Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14472</link>
      <description>An exploitable access control vulnerability exists in the data, program, and function file permissions functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a read or write operation resulting in disclosure of sensitive information, modification of settings, or modification of ladder logic. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability. Required Keyswitch State: Any Description: Requests a specific set of bytes from an undocumented data file and returns the ASCII version of the master password.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14472|2024-09-16T16:12:37.038Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12120|2024-09-16T16:33:59.260Z -- talos -- moxa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12120</link>
      <description>An exploitable command injection vulnerability exists in the web server functionality of Moxa EDR-810 V4.1 build 17030317. A specially crafted HTTP POST can cause a privilege escalation, resulting in a root shell. An attacker can inject OS commands into the ip= parm in the "/goform/net_WebPingGetValue" URI to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12120|2024-09-16T16:33:59.260Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3889|2024-09-16T17:28:04.613Z -- talos -- computerinsel%20photoline
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3889</link>
      <description>A specially crafted PCX image processed via the application can lead to an out-of-bounds write, overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker can deliver a PCX image to trigger this vulnerability and gain code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3889|2024-09-16T17:28:04.613Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2888|2024-09-16T20:17:03.901Z -- talos -- simple%20direct%20media
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2888</link>
      <description>An exploitable integer overflow vulnerability exists when creating a new RGB Surface in SDL 2.0.5. A specially crafted file can cause an integer overflow resulting in too little memory being allocated which can lead to a buffer overflow and potential code execution. An attacker can provide a specially crafted image file to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2888|2024-09-16T20:17:03.901Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14479|2024-09-16T16:48:49.870Z -- talos -- mysql%20mmm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14479</link>
      <description>In the MMM::Agent::Helpers::Network::clear_ip function in MySQL Multi-Master Replication Manager (MMM) mmm_agentd 2.2.1 (for Solaris), a specially crafted MMM protocol message can cause a shell command injection resulting in arbitrary command execution with the privileges of the mmm\_agentd process. An attacker that can initiate a TCP session with mmm\_agentd can trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14479|2024-09-16T16:48:49.870Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3938|2024-09-16T18:08:43.570Z -- talos -- sony
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3938</link>
      <description>An exploitable stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the 802dot1xclientcert.cgi functionality of Sony IPELA E Series Camera G5 firmware 1.87.00. A specially crafted POST can cause a stack-based buffer overflow, resulting in remote code execution. An attacker can send a malicious POST request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3938|2024-09-16T18:08:43.570Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3852|2024-09-16T18:04:21.639Z -- talos -- ocularis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3852</link>
      <description>An exploitable denial of service vulnerability exists in the Ocularis Recorder functionality of Ocularis 5.5.0.242. A specially crafted TCP packet can cause a process to terminate resulting in denial of service. An attacker can send a crafted TCP packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3852|2024-09-16T18:04:21.639Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12088|2024-09-16T17:54:26.277Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12088</link>
      <description>An exploitable denial of service vulnerability exists in the Ethernet functionality of the Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and below. A specially crafted packet can cause a device power cycle resulting in a fault state and deletion of ladder logic. An attacker can send one unauthenticated packet to trigger this vulnerability</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12088|2024-09-16T17:54:26.277Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12115|2024-09-16T16:58:17.274Z -- talos -- cpp-ethereum
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12115</link>
      <description>An exploitable improper authorization vulnerability exists in miner_setEtherbase API of cpp-ethereum's JSON-RPC (commit 4e1015743b95821849d001618a7ce82c7c073768). A JSON request can cause an access to the restricted functionality resulting in authorization bypass.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12115|2024-09-16T16:58:17.274Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2860|2024-09-16T18:13:06.563Z -- talos -- natus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2860</link>
      <description>An exploitable denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the lookup entry functionality of KeyTrees in Natus Xltek NeuroWorks 8. A specially crafted network packet can cause an out-of-bounds read, resulting in a denial of service. An attacker can send a malicious packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2860|2024-09-16T18:13:06.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14471|2024-09-16T16:48:44.116Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14471</link>
      <description>An exploitable access control vulnerability exists in the data, program, and function file permissions functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a read or write operation resulting in disclosure of sensitive information, modification of settings, or modification of ladder logic. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability. Required Keyswitch State: REMOTE or PROG Associated Fault Codes: 0023, 002e, and 0037 Fault Type: Recoverable Description: The STI, EII, and HSC function files contain bits signifying whether or not a fault has occurred. Additionally there is a bit signaling the module to auto start. When these bits are set for any of the three modules and the device is moved into a run state, a fault is triggered.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14471|2024-09-16T16:48:44.116Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12118|2024-09-16T20:47:22.337Z -- talos -- cpp-ethereum
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12118</link>
      <description>An exploitable improper authorization vulnerability exists in miner_stop API of cpp-ethereum's JSON-RPC (commit 4e1015743b95821849d001618a7ce82c7c073768). An attacker can send JSON to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12118|2024-09-16T20:47:22.337Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14473|2024-09-16T17:42:37.052Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14473</link>
      <description>An exploitable access control vulnerability exists in the data, program, and function file permissions functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a read or write operation resulting in disclosure of sensitive information, modification of settings, or modification of ladder logic. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability. Required Keyswitch State: Any Description: Reads the encoded ladder logic from its data file and print it out in HEX.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14473|2024-09-16T17:42:37.052Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4010|2024-09-16T17:54:36.228Z -- talos -- protonvpn
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4010</link>
      <description>An exploitable code execution vulnerability exists in the connect functionality of ProtonVPN VPN client 1.5.1. A specially crafted configuration file can cause a privilege escalation, resulting in the ability to execute arbitrary commands with the system's privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4010|2024-09-16T17:54:36.228Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12121|2024-09-16T18:13:49.032Z -- talos -- moxa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12121</link>
      <description>An exploitable command injection vulnerability exists in the web server functionality of Moxa EDR-810 V4.1 build 17030317. A specially crafted HTTP POST can cause a privilege escalation resulting in root shell. An attacker can inject OS commands into the rsakey\_name= parm in the "/goform/WebRSAKEYGen" uri to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12121|2024-09-16T18:13:49.032Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3973|2024-09-16T22:14:14.200Z -- talos -- acd%20systems
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3973</link>
      <description>An exploitable out of bounds write exists in the CAL parsing functionality of Canvas Draw version 5.0.0. A specially crafted CAL image processed via the application can lead to an out of bounds write overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker can deliver a PCX image to trigger this vulnerability and gain code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3973|2024-09-16T22:14:14.200Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12125|2024-09-16T19:00:52.724Z -- talos -- moxa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12125</link>
      <description>An exploitable command injection vulnerability exists in the web server functionality of Moxa EDR-810 V4.1 build 17030317. A specially crafted HTTP POST can cause a privilege escalation resulting in root shell. An attacker can inject OS commands into the CN= parm in the "/goform/net_WebCSRGen" uri to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12125|2024-09-16T19:00:52.724Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14437|2024-09-16T22:45:06.262Z -- talos -- moxa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14437</link>
      <description>An exploitable denial of service vulnerability exists in the web server functionality of Moxa EDR-810 V4.1 build 17030317. A specially crafted HTTP URI can cause a null pointer dereference resulting in denial of service. An attacker can send a GET request to "/MOXA\_LOG.ini" without a cookie header to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14437|2024-09-16T22:45:06.262Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14432|2024-09-16T17:54:38.060Z -- talos -- moxa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14432</link>
      <description>An exploitable command injection vulnerability exists in the web server functionality of Moxa EDR-810 V4.1 build 17030317. A specially crafted HTTP POST can cause a privilege escalation resulting in root shell. An attacker can inject OS commands into the openvpnServer0_tmp= parameter in the "/goform/net\_Web\_get_value" uri to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14432|2024-09-16T17:54:38.060Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3937|2024-09-16T16:13:19.122Z -- talos -- sony
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3937</link>
      <description>An exploitable command injection vulnerability exists in the measurementBitrateExec functionality of Sony IPELA E Series Network Camera G5 firmware 1.87.00. A specially crafted GET request can cause arbitrary commands to be executed. An attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3937|2024-09-16T16:13:19.122Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4039|2024-09-16T19:19:06.200Z -- talos -- atlantis%20word%20processor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4039</link>
      <description>An exploitable out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in the PNG implementation of Atlantis Word Processor, version 3.2.7.2. This can allow an attacker to corrupt memory, which can result in code execution under the context of the application. An attacker must convince a victim to open a specially crafted document in order to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4039|2024-09-16T19:19:06.200Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12123|2024-09-16T22:35:55.803Z -- talos -- moxa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12123</link>
      <description>An exploitable clear text transmission of password vulnerability exists in the web server and telnet functionality of Moxa EDR-810 V4.1 build 17030317. An attacker can look at network traffic to get the admin password for the device. The attacker can then use the credentials to login as admin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12123|2024-09-16T22:35:55.803Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3861|2024-09-16T18:38:42.623Z -- talos -- computerinsel%20photoline
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3861</link>
      <description>A specially crafted TIFF image processed via the application can lead to an out-of-bounds write, overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker can deliver a TIFF image to trigger this vulnerability and gain code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3861|2024-09-16T18:38:42.623Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3850|2024-09-16T22:51:28.628Z -- talos -- foxit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3850</link>
      <description>An exploitable use-after-free vulnerability exists in the JavaScript engine Foxit Software Foxit PDF Reader version 9.0.1.1049. A specially crafted PDF document can trigger a previously freed object in memory to be reused, resulting in arbitrary code execution. An attacker needs to trick the user to open the malicious file to trigger this vulnerability. If a browser plugin extension is enabled, visiting a malicious site can also trigger the vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3850|2024-09-16T22:51:28.628Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14458|2024-09-16T23:00:32.687Z -- talos -- foxit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14458</link>
      <description>An exploitable use-after-free vulnerability exists in the JavaScript engine of Foxit Software's Foxit PDF Reader version 8.3.2.25013. A specially crafted PDF document can trigger a previously freed object in memory to be reused, resulting in arbitrary code execution. An attacker needs to trick the user to open the malicious file to trigger this vulnerability. If the browser plugin extension is enabled, visiting a malicious site can also trigger the vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14458|2024-09-16T23:00:32.687Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12093|2024-09-16T18:45:15.530Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12093</link>
      <description>An exploitable insufficient resource pool vulnerability exists in the session communication functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B Firmware 21.2 and before. A specially crafted stream of packets can cause a flood of the session resource pool resulting in legitimate connections to the PLC being disconnected. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12093|2024-09-16T18:45:15.530Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14447|2024-09-16T17:28:01.654Z -- talos -- insteon
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14447</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the PubNub message handler for the 'ad' channel of Insteon Hub running firmware version 1012. Specially crafted commands sent through the PubNub service can cause a stack-based buffer overflow overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker should send an authenticated HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14447|2024-09-16T17:28:01.654Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14435|2024-09-16T17:38:22.584Z -- talos -- moxa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14435</link>
      <description>An exploitable denial of service vulnerability exists in the web server functionality of Moxa EDR-810 V4.1 build 17030317. A specially crafted HTTP URI can cause a null pointer dereference resulting in denial of service. An attacker can send a GET request to "/MOXA\_CFG.ini" without a cookie header to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14435|2024-09-16T17:38:22.584Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3835|2024-09-16T16:42:37.311Z -- talos -- walt%20disney%20animation%20studios%20ptex
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3835</link>
      <description>An exploitable out of bounds write vulnerability exists in version 2.2 of the Per Face Texture mapping application known as PTEX. The vulnerability is present in the reading of a file without proper parameter checking. The value read in, is not verified to be valid and its use can lead to a buffer overflow, potentially resulting in code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3835|2024-09-16T16:42:37.311Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14464|2024-09-16T21:57:12.189Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14464</link>
      <description>An exploitable access control vulnerability exists in the data, program, and function file permissions functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a read or write operation resulting in disclosure of sensitive information, modification of settings, or modification of ladder logic. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability.Required Keyswitch State: REMOTE or PROG Associated Fault Code: 0001 Fault Type: Non-User Description: A fault state can be triggered by setting the NVRAM/memory module user program mismatch bit (S2:9) when a memory module is NOT installed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14464|2024-09-16T21:57:12.189Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12090|2024-09-16T22:14:12.132Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12090</link>
      <description>An exploitable denial of service vulnerability exists in the processing of snmp-set commands of the Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and below. A specially crafted snmp-set request, when sent without associated firmware flashing snmp-set commands, can cause a device power cycle resulting in downtime for the device. An attacker can send one packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12090|2024-09-16T22:14:12.132Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14467|2024-09-16T18:44:20.457Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14467</link>
      <description>An exploitable access control vulnerability exists in the data, program, and function file permissions functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a read or write operation resulting in disclosure of sensitive information, modification of settings, or modification of ladder logic. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability. Required Keyswitch State: REMOTE Description: Live rung edits are able to be made by an unauthenticated user allowing for addition, deletion, or modification of existing ladder logic. Additionally, faults and cpu state modification can be triggered if specific ladder logic is used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14467|2024-09-16T18:44:20.457Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
