<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Talos -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/talos/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Talos -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 05:23:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2880|2024-09-17T02:57:13.420Z -- talos -- computerinsel%20photoline
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2880</link>
      <description>An memory corruption vulnerability exists in the .GIF parsing functionality of Computerinsel Photoline 20.02. A specially crafted .GIF file can cause a vulnerability resulting in potential code execution. An attacker can send specific .GIF file to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2880|2024-09-17T02:57:13.420Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14438|2024-09-17T02:02:46.784Z -- talos -- moxa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14438</link>
      <description>Exploitable denial of service vulnerabilities exists in the Service Agent functionality of Moxa EDR-810 V4.1 build 17030317. A specially crafted packet can cause a denial of service. An attacker can send a large packet to 4000/tcp to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14438|2024-09-17T02:02:46.784Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3842|2024-09-17T00:06:32.085Z -- talos -- foxit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3842</link>
      <description>An exploitable use of an uninitialized pointer vulnerability exists in the JavaScript engine in Foxit PDF Reader version 9.0.1.1049. A specially crafted PDF document can lead to a dereference of an uninitialized pointer which, if under attacker control, can result in arbitrary code execution. An attacker needs to trick the user to open a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability. If the browser plugin extension is enabled, visiting a malicious site can also trigger the vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3842|2024-09-17T00:06:32.085Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12127|2024-09-17T02:21:40.475Z -- talos -- moxa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12127</link>
      <description>A password storage vulnerability exists in the operating system functionality of Moxa EDR-810 V4.1 build 17030317. An attacker with shell access could extract passwords in clear text from the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12127|2024-09-17T02:21:40.475Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2852|2024-09-17T02:31:31.833Z -- talos -- natus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2852</link>
      <description>An exploitable denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the unserialization of lists functionality of Natus Xltek NeuroWorks 8. A specially crafted network packet can cause an out-of-bounds read, resulting in a denial of service. An attacker can send a malicious packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2852|2024-09-17T02:31:31.833Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12116|2024-09-17T01:56:02.137Z -- talos -- cpp-ethereum
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12116</link>
      <description>An exploitable improper authorization vulnerability exists in miner_setGasPrice API of cpp-ethereum's JSON-RPC (commit 4e1015743b95821849d001618a7ce82c7c073768). A JSON request can cause an access to the restricted functionality resulting in authorization bypass. An attacker can send JSON to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12116|2024-09-17T01:56:02.137Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4055|2024-09-17T00:37:04.203Z -- talos -- pixar%20renderman
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4055</link>
      <description>A local privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the install helper tool of the Mac OS X version of Pixar Renderman, version 22.2.0. A user with local access can use this vulnerability to read any root file from the file system. An attacker would need local access to the machine to successfully exploit this flaw.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4055|2024-09-17T00:37:04.203Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3980|2024-09-17T01:25:44.448Z -- talos -- acd%20systems
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3980</link>
      <description>An exploitable out-of-bounds write exists in the TIFF-parsing functionality of Canvas Draw version 5.0.0. A specially crafted TIFF image processed via the application can lead to an out-of-bounds write, overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker can deliver a TIFF image to trigger this vulnerability and gain code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3980|2024-09-17T01:25:44.448Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4040|2024-09-17T00:36:10.536Z -- talos -- atlantis%20word%20processor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4040</link>
      <description>An exploitable uninitialized pointer vulnerability exists in the rich text format parser of Atlantis Word Processor, version 3.2.7.2. A specially crafted document can cause certain RTF tokens to dereference a pointer that has been uninitialized and then write to it. An attacker must convince a victim to open a specially crafted document in order to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4040|2024-09-17T00:36:10.536Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2826|2024-09-17T00:15:28.741Z -- talos -- zabbix
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2826</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability exists in the iConfig proxy request of Zabbix server 2.4.X. A specially crafted iConfig proxy request can cause the Zabbix server to send the configuration information of any Zabbix proxy, resulting in information disclosure. An attacker can make requests from an active Zabbix proxy to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2826|2024-09-17T00:15:28.741Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12117|2024-09-17T03:52:34.712Z -- talos -- cpp-ethereum
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12117</link>
      <description>An exploitable improper authorization vulnerability exists in miner_start API of cpp-ethereum's JSON-RPC (commit 4e1015743b95821849d001618a7ce82c7c073768). A JSON request can cause an access to the restricted functionality resulting in authorization bypass. An attacker can send JSON to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12117|2024-09-17T03:52:34.712Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3868|2024-09-17T04:25:00.865Z -- talos -- computerinsel%20photoline
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3868</link>
      <description>A specially crafted TIFF image processed via the application can lead to an out-of-bounds write, overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker can deliver a TIFF image to trigger this vulnerability and gain code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3868|2024-09-17T04:25:00.865Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3849|2024-09-17T01:32:06.589Z -- talos -- nasa%20cfitsio
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3849</link>
      <description>In the ffghtb function in NASA CFITSIO 3.42, specially crafted images parsed via the library can cause a stack-based buffer overflow overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker can deliver an FIT image to trigger this vulnerability and potentially gain code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3849|2024-09-17T01:32:06.589Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14478|2024-09-17T03:48:02.494Z -- talos -- mysql%20mmm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14478</link>
      <description>In the MMM::Agent::Helpers::Network::clear_ip function in MySQL Multi-Master Replication Manager (MMM) mmm_agentd 2.2.1 (for Linux), a specially crafted MMM protocol message can cause a shell command injection resulting in arbitrary command execution with the privileges of the mmm\_agentd process. An attacker that can initiate a TCP session with mmm\_agentd can trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14478|2024-09-17T03:48:02.494Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14457|2024-09-17T00:05:51.191Z -- talos -- cpp-ethereum
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14457</link>
      <description>An exploitable information leak/denial of service vulnerability exists in the libevm (Ethereum Virtual Machine) `create2` opcode handler of CPP-Ethereum. A specially crafted smart contract code can cause an out-of-bounds read leading to memory disclosure or denial of service. An attacker can create/send malicious a smart contract to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14457|2024-09-17T00:05:51.191Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3853|2024-09-17T02:57:04.382Z -- talos -- foxit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3853</link>
      <description>An exploitable use-after-free vulnerability exists in the JavaScript engine of Foxit Software Foxit PDF Reader version 9.0.1.1049. A specially crafted PDF document can trigger a previously freed object in memory to be reused resulting in arbitrary code execution. An attacker needs to trick the user to open the malicious file to trigger this vulnerability. If the browser plugin extension is enabled, visiting a malicious site can also trigger the vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3853|2024-09-17T02:57:04.382Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14470|2024-09-17T01:06:52.162Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14470</link>
      <description>An exploitable access control vulnerability exists in the data, program, and function file permissions functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a read or write operation resulting in disclosure of sensitive information, modification of settings, or modification of ladder logic. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability. Required Keyswitch State: REMOTE or PROG or RUN Description: The value 0xffffffff is considered NaN for the Float data type. When a float is set to this value and used in the PLC, a fault is triggered. NOTE: This is not possible through RSLogix.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14470|2024-09-17T01:06:52.162Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14476|2024-09-17T02:02:35.827Z -- talos -- mysql%20mmm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14476</link>
      <description>In the MMM::Agent::Helpers::Network::add_ip function in MySQL Multi-Master Replication Manager (MMM) mmm_agentd 2.2.1 (for Solaris), a specially crafted MMM protocol message can cause a shell command injection resulting in arbitrary command execution with the privileges of the mmm\_agentd process. An attacker that can initiate a TCP session with mmm\_agentd can trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14476|2024-09-17T02:02:35.827Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14439|2024-09-17T00:15:38.598Z -- talos -- moxa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14439</link>
      <description>Exploitable denial of service vulnerabilities exists in the Service Agent functionality of Moxa EDR-810 V4.1 build 17030317. A specially crafted packet can cause a denial of service. An attacker can send a large packet to 4001/tcp to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14439|2024-09-17T00:15:38.598Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3909|2024-09-17T02:10:41.755Z -- talos -- samsung
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3909</link>
      <description>An exploitable vulnerability exists in the REST parser of video-core's HTTP server of the Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 - Firmware version 0.20.17. The video-core process incorrectly handles pipelined HTTP requests, which allows successive requests to overwrite the previously parsed HTTP method, 'onmessagecomplete' callback. An attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3909|2024-09-17T02:10:41.755Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14463|2024-09-17T02:32:56.277Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14463</link>
      <description>An exploitable access control vulnerability exists in the data, program, and function file permissions functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a read or write operation resulting in disclosure of sensitive information, modification of settings, or modification of ladder logic. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability. Required Keyswitch State: REMOTE or PROG Associated Fault Code: 0012 Fault Type: Non-User Description: A fault state can be triggered by overwriting the ladder logic data file (type 0x22 number 0x02) with null values.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14463|2024-09-17T02:32:56.277Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3846|2024-09-17T02:21:57.506Z -- talos -- nasa%20cfitsio
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3846</link>
      <description>In the ffgphd and ffgtkn functions in NASA CFITSIO 3.42, specially crafted images parsed via the library can cause a stack-based buffer overflow overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker can deliver an FIT image to trigger this vulnerability and potentially gain code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3846|2024-09-17T02:21:57.506Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14468|2024-09-17T01:55:44.052Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14468</link>
      <description>An exploitable access control vulnerability exists in the data, program, and function file permissions functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a read or write operation resulting in disclosure of sensitive information, modification of settings, or modification of ladder logic. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability. Required Keyswitch State: REMOTE or PROG Description: This ability is leveraged in a larger exploit to flash custom firmware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14468|2024-09-17T01:55:44.052Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3848|2024-09-17T01:17:05.927Z -- talos -- nasa%20cfitsio
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3848</link>
      <description>In the ffghbn function in NASA CFITSIO 3.42, specially crafted images parsed via the library can cause a stack-based buffer overflow overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker can deliver an FIT image to trigger this vulnerability and potentially gain code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3848|2024-09-17T01:17:05.927Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4056|2024-09-17T00:05:30.162Z -- talos -- coturn
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4056</link>
      <description>An exploitable SQL injection vulnerability exists in the administrator web portal function of coTURN prior to version 4.5.0.9. A login message with a specially crafted username can cause an SQL injection, resulting in authentication bypass, which could give access to the TURN server administrator web portal. An attacker can log in via the external interface of the TURN server to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4056|2024-09-17T00:05:30.162Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14481|2024-09-17T01:46:03.102Z -- talos -- mysql%20mmm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14481</link>
      <description>In the MMM::Agent::Helpers::Network::send_arp function in MySQL Multi-Master Replication Manager (MMM) mmm_agentd 2.2.1 (for Solaris), a specially crafted MMM protocol message can cause a shell command injection resulting in arbitrary command execution with the privileges of the mmm\_agentd process. An attacker that can initiate a TCP session with mmm\_agentd can trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14481|2024-09-17T01:46:03.102Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3970|2024-09-17T00:50:30.503Z -- talos -- sophos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3970</link>
      <description>An exploitable memory disclosure vulnerability exists in the 0x222000 IOCTL handler functionality of Sophos HitmanPro.Alert 3.7.6.744. A specially crafted IRP request can cause the driver to return uninitialized memory, resulting in kernel memory disclosure. An attacker can send an IRP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3970|2024-09-17T00:50:30.503Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3949|2024-09-17T01:01:34.084Z -- talos -- tp-link
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3949</link>
      <description>An exploitable information disclosure vulnerability exists in the HTTP server functionality of the TP-Link TL-R600VPN. A specially crafted URL can cause a directory traversal, resulting in the disclosure of sensitive system files. An attacker can send either an unauthenticated or an authenticated web request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3949|2024-09-17T01:01:34.084Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12119|2024-09-17T03:53:37.460Z -- talos -- cpp-ethereum
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12119</link>
      <description>An exploitable unhandled exception vulnerability exists in multiple APIs of CPP-Ethereum JSON-RPC. Specially crafted JSON requests can cause an unhandled exception resulting in denial of service. An attacker can send malicious JSON to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12119|2024-09-17T03:53:37.460Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14433|2024-09-17T00:21:20.859Z -- talos -- moxa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14433</link>
      <description>An exploitable command injection vulnerability exists in the web server functionality of Moxa EDR-810 V4.1 build 17030317. A specially crafted HTTP POST can cause a privilege escalation resulting in root shell. An attacker can inject OS commands into the remoteNetwork0= parameter in the "/goform/net\_Web\_get_value" uri to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14433|2024-09-17T00:21:20.859Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12089|2024-09-17T00:56:21.961Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12089</link>
      <description>An exploitable denial of service vulnerability exists in the program download functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a device fault resulting in halted operations. An attacker can send an unauthenticated packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12089|2024-09-17T00:56:21.961Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14477|2024-09-17T04:09:17.916Z -- talos -- mysql%20mmm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14477</link>
      <description>In the MMM::Agent::Helpers::Network::add_ip function in MySQL Multi-Master Replication Manager (MMM) mmm_agentd 2.2.1 (for FreeBSD), a specially crafted MMM protocol message can cause a shell command injection resulting in arbitrary command execution with the privileges of the mmm\_agentd process. An attacker that can initiate a TCP session with mmm\_agentd can trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14477|2024-09-17T04:09:17.916Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3926|2024-09-17T00:46:06.691Z -- talos -- samsung
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3926</link>
      <description>An exploitable integer underflow vulnerability exists in the ZigBee firmware update routine of the hubCore binary of the Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 - Firmware version 0.20.17. The hubCore process incorrectly handles malformed files existing in its data directory, leading to an infinite loop, which eventually causes the process to crash. An attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3926|2024-09-17T00:46:06.691Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12114|2024-09-17T00:36:20.233Z -- talos -- cpp-ethereum
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12114</link>
      <description>An exploitable improper authorization vulnerability exists in admin_peers API of cpp-ethereum's JSON-RPC (commit 4e1015743b95821849d001618a7ce82c7c073768). A JSON request can cause an access to the restricted functionality resulting in authorization bypass. An attacker can send JSON to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12114|2024-09-17T00:36:20.233Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3883|2024-09-17T03:43:30.337Z -- talos -- erpnext
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3883</link>
      <description>An exploitable SQL injection vulnerability exists in the authenticated part of ERPNext v10.1.6. Specially crafted web requests can cause SQL injections resulting in data compromise. The employee and sort_order parameter can be used to perform an SQL injection attack. An attacker can use a browser to trigger these vulnerabilities, and no special tools are required.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3883|2024-09-17T03:43:30.337Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3951|2024-09-17T01:35:33.109Z -- talos -- tp-link
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3951</link>
      <description>An exploitable remote code execution vulnerability exists in the HTTP header-parsing function of the TP-Link TL-R600VPN HTTP Server. A specially crafted HTTP request can cause a buffer overflow, resulting in remote code execution on the device. An attacker can send an authenticated HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3951|2024-09-17T01:35:33.109Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3843|2024-09-17T00:20:46.489Z -- talos -- foxit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3843</link>
      <description>An exploitable type confusion vulnerability exists in the way Foxit PDF Reader version 9.0.1.1049 parses files with associated file annotations. A specially crafted PDF document can lead to an object of invalid type to be dereferenced, which can potentially lead to sensitive memory disclosure, and possibly to arbitrary code execution. An attacker needs to trick the user into opening the malicious file to trigger this vulnerability. If the browser plugin extension is enabled, visiting a malicious site can also trigger the vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3843|2024-09-17T00:20:46.489Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14466|2024-09-17T03:59:42.744Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14466</link>
      <description>An exploitable access control vulnerability exists in the data, program, and function file permissions functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a read or write operation resulting in disclosure of sensitive information, modification of settings, or modification of ladder logic. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability. Required Keyswitch State: REMOTE or PROG Description: The filetype 0x03 allows users write access, allowing the ability to overwrite the Master Password value stored in the file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14466|2024-09-17T03:59:42.744Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3976|2024-09-17T00:56:15.077Z -- talos -- acd%20systems
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3976</link>
      <description>An exploitable out-of-bounds write exists in the CALS Raster file format-parsing functionality of Canvas Draw version 5.0.0.28. A specially crafted CAL image processed via the application can lead to an out-of-bounds write, overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker can deliver a CAL image to trigger this vulnerability and gain code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3976|2024-09-17T00:56:15.077Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12124|2024-09-17T03:52:49.594Z -- talos -- moxa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12124</link>
      <description>An exploitable denial of service vulnerability exists in the web server functionality of Moxa EDR-810 V4.1 build 17030317. A specially crafted HTTP URI can cause a null pointer dereference resulting in the web server crashing. An attacker can send a crafted URI to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12124|2024-09-17T03:52:49.594Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3981|2024-09-17T00:50:44.146Z -- talos -- acd%20systems
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3981</link>
      <description>An exploitable out-of-bounds write exists in the TIFF-parsing functionality of Canvas Draw version 5.0.0. An attacker can deliver a TIFF image to trigger this vulnerability and gain code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3981|2024-09-17T00:50:44.146Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16252|2024-09-17T03:43:03.723Z -- talos -- insteon
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16252</link>
      <description>Specially crafted commands sent through the PubNub service in Insteon Hub 2245-222 with firmware version 1012 can cause a stack-based buffer overflow overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker should send an authenticated HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.At 0x9d014cc0 the value for the cmd key is copied using strcpy to the buffer at $sp+0x11c. This buffer is 20 bytes large, sending anything longer will cause a buffer overflow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16252|2024-09-17T03:43:03.723Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14436|2024-09-17T02:06:23.852Z -- talos -- moxa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14436</link>
      <description>An exploitable denial of service vulnerability exists in the web server functionality of Moxa EDR-810 V4.1 build 17030317. A specially crafted HTTP URI can cause a null pointer dereference resulting in denial of service. An attacker can send a GET request to "/MOXA\_CFG2.ini" without a cookie header to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14436|2024-09-17T02:06:23.852Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3950|2024-09-17T04:09:57.222Z -- talos -- tp-link
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3950</link>
      <description>An exploitable remote code execution vulnerability exists in the ping and tracert functionality of the TP-Link TL-R600VPN HWv3 FRNv1.3.0 and HWv2 FRNv1.2.3 http server. A specially crafted IP address can cause a stack overflow, resulting in remote code execution. An attacker can send a single authenticated HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3950|2024-09-17T04:09:57.222Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3903|2024-09-17T01:02:01.708Z -- talos -- samsung
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3903</link>
      <description>On Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 devices with firmware version 0.20.17, the video-core process incorrectly extracts fields from a user-controlled JSON payload, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. An attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability. The memcpy call overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 512 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "url" value in order to overwrite the saved-PC with 0x42424242.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3903|2024-09-17T01:02:01.708Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-9042|2024-09-17T03:53:51.612Z -- talos -- network%20time%20protocol
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-9042</link>
      <description>An exploitable denial of service vulnerability exists in the origin timestamp check functionality of ntpd 4.2.8p9. A specially crafted unauthenticated network packet can be used to reset the expected origin timestamp for target peers. Legitimate replies from targeted peers will fail the origin timestamp check (TEST2) causing the reply to be dropped and creating a denial of service condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-9042|2024-09-17T03:53:51.612Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14460|2024-09-17T02:11:42.400Z -- talos -- parity
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14460</link>
      <description>An exploitable overly permissive cross-domain (CORS) whitelist vulnerability exists in JSON-RPC of Parity Ethereum client version 1.7.8. An automatically sent JSON object to JSON-RPC endpoint can trigger this vulnerability. A victim needs to visit a malicious website to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14460|2024-09-17T02:11:42.400Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3971|2024-09-17T02:27:34.114Z -- talos -- sophos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3971</link>
      <description>An exploitable arbitrary write vulnerability exists in the 0x2222CC IOCTL handler functionality of Sophos HitmanPro.Alert 3.7.6.744. A specially crafted IRP request can cause the driver to write data under controlled by an attacker address, resulting in memory corruption. An attacker can send IRP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3971|2024-09-17T02:27:34.114Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12129|2024-09-17T02:47:55.223Z -- talos -- moxa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12129</link>
      <description>An exploitable Weak Cryptography for Passwords vulnerability exists in the web server functionality of Moxa EDR-810 V4.1 build 17030317. An attacker could intercept weakly encrypted passwords and could brute force them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12129|2024-09-17T02:47:55.223Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2920|2024-09-17T01:40:55.531Z -- talos -- computerinsel%20photoline
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2920</link>
      <description>An memory corruption vulnerability exists in the .SVG parsing functionality of Computerinsel Photoline 20.02. A specially crafted .SVG file can cause a vulnerability resulting in memory corruption, which can potentially lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can send a specific .SVG file to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2920|2024-09-17T01:40:55.531Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2887|2024-09-17T02:57:14.504Z -- talos -- simple%20direct%20media
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2887</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the XCF property handling functionality of SDL_image 2.0.1. A specially crafted xcf file can cause a stack-based buffer overflow resulting in potential code execution. An attacker can provide a specially crafted XCF file to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2887|2024-09-17T02:57:14.504Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
