<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Talos -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/talos/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Talos -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 21:22:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5015|2024-08-04T19:40:49.177Z -- talos -- pixar%20renderman
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5015</link>
      <description>A local privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the Mac OS X version of Pixar Renderman 22.3.0's Install Helper helper tool. A user with local access can use this vulnerability to escalate their privileges to root. An attacker would need local access to the machine for a successful exploit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5015|2024-08-04T19:40:49.177Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5016|2024-08-04T19:40:48.991Z -- talos -- kcodes
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5016</link>
      <description>An exploitable arbitrary memory read vulnerability exists in the KCodes NetUSB.ko kernel module which enables the ReadySHARE Printer functionality of at least two NETGEAR Nighthawk Routers and potentially several other vendors/products. A specially crafted index value can cause an invalid memory read, resulting in a denial of service or remote information disclosure. An unauthenticated attacker can send a crafted packet on the local network to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5016|2024-08-04T19:40:48.991Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 20:29:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5066|2024-08-04T19:47:56.635Z -- talos -- aspose
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5066</link>
      <description>An exploitable use-after-free vulnerability exists in the way LZW-compressed streams are processed in Aspose.PDF 19.2 for C++. A specially crafted PDF can cause a dangling heap pointer, resulting in a use-after-free condition. To trigger this vulnerability, a specifically crafted PDF document needs to be processed by the target application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5066|2024-08-04T19:47:56.635Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 20:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5067|2024-08-04T19:47:56.629Z -- talos -- aspose
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5067</link>
      <description>An uninitialized memory access vulnerability exists in the way Aspose.PDF 19.2 for C++ handles invalid parent object pointers. A specially crafted PDF can cause a read and write from uninitialized memory, resulting in memory corruption and possibly arbitrary code execution. To trigger this vulnerability, a specifically crafted PDF document needs to be processed by the target application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5067|2024-08-04T19:47:56.629Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 20:17:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5042|2024-08-04T19:47:55.846Z -- talos -- aspose.pdf%20for%20c%2B%2B
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5042</link>
      <description>An exploitable Use-After-Free vulnerability exists in the way FunctionType 0 PDF elements are processed in Aspose.PDF 19.2 for C++. A specially crafted PDF can cause a dangling heap pointer, resulting in a use-after-free. An attacker can send a malicious PDF to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5042|2024-08-04T19:47:55.846Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 20:41:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-5017|2024-08-04T19:40:49.264Z -- talos -- kcodes
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-5017</link>
      <description>An exploitable information disclosure vulnerability exists in the KCodes NetUSB.ko kernel module that enables the ReadySHARE Printer functionality of at least two NETGEAR Nighthawk Routers and potentially several other vendors/products. An unauthenticated, remote attacker can craft and send a packet containing an opcode that will trigger the kernel module to return several addresses. One of which can be used to calculate the dynamic base address of the module for further exploitation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-5017|2024-08-04T19:40:49.264Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 20:34:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
