<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Talos -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/talos/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Talos -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 21:23:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14465|2024-08-05T19:27:40.738Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14465</link>
      <description>An exploitable access control vulnerability exists in the data, program, and function file permissions functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a read or write operation resulting in disclosure of sensitive information, modification of settings, or modification of ladder logic. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability. Required Keyswitch State: REMOTE Description: Any input or output can be forced, causing unpredictable activity from the PLC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14465|2024-08-05T19:27:40.738Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12090|2024-08-05T18:28:16.302Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12090</link>
      <description>An exploitable denial of service vulnerability exists in the processing of snmp-set commands of the Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and below. A specially crafted snmp-set request, when sent without associated firmware flashing snmp-set commands, can cause a device power cycle resulting in downtime for the device. An attacker can send one packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12090|2024-08-05T18:28:16.302Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12123|2024-08-05T18:28:16.518Z -- talos -- moxa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12123</link>
      <description>An exploitable clear text transmission of password vulnerability exists in the web server and telnet functionality of Moxa EDR-810 V4.1 build 17030317. An attacker can look at network traffic to get the admin password for the device. The attacker can then use the credentials to login as admin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12123|2024-08-05T18:28:16.518Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2920|2024-08-05T14:09:17.776Z -- talos -- computerinsel%20photoline
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2920</link>
      <description>An memory corruption vulnerability exists in the .SVG parsing functionality of Computerinsel Photoline 20.02. A specially crafted .SVG file can cause a vulnerability resulting in memory corruption, which can potentially lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can send a specific .SVG file to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2920|2024-08-05T14:09:17.776Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3861|2024-08-05T04:57:24.267Z -- talos -- computerinsel%20photoline
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3861</link>
      <description>A specially crafted TIFF image processed via the application can lead to an out-of-bounds write, overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker can deliver a TIFF image to trigger this vulnerability and gain code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3861|2024-08-05T04:57:24.267Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3903|2024-08-05T04:57:24.494Z -- talos -- samsung
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3903</link>
      <description>On Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 devices with firmware version 0.20.17, the video-core process incorrectly extracts fields from a user-controlled JSON payload, leading to a buffer overflow on the stack. An attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability. The memcpy call overflows the destination buffer, which has a size of 512 bytes. An attacker can send an arbitrarily long "url" value in order to overwrite the saved-PC with 0x42424242.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3903|2024-08-05T04:57:24.494Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14434|2024-08-05T19:27:40.570Z -- talos -- moxa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14434</link>
      <description>An exploitable command injection vulnerability exists in the web server functionality of Moxa EDR-810 V4.1 build 17030317. A specially crafted HTTP POST can cause a privilege escalation resulting in root shell. An attacker can inject OS commands into the remoteNetmask0= parameter in the "/goform/net\_Web\_get_value" uri to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14434|2024-08-05T19:27:40.570Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12097|2024-08-05T18:28:16.375Z -- talos -- delayed_job_web%20rails%20gem
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12097</link>
      <description>An exploitable cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the filter functionality of the delayed_job_web rails gem version 1.4. A specially crafted URL can cause an XSS flaw resulting in an attacker being able to execute arbitrary javascript on the victim's browser. An attacker can phish an authenticated user to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12097|2024-08-05T18:28:16.375Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2826|2024-08-05T14:09:16.674Z -- talos -- zabbix
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2826</link>
      <description>An information disclosure vulnerability exists in the iConfig proxy request of Zabbix server 2.4.X. A specially crafted iConfig proxy request can cause the Zabbix server to send the configuration information of any Zabbix proxy, resulting in information disclosure. An attacker can make requests from an active Zabbix proxy to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2826|2024-08-05T14:09:16.674Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14471|2024-08-05T19:27:40.811Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14471</link>
      <description>An exploitable access control vulnerability exists in the data, program, and function file permissions functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a read or write operation resulting in disclosure of sensitive information, modification of settings, or modification of ladder logic. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability. Required Keyswitch State: REMOTE or PROG Associated Fault Codes: 0023, 002e, and 0037 Fault Type: Recoverable Description: The STI, EII, and HSC function files contain bits signifying whether or not a fault has occurred. Additionally there is a bit signaling the module to auto start. When these bits are set for any of the three modules and the device is moved into a run state, a fault is triggered.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14471|2024-08-05T19:27:40.811Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2860|2024-08-05T14:09:17.283Z -- talos -- natus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2860</link>
      <description>An exploitable denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the lookup entry functionality of KeyTrees in Natus Xltek NeuroWorks 8. A specially crafted network packet can cause an out-of-bounds read, resulting in a denial of service. An attacker can send a malicious packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2860|2024-08-05T14:09:17.283Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14480|2024-08-05T19:27:40.617Z -- talos -- mysql%20mmm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14480</link>
      <description>In the MMM::Agent::Helpers::Network::clear_ip function in MySQL Multi-Master Replication Manager (MMM) mmm_agentd 2.2.1 (for FreeBSD), a specially crafted MMM protocol message can cause a shell command injection resulting in arbitrary command execution with the privileges of the mmm\_agentd process. An attacker that can initiate a TCP session with mmm\_agentd can trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14480|2024-08-05T19:27:40.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14472|2024-08-05T19:27:40.687Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14472</link>
      <description>An exploitable access control vulnerability exists in the data, program, and function file permissions functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a read or write operation resulting in disclosure of sensitive information, modification of settings, or modification of ladder logic. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability. Required Keyswitch State: Any Description: Requests a specific set of bytes from an undocumented data file and returns the ASCII version of the master password.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14472|2024-08-05T19:27:40.687Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4054|2024-08-05T05:04:28.945Z -- talos -- pixar%20renderman
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4054</link>
      <description>A local privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the install helper tool of the Mac OS X version of Pixar Renderman, version 22.2.0. A user with local access can use this vulnerability to escalate their privileges to root. An attacker would need local access to the machine to successfully exploit this flaw.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4054|2024-08-05T05:04:28.945Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4040|2024-08-05T05:04:29.553Z -- talos -- atlantis%20word%20processor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4040</link>
      <description>An exploitable uninitialized pointer vulnerability exists in the rich text format parser of Atlantis Word Processor, version 3.2.7.2. A specially crafted document can cause certain RTF tokens to dereference a pointer that has been uninitialized and then write to it. An attacker must convince a victim to open a specially crafted document in order to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4040|2024-08-05T05:04:29.553Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14468|2024-08-05T19:27:40.638Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14468</link>
      <description>An exploitable access control vulnerability exists in the data, program, and function file permissions functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a read or write operation resulting in disclosure of sensitive information, modification of settings, or modification of ladder logic. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability. Required Keyswitch State: REMOTE or PROG Description: This ability is leveraged in a larger exploit to flash custom firmware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14468|2024-08-05T19:27:40.638Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14458|2024-08-05T19:27:40.561Z -- talos -- foxit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14458</link>
      <description>An exploitable use-after-free vulnerability exists in the JavaScript engine of Foxit Software's Foxit PDF Reader version 8.3.2.25013. A specially crafted PDF document can trigger a previously freed object in memory to be reused, resulting in arbitrary code execution. An attacker needs to trick the user to open the malicious file to trigger this vulnerability. If the browser plugin extension is enabled, visiting a malicious site can also trigger the vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14458|2024-08-05T19:27:40.561Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3886|2024-08-05T04:57:24.247Z -- talos -- computerinsel%20photoline
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3886</link>
      <description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the PCX-parsing functionality of Computerinsel Photoline 20.53. A specially crafted PCX image processed via the application can lead to an out-of-bounds write, overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker can deliver a PCX image to trigger this vulnerability and gain code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3886|2024-08-05T04:57:24.247Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2815|2024-08-05T14:02:07.787Z -- talos -- open%20fire%20user%20import%20export%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2815</link>
      <description>An exploitable XML entity injection vulnerability exists in OpenFire User Import Export Plugin 2.6.0. A specially crafted web request can cause the retrieval of arbitrary files or denial of service. An authenticated attacker can send a crafted web request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2815|2024-08-05T14:02:07.787Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12116|2024-08-05T18:28:16.344Z -- talos -- cpp-ethereum
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12116</link>
      <description>An exploitable improper authorization vulnerability exists in miner_setGasPrice API of cpp-ethereum's JSON-RPC (commit 4e1015743b95821849d001618a7ce82c7c073768). A JSON request can cause an access to the restricted functionality resulting in authorization bypass. An attacker can send JSON to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12116|2024-08-05T18:28:16.344Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12092|2024-08-05T18:28:16.293Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12092</link>
      <description>An exploitable file write vulnerability exists in the memory module functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a file write resulting in a new program being written to the memory module. An attacker can send an unauthenticated packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12092|2024-08-05T18:28:16.293Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3951|2024-08-05T04:57:24.708Z -- talos -- tp-link
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3951</link>
      <description>An exploitable remote code execution vulnerability exists in the HTTP header-parsing function of the TP-Link TL-R600VPN HTTP Server. A specially crafted HTTP request can cause a buffer overflow, resulting in remote code execution on the device. An attacker can send an authenticated HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3951|2024-08-05T04:57:24.708Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14474|2024-08-05T19:27:40.751Z -- talos -- mysql%20mmm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14474</link>
      <description>In the MMM::Agent::Helpers::_execute function in MySQL Multi-Master Replication Manager (MMM) mmm_agentd 2.2.1, a specially crafted MMM protocol message can cause a shell command injection resulting in arbitrary command execution with the privileges of the mmm\_agentd process. An attacker that can initiate a TCP session with mmm\_agentd can trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14474|2024-08-05T19:27:40.751Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3937|2024-08-05T04:57:24.472Z -- talos -- sony
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3937</link>
      <description>An exploitable command injection vulnerability exists in the measurementBitrateExec functionality of Sony IPELA E Series Network Camera G5 firmware 1.87.00. A specially crafted GET request can cause arbitrary commands to be executed. An attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3937|2024-08-05T04:57:24.472Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14437|2024-08-05T19:27:40.462Z -- talos -- moxa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14437</link>
      <description>An exploitable denial of service vulnerability exists in the web server functionality of Moxa EDR-810 V4.1 build 17030317. A specially crafted HTTP URI can cause a null pointer dereference resulting in denial of service. An attacker can send a GET request to "/MOXA\_LOG.ini" without a cookie header to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14437|2024-08-05T19:27:40.462Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14475|2024-08-05T19:27:40.664Z -- talos -- mysql%20mmm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14475</link>
      <description>In the MMM::Agent::Helpers::Network::add_ip function in MySQL Multi-Master Replication Manager (MMM) mmm_agentd 2.2.1 (for Linux), a specially crafted MMM protocol message can cause a shell command injection resulting in arbitrary command execution with the privileges of the mmm\_agentd process. An attacker that can initiate a TCP session with mmm\_agentd can trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14475|2024-08-05T19:27:40.664Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14463|2024-08-05T19:27:40.738Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14463</link>
      <description>An exploitable access control vulnerability exists in the data, program, and function file permissions functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a read or write operation resulting in disclosure of sensitive information, modification of settings, or modification of ladder logic. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability. Required Keyswitch State: REMOTE or PROG Associated Fault Code: 0012 Fault Type: Non-User Description: A fault state can be triggered by overwriting the ladder logic data file (type 0x22 number 0x02) with null values.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14463|2024-08-05T19:27:40.738Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2852|2024-08-05T14:09:16.752Z -- talos -- natus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2852</link>
      <description>An exploitable denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the unserialization of lists functionality of Natus Xltek NeuroWorks 8. A specially crafted network packet can cause an out-of-bounds read, resulting in a denial of service. An attacker can send a malicious packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2852|2024-08-05T14:09:16.752Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3907|2024-08-05T04:57:24.466Z -- talos -- samsung
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3907</link>
      <description>An exploitable vulnerability exists in the REST parser of video-core's HTTP server of the Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 - Firmware version 0.20.17. The video-core process incorrectly handles pipelined HTTP requests, which allows successive requests to overwrite the previously parsed HTTP method, 'on_url' callback. An attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3907|2024-08-05T04:57:24.466Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3883|2024-08-05T04:57:24.473Z -- talos -- erpnext
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3883</link>
      <description>An exploitable SQL injection vulnerability exists in the authenticated part of ERPNext v10.1.6. Specially crafted web requests can cause SQL injections resulting in data compromise. The employee and sort_order parameter can be used to perform an SQL injection attack. An attacker can use a browser to trigger these vulnerabilities, and no special tools are required.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3883|2024-08-05T04:57:24.473Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3926|2024-08-05T04:57:24.392Z -- talos -- samsung
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3926</link>
      <description>An exploitable integer underflow vulnerability exists in the ZigBee firmware update routine of the hubCore binary of the Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 - Firmware version 0.20.17. The hubCore process incorrectly handles malformed files existing in its data directory, leading to an infinite loop, which eventually causes the process to crash. An attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3926|2024-08-05T04:57:24.392Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12129|2024-08-05T18:28:16.808Z -- talos -- moxa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12129</link>
      <description>An exploitable Weak Cryptography for Passwords vulnerability exists in the web server functionality of Moxa EDR-810 V4.1 build 17030317. An attacker could intercept weakly encrypted passwords and could brute force them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12129|2024-08-05T18:28:16.808Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12113|2024-08-05T18:28:16.468Z -- talos -- cpp-ethereum
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12113</link>
      <description>An exploitable improper authorization vulnerability exists in admin_nodeInfo API of cpp-ethereum's JSON-RPC (commit 4e1015743b95821849d001618a7ce82c7c073768). A JSON request can cause an access to the restricted functionality resulting in authorization bypass. An attacker can send JSON to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12113|2024-08-05T18:28:16.468Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3971|2024-08-05T04:57:24.492Z -- talos -- sophos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3971</link>
      <description>An exploitable arbitrary write vulnerability exists in the 0x2222CC IOCTL handler functionality of Sophos HitmanPro.Alert 3.7.6.744. A specially crafted IRP request can cause the driver to write data under controlled by an attacker address, resulting in memory corruption. An attacker can send IRP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3971|2024-08-05T04:57:24.492Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14464|2024-08-05T19:27:40.681Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14464</link>
      <description>An exploitable access control vulnerability exists in the data, program, and function file permissions functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a read or write operation resulting in disclosure of sensitive information, modification of settings, or modification of ladder logic. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability.Required Keyswitch State: REMOTE or PROG Associated Fault Code: 0001 Fault Type: Non-User Description: A fault state can be triggered by setting the NVRAM/memory module user program mismatch bit (S2:9) when a memory module is NOT installed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14464|2024-08-05T19:27:40.681Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14470|2024-08-05T19:27:40.657Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14470</link>
      <description>An exploitable access control vulnerability exists in the data, program, and function file permissions functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a read or write operation resulting in disclosure of sensitive information, modification of settings, or modification of ladder logic. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability. Required Keyswitch State: REMOTE or PROG or RUN Description: The value 0xffffffff is considered NaN for the Float data type. When a float is set to this value and used in the PLC, a fault is triggered. NOTE: This is not possible through RSLogix.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14470|2024-08-05T19:27:40.657Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4039|2024-08-05T05:04:29.203Z -- talos -- atlantis%20word%20processor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4039</link>
      <description>An exploitable out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in the PNG implementation of Atlantis Word Processor, version 3.2.7.2. This can allow an attacker to corrupt memory, which can result in code execution under the context of the application. An attacker must convince a victim to open a specially crafted document in order to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4039|2024-08-05T05:04:29.203Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3884|2024-08-05T04:57:24.219Z -- talos -- erpnext
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3884</link>
      <description>An exploitable SQL injection vulnerability exists in the authenticated part of ERPNext v10.1.6. Specially crafted web requests can cause SQL injections resulting in data compromise. The sort_by and start parameter can be used to perform an SQL injection attack. An attacker can use a browser to trigger these vulnerabilities, and no special tools are required.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3884|2024-08-05T04:57:24.219Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2888|2024-08-05T14:09:17.782Z -- talos -- simple%20direct%20media
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2888</link>
      <description>An exploitable integer overflow vulnerability exists when creating a new RGB Surface in SDL 2.0.5. A specially crafted file can cause an integer overflow resulting in too little memory being allocated which can lead to a buffer overflow and potential code execution. An attacker can provide a specially crafted image file to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2888|2024-08-05T14:09:17.782Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3952|2024-08-05T04:57:24.473Z -- talos -- nordvpn
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3952</link>
      <description>An exploitable code execution vulnerability exists in the connect functionality of NordVPN 6.14.28.0. A specially crafted configuration file can cause a privilege escalation, resulting in the execution of arbitrary commands with system privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3952|2024-08-05T04:57:24.473Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3835|2024-08-05T04:57:23.851Z -- talos -- walt%20disney%20animation%20studios%20ptex
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3835</link>
      <description>An exploitable out of bounds write vulnerability exists in version 2.2 of the Per Face Texture mapping application known as PTEX. The vulnerability is present in the reading of a file without proper parameter checking. The value read in, is not verified to be valid and its use can lead to a buffer overflow, potentially resulting in code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3835|2024-08-05T04:57:23.851Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3849|2024-08-05T04:57:24.249Z -- talos -- nasa%20cfitsio
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3849</link>
      <description>In the ffghtb function in NASA CFITSIO 3.42, specially crafted images parsed via the library can cause a stack-based buffer overflow overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker can deliver an FIT image to trigger this vulnerability and potentially gain code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3849|2024-08-05T04:57:24.249Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12128|2024-08-05T18:28:16.349Z -- talos -- moxa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12128</link>
      <description>An exploitable information disclosure vulnerability exists in the Server Agent functionality of Moxa EDR-810 V4.1 build 17030317. A specially crafted TCP packet can cause information disclosure. An attacker can send a crafted TCP packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12128|2024-08-05T18:28:16.349Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14435|2024-08-05T19:27:40.480Z -- talos -- moxa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14435</link>
      <description>An exploitable denial of service vulnerability exists in the web server functionality of Moxa EDR-810 V4.1 build 17030317. A specially crafted HTTP URI can cause a null pointer dereference resulting in denial of service. An attacker can send a GET request to "/MOXA\_CFG.ini" without a cookie header to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14435|2024-08-05T19:27:40.480Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3868|2024-08-05T04:57:24.045Z -- talos -- computerinsel%20photoline
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3868</link>
      <description>A specially crafted TIFF image processed via the application can lead to an out-of-bounds write, overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker can deliver a TIFF image to trigger this vulnerability and gain code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3868|2024-08-05T04:57:24.045Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14433|2024-08-05T19:27:40.460Z -- talos -- moxa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14433</link>
      <description>An exploitable command injection vulnerability exists in the web server functionality of Moxa EDR-810 V4.1 build 17030317. A specially crafted HTTP POST can cause a privilege escalation resulting in root shell. An attacker can inject OS commands into the remoteNetwork0= parameter in the "/goform/net\_Web\_get_value" uri to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14433|2024-08-05T19:27:40.460Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3841|2024-08-05T04:57:24.381Z -- talos -- pixar%20renderman
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3841</link>
      <description>A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the Pixar Renderman IT Display Service 21.6 (0x69). The vulnerability is present in the parsing of a network packet without proper validation of the packet. The data read-in is not validated, and its use can lead to a null pointer dereference. The IT application is opened by a user and then listens for a connection on port 4001. An attacker can deliver an attack once the application has been opened.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3841|2024-08-05T04:57:24.381Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3850|2024-08-05T04:57:24.079Z -- talos -- foxit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3850</link>
      <description>An exploitable use-after-free vulnerability exists in the JavaScript engine Foxit Software Foxit PDF Reader version 9.0.1.1049. A specially crafted PDF document can trigger a previously freed object in memory to be reused, resulting in arbitrary code execution. An attacker needs to trick the user to open the malicious file to trigger this vulnerability. If a browser plugin extension is enabled, visiting a malicious site can also trigger the vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3850|2024-08-05T04:57:24.079Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12106|2024-08-05T18:28:16.599Z -- talos -- computerinsel%20photoline
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12106</link>
      <description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the .TGA parsing functionality of Computerinsel Photoline 20.02. A specially crafted .TGA file can cause an out of bounds write resulting in potential code execution. An attacker can send a specific .TGA file to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12106|2024-08-05T18:28:16.599Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2825|2024-08-05T14:09:16.754Z -- talos -- zabbix
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2825</link>
      <description>In the trapper functionality of Zabbix Server 2.4.x, specifically crafted trapper packets can pass database logic checks, resulting in database writes. An attacker can set up a Man-in-the-Middle server to alter trapper requests made between an active Zabbix proxy and Server to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2825|2024-08-05T14:09:16.754Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12115|2024-08-05T18:28:16.275Z -- talos -- cpp-ethereum
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12115</link>
      <description>An exploitable improper authorization vulnerability exists in miner_setEtherbase API of cpp-ethereum's JSON-RPC (commit 4e1015743b95821849d001618a7ce82c7c073768). A JSON request can cause an access to the restricted functionality resulting in authorization bypass.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12115|2024-08-05T18:28:16.275Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14457|2024-08-05T19:27:40.681Z -- talos -- cpp-ethereum
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14457</link>
      <description>An exploitable information leak/denial of service vulnerability exists in the libevm (Ethereum Virtual Machine) `create2` opcode handler of CPP-Ethereum. A specially crafted smart contract code can cause an out-of-bounds read leading to memory disclosure or denial of service. An attacker can create/send malicious a smart contract to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14457|2024-08-05T19:27:40.681Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14473|2024-08-05T19:27:40.664Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14473</link>
      <description>An exploitable access control vulnerability exists in the data, program, and function file permissions functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a read or write operation resulting in disclosure of sensitive information, modification of settings, or modification of ladder logic. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability. Required Keyswitch State: Any Description: Reads the encoded ladder logic from its data file and print it out in HEX.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14473|2024-08-05T19:27:40.664Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4059|2024-08-05T05:04:29.198Z -- talos -- coturn
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4059</link>
      <description>An exploitable unsafe default configuration vulnerability exists in the TURN server function of coTURN prior to version 4.5.0.9. By default, the TURN server runs an unauthenticated telnet admin portal on the loopback interface. This can provide administrator access to the TURN server configuration, which can lead to additional attacks. An attacker who can get access to the telnet port can gain administrator access to the TURN server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4059|2024-08-05T05:04:29.198Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 14:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12114|2024-08-05T18:28:16.658Z -- talos -- cpp-ethereum
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12114</link>
      <description>An exploitable improper authorization vulnerability exists in admin_peers API of cpp-ethereum's JSON-RPC (commit 4e1015743b95821849d001618a7ce82c7c073768). A JSON request can cause an access to the restricted functionality resulting in authorization bypass. An attacker can send JSON to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12114|2024-08-05T18:28:16.658Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3853|2024-08-05T04:57:24.307Z -- talos -- foxit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3853</link>
      <description>An exploitable use-after-free vulnerability exists in the JavaScript engine of Foxit Software Foxit PDF Reader version 9.0.1.1049. A specially crafted PDF document can trigger a previously freed object in memory to be reused resulting in arbitrary code execution. An attacker needs to trick the user to open the malicious file to trigger this vulnerability. If the browser plugin extension is enabled, visiting a malicious site can also trigger the vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3853|2024-08-05T04:57:24.307Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4055|2024-08-05T05:04:28.413Z -- talos -- pixar%20renderman
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4055</link>
      <description>A local privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the install helper tool of the Mac OS X version of Pixar Renderman, version 22.2.0. A user with local access can use this vulnerability to read any root file from the file system. An attacker would need local access to the machine to successfully exploit this flaw.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4055|2024-08-05T05:04:28.413Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3862|2024-08-05T04:57:24.326Z -- talos -- computerinsel%20photoline
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3862</link>
      <description>A specially crafted TIFF image processed via the application can lead to an out-of-bounds write, overwriting</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3862|2024-08-05T04:57:24.326Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12127|2024-08-05T18:28:16.432Z -- talos -- moxa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12127</link>
      <description>A password storage vulnerability exists in the operating system functionality of Moxa EDR-810 V4.1 build 17030317. An attacker with shell access could extract passwords in clear text from the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12127|2024-08-05T18:28:16.432Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4058|2024-08-05T05:04:28.675Z -- talos -- coturn
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4058</link>
      <description>An exploitable unsafe default configuration vulnerability exists in the TURN server functionality of coTURN prior to 4.5.0.9. By default, the TURN server allows relaying external traffic to the loopback interface of its own host. This can provide access to other private services running on that host, which can lead to further attacks. An attacker can set up a relay with a loopback address as the peer on an affected TURN server to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4058|2024-08-05T05:04:28.675Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 14:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12088|2024-08-05T18:28:16.359Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12088</link>
      <description>An exploitable denial of service vulnerability exists in the Ethernet functionality of the Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and below. A specially crafted packet can cause a device power cycle resulting in a fault state and deletion of ladder logic. An attacker can send one unauthenticated packet to trigger this vulnerability</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12088|2024-08-05T18:28:16.359Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12093|2024-08-05T18:28:16.501Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12093</link>
      <description>An exploitable insufficient resource pool vulnerability exists in the session communication functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B Firmware 21.2 and before. A specially crafted stream of packets can cause a flood of the session resource pool resulting in legitimate connections to the PLC being disconnected. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12093|2024-08-05T18:28:16.501Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3885|2024-08-05T04:57:24.456Z -- talos -- erpnext
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3885</link>
      <description>An exploitable SQL injection vulnerability exists in the authenticated part of ERPNext v10.1.6. Specially crafted web requests can cause SQL injections resulting in data compromise. The order_by parameter can be used to perform an SQL injection attack. An attacker can use a browser to trigger these vulnerabilities, and no special tools are required.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3885|2024-08-05T04:57:24.456Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3950|2024-08-05T04:57:24.701Z -- talos -- tp-link
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3950</link>
      <description>An exploitable remote code execution vulnerability exists in the ping and tracert functionality of the TP-Link TL-R600VPN HWv3 FRNv1.3.0 and HWv2 FRNv1.2.3 http server. A specially crafted IP address can cause a stack overflow, resulting in remote code execution. An attacker can send a single authenticated HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3950|2024-08-05T04:57:24.701Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3949|2024-08-05T04:57:24.537Z -- talos -- tp-link
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3949</link>
      <description>An exploitable information disclosure vulnerability exists in the HTTP server functionality of the TP-Link TL-R600VPN. A specially crafted URL can cause a directory traversal, resulting in the disclosure of sensitive system files. An attacker can send either an unauthenticated or an authenticated web request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3949|2024-08-05T04:57:24.537Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3980|2024-08-05T04:57:24.560Z -- talos -- acd%20systems
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3980</link>
      <description>An exploitable out-of-bounds write exists in the TIFF-parsing functionality of Canvas Draw version 5.0.0. A specially crafted TIFF image processed via the application can lead to an out-of-bounds write, overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker can deliver a TIFF image to trigger this vulnerability and gain code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3980|2024-08-05T04:57:24.560Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14438|2024-08-05T19:27:40.554Z -- talos -- moxa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14438</link>
      <description>Exploitable denial of service vulnerabilities exists in the Service Agent functionality of Moxa EDR-810 V4.1 build 17030317. A specially crafted packet can cause a denial of service. An attacker can send a large packet to 4000/tcp to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14438|2024-08-05T19:27:40.554Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12117|2024-08-05T18:28:16.253Z -- talos -- cpp-ethereum
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12117</link>
      <description>An exploitable improper authorization vulnerability exists in miner_start API of cpp-ethereum's JSON-RPC (commit 4e1015743b95821849d001618a7ce82c7c073768). A JSON request can cause an access to the restricted functionality resulting in authorization bypass. An attacker can send JSON to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12117|2024-08-05T18:28:16.253Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14469|2024-08-05T19:27:40.741Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14469</link>
      <description>An exploitable access control vulnerability exists in the data, program, and function file permissions functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a read or write operation resulting in disclosure of sensitive information, modification of settings, or modification of ladder logic. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability. Required Keyswitch State: REMOTE or PROG Associated Fault Code: 0028 Fault Type: Non-User Description: Values 0x01 and 0x02 are invalid values for the user fault routine. By writing directly to the file it is possible to set these values. When this is done and the device is moved into a run state, a fault is triggered. NOTE: This is not possible through RSLogix.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14469|2024-08-05T19:27:40.741Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12124|2024-08-05T18:28:16.571Z -- talos -- moxa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12124</link>
      <description>An exploitable denial of service vulnerability exists in the web server functionality of Moxa EDR-810 V4.1 build 17030317. A specially crafted HTTP URI can cause a null pointer dereference resulting in the web server crashing. An attacker can send a crafted URI to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12124|2024-08-05T18:28:16.571Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12121|2024-08-05T18:28:16.346Z -- talos -- moxa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12121</link>
      <description>An exploitable command injection vulnerability exists in the web server functionality of Moxa EDR-810 V4.1 build 17030317. A specially crafted HTTP POST can cause a privilege escalation resulting in root shell. An attacker can inject OS commands into the rsakey\_name= parm in the "/goform/WebRSAKEYGen" uri to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12121|2024-08-05T18:28:16.346Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3840|2024-08-05T04:57:23.965Z -- talos -- pixar%20renderman
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3840</link>
      <description>A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the Pixar Renderman IT Display Service 21.6 (0x67). The vulnerability is present in the parsing of a network packet without proper validation of the packet. The data read by the application is not validated, and its use can lead to a null pointer dereference. The IT application is opened by a user and then listens for a connection on port 4001. An attacker can deliver an attack once the application has been opened.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3840|2024-08-05T04:57:23.965Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2880|2024-08-05T14:09:17.420Z -- talos -- computerinsel%20photoline
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2880</link>
      <description>An memory corruption vulnerability exists in the .GIF parsing functionality of Computerinsel Photoline 20.02. A specially crafted .GIF file can cause a vulnerability resulting in potential code execution. An attacker can send specific .GIF file to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2880|2024-08-05T14:09:17.420Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3887|2024-08-05T04:57:24.376Z -- talos -- computerinsel%20photoline
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3887</link>
      <description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the PCX-parsing functionality of Computerinsel Photoline 20.53. A specially crafted PCX image processed via the application can lead to an out-of-bounds write, overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker can deliver a PCX image to trigger this vulnerability and gain code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3887|2024-08-05T04:57:24.376Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4010|2024-08-05T04:57:24.601Z -- talos -- protonvpn
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4010</link>
      <description>An exploitable code execution vulnerability exists in the connect functionality of ProtonVPN VPN client 1.5.1. A specially crafted configuration file can cause a privilege escalation, resulting in the ability to execute arbitrary commands with the system's privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4010|2024-08-05T04:57:24.601Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14481|2024-08-05T19:27:40.631Z -- talos -- mysql%20mmm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14481</link>
      <description>In the MMM::Agent::Helpers::Network::send_arp function in MySQL Multi-Master Replication Manager (MMM) mmm_agentd 2.2.1 (for Solaris), a specially crafted MMM protocol message can cause a shell command injection resulting in arbitrary command execution with the privileges of the mmm\_agentd process. An attacker that can initiate a TCP session with mmm\_agentd can trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14481|2024-08-05T19:27:40.631Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4038|2024-08-05T05:04:28.589Z -- talos -- atlantis%20word%20processor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4038</link>
      <description>An exploitable arbitrary write vulnerability exists in the open document format parser of the Atlantis Word Processor, version 3.2.7.2, while trying to null-terminate a string. A specially crafted document can allow an attacker to pass an untrusted value as a length to a constructor. This constructor will miscalculate a length and then use it to calculate the position to write a null byte. This can allow an attacker to corrupt memory, which can result in code execution under the context of the application. An attacker must convince a victim to open a specially crafted document in order to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4038|2024-08-05T05:04:28.589Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12112|2024-08-05T18:28:16.563Z -- talos -- cpp-ethereum
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12112</link>
      <description>An exploitable improper authorization vulnerability exists in admin_addPeer API of cpp-ethereum's JSON-RPC (commit 4e1015743b95821849d001618a7ce82c7c073768). A JSON request can cause an access to the restricted functionality resulting in authorization bypass. An attacker can send JSON to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12112|2024-08-05T18:28:16.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2858|2024-08-05T14:09:17.261Z -- talos -- natus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2858</link>
      <description>An exploitable denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the traversal of lists functionality of Natus Xltek NeuroWorks 8. A specially crafted network packet can cause an out-of-bounds read, resulting in a denial of service. An attacker can send a malicious packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2858|2024-08-05T14:09:17.261Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3973|2024-08-05T04:57:24.469Z -- talos -- acd%20systems
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3973</link>
      <description>An exploitable out of bounds write exists in the CAL parsing functionality of Canvas Draw version 5.0.0. A specially crafted CAL image processed via the application can lead to an out of bounds write overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker can deliver a PCX image to trigger this vulnerability and gain code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3973|2024-08-05T04:57:24.469Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3889|2024-08-05T04:57:24.471Z -- talos -- computerinsel%20photoline
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3889</link>
      <description>A specially crafted PCX image processed via the application can lead to an out-of-bounds write, overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker can deliver a PCX image to trigger this vulnerability and gain code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3889|2024-08-05T04:57:24.471Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3981|2024-08-05T04:57:24.602Z -- talos -- acd%20systems
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3981</link>
      <description>An exploitable out-of-bounds write exists in the TIFF-parsing functionality of Canvas Draw version 5.0.0. An attacker can deliver a TIFF image to trigger this vulnerability and gain code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3981|2024-08-05T04:57:24.602Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12089|2024-08-05T18:28:16.534Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12089</link>
      <description>An exploitable denial of service vulnerability exists in the program download functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a device fault resulting in halted operations. An attacker can send an unauthenticated packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12089|2024-08-05T18:28:16.534Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14462|2024-08-05T19:27:40.739Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14462</link>
      <description>An exploitable access control vulnerability exists in the data, program, and function file permissions functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a read or write operation resulting in disclosure of sensitive information, modification of settings, or modification of ladder logic. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability. Required Keyswitch State: REMOTE or PROG (also RUN for some) Description: Allows an attacker to enable SNMP, Modbus, DNP, and any other features in the channel configuration. Also allows attackers to change network parameters, such as IP address, name server, and domain name.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14462|2024-08-05T19:27:40.739Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4056|2024-08-05T05:04:28.898Z -- talos -- coturn
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4056</link>
      <description>An exploitable SQL injection vulnerability exists in the administrator web portal function of coTURN prior to version 4.5.0.9. A login message with a specially crafted username can cause an SQL injection, resulting in authentication bypass, which could give access to the TURN server administrator web portal. An attacker can log in via the external interface of the TURN server to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4056|2024-08-05T05:04:28.898Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12126|2024-08-05T18:28:16.415Z -- talos -- moxa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12126</link>
      <description>An exploitable cross-site request forgery vulnerability exists in the web server functionality of Moxa EDR-810 V4.1 build 17030317. A specially crafted HTTP packet can cause cross-site request forgery. An attacker can create malicious HTML to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12126|2024-08-05T18:28:16.415Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12125|2024-08-05T18:28:16.563Z -- talos -- moxa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12125</link>
      <description>An exploitable command injection vulnerability exists in the web server functionality of Moxa EDR-810 V4.1 build 17030317. A specially crafted HTTP POST can cause a privilege escalation resulting in root shell. An attacker can inject OS commands into the CN= parm in the "/goform/net_WebCSRGen" uri to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12125|2024-08-05T18:28:16.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3852|2024-08-05T04:57:24.391Z -- talos -- ocularis
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3852</link>
      <description>An exploitable denial of service vulnerability exists in the Ocularis Recorder functionality of Ocularis 5.5.0.242. A specially crafted TCP packet can cause a process to terminate resulting in denial of service. An attacker can send a crafted TCP packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3852|2024-08-05T04:57:24.391Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14466|2024-08-05T19:27:40.796Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14466</link>
      <description>An exploitable access control vulnerability exists in the data, program, and function file permissions functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a read or write operation resulting in disclosure of sensitive information, modification of settings, or modification of ladder logic. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability. Required Keyswitch State: REMOTE or PROG Description: The filetype 0x03 allows users write access, allowing the ability to overwrite the Master Password value stored in the file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14466|2024-08-05T19:27:40.796Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4050|2024-08-05T05:04:29.151Z -- talos -- gog%20galaxy
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4050</link>
      <description>An exploitable local privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the privileged helper tool of GOG Galaxy's Games, version 1.2.47 for macOS. An attacker can globally adjust folder permissions leading to execution of arbitrary code with elevated privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4050|2024-08-05T05:04:29.151Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 18:29:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14479|2024-08-05T19:27:40.881Z -- talos -- mysql%20mmm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14479</link>
      <description>In the MMM::Agent::Helpers::Network::clear_ip function in MySQL Multi-Master Replication Manager (MMM) mmm_agentd 2.2.1 (for Solaris), a specially crafted MMM protocol message can cause a shell command injection resulting in arbitrary command execution with the privileges of the mmm\_agentd process. An attacker that can initiate a TCP session with mmm\_agentd can trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14479|2024-08-05T19:27:40.881Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3976|2024-08-05T04:57:24.567Z -- talos -- acd%20systems
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3976</link>
      <description>An exploitable out-of-bounds write exists in the CALS Raster file format-parsing functionality of Canvas Draw version 5.0.0.28. A specially crafted CAL image processed via the application can lead to an out-of-bounds write, overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker can deliver a CAL image to trigger this vulnerability and gain code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3976|2024-08-05T04:57:24.567Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14459|2024-08-05T19:27:40.529Z -- talos -- moxa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14459</link>
      <description>An exploitable OS Command Injection vulnerability exists in the Telnet, SSH, and console login functionality of Moxa AWK-3131A Industrial IEEE 802.11a/b/g/n wireless AP/bridge/client in firmware versions 1.4 to 1.7 (current). An attacker can inject commands via the username parameter of several services (SSH, Telnet, console), resulting in remote, unauthenticated, root-level operating system command execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14459|2024-08-05T19:27:40.529Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12119|2024-08-05T18:28:16.299Z -- talos -- cpp-ethereum
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12119</link>
      <description>An exploitable unhandled exception vulnerability exists in multiple APIs of CPP-Ethereum JSON-RPC. Specially crafted JSON requests can cause an unhandled exception resulting in denial of service. An attacker can send malicious JSON to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12119|2024-08-05T18:28:16.299Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3846|2024-08-05T04:57:24.134Z -- talos -- nasa%20cfitsio
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3846</link>
      <description>In the ffgphd and ffgtkn functions in NASA CFITSIO 3.42, specially crafted images parsed via the library can cause a stack-based buffer overflow overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker can deliver an FIT image to trigger this vulnerability and potentially gain code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3846|2024-08-05T04:57:24.134Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12118|2024-08-05T18:28:16.535Z -- talos -- cpp-ethereum
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12118</link>
      <description>An exploitable improper authorization vulnerability exists in miner_stop API of cpp-ethereum's JSON-RPC (commit 4e1015743b95821849d001618a7ce82c7c073768). An attacker can send JSON to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12118|2024-08-05T18:28:16.535Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14436|2024-08-05T19:27:40.487Z -- talos -- moxa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14436</link>
      <description>An exploitable denial of service vulnerability exists in the web server functionality of Moxa EDR-810 V4.1 build 17030317. A specially crafted HTTP URI can cause a null pointer dereference resulting in denial of service. An attacker can send a GET request to "/MOXA\_CFG2.ini" without a cookie header to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14436|2024-08-05T19:27:40.487Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14447|2024-08-05T19:27:40.758Z -- talos -- insteon
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14447</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the PubNub message handler for the 'ad' channel of Insteon Hub running firmware version 1012. Specially crafted commands sent through the PubNub service can cause a stack-based buffer overflow overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker should send an authenticated HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14447|2024-08-05T19:27:40.758Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3848|2024-08-05T04:57:24.083Z -- talos -- nasa%20cfitsio
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3848</link>
      <description>In the ffghbn function in NASA CFITSIO 3.42, specially crafted images parsed via the library can cause a stack-based buffer overflow overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker can deliver an FIT image to trigger this vulnerability and potentially gain code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3848|2024-08-05T04:57:24.083Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2871|2024-08-05T14:09:17.325Z -- talos -- foscam
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2871</link>
      <description>Insufficient security checks exist in the recovery procedure used by the Foscam C1 Indoor HD Camera running application firmware 2.52.2.43. An attacker who is in the same subnetwork of the camera or has remote administrator access can fully compromise the device by performing a firmware recovery using a custom image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2871|2024-08-05T14:09:17.325Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14478|2024-08-05T19:27:40.646Z -- talos -- mysql%20mmm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14478</link>
      <description>In the MMM::Agent::Helpers::Network::clear_ip function in MySQL Multi-Master Replication Manager (MMM) mmm_agentd 2.2.1 (for Linux), a specially crafted MMM protocol message can cause a shell command injection resulting in arbitrary command execution with the privileges of the mmm\_agentd process. An attacker that can initiate a TCP session with mmm\_agentd can trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14478|2024-08-05T19:27:40.646Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14432|2024-08-05T19:27:40.519Z -- talos -- moxa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14432</link>
      <description>An exploitable command injection vulnerability exists in the web server functionality of Moxa EDR-810 V4.1 build 17030317. A specially crafted HTTP POST can cause a privilege escalation resulting in root shell. An attacker can inject OS commands into the openvpnServer0_tmp= parameter in the "/goform/net\_Web\_get_value" uri to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14432|2024-08-05T19:27:40.519Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14476|2024-08-05T19:27:40.752Z -- talos -- mysql%20mmm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14476</link>
      <description>In the MMM::Agent::Helpers::Network::add_ip function in MySQL Multi-Master Replication Manager (MMM) mmm_agentd 2.2.1 (for Solaris), a specially crafted MMM protocol message can cause a shell command injection resulting in arbitrary command execution with the privileges of the mmm\_agentd process. An attacker that can initiate a TCP session with mmm\_agentd can trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14476|2024-08-05T19:27:40.752Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14477|2024-08-05T19:27:40.735Z -- talos -- mysql%20mmm
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14477</link>
      <description>In the MMM::Agent::Helpers::Network::add_ip function in MySQL Multi-Master Replication Manager (MMM) mmm_agentd 2.2.1 (for FreeBSD), a specially crafted MMM protocol message can cause a shell command injection resulting in arbitrary command execution with the privileges of the mmm\_agentd process. An attacker that can initiate a TCP session with mmm\_agentd can trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14477|2024-08-05T19:27:40.735Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3938|2024-08-05T04:57:24.504Z -- talos -- sony
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3938</link>
      <description>An exploitable stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the 802dot1xclientcert.cgi functionality of Sony IPELA E Series Camera G5 firmware 1.87.00. A specially crafted POST can cause a stack-based buffer overflow, resulting in remote code execution. An attacker can send a malicious POST request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3938|2024-08-05T04:57:24.504Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4048|2024-08-05T05:04:29.440Z -- talos -- gog%20galaxy
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4048</link>
      <description>An exploitable local privilege elevation vulnerability exists in the file system permissions of the `Temp` directory in GOG Galaxy 1.2.48.36 (Windows 64-bit Installer). An attacker can overwrite executables of the Desktop Galaxy Updater to exploit this vulnerability and execute arbitrary code with SYSTEM privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4048|2024-08-05T05:04:29.440Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 16:06:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3970|2024-08-05T04:57:24.562Z -- talos -- sophos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3970</link>
      <description>An exploitable memory disclosure vulnerability exists in the 0x222000 IOCTL handler functionality of Sophos HitmanPro.Alert 3.7.6.744. A specially crafted IRP request can cause the driver to return uninitialized memory, resulting in kernel memory disclosure. An attacker can send an IRP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3970|2024-08-05T04:57:24.562Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14439|2024-08-05T19:27:40.801Z -- talos -- moxa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14439</link>
      <description>Exploitable denial of service vulnerabilities exists in the Service Agent functionality of Moxa EDR-810 V4.1 build 17030317. A specially crafted packet can cause a denial of service. An attacker can send a large packet to 4001/tcp to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14439|2024-08-05T19:27:40.801Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3842|2024-08-05T04:57:24.102Z -- talos -- foxit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3842</link>
      <description>An exploitable use of an uninitialized pointer vulnerability exists in the JavaScript engine in Foxit PDF Reader version 9.0.1.1049. A specially crafted PDF document can lead to a dereference of an uninitialized pointer which, if under attacker control, can result in arbitrary code execution. An attacker needs to trick the user to open a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability. If the browser plugin extension is enabled, visiting a malicious site can also trigger the vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3842|2024-08-05T04:57:24.102Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14460|2024-08-05T19:27:40.674Z -- talos -- parity
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14460</link>
      <description>An exploitable overly permissive cross-domain (CORS) whitelist vulnerability exists in JSON-RPC of Parity Ethereum client version 1.7.8. An automatically sent JSON object to JSON-RPC endpoint can trigger this vulnerability. A victim needs to visit a malicious website to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14460|2024-08-05T19:27:40.674Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16252|2024-08-05T20:20:04.668Z -- talos -- insteon
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16252</link>
      <description>Specially crafted commands sent through the PubNub service in Insteon Hub 2245-222 with firmware version 1012 can cause a stack-based buffer overflow overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker should send an authenticated HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.At 0x9d014cc0 the value for the cmd key is copied using strcpy to the buffer at $sp+0x11c. This buffer is 20 bytes large, sending anything longer will cause a buffer overflow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16252|2024-08-05T20:20:04.668Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2887|2024-08-05T14:09:17.429Z -- talos -- simple%20direct%20media
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2887</link>
      <description>An exploitable buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the XCF property handling functionality of SDL_image 2.0.1. A specially crafted xcf file can cause a stack-based buffer overflow resulting in potential code execution. An attacker can provide a specially crafted XCF file to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2887|2024-08-05T14:09:17.429Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3888|2024-08-05T04:57:24.151Z -- talos -- computerinsel%20photoline
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3888</link>
      <description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the PCX-parsing functionality of Computerinsel Photoline 20.53. A specially crafted PCX image processed via the application can lead to an out-of-bounds write, overwriting arbitrary data. An attacker can deliver a PCX image to trigger this vulnerability and gain code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3888|2024-08-05T04:57:24.151Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12130|2024-08-05T18:28:16.564Z -- talos -- tinysvcmdns
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12130</link>
      <description>An exploitable NULL pointer dereference vulnerability exists in the tinysvcmdns library version 2017-11-05. A specially crafted packet can make the library dereference a NULL pointer leading to a server crash and denial of service. An attacker needs to send a DNS query to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12130|2024-08-05T18:28:16.564Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3843|2024-08-05T04:57:24.082Z -- talos -- foxit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3843</link>
      <description>An exploitable type confusion vulnerability exists in the way Foxit PDF Reader version 9.0.1.1049 parses files with associated file annotations. A specially crafted PDF document can lead to an object of invalid type to be dereferenced, which can potentially lead to sensitive memory disclosure, and possibly to arbitrary code execution. An attacker needs to trick the user into opening the malicious file to trigger this vulnerability. If the browser plugin extension is enabled, visiting a malicious site can also trigger the vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3843|2024-08-05T04:57:24.082Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14467|2024-08-05T19:27:40.644Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14467</link>
      <description>An exploitable access control vulnerability exists in the data, program, and function file permissions functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a read or write operation resulting in disclosure of sensitive information, modification of settings, or modification of ladder logic. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability. Required Keyswitch State: REMOTE Description: Live rung edits are able to be made by an unauthenticated user allowing for addition, deletion, or modification of existing ladder logic. Additionally, faults and cpu state modification can be triggered if specific ladder logic is used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14467|2024-08-05T19:27:40.644Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12120|2024-08-05T18:28:16.339Z -- talos -- moxa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12120</link>
      <description>An exploitable command injection vulnerability exists in the web server functionality of Moxa EDR-810 V4.1 build 17030317. A specially crafted HTTP POST can cause a privilege escalation, resulting in a root shell. An attacker can inject OS commands into the ip= parm in the "/goform/net_WebPingGetValue" URI to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12120|2024-08-05T18:28:16.339Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-3909|2024-08-05T04:57:24.397Z -- talos -- samsung
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-3909</link>
      <description>An exploitable vulnerability exists in the REST parser of video-core's HTTP server of the Samsung SmartThings Hub STH-ETH-250 - Firmware version 0.20.17. The video-core process incorrectly handles pipelined HTTP requests, which allows successive requests to overwrite the previously parsed HTTP method, 'onmessagecomplete' callback. An attacker can send an HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-3909|2024-08-05T04:57:24.397Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
