<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Talos -- Allen Bradley</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/talos/allen%20bradley.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Talos -- Allen Bradley</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:23:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14465|2024-08-05T19:27:40.738Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14465</link>
      <description>An exploitable access control vulnerability exists in the data, program, and function file permissions functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a read or write operation resulting in disclosure of sensitive information, modification of settings, or modification of ladder logic. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability. Required Keyswitch State: REMOTE Description: Any input or output can be forced, causing unpredictable activity from the PLC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14465|2024-08-05T19:27:40.738Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12090|2024-08-05T18:28:16.302Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12090</link>
      <description>An exploitable denial of service vulnerability exists in the processing of snmp-set commands of the Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and below. A specially crafted snmp-set request, when sent without associated firmware flashing snmp-set commands, can cause a device power cycle resulting in downtime for the device. An attacker can send one packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12090|2024-08-05T18:28:16.302Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14471|2024-08-05T19:27:40.811Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14471</link>
      <description>An exploitable access control vulnerability exists in the data, program, and function file permissions functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a read or write operation resulting in disclosure of sensitive information, modification of settings, or modification of ladder logic. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability. Required Keyswitch State: REMOTE or PROG Associated Fault Codes: 0023, 002e, and 0037 Fault Type: Recoverable Description: The STI, EII, and HSC function files contain bits signifying whether or not a fault has occurred. Additionally there is a bit signaling the module to auto start. When these bits are set for any of the three modules and the device is moved into a run state, a fault is triggered.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14471|2024-08-05T19:27:40.811Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14472|2024-08-05T19:27:40.687Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14472</link>
      <description>An exploitable access control vulnerability exists in the data, program, and function file permissions functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a read or write operation resulting in disclosure of sensitive information, modification of settings, or modification of ladder logic. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability. Required Keyswitch State: Any Description: Requests a specific set of bytes from an undocumented data file and returns the ASCII version of the master password.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14472|2024-08-05T19:27:40.687Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14468|2024-08-05T19:27:40.638Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14468</link>
      <description>An exploitable access control vulnerability exists in the data, program, and function file permissions functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a read or write operation resulting in disclosure of sensitive information, modification of settings, or modification of ladder logic. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability. Required Keyswitch State: REMOTE or PROG Description: This ability is leveraged in a larger exploit to flash custom firmware.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14468|2024-08-05T19:27:40.638Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12092|2024-08-05T18:28:16.293Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12092</link>
      <description>An exploitable file write vulnerability exists in the memory module functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a file write resulting in a new program being written to the memory module. An attacker can send an unauthenticated packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12092|2024-08-05T18:28:16.293Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14463|2024-08-05T19:27:40.738Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14463</link>
      <description>An exploitable access control vulnerability exists in the data, program, and function file permissions functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a read or write operation resulting in disclosure of sensitive information, modification of settings, or modification of ladder logic. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability. Required Keyswitch State: REMOTE or PROG Associated Fault Code: 0012 Fault Type: Non-User Description: A fault state can be triggered by overwriting the ladder logic data file (type 0x22 number 0x02) with null values.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14463|2024-08-05T19:27:40.738Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14464|2024-08-05T19:27:40.681Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14464</link>
      <description>An exploitable access control vulnerability exists in the data, program, and function file permissions functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a read or write operation resulting in disclosure of sensitive information, modification of settings, or modification of ladder logic. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability.Required Keyswitch State: REMOTE or PROG Associated Fault Code: 0001 Fault Type: Non-User Description: A fault state can be triggered by setting the NVRAM/memory module user program mismatch bit (S2:9) when a memory module is NOT installed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14464|2024-08-05T19:27:40.681Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14470|2024-08-05T19:27:40.657Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14470</link>
      <description>An exploitable access control vulnerability exists in the data, program, and function file permissions functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a read or write operation resulting in disclosure of sensitive information, modification of settings, or modification of ladder logic. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability. Required Keyswitch State: REMOTE or PROG or RUN Description: The value 0xffffffff is considered NaN for the Float data type. When a float is set to this value and used in the PLC, a fault is triggered. NOTE: This is not possible through RSLogix.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14470|2024-08-05T19:27:40.657Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14473|2024-08-05T19:27:40.664Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14473</link>
      <description>An exploitable access control vulnerability exists in the data, program, and function file permissions functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a read or write operation resulting in disclosure of sensitive information, modification of settings, or modification of ladder logic. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability. Required Keyswitch State: Any Description: Reads the encoded ladder logic from its data file and print it out in HEX.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14473|2024-08-05T19:27:40.664Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12088|2024-08-05T18:28:16.359Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12088</link>
      <description>An exploitable denial of service vulnerability exists in the Ethernet functionality of the Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and below. A specially crafted packet can cause a device power cycle resulting in a fault state and deletion of ladder logic. An attacker can send one unauthenticated packet to trigger this vulnerability</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12088|2024-08-05T18:28:16.359Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12093|2024-08-05T18:28:16.501Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12093</link>
      <description>An exploitable insufficient resource pool vulnerability exists in the session communication functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B Firmware 21.2 and before. A specially crafted stream of packets can cause a flood of the session resource pool resulting in legitimate connections to the PLC being disconnected. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12093|2024-08-05T18:28:16.501Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14469|2024-08-05T19:27:40.741Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14469</link>
      <description>An exploitable access control vulnerability exists in the data, program, and function file permissions functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a read or write operation resulting in disclosure of sensitive information, modification of settings, or modification of ladder logic. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability. Required Keyswitch State: REMOTE or PROG Associated Fault Code: 0028 Fault Type: Non-User Description: Values 0x01 and 0x02 are invalid values for the user fault routine. By writing directly to the file it is possible to set these values. When this is done and the device is moved into a run state, a fault is triggered. NOTE: This is not possible through RSLogix.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14469|2024-08-05T19:27:40.741Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12089|2024-08-05T18:28:16.534Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12089</link>
      <description>An exploitable denial of service vulnerability exists in the program download functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a device fault resulting in halted operations. An attacker can send an unauthenticated packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12089|2024-08-05T18:28:16.534Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14462|2024-08-05T19:27:40.739Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14462</link>
      <description>An exploitable access control vulnerability exists in the data, program, and function file permissions functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a read or write operation resulting in disclosure of sensitive information, modification of settings, or modification of ladder logic. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability. Required Keyswitch State: REMOTE or PROG (also RUN for some) Description: Allows an attacker to enable SNMP, Modbus, DNP, and any other features in the channel configuration. Also allows attackers to change network parameters, such as IP address, name server, and domain name.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14462|2024-08-05T19:27:40.739Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14466|2024-08-05T19:27:40.796Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14466</link>
      <description>An exploitable access control vulnerability exists in the data, program, and function file permissions functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a read or write operation resulting in disclosure of sensitive information, modification of settings, or modification of ladder logic. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability. Required Keyswitch State: REMOTE or PROG Description: The filetype 0x03 allows users write access, allowing the ability to overwrite the Master Password value stored in the file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14466|2024-08-05T19:27:40.796Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-14467|2024-08-05T19:27:40.644Z -- talos -- allen%20bradley
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-14467</link>
      <description>An exploitable access control vulnerability exists in the data, program, and function file permissions functionality of Allen Bradley Micrologix 1400 Series B FRN 21.2 and before. A specially crafted packet can cause a read or write operation resulting in disclosure of sensitive information, modification of settings, or modification of ladder logic. An attacker can send unauthenticated packets to trigger this vulnerability. Required Keyswitch State: REMOTE Description: Live rung edits are able to be made by an unauthenticated user allowing for addition, deletion, or modification of existing ladder logic. Additionally, faults and cpu state modification can be triggered if specific ladder logic is used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-14467|2024-08-05T19:27:40.644Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
