<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Talos -- Atlantis Word Processor</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/talos/atlantis%20word%20processor.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Talos -- Atlantis Word Processor</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 07:21:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4040|2024-08-05T05:04:29.553Z -- talos -- atlantis%20word%20processor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4040</link>
      <description>An exploitable uninitialized pointer vulnerability exists in the rich text format parser of Atlantis Word Processor, version 3.2.7.2. A specially crafted document can cause certain RTF tokens to dereference a pointer that has been uninitialized and then write to it. An attacker must convince a victim to open a specially crafted document in order to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4040|2024-08-05T05:04:29.553Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4039|2024-08-05T05:04:29.203Z -- talos -- atlantis%20word%20processor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4039</link>
      <description>An exploitable out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in the PNG implementation of Atlantis Word Processor, version 3.2.7.2. This can allow an attacker to corrupt memory, which can result in code execution under the context of the application. An attacker must convince a victim to open a specially crafted document in order to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4039|2024-08-05T05:04:29.203Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4038|2024-08-05T05:04:28.589Z -- talos -- atlantis%20word%20processor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4038</link>
      <description>An exploitable arbitrary write vulnerability exists in the open document format parser of the Atlantis Word Processor, version 3.2.7.2, while trying to null-terminate a string. A specially crafted document can allow an attacker to pass an untrusted value as a length to a constructor. This constructor will miscalculate a length and then use it to calculate the position to write a null byte. This can allow an attacker to corrupt memory, which can result in code execution under the context of the application. An attacker must convince a victim to open a specially crafted document in order to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4038|2024-08-05T05:04:28.589Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
