<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for ATM Consulting -- dolibarr_module_quicksupplierprice</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/atm%20consulting/dolibarr_module_quicksupplierprice.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for ATM Consulting -- dolibarr_module_quicksupplierprice</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 05:22:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4933|2024-08-03T01:55:46.050Z -- atm%20consulting -- dolibarr_module_quicksupplierprice
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4933</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in ATM Consulting dolibarr_module_quicksupplierprice up to 1.1.6. Affected by this issue is the function upatePrice of the file script/interface.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 1.1.7 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as ccad1e4282b0e393a32fcc852e82ec0e0af5446f. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-223382 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in ATM Consulting dolibarr_module_quicksupplierprice bis 1.1.6 entdeckt. Dies betrifft die Funktion upatePrice der Datei script/interface.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 1.1.7 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als ccad1e4282b0e393a32fcc852e82ec0e0af5446f bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4933|2024-08-03T01:55:46.050Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 04:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
