<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for dfir-iris -- iris-web</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/dfir-iris/iris-web.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for dfir-iris -- iris-web</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 22:02:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-25640|2024-02-19T19:56:33.044Z -- dfir-iris -- iris-web
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25640</link><description>Iris is a web collaborative platform that helps incident responders share technical details during investigations. A stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been identified in iris-web, affecting multiple locations in versions prior to v2.4.0. The vulnerability may allow an attacker to inject malicious scripts into the application, which could then be executed when a user visits the affected locations. This could lead to unauthorized access, data theft, or other related malicious activities. An attacker need to be authenticated on the application to exploit this vulnerability. The issue is fixed in version v2.4.0 of iris-web. No workarounds are available.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25640|2024-02-19T19:56:33.044Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 19:56:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25624|2024-04-25T16:30:43.979Z -- dfir-iris -- iris-web
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25624</link><description>Iris is a web collaborative platform aiming to help incident responders sharing technical details during investigations. Due to an improper setup of Jinja2 environment, reports generation in `iris-web` is prone to a Server Side Template Injection (SSTI). Successful exploitation of the vulnerability can lead to an arbitrary Remote Code Execution. An authenticated administrator has to upload a crafted report template containing the payload. Upon generation of a report based on the weaponized report, any user can trigger the vulnerability.  The vulnerability is patched in IRIS v2.4.6. No workaround is available. It is recommended to update as soon as possible. Until patching, review the report templates and keep the administrative privileges that include the upload of report templates limited to dedicated users. 
</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25624|2024-04-25T16:30:43.979Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>