<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for RSA -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/rsa/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for RSA -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 14:22:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11073|2024-09-17T01:20:47.843Z -- rsa -- authentication%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11073</link>
      <description>RSA Authentication Manager versions prior to 8.3 P3 contain a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Operations Console. A malicious Operations Console administrator could exploit this vulnerability to store arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code through the web interface. When other Operations Console administrators open the affected page, the injected scripts could potentially be executed in their browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11073|2024-09-17T01:20:47.843Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1252|2024-09-17T03:32:36.574Z -- rsa -- web%20threat%20detection
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1252</link>
      <description>RSA Web Threat Detection versions prior to 6.4, contain an SQL injection vulnerability in the Administration and Forensics applications. An authenticated malicious user with low privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability to execute SQL commands on the back-end database to gain unauthorized access to the tool's monitoring and user information by supplying specially crafted input data to the affected application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1252|2024-09-17T03:32:36.574Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1253|2024-09-17T03:52:50.534Z -- rsa -- authentication%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1253</link>
      <description>RSA Authentication Manager Operation Console, versions 8.3 P1 and earlier, contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability. A malicious Operations Console administrator could potentially exploit this vulnerability to store arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code through the web interface. When other Operations Console administrators open the affected page, the injected scripts could potentially be executed in their browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1253|2024-09-17T03:52:50.534Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11075|2024-09-17T00:30:53.695Z -- rsa -- authentication%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11075</link>
      <description>RSA Authentication Manager versions prior to 8.3 P3 contain a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability in a Security Console page. A remote, unauthenticated malicious user, with the knowledge of a target user's anti-CSRF token, could potentially exploit this vulnerability by tricking a victim Security Console user to supply malicious HTML or JavaScript code to the vulnerable web application, which code is then executed by the victim's web browser in the context of the vulnerable web application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11075|2024-09-17T00:30:53.695Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1254|2024-09-17T02:11:11.898Z -- rsa -- rsa%20authentication%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1254</link>
      <description>RSA Authentication Manager Security Console, versions 8.3 P1 and earlier, contains a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability by tricking a victim Security Console administrator to supply malicious HTML or JavaScript code to a vulnerable web application, which is then reflected back to the victim and executed by the web browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1254|2024-09-17T02:11:11.898Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1255|2024-09-17T02:16:59.328Z -- rsa -- rsa%20identity%20governance%20and%20lifecycle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1255</link>
      <description>RSA Identity Lifecycle and Governance versions 7.0.1, 7.0.2 and 7.1.0 contains a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability by tricking a victim application user to supply malicious HTML or JavaScript code to a vulnerable web application, which is then reflected back to the victim and executed by the web browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1255|2024-09-17T02:16:59.328Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
