<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for RSA -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/rsa/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for RSA -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 08:24:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11054|2024-08-05T07:54:36.640Z -- rsa -- bsafe%20micro%20edition%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11054</link>
      <description>RSA BSAFE Micro Edition Suite, version 4.1.6, contains an integer overflow vulnerability. A remote attacker could use maliciously constructed ASN.1 data to potentially cause a Denial Of Service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11054|2024-08-05T07:54:36.640Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1254|2024-08-05T03:51:49.104Z -- rsa -- rsa%20authentication%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1254</link>
      <description>RSA Authentication Manager Security Console, versions 8.3 P1 and earlier, contains a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability by tricking a victim Security Console administrator to supply malicious HTML or JavaScript code to a vulnerable web application, which is then reflected back to the victim and executed by the web browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1254|2024-08-05T03:51:49.104Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1255|2024-08-05T03:51:49.138Z -- rsa -- rsa%20identity%20governance%20and%20lifecycle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1255</link>
      <description>RSA Identity Lifecycle and Governance versions 7.0.1, 7.0.2 and 7.1.0 contains a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability by tricking a victim application user to supply malicious HTML or JavaScript code to a vulnerable web application, which is then reflected back to the victim and executed by the web browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1255|2024-08-05T03:51:49.138Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11051|2024-08-05T07:54:36.560Z -- rsa -- certificate%20manager%20path%20traversal%20vulnerability
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11051</link>
      <description>RSA Certificate Manager Versions 6.9 build 560 through 6.9 build 564 contain a path traversal vulnerability in the RSA CMP Enroll Server and the RSA REST Enroll Server. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability by manipulating input parameters of the application to gain unauthorized read access to the files stored on the server filesystem, with the privileges of the running web application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11051|2024-08-05T07:54:36.560Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11056|2024-08-05T07:54:36.548Z -- rsa -- bsafe%20micro%20edition%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11056</link>
      <description>RSA BSAFE Micro Edition Suite, prior to 4.1.6.1 (in 4.1.x), and RSA BSAFE Crypto-C Micro Edition versions prior to 4.0.5.3 (in 4.0.x) contain an Uncontrolled Resource Consumption ('Resource Exhaustion') vulnerability when parsing ASN.1 data. A remote attacker could use maliciously constructed ASN.1 data that would exhaust the stack, potentially causing a Denial Of Service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11056|2024-08-05T07:54:36.548Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11074|2024-08-05T07:54:36.508Z -- rsa -- authentication%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11074</link>
      <description>RSA Authentication Manager versions prior to 8.3 P3 are affected by a DOM-based cross-site scripting vulnerability which exists in its embedded MadCap Flare Help files. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability by tricking a victim application user to supply malicious HTML or JavaScript code to the browser DOM, which code is then executed by the web browser in the context of the vulnerable web application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11074|2024-08-05T07:54:36.508Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11073|2024-08-05T07:54:36.541Z -- rsa -- authentication%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11073</link>
      <description>RSA Authentication Manager versions prior to 8.3 P3 contain a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Operations Console. A malicious Operations Console administrator could exploit this vulnerability to store arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code through the web interface. When other Operations Console administrators open the affected page, the injected scripts could potentially be executed in their browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11073|2024-08-05T07:54:36.541Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11075|2024-08-05T07:54:36.584Z -- rsa -- authentication%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11075</link>
      <description>RSA Authentication Manager versions prior to 8.3 P3 contain a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability in a Security Console page. A remote, unauthenticated malicious user, with the knowledge of a target user's anti-CSRF token, could potentially exploit this vulnerability by tricking a victim Security Console user to supply malicious HTML or JavaScript code to the vulnerable web application, which code is then executed by the victim's web browser in the context of the vulnerable web application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11075|2024-08-05T07:54:36.584Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11055|2024-08-05T07:54:36.580Z -- rsa -- bsafe%20micro%20edition%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11055</link>
      <description>RSA BSAFE Micro Edition Suite, versions prior to 4.0.11 (in 4.0.x) and prior to 4.1.6.1 (in 4.1.x), contains an Improper Clearing of Heap Memory Before Release ('Heap Inspection') vulnerability. Decoded PKCS #12 data in heap memory is not zeroized by MES before releasing the memory internally and a malicious local user could gain access to the unauthorized data by doing heap inspection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11055|2024-08-05T07:54:36.580Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11058|2024-08-05T07:54:36.479Z -- rsa -- bsafe%20micro%20edition%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11058</link>
      <description>RSA BSAFE Micro Edition Suite, versions prior to 4.0.11 (in 4.0.x) and prior to 4.1.6 (in 4.1.x), and RSA BSAFE Crypto-C Micro Edition, version prior to 4.0.5.3 (in 4.0.x) contain a Buffer Over-Read vulnerability when parsing ASN.1 data. A remote attacker could use maliciously constructed ASN.1 data that would result in such issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11058|2024-08-05T07:54:36.479Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1252|2024-08-05T03:51:48.993Z -- rsa -- web%20threat%20detection
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1252</link>
      <description>RSA Web Threat Detection versions prior to 6.4, contain an SQL injection vulnerability in the Administration and Forensics applications. An authenticated malicious user with low privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability to execute SQL commands on the back-end database to gain unauthorized access to the tool's monitoring and user information by supplying specially crafted input data to the affected application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1252|2024-08-05T03:51:48.993Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1245|2024-08-05T03:51:48.976Z -- rsa -- rsa%20identity%20governance%20and%20lifecycle
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1245</link>
      <description>RSA Identity Lifecycle and Governance versions 7.0.1, 7.0.2 and 7.1.0 contains an authorization bypass vulnerability within the workflow architect component (ACM). A remote authenticated malicious user with non-admin privileges could potentially bypass the Java Security Policies. Once bypassed, a malicious user could potentially run arbitrary system commands at the OS level with application owner privileges on the affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1245|2024-08-05T03:51:48.976Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11057|2024-08-05T07:54:36.548Z -- rsa -- bsafe%20micro%20edition%20suite
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11057</link>
      <description>RSA BSAFE Micro Edition Suite, versions prior to 4.0.11 (in 4.0.x) and prior to 4.1.6.1 (in 4.1.x) contains a Covert Timing Channel vulnerability during RSA decryption, also known as a Bleichenbacher attack on RSA decryption. A remote attacker may be able to recover a RSA key.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11057|2024-08-05T07:54:36.548Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1253|2024-08-05T03:51:49.056Z -- rsa -- authentication%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1253</link>
      <description>RSA Authentication Manager Operation Console, versions 8.3 P1 and earlier, contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability. A malicious Operations Console administrator could potentially exploit this vulnerability to store arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code through the web interface. When other Operations Console administrators open the affected page, the injected scripts could potentially be executed in their browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1253|2024-08-05T03:51:49.056Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
