<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Eclipse Foundation -- Jetty</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/eclipse%20foundation/jetty.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Eclipse Foundation -- Jetty</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 16:24:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6763|2024-10-14T15:30:38.815Z -- eclipse%20foundation -- jetty
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6763</link>
      <description>Eclipse Jetty is a lightweight, highly scalable, Java-based web server and Servlet engine . It includes a utility class, HttpURI, for URI/URL parsing.

The HttpURI class does insufficient validation on the authority segment of a URI.  However the behaviour of HttpURI
 differs from the common browsers in how it handles a URI that would be 
considered invalid if fully validated against the RRC.  Specifically HttpURI
 and the browser may differ on the value of the host extracted from an 
invalid URI and thus a combination of Jetty and a vulnerable browser may
 be vulnerable to a open redirect attack or to a SSRF attack if the URI 
is used after passing validation checks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6763|2024-10-14T15:30:38.815Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 15:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8184|2024-10-14T15:30:02.698Z -- eclipse%20foundation -- jetty
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8184</link>
      <description>There exists a security vulnerability in Jetty's ThreadLimitHandler.getRemote() which can be exploited by unauthorized users to cause remote denial-of-service (DoS) attack.  By repeatedly sending crafted requests, attackers can trigger OutofMemory errors and exhaust the server's memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8184|2024-10-14T15:30:02.698Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 15:09:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-9823|2024-10-14T15:29:14.390Z -- eclipse%20foundation -- jetty
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9823</link>
      <description>There exists a security vulnerability in Jetty's DosFilter which can be exploited by unauthorized users to cause remote denial-of-service (DoS) attack on the server using DosFilter. By repeatedly sending crafted requests, attackers can trigger OutofMemory errors and exhaust the server's memory finally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-9823|2024-10-14T15:29:14.390Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 15:03:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6762|2024-10-14T15:07:10.942Z -- eclipse%20foundation -- jetty
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6762</link>
      <description>Jetty PushSessionCacheFilter can be exploited by unauthenticated users 
to launch remote DoS attacks by exhausting the server’s memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6762|2024-10-14T15:07:10.942Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 15:07:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
