<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Ingenico -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ingenico/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Ingenico -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 19:19:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6415|2024-07-02T18:40:17.711Z -- ingenico -- estate%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6415</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Ingenico Estate Manager 2023. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /emgui/rest/preferences/PREF_HOME_PAGE/sponsor/3/ of the component New Widget Handler. The manipulation of the argument URL leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-270001 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Ingenico Estate Manager 2023 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei /emgui/rest/preferences/PREF_HOME_PAGE/sponsor/3/ der Komponente New Widget Handler. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments URL mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6415|2024-07-02T18:40:17.711Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 04:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6059|2024-06-17T18:31:04.757Z -- ingenico -- estate%20manager</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6059</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Ingenico Estate Manager 2023. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /emgui/rest/ums/messages of the component News Feed. The manipulation of the argument message leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-268787. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Ingenico Estate Manager 2023 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei /emgui/rest/ums/messages der Komponente News Feed. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments message mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6059|2024-06-17T18:31:04.757Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 18:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6415|2024-06-30T04:00:05.417Z -- ingenico -- estate%20manager</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6415</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Ingenico Estate Manager 2023. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /emgui/rest/preferences/PREF_HOME_PAGE/sponsor/3/ of the component New Widget Handler. The manipulation of the argument URL leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-270001 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Ingenico Estate Manager 2023 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei /emgui/rest/preferences/PREF_HOME_PAGE/sponsor/3/ der Komponente New Widget Handler. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments URL mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6415|2024-06-30T04:00:05.417Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 04:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
