<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for epiphyt -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/epiphyt/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for epiphyt -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 23:22:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-48300|2024-08-02T21:23:39.493Z -- epiphyt -- embed-privacy
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48300</link>
      <description>The `Embed Privacy` plugin for WordPress that prevents the loading of embedded external content is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via `embed_privacy_opt_out` shortcode in versions up to, and including, 1.8.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. Version 1.8.1 contains a patch for this issue.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-48300|2024-08-02T21:23:39.493Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 18:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-30616|2024-08-02T14:28:51.827Z -- epiphyt -- form-block
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30616</link>
      <description>Form block is a wordpress plugin designed to make form creation easier. Versions prior to 1.0.2 are subject to a Cross-Site Request Forgery due to a missing nonce check. There is potential for a Cross Site Request Forgery for all form blocks, since it allows to send requests to the forms from any website without a user noticing. Users are advised to upgrade to version 1.0.2. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-30616|2024-08-02T14:28:51.827Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 17:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51694|2024-08-02T22:40:34.151Z -- epiphyt -- embed%20privacy
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51694</link>
      <description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Epiphyt Embed Privacy allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Embed Privacy: from n/a through 1.8.0.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51694|2024-08-02T22:40:34.151Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 11:04:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
