<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Dojo -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/dojo/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Dojo -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 11:20:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5258|2024-08-04T08:22:09.130Z -- dojo -- dojo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5258</link>
      <description>In affected versions of dojo (NPM package), the deepCopy method is vulnerable to Prototype Pollution. Prototype Pollution refers to the ability to inject properties into existing JavaScript language construct prototypes, such as objects. An attacker manipulates these attributes to overwrite, or pollute, a JavaScript application object prototype of the base object by injecting other values. This has been patched in versions 1.12.8, 1.13.7, 1.14.6, 1.15.3 and 1.16.2</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5258|2024-08-04T08:22:09.130Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 17:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-4051|2024-08-04T07:52:20.806Z -- dojo -- dijit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-4051</link>
      <description>In Dijit before versions 1.11.11, and greater than or equal to 1.12.0 and less than 1.12.9, and greater than or equal to 1.13.0 and less than 1.13.8, and greater than or equal to 1.14.0 and less than 1.14.7, and greater than or equal to 1.15.0 and less than 1.15.4, and greater than or equal to 1.16.0 and less than 1.16.3, there is a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Editor's LinkDialog plugin. This has been fixed in 1.11.11, 1.12.9, 1.13.8, 1.14.7, 1.15.4, 1.16.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-4051|2024-08-04T07:52:20.806Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5259|2024-08-04T08:22:09.035Z -- dojo -- dojox
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5259</link>
      <description>In affected versions of dojox (NPM package), the jqMix method is vulnerable to Prototype Pollution. Prototype Pollution refers to the ability to inject properties into existing JavaScript language construct prototypes, such as objects. An attacker manipulates these attributes to overwrite, or pollute, a JavaScript application object prototype of the base object by injecting other values. This has been patched in versions 1.11.10, 1.12.8, 1.13.7, 1.14.6, 1.15.3 and 1.16.2</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5259|2024-08-04T08:22:09.035Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 17:50:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
