<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for RRJ -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/rrj/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for RRJ -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 22:02:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-0185|2024-01-02T00:00:06.730Z -- RRJ -- Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0185</link><description>A vulnerability was found in RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file dasboard_teacher.php of the component Avatar Handler. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249443.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei dasboard_teacher.php der Komponente Avatar Handler. Durch das Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0185|2024-01-02T00:00:06.730Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 00:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0189|2024-01-02T18:00:04.652Z -- RRJ -- Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0189</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file teacher_message.php of the component Create Message Handler. The manipulation of the argument Content with the input &lt;/title&gt;&lt;scRipt&gt;alert(x)&lt;/scRipt&gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249502 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal 1.0 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle gefunden. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei teacher_message.php der Komponente Create Message Handler. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments Content mit der Eingabe &lt;/title&gt;&lt;scRipt&gt;alert(x)&lt;/scRipt&gt; mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0189|2024-01-02T18:00:04.652Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 18:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0188|2024-01-02T15:00:04.424Z -- RRJ -- Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0188</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file change_password_teacher.php. The manipulation leads to weak password requirements. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249501 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal 1.0 gefunden. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei change_password_teacher.php. Durch Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine weak password requirements-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Sie ist schwierig auszunutzen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0188|2024-01-02T15:00:04.424Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 15:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0184|2024-01-01T23:31:03.959Z -- RRJ -- Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0184</link><description>A vulnerability was found in RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/edit_teacher.php of the component Add Enginer. The manipulation of the argument Firstname/Lastname leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249442 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei /admin/edit_teacher.php der Komponente Add Enginer. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments Firstname/Lastname mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0184|2024-01-01T23:31:03.959Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 23:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0192|2024-01-02T20:00:04.419Z -- RRJ -- Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0192</link><description>A vulnerability was found in RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file downloadable.php of the component Add Downloadable. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249505 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei downloadable.php der Komponente Add Downloadable. Durch die Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0192|2024-01-02T20:00:04.419Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 20:00:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0183|2024-01-01T23:00:05.201Z -- RRJ -- Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0183</link><description>A vulnerability was found in RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/students.php of the component NIA Office. The manipulation leads to basic cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249441 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei /admin/students.php der Komponente NIA Office. Mittels dem Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine basic cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0183|2024-01-01T23:00:05.201Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 23:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0181|2024-01-01T16:31:03.353Z -- RRJ -- Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0181</link><description>A vulnerability was found in RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/admin_user.php of the component Admin Panel. The manipulation of the argument Firstname/Lastname/Username leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249433 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal 1.0 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei /admin/admin_user.php der Komponente Admin Panel. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments Firstname/Lastname/Username mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0181|2024-01-01T16:31:03.353Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 16:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0191|2024-01-02T19:31:03.405Z -- RRJ -- Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0191</link><description>A vulnerability was found in RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/uploads/. The manipulation leads to file and directory information exposure. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249504.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal 1.0 ausgemacht. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei /admin/uploads/. Mit der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine file and directory information exposure-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0191|2024-01-02T19:31:03.405Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 19:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0190|2024-01-02T18:31:03.630Z -- RRJ -- Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0190</link><description>A vulnerability was found in RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file add_quiz.php of the component Quiz Handler. The manipulation of the argument Quiz Title/Quiz Description with the input &lt;/title&gt;&lt;scRipt&gt;alert(x)&lt;/scRipt&gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249503.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal 1.0 gefunden. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei add_quiz.php der Komponente Quiz Handler. Dank Manipulation des Arguments Quiz Title/Quiz Description mit der Eingabe &lt;/title&gt;&lt;scRipt&gt;alert(x)&lt;/scRipt&gt; mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0190|2024-01-02T18:31:03.630Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 18:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>