<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Bug Finder -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/bug%20finder/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Bug Finder -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 13:23:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3831|2024-08-02T07:08:50.349Z -- bug%20finder -- finounce
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3831</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Bug Finder Finounce 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /user/ticket/create of the component Ticket Handler. The manipulation of the argument message leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The identifier VDB-235157 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in Bug Finder Finounce 1.0 gefunden. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei /user/ticket/create der Komponente Ticket Handler. Durch Beeinflussen des Arguments message mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3831|2024-08-02T07:08:50.349Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 15:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3834|2024-08-02T07:08:50.234Z -- bug%20finder -- ex-rate
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3834</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Bug Finder EX-RATE 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /user/ticket/create of the component Ticket Handler. The manipulation of the argument message leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-235160. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in Bug Finder EX-RATE 1.0 ausgemacht. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei /user/ticket/create der Komponente Ticket Handler. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments message mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3834|2024-08-02T07:08:50.234Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 17:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3796|2024-08-02T07:08:50.184Z -- bug%20finder -- foody%20friend
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3796</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Bug Finder Foody Friend 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /user/profile of the component Profile Picture Handler. The manipulation of the argument profile_picture leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-235064. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine problematische Schwachstelle wurde in Bug Finder Foody Friend 1.0 entdeckt. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei /user/profile der Komponente Profile Picture Handler. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments profile_picture mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3796|2024-08-02T07:08:50.184Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 21:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3829|2024-08-02T07:08:50.500Z -- bug%20finder -- icogenie
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3829</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Bug Finder ICOGenie 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /user/ticket/create of the component Support Ticket Handler. The manipulation of the argument message leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. VDB-235150 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Bug Finder ICOGenie 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei /user/ticket/create der Komponente Support Ticket Handler. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments message mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3829|2024-08-02T07:08:50.500Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3827|2024-08-02T07:08:50.577Z -- bug%20finder -- listplace%20directory%20listing%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3827</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Bug Finder Listplace Directory Listing Platform 3.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /listplace/user/ticket/create of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument message leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-235148. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Bug Finder Listplace Directory Listing Platform 3.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei /listplace/user/ticket/create der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Dank Manipulation des Arguments message mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3827|2024-08-02T07:08:50.577Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 09:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3833|2024-08-02T07:08:50.661Z -- bug%20finder -- montage
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3833</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Bug Finder Montage 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /user/ticket/create of the component Ticket Handler. The manipulation of the argument message leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-235159. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Bug Finder Montage 1.0 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei /user/ticket/create der Komponente Ticket Handler. Dank Manipulation des Arguments message mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3833|2024-08-02T07:08:50.661Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 16:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3835|2024-08-02T07:08:50.508Z -- bug%20finder -- minestack
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3835</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Bug Finder MineStack 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /user/ticket/create of the component Ticket Handler. The manipulation of the argument message leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The identifier VDB-235161 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Bug Finder MineStack 1.0 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei /user/ticket/create der Komponente Ticket Handler. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments message mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3835|2024-08-02T07:08:50.508Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 17:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3794|2024-08-02T07:08:50.159Z -- bug%20finder -- chaincity%20real%20estate%20investment%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3794</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Bug Finder ChainCity Real Estate Investment Platform 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /chaincity/user/ticket/create of the component New Ticket Handler. The manipulation of the argument subject leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. VDB-235062 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in Bug Finder ChainCity Real Estate Investment Platform 1.0 entdeckt. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei /chaincity/user/ticket/create der Komponente New Ticket Handler. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments subject mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3794|2024-08-02T07:08:50.159Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 20:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3832|2024-08-02T07:08:50.660Z -- bug%20finder -- wedding%20wonders
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3832</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Bug Finder Wedding Wonders 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /user/ticket/create of the component Ticket Handler. The manipulation of the argument message leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. VDB-235158 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in Bug Finder Wedding Wonders 1.0 ausgemacht. Dabei betrifft es einen unbekannter Codeteil der Datei /user/ticket/create der Komponente Ticket Handler. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments message mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3832|2024-08-02T07:08:50.660Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 15:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3795|2024-08-02T07:08:50.116Z -- bug%20finder -- chaincity%20real%20estate%20investment%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3795</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Bug Finder ChainCity Real Estate Investment Platform 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /property of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument name leads to sql injection. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-235063. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Bug Finder ChainCity Real Estate Investment Platform 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle entdeckt. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei /property der Komponente GET Parameter Handler. Durch Manipulation des Arguments name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3795|2024-08-02T07:08:50.116Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 20:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3828|2024-08-02T07:08:50.237Z -- bug%20finder -- listplace%20directory%20listing%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3828</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Bug Finder Listplace Directory Listing Platform 3.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /listplace/user/coverPhotoUpdate of the component Photo Handler. The manipulation of the argument user_cover_photo leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The identifier VDB-235149 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Bug Finder Listplace Directory Listing Platform 3.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei /listplace/user/coverPhotoUpdate der Komponente Photo Handler. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments user_cover_photo mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3828|2024-08-02T07:08:50.237Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 10:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3830|2024-08-02T07:08:50.471Z -- bug%20finder -- sass%20biller
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3830</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Bug Finder SASS BILLER 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /company/store. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-235151. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Bug Finder SASS BILLER 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei /company/store. Durch Manipulation des Arguments name mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3830|2024-08-02T07:08:50.471Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 14:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
