<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Bug Finder -- Listplace Directory Listing Platform</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/bug%20finder/listplace%20directory%20listing%20platform.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Bug Finder -- Listplace Directory Listing Platform</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 09:23:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3828|2024-08-02T07:08:50.237Z -- bug%20finder -- listplace%20directory%20listing%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3828</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Bug Finder Listplace Directory Listing Platform 3.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /listplace/user/coverPhotoUpdate of the component Photo Handler. The manipulation of the argument user_cover_photo leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The identifier VDB-235149 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Bug Finder Listplace Directory Listing Platform 3.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei /listplace/user/coverPhotoUpdate der Komponente Photo Handler. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments user_cover_photo mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3828|2024-08-02T07:08:50.237Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 10:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3827|2024-08-02T07:08:50.577Z -- bug%20finder -- listplace%20directory%20listing%20platform
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3827</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Bug Finder Listplace Directory Listing Platform 3.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /listplace/user/ticket/create of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument message leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-235148. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Bug Finder Listplace Directory Listing Platform 3.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist ein unbekannter Prozess der Datei /listplace/user/ticket/create der Komponente HTTP POST Request Handler. Dank Manipulation des Arguments message mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3827|2024-08-02T07:08:50.577Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 09:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
