<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for rogierlankhorst -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/rogierlankhorst/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for rogierlankhorst -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 21:54:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-1592|2024-03-02T06:46:19.551Z -- rogierlankhorst -- Complianz – GDPR/CCPA Cookie Consent
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1592</link><description>The Complianz – GDPR/CCPA Cookie Consent plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 6.5.6. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the process_delete function in class-DNSMPD.php. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete GDPR data requests via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1592|2024-03-02T06:46:19.551Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 06:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1894|2024-03-13T15:27:26.563Z -- rogierlankhorst -- Burst Statistics – Privacy-Friendly Analytics for WordPress
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1894</link><description>The Burst Statistics – Privacy-Friendly Analytics for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'burst_total_pageviews_count' custom meta field in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.6.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. Note that this exploit only functions if the victim has the 'Show Toolbar when viewing site' option enabled in their profile.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1894|2024-03-13T15:27:26.563Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:27:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0405|2024-01-17T04:32:16.771Z -- rogierlankhorst -- Burst Statistics – Privacy-Friendly Analytics for WordPress
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0405</link><description>The Burst Statistics – Privacy-Friendly Analytics for WordPress plugin, version 1.5.3, is vulnerable to Post-Authenticated SQL Injection via multiple JSON parameters in the /wp-json/burst/v1/data/compare endpoint. Affected parameters include 'browser', 'device', 'page_id', 'page_url', 'platform', and 'referrer'. This vulnerability arises due to insufficient escaping of user-supplied parameters and the lack of adequate preparation in SQL queries. As a result, authenticated attackers with editor access or higher can append additional SQL queries into existing ones, potentially leading to unauthorized access to sensitive information from the database.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0405|2024-01-17T04:32:16.771Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 04:32:16 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>