<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for pterodactyl -- panel</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/pterodactyl/panel.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for pterodactyl -- panel</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 22:23:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-49762|2024-10-24T21:39:24.986Z -- pterodactyl -- panel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49762</link>
      <description>Pterodactyl is a free, open-source game server management panel. When a user disables two-factor authentication via the Panel, a `DELETE` request with their current password in a query parameter will be sent.  While query parameters are encrypted when using TLS, many webservers (including ones officially documented for use with Pterodactyl) will log query parameters in plain-text, storing a user's password in plain text. Prior to version 1.11.8, if a malicious user obtains access to these logs they could potentially authenticate against a user's account; assuming they are able to discover the account's email address or username separately. This problem has been patched in version 1.11.8. There are no workarounds at this time. There is not a direct vulnerability within the software as it relates to logs generated by intermediate components such as web servers or Layer 7 proxies. Updating to `v1.11.8` or adding the linked patch manually are the only ways to avoid this problem. As this vulnerability relates to historical logging of sensitive data, users who have ever disabled 2FA on a Panel (self-hosted or operated by a company) should change their passwords and consider enabling 2FA if it was left disabled. While it's unlikely that their account swill be compromised by this vulnerability, it's not impossible. Panel administrators should consider clearing any access logs that may contain sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-49762|2024-10-24T21:39:24.986Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 21:39:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34067|2024-08-02T02:42:59.886Z -- pterodactyl -- panel</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34067</link>
      <description>Pterodactyl is a free, open-source game server management panel built with PHP, React, and Go. Importing a malicious egg or gaining access to wings instance could lead to cross site scripting (XSS) on the panel, which could be used to gain an administrator account on the panel. Specifically, the following things are impacted: Egg Docker images and Egg variables: Name, Environment variable, Default value, Description, Validation rules. Additionally, certain fields would reflect malicious input, but it would require the user knowingly entering such input to have an impact. To iterate, this would require an administrator to perform actions and can't be triggered by a normal panel user. This issue has has been addressed in version 1.11.6 and users are advised to upgrade. No workaround is available other than updating to the latest version of the panel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34067|2024-08-02T02:42:59.886Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 17:38:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34067|2024-06-06T17:59:27.038Z -- pterodactyl -- panel</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-34067</link>
      <description>Pterodactyl is a free, open-source game server management panel built with PHP, React, and Go. Importing a malicious egg or gaining access to wings instance could lead to cross site scripting (XSS) on the panel, which could be used to gain an administrator account on the panel. Specifically, the following things are impacted: Egg Docker images and Egg variables: Name, Environment variable, Default value, Description, Validation rules. Additionally, certain fields would reflect malicious input, but it would require the user knowingly entering such input to have an impact. To iterate, this would require an administrator to perform actions and can't be triggered by a normal panel user. This issue has has been addressed in version 1.11.6 and users are advised to upgrade. No workaround is available other than updating to the latest version of the panel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34067|2024-06-06T17:59:27.038Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 17:38:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
