<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for pterodactyl -- wings</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/pterodactyl/wings.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for pterodactyl -- wings</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 16:28:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-27102|2024-03-13T20:28:07.637Z -- pterodactyl -- wings
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27102</link><description>Wings is the server control plane for Pterodactyl Panel. This vulnerability impacts anyone running the affected versions of Wings. The vulnerability can potentially be used to access files and directories on the host system. The full scope of impact is exactly unknown, but reading files outside of a server's base directory (sandbox root) is possible. In order to use this exploit, an attacker must have an existing "server" allocated and controlled by Wings. Details on the exploitation of this vulnerability are embargoed until March 27th, 2024 at 18:00 UTC. In order to mitigate this vulnerability, a full rewrite of the entire server filesystem was necessary. Because of this, the size of the patch is massive, however effort was made to reduce the amount of breaking changes. Users are advised to update to version 1.11.9. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27102|2024-03-13T20:28:07.637Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 20:28:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34066|2024-05-03T17:42:12.412Z -- pterodactyl -- wings
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-34066</link><description>Pterodactyl wings is the server control plane for Pterodactyl Panel. If the Wings token is leaked either by viewing the node configuration or posting it accidentally somewhere, an attacker can use it to gain arbitrary file write and read access on the node the token is associated to. This issue has been addressed in version 1.11.12 and users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade may enable the `ignore_panel_config_updates` option as a workaround.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34066|2024-05-03T17:42:12.412Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 17:42:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34068|2024-05-03T17:34:16.318Z -- pterodactyl -- wings
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-34068</link><description>Pterodactyl wings is the server control plane for Pterodactyl Panel. An authenticated user who has access to a game server is able to bypass the previously implemented access control (GHSA-6rg3-8h8x-5xfv) that prevents accessing internal endpoints of the node hosting Wings in the pull endpoint. This would allow malicious users to potentially access resources on local networks that would otherwise be inaccessible. This issue has been addressed in version 1.11.2 and users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade may enable the `api.disable_remote_download` option as a workaround. </description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34068|2024-05-03T17:34:16.318Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 17:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>