<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for itsourcecode -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/itsourcecode/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for itsourcecode -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 19:19:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5636|2024-06-05T00:31:03.782Z -- itsourcecode -- bakery%20online%20ordering%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5636</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Bakery Online Ordering System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file report/index.php. The manipulation of the argument procduct leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-267092.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in itsourcecode Bakery Online Ordering System 1.0 ausgemacht. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei report/index.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments procduct mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5636|2024-06-05T00:31:03.782Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5392|2024-05-27T01:00:04.713Z -- itsourcecode -- online%20student%20enrollment%20system</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5392</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Online Student Enrollment System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file editSubject.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-266306 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in itsourcecode Online Student Enrollment System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei editSubject.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5392|2024-05-27T01:00:04.713Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 01:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
