<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for itsourcecode -- Gym Management System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/itsourcecode/gym%20management%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for itsourcecode -- Gym Management System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 17:22:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6652|2024-07-25T16:30:47.159Z -- itsourcecode -- gym%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6652</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Gym Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file manage_member.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-271059.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in itsourcecode Gym Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei manage_member.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6652|2024-07-25T16:30:47.159Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6041|2024-06-17T13:58:57.888Z -- itsourcecode -- gym%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6041</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Gym Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file manage_user.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-268765 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In itsourcecode Gym Management System 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei manage_user.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6041|2024-06-17T13:58:57.888Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 23:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6652|2024-07-10T23:00:06.798Z -- itsourcecode -- gym%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6652</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Gym Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file manage_member.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-271059.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in itsourcecode Gym Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei manage_member.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6652|2024-07-10T23:00:06.798Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
