<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for itsourcecode -- Tailoring Management System</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/itsourcecode/tailoring%20management%20system.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for itsourcecode -- Tailoring Management System</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 15:23:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8220|2024-08-28T14:02:24.499Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8220</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file staffedit.php. The manipulation of the argument id/stafftype/address/fullname/phonenumber/salary leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.
In itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei staffedit.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments id/stafftype/address/fullname/phonenumber/salary mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8220|2024-08-28T14:02:24.499Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 22:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8171|2024-08-26T15:39:50.636Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8171</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file staffcatedit.php. The manipulation of the argument title leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.
In itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei staffcatedit.php. Dank der Manipulation des Arguments title mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8171|2024-08-26T15:39:50.636Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 15:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7680|2024-08-11T22:00:07.007Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7680</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /incedit.php?id=4. The manipulation of the argument id/inccat/desc/date/amount leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei /incedit.php?id=4. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments id/inccat/desc/date/amount mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7680|2024-08-11T22:00:07.007Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 22:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7506|2024-08-06T04:31:05.937Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7506</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /setlogo.php. The manipulation of the argument bgimg leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273649 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei /setlogo.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments bgimg mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7506|2024-08-06T04:31:05.937Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 04:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7455|2024-08-04T11:31:04.327Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7455</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file partedit.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273549 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 gefunden. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei partedit.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7455|2024-08-04T11:31:04.327Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 11:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7081|2024-07-26T19:33:51.380Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7081</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file expcatadd.php. The manipulation of the argument title leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272366 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei expcatadd.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments title mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7081|2024-07-26T19:33:51.380Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 21:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6970|2024-07-23T16:10:43.860Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6970</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /staffcatadd.php. The manipulation of the argument title leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272124.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei /staffcatadd.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments title mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6970|2024-07-23T16:10:43.860Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 04:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6970|2024-07-22T04:00:05.170Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6970</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /staffcatadd.php. The manipulation of the argument title leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272124.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei /staffcatadd.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments title mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6970|2024-07-22T04:00:05.170Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 04:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6733|2024-07-16T13:25:14.119Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6733</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file templateedit.php. The manipulation of the argument id/title/msg leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-271454 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei templateedit.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments id/title/msg mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6733|2024-07-16T13:25:14.119Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 23:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6728|2024-07-15T13:48:58.781Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6728</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file typeedit.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-271401 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei typeedit.php. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6728|2024-07-15T13:48:58.781Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 00:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6109|2024-07-02T19:53:03.466Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6109</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file addmeasurement.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-268855.
In itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei addmeasurement.php. Durch Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6109|2024-07-02T19:53:03.466Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 11:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6372|2024-07-01T15:34:39.702Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6372</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file customeradd.php. The manipulation of the argument fullname/address/phonenumber/sex/email/city/comment leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-269805 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 gefunden. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei customeradd.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments fullname/address/phonenumber/sex/email/city/comment mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6372|2024-07-01T15:34:39.702Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 13:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6195|2024-06-20T19:49:46.865Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6195</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file orderadd.php. The manipulation of the argument customer leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-269167.
In itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei orderadd.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments customer mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6195|2024-06-20T19:49:46.865Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 16:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6109|2024-06-18T11:31:03.956Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6109</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file addmeasurement.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-268855.
In itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei addmeasurement.php. Durch Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6109|2024-06-18T11:31:03.956Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 11:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6195|2024-06-20T16:00:05.278Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6195</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file orderadd.php. The manipulation of the argument customer leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-269167.
In itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei orderadd.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments customer mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6195|2024-06-20T16:00:05.278Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 16:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6194|2024-06-20T15:31:06.025Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6194</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file editmeasurement.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-269166 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei editmeasurement.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6194|2024-06-20T15:31:06.025Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 15:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6372|2024-06-27T13:00:06.217Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6372</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file customeradd.php. The manipulation of the argument fullname/address/phonenumber/sex/email/city/comment leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-269805 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 gefunden. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei customeradd.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments fullname/address/phonenumber/sex/email/city/comment mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6372|2024-06-27T13:00:06.217Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 13:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6194|2024-07-01T18:36:00.887Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6194</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file editmeasurement.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-269166 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei editmeasurement.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6194|2024-07-01T18:36:00.887Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 15:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6734|2024-07-15T12:34:28.129Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6734</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file templateadd.php. The manipulation of the argument title/msg leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-271455.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei templateadd.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments title/msg mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6734|2024-07-15T12:34:28.129Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 23:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6735|2024-07-15T20:24:48.501Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6735</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file setgeneral.php. The manipulation of the argument sitename/email/mobile/sms/currency leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-271456.
In itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei setgeneral.php. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments sitename/email/mobile/sms/currency mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6735|2024-07-15T20:24:48.501Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 00:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6953|2024-07-21T12:00:06.475Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6953</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file sms.php. The manipulation of the argument customer leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272075.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 gefunden. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei sms.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments customer mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6953|2024-07-21T12:00:06.475Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 12:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6953|2024-07-23T14:54:18.572Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6953</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file sms.php. The manipulation of the argument customer leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272075.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 gefunden. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei sms.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments customer mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6953|2024-07-23T14:54:18.572Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 12:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7081|2024-07-24T21:00:06.563Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7081</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file expcatadd.php. The manipulation of the argument title leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272366 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei expcatadd.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments title mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7081|2024-07-24T21:00:06.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 21:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6953|2024-08-01T21:45:38.350Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6953</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file sms.php. The manipulation of the argument customer leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272075.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 gefunden. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei sms.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments customer mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6953|2024-08-01T21:45:38.350Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 12:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7081|2024-08-01T21:52:30.602Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7081</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file expcatadd.php. The manipulation of the argument title leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-272366 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Es geht hierbei um eine nicht näher spezifizierte Funktion der Datei expcatadd.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments title mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7081|2024-08-01T21:52:30.602Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 21:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6728|2024-08-01T21:41:04.555Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6728</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file typeedit.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-271401 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei typeedit.php. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6728|2024-08-01T21:41:04.555Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 00:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6195|2024-08-01T21:33:05.091Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6195</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file orderadd.php. The manipulation of the argument customer leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-269167.
In itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei orderadd.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments customer mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6195|2024-08-01T21:33:05.091Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 16:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6194|2024-08-01T21:33:05.154Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6194</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file editmeasurement.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-269166 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hiervon betroffen ist ein unbekannter Codeblock der Datei editmeasurement.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6194|2024-08-01T21:33:05.154Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 15:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6735|2024-08-01T21:41:04.576Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6735</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file setgeneral.php. The manipulation of the argument sitename/email/mobile/sms/currency leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-271456.
In itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Das betrifft eine unbekannte Funktionalität der Datei setgeneral.php. Durch das Beeinflussen des Arguments sitename/email/mobile/sms/currency mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6735|2024-08-01T21:41:04.576Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 00:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6372|2024-08-01T21:33:05.456Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6372</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file customeradd.php. The manipulation of the argument fullname/address/phonenumber/sex/email/city/comment leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-269805 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 gefunden. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei customeradd.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments fullname/address/phonenumber/sex/email/city/comment mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6372|2024-08-01T21:33:05.456Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 13:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6733|2024-08-01T21:41:04.607Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6733</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file templateedit.php. The manipulation of the argument id/title/msg leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-271454 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei templateedit.php. Durch das Manipulieren des Arguments id/title/msg mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6733|2024-08-01T21:41:04.607Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 23:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6970|2024-08-01T21:45:38.403Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6970</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /staffcatadd.php. The manipulation of the argument title leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-272124.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 entdeckt. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei /staffcatadd.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments title mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6970|2024-08-01T21:45:38.403Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 04:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6109|2024-08-01T21:33:04.477Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6109</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file addmeasurement.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-268855.
In itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Es geht um eine nicht näher bekannte Funktion der Datei addmeasurement.php. Durch Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6109|2024-08-01T21:33:04.477Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 11:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6734|2024-08-01T21:41:04.575Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6734</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file templateadd.php. The manipulation of the argument title/msg leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-271455.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es betrifft eine unbekannte Funktion der Datei templateadd.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments title/msg mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6734|2024-08-01T21:41:04.575Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 23:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7455|2024-08-05T10:20:36.661Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7455</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file partedit.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273549 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 gefunden. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Datei partedit.php. Dank Manipulation des Arguments id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7455|2024-08-05T10:20:36.661Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 11:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7506|2024-08-06T16:13:18.907Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7506</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /setlogo.php. The manipulation of the argument bgimg leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273649 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei /setlogo.php. Mit der Manipulation des Arguments bgimg mit unbekannten Daten kann eine unrestricted upload-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7506|2024-08-06T16:13:18.907Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 04:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7680|2024-08-12T12:34:32.203Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7680</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /incedit.php?id=4. The manipulation of the argument id/inccat/desc/date/amount leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht dabei um eine nicht klar definierte Funktion der Datei /incedit.php?id=4. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments id/inccat/desc/date/amount mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-7680|2024-08-12T12:34:32.203Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 22:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8220|2024-08-27T22:00:05.443Z -- itsourcecode -- tailoring%20management%20system</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8220</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file staffedit.php. The manipulation of the argument id/stafftype/address/fullname/phonenumber/salary leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.
In itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Hierbei betrifft es unbekannten Programmcode der Datei staffedit.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments id/stafftype/address/fullname/phonenumber/salary mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8220|2024-08-27T22:00:05.443Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 22:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
