<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Rockwell Automation -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/rockwell%20automation/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Rockwell Automation -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 08:24:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3752|2024-08-03T01:20:57.729Z -- rockwell%20automation -- compactlogix%205480
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3752</link>
      <description>An unauthorized user could use a specially crafted sequence of Ethernet/IP messages, combined with heavy traffic 
loading to cause a denial-of-service condition in Rockwell Automation Logix controllers resulting in a major non-recoverable fault. If the target device becomes unavailable, a user would have to clear the fault and redownload 
the user project file to bring the device back online and continue normal operation.


</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3752|2024-08-03T01:20:57.729Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 22:23:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3156|2024-08-03T01:00:10.643Z -- rockwell%20automation -- studio%205000%20logix%20emulate
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3156</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in Rockwell Automation Studio 5000 Logix Emulate software.  Users are granted elevated permissions on certain product services when the software is installed. Due to 
this misconfiguration, a malicious user could potentially achieve remote code execution on the targeted software.

 


</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3156|2024-08-03T01:00:10.643Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 18:17:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-1797|2024-08-03T00:16:59.935Z -- rockwell%20automation -- compactlogix%205380%20controllers
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1797</link>
      <description>A malformed Class 3 common industrial protocol message with a cached connection can cause a denial-of-service condition in Rockwell Automation Logix Controllers, resulting in a major nonrecoverable fault. If the target device becomes unavailable, a user would have to clear the fault and redownload the user project file to bring the device back online.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-1797|2024-08-03T00:16:59.935Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 19:04:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2463|2024-08-03T00:39:07.530Z -- rockwell%20automation -- isagraf%20workbench
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2463</link>
      <description>Rockwell Automation ISaGRAF Workbench software versions 6.0 through 6.6.9 are affected by a Path Traversal vulnerability. A crafted malicious .7z exchange file may allow an attacker to gain the privileges of the ISaGRAF Workbench software when opened. If the software is running at the SYSTEM level, then the attacker will gain admin level privileges. User interaction is required for this exploit to be successful.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2463|2024-08-03T00:39:07.530Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 17:24:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2179|2024-08-03T00:32:07.933Z -- rockwell%20automation -- micrologix%201400
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2179</link>
      <description>The X-Frame-Options header in Rockwell Automation MicroLogix 1100/1400 Versions 21.007 and prior is not configured in the HTTP response, which could allow clickjacking attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2179|2024-08-03T00:32:07.933Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2465|2024-08-03T00:39:07.767Z -- rockwell%20automation -- isagraf%20workbench
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2465</link>
      <description>Rockwell Automation ISaGRAF Workbench software versions 6.0 through 6.6.9 are affected by a Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability. ISaGRAF Workbench does not limit the objects that can be deserialized. This vulnerability allows attackers to craft a malicious serialized object that, if opened by a local user in ISaGRAF Workbench, may result in remote code execution. This vulnerability requires user interaction to be successfully exploited.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2465|2024-08-03T00:39:07.767Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 17:25:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3166|2024-08-03T01:00:10.526Z -- rockwell%20automation -- micrologix%201100
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3166</link>
      <description>
Rockwell Automation was made aware that the webservers of the Micrologix 1100 and 1400 controllers contain a vulnerability that may lead to a denial-of-service condition. The security vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker with network access to the affected systems by sending TCP packets to webserver and closing it abruptly which would cause a denial-of-service condition for the web server application on the device

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3166|2024-08-03T01:00:10.526Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 19:59:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-2464|2024-08-03T00:39:07.551Z -- rockwell%20automation -- isagraf%20workbench
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2464</link>
      <description>Rockwell Automation ISaGRAF Workbench software versions 6.0 through 6.6.9 are affected by a Path Traversal vulnerability. Crafted malicious files can allow an attacker to traverse the file system when opened by ISaGRAF Workbench. If successfully exploited, an attacker could overwrite existing files and create additional files with the same permissions of the ISaGRAF Workbench software. User interaction is required for this exploit to be successful.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-2464|2024-08-03T00:39:07.551Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 17:24:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3157|2024-08-03T01:00:10.589Z -- rockwell%20automation -- compactlogix%205370
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3157</link>
      <description>
A vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation controllers that allows a malformed CIP request to cause a major non-recoverable fault (MNRF) and a denial-of-service condition (DOS). 

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3157|2024-08-03T01:00:10.589Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 20:35:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21913|2024-08-02T20:03:36.781Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21913</link>
      <description>A heap-based memory buffer overflow vulnerability in Rockwell Automation Arena Simulation software could potentially allow a malicious user to insert unauthorized code into the software by overstepping the memory boundaries, which triggers an access violation.  Once inside, the threat actor can run harmful code on the system. This affects the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the product. To trigger this, the user would unwittingly need to open a malicious file shared by the threat actor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21913|2024-08-02T20:03:36.781Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 15:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21914|2024-08-01T22:35:34.456Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20view%20me</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21914</link>
      <description>A vulnerability exists in the affected product that allows a malicious user to restart the Rockwell Automation PanelView™ Plus 7 terminal remotely without security protections. If the vulnerability is exploited, it could lead to the loss of view or control of the PanelView™ product.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21914|2024-08-01T22:35:34.456Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 21:27:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21912|2024-08-01T22:35:34.363Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21912</link>
      <description>An arbitrary code execution vulnerability in Rockwell Automation Arena Simulation could let a malicious user insert unauthorized code into the software. This is done by writing beyond the designated memory area, which causes an access violation. Once inside, the threat actor can run harmful code on the system. This affects the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the product. To trigger this, the user would unwittingly need to open a malicious file shared by the threat actor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21912|2024-08-01T22:35:34.363Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 15:34:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21919|2024-08-01T22:35:34.615Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21919</link>
      <description>An uninitialized pointer in Rockwell Automation Arena Simulation software could potentially allow a malicious user to insert unauthorized code to the software by leveraging the pointer after it is properly.  Once inside, the threat actor can run harmful code on the system. This affects the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the product. To trigger this, the user would unwittingly need to open a malicious file shared by the threat actor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21919|2024-08-01T22:35:34.615Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 15:46:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21920|2024-08-01T22:35:34.484Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21920</link>
      <description>A memory buffer vulnerability in Rockwell Automation Arena Simulation could potentially let a threat actor read beyond the intended memory boundaries. This could reveal sensitive information and even cause the application to crash, resulting in a denial-of-service condition. To trigger this, the user would unwittingly need to open a malicious file shared by the threat actor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21920|2024-08-01T22:35:34.484Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 15:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21915|2024-08-01T22:35:34.363Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20service%20platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21915</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® Service Platform (FTSP). If exploited, a malicious user with basic user group privileges could potentially sign into the software and receive FTSP Administrator Group privileges. A threat actor could potentially read and modify sensitive data, delete data and render the FTSP system unavailable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21915|2024-08-01T22:35:34.363Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 18:20:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21913|2024-08-01T22:35:34.486Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21913</link>
      <description>A heap-based memory buffer overflow vulnerability in Rockwell Automation Arena Simulation software could potentially allow a malicious user to insert unauthorized code into the software by overstepping the memory boundaries, which triggers an access violation.  Once inside, the threat actor can run harmful code on the system. This affects the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the product. To trigger this, the user would unwittingly need to open a malicious file shared by the threat actor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21913|2024-08-01T22:35:34.486Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 15:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21918|2024-08-01T22:35:34.549Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21918</link>
      <description>A memory buffer vulnerability in Rockwell Automation Arena Simulation software could potentially allow a malicious user to insert unauthorized code to the software by corrupting the memory and triggering an access violation.  Once inside, the threat actor can run harmful code on the system. This affects the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the product. To trigger this, the user would unwittingly need to open a malicious file shared by the threat actor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21918|2024-08-01T22:35:34.549Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 15:44:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4609|2024-08-01T20:47:41.128Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20view%20se</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4609</link>
      <description>A vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® View SE Datalog function that could allow a threat actor to inject a malicious SQL statement if the SQL database has no authentication in place or if legitimate credentials were stolen. If exploited, the attack could result in information exposure, revealing sensitive information. Additionally, a threat actor could potentially modify and delete the data in a remote database. An attack would only affect the HMI design time, not runtime.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4609|2024-08-01T20:47:41.128Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 15:13:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3640|2024-08-01T20:20:00.578Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20remote%20access%E2%84%A2</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3640</link>
      <description>An unquoted executable path exists in the Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® Remote Access™ possibly resulting in remote code execution if exploited. While running the FTRA installer package, the executable path is not properly quoted, which could allow a threat actor to enter a malicious executable and run it as a System user. A threat actor needs admin privileges to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3640|2024-08-01T20:20:00.578Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 15:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3493|2024-08-01T20:12:07.675Z -- rockwell%20automation -- controllogix%205580</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3493</link>
      <description>A specific malformed fragmented packet type (fragmented packets may be generated automatically by devices that send large amounts of data) can cause a major nonrecoverable fault (MNRF) Rockwell Automation's ControlLogix 5580, Guard Logix 5580, CompactLogix 5380, and 1756-EN4TR. If exploited, the affected product will become unavailable and require a manual restart to recover it. Additionally, an MNRF could result in a loss of view and/or control of connected devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3493|2024-08-01T20:12:07.675Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 21:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6242|2024-08-01T18:01:01.646Z -- rockwell%20automation -- controllogix%C2%AE%205580%20%281756-l8z%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6242</link>
      <description>A vulnerability exists in Rockwell Automation affected products that allows a threat actor to bypass the Trusted® Slot feature in a ControlLogix® controller. If exploited on any affected module in a 1756 chassis, a threat actor could potentially execute CIP commands that modify user projects and/or device configuration on a Logix controller in the chassis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6242|2024-08-01T18:01:01.646Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 15:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6435|2024-07-19T17:34:25.778Z -- rockwell%20automation -- pavilion8%C2%AE</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6435</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the affected products which could allow a malicious user with basic privileges to access functions which should only be available to users with administrative level privileges. If exploited, an attacker could read sensitive data, and create users. For example, a malicious user with basic privileges could perform critical functions such as creating a user with elevated privileges and reading sensitive information in the “views” section.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6435|2024-07-19T17:34:25.778Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 13:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6326|2024-07-16T17:50:07.305Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20system%20services%20%28installed%20via%20ftpm%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6326</link>
      <description>An exposure of sensitive information vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® System Service. A malicious user could exploit this vulnerability by starting a back-up or restore process, which temporarily exposes private keys, passwords, pre-shared keys, and database folders when they are temporarily copied to an interim folder. This vulnerability is due to the lack of explicit permissions set on the backup folder. If private keys are obtained by a malicious user, they could impersonate resources on the secured network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6326|2024-07-16T17:50:07.305Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 16:51:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6089|2024-07-16T17:10:21.810Z -- rockwell%20automation -- 5015%20-%20aenftxt</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6089</link>
      <description>An input validation vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation 5015 - AENFTXT when a manipulated PTP packet is sent, causing the secondary adapter to result in a major nonrecoverable fault. If exploited, a power cycle is required to recover the product.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6089|2024-07-16T17:10:21.810Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 17:10:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6435|2024-07-16T13:00:42.859Z -- rockwell%20automation -- pavilion8%C2%AE</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6435</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the affected products which could allow a malicious user with basic privileges to access functions which should only be available to users with administrative level privileges. If exploited, an attacker could read sensitive data, and create users. For example, a malicious user with basic privileges could perform critical functions such as creating a user with elevated privileges and reading sensitive information in the “views” section.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6435|2024-07-16T13:00:42.859Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 13:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5988|2024-06-26T17:05:32.829Z -- rockwell%20automation -- thinmanager%C2%AE%20thinserver%E2%84%A2</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5988</link>
      <description>Due to an improper input validation, an unauthenticated threat actor can send a malicious message to invoke a local or remote executable and cause a remote code execution condition on the Rockwell Automation ThinManager® ThinServer™.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5988|2024-06-26T17:05:32.829Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 15:53:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5989|2024-06-26T17:06:20.972Z -- rockwell%20automation -- thinmanager%C2%AE%20thinserver%E2%84%A2</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5989</link>
      <description>Due to an improper input validation, an unauthenticated threat actor can send a malicious message to invoke SQL injection into the program and cause a remote code execution condition on the Rockwell Automation ThinManager® ThinServer™.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5989|2024-06-26T17:06:20.972Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 16:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5990|2024-06-26T17:01:59.269Z -- rockwell%20automation -- thinmanager%C2%AE%20thinserver%E2%84%A2</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5990</link>
      <description>Due to an improper input validation, an unauthenticated threat actor can send a malicious message to a monitor thread within Rockwell Automation ThinServer™ and cause a denial-of-service condition on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5990|2024-06-26T17:01:59.269Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 16:11:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5990|2024-06-25T16:11:01.407Z -- rockwell%20automation -- thinmanager%C2%AE%20thinserver%E2%84%A2</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5990</link>
      <description>Due to an improper input validation, an unauthenticated threat actor can send a malicious message to a monitor thread within Rockwell Automation ThinServer™ and cause a denial-of-service condition on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5990|2024-06-25T16:11:01.407Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 16:11:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37368|2024-06-18T16:33:16.826Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20view%20se</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37368</link>
      <description>A user authentication vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® View SE. The vulnerability allows a user from a remote system with FTView to send a packet to the customer’s server to view an HMI project. Due to the lack of proper authentication, this action is allowed without proper authentication verification.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37368|2024-06-18T16:33:16.826Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5659|2024-06-15T20:23:20.243Z -- rockwell%20automation -- controllogix%C2%AE%205580</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5659</link>
      <description>Rockwell Automation was made aware of a vulnerability that causes all affected controllers on the same network to result in a major nonrecoverable fault(MNRF/Assert). This vulnerability could be exploited by sending abnormal packets to the mDNS port. If exploited, the availability of the device would be compromised.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5659|2024-06-15T20:23:20.243Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 16:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5659|2024-06-14T16:42:20.699Z -- rockwell%20automation -- controllogix%C2%AE%205580</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5659</link>
      <description>Rockwell Automation was made aware of a vulnerability that causes all affected controllers on the same network to result in a major nonrecoverable fault(MNRF/Assert). This vulnerability could be exploited by sending abnormal packets to the mDNS port. If exploited, the availability of the device would be compromised.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5659|2024-06-14T16:42:20.699Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 16:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37369|2024-06-14T16:50:20.187Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20view%20se</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37369</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the affected product. The vulnerability allows low-privilege users to edit scripts, bypassing Access Control Lists, and potentially gaining further access within the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37369|2024-06-14T16:50:20.187Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 16:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4609|2024-06-04T17:53:40.228Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20view%20se</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4609</link>
      <description>A vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® View SE Datalog function that could allow a threat actor to inject a malicious SQL statement if the SQL database has no authentication in place or if legitimate credentials were stolen. If exploited, the attack could result in information exposure, revealing sensitive information. Additionally, a threat actor could potentially modify and delete the data in a remote database. An attack would only affect the HMI design time, not runtime.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4609|2024-06-04T17:53:40.228Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 15:13:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21920|2024-03-26T15:48:59.735Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21920</link>
      <description>A memory buffer vulnerability in Rockwell Automation Arena Simulation could potentially let a threat actor read beyond the intended memory boundaries. This could reveal sensitive information and even cause the application to crash, resulting in a denial-of-service condition. To trigger this, the user would unwittingly need to open a malicious file shared by the threat actor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21920|2024-03-26T15:48:59.735Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 15:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21915|2024-02-16T18:20:43.862Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20service%20platform</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21915</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® Service Platform (FTSP). If exploited, a malicious user with basic user group privileges could potentially sign into the software and receive FTSP Administrator Group privileges. A threat actor could potentially read and modify sensitive data, delete data and render the FTSP system unavailable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21915|2024-02-16T18:20:43.862Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 18:20:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21919|2024-03-26T15:46:38.129Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21919</link>
      <description>An uninitialized pointer in Rockwell Automation Arena Simulation software could potentially allow a malicious user to insert unauthorized code to the software by leveraging the pointer after it is properly.  Once inside, the threat actor can run harmful code on the system. This affects the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the product. To trigger this, the user would unwittingly need to open a malicious file shared by the threat actor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21919|2024-03-26T15:46:38.129Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 15:46:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21918|2024-03-26T15:44:33.835Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21918</link>
      <description>A memory buffer vulnerability in Rockwell Automation Arena Simulation software could potentially allow a malicious user to insert unauthorized code to the software by corrupting the memory and triggering an access violation.  Once inside, the threat actor can run harmful code on the system. This affects the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the product. To trigger this, the user would unwittingly need to open a malicious file shared by the threat actor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21918|2024-03-26T15:44:33.835Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 15:44:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21914|2024-03-25T21:27:18.975Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20view%20me</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21914</link>
      <description>A vulnerability exists in the affected product that allows a malicious user to restart the Rockwell Automation PanelView™ Plus 7 terminal remotely without security protections. If the vulnerability is exploited, it could lead to the loss of view or control of the PanelView™ product.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21914|2024-03-25T21:27:18.975Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 21:27:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21913|2024-03-26T15:38:23.962Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21913</link>
      <description>A heap-based memory buffer overflow vulnerability in Rockwell Automation Arena Simulation software could potentially allow a malicious user to insert unauthorized code into the software by overstepping the memory boundaries, which triggers an access violation.  Once inside, the threat actor can run harmful code on the system. This affects the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the product. To trigger this, the user would unwittingly need to open a malicious file shared by the threat actor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21913|2024-03-26T15:38:23.962Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 15:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21912|2024-03-26T15:34:35.837Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21912</link>
      <description>An arbitrary code execution vulnerability in Rockwell Automation Arena Simulation could let a malicious user insert unauthorized code into the software. This is done by writing beyond the designated memory area, which causes an access violation. Once inside, the threat actor can run harmful code on the system. This affects the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the product. To trigger this, the user would unwittingly need to open a malicious file shared by the threat actor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21912|2024-03-26T15:34:35.837Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 15:34:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3493|2024-04-15T21:29:33.269Z -- rockwell%20automation -- controllogix%205580</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3493</link>
      <description>A specific malformed fragmented packet type (fragmented packets may be generated automatically by devices that send large amounts of data) can cause a major nonrecoverable fault (MNRF) Rockwell Automation's ControlLogix 5580, Guard Logix 5580, CompactLogix 5380, and 1756-EN4TR. If exploited, the affected product will become unavailable and require a manual restart to recover it. Additionally, an MNRF could result in a loss of view and/or control of connected devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3493|2024-04-15T21:29:33.269Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 21:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3640|2024-06-04T17:31:28.680Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20remote%20access%E2%84%A2</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3640</link>
      <description>An unquoted executable path exists in the Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® Remote Access™ possibly resulting in remote code execution if exploited. While running the FTRA installer package, the executable path is not properly quoted, which could allow a threat actor to enter a malicious executable and run it as a System user. A threat actor needs admin privileges to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3640|2024-06-04T17:31:28.680Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 15:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2425|2024-06-04T17:30:25.436Z -- rockwell%20automation -- powerflex%C2%AE%20527</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2425</link>
      <description>A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation PowerFlex® 527 due to improper input validation in the device. If exploited, the web server will crash and need a manual restart to recover it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2425|2024-06-04T17:30:25.436Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 20:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2424|2024-06-04T17:29:58.099Z -- rockwell%20automation -- 5015-aenftxt</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2424</link>
      <description>An input validation vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation 5015-AENFTXT that causes the secondary adapter to result in a major nonrecoverable fault (MNRF) when malicious input is entered. If exploited, the availability of the device will be impacted, and a manual restart is required. Additionally, a malformed PTP packet is needed to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2424|2024-06-04T17:29:58.099Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 21:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2427|2024-03-25T20:20:41.295Z -- rockwell%20automation -- powerflex%C2%AE%20527</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2427</link>
      <description>A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation PowerFlex® 527 due to improper traffic throttling in the device. If multiple data packets are sent to the device repeatedly the device will crash and require a manual restart to recover.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2427|2024-03-25T20:20:41.295Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 20:20:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2426|2024-03-25T20:18:33.240Z -- rockwell%20automation -- powerflex%C2%AE%20527</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2426</link>
      <description>A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation PowerFlex® 527 due to improper input validation in the device. If exploited, a disruption in the CIP communication will occur and a manual restart will be required by the user to recover it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2426|2024-03-25T20:18:33.240Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 20:17:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2929|2024-03-26T15:56:31.967Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2929</link>
      <description>A memory corruption vulnerability in Rockwell Automation Arena Simulation software could potentially allow a malicious user to insert unauthorized code to the software by corrupting the memory triggering an access violation.  Once inside, the threat actor can run harmful code on the system. This affects the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the product. To trigger this, the user would unwittingly need to open a malicious file shared by the threat actor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2929|2024-03-26T15:56:31.967Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 15:56:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37368|2024-06-14T14:30:53.422Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20view%20se</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37368</link>
      <description>A user authentication vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® View SE. The vulnerability allows a user from a remote system with FTView to send a packet to the customer’s server to view an HMI project. Due to the lack of proper authentication, this action is allowed without proper authentication verification.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37368|2024-06-14T14:30:53.422Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37367|2024-06-14T14:17:54.951Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20view%20se</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37367</link>
      <description>A user authentication vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® View SE v12. The vulnerability allows a user from a remote system with FTView to send a packet to the customer’s server to view an HMI project.  This action is allowed without proper authentication verification.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37367|2024-06-14T14:17:54.951Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:17:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37369|2024-06-14T18:13:03.399Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20view%20se</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37369</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the affected product. The vulnerability allows low-privilege users to edit scripts, bypassing Access Control Lists, and potentially gaining further access within the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37369|2024-06-14T18:13:03.399Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 16:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37367|2024-06-17T15:37:26.533Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20view%20se</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37367</link>
      <description>A user authentication vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® View SE v12. The vulnerability allows a user from a remote system with FTView to send a packet to the customer’s server to view an HMI project.  This action is allowed without proper authentication verification.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37367|2024-06-17T15:37:26.533Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:17:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5989|2024-06-25T16:01:39.103Z -- rockwell%20automation -- thinmanager%C2%AE%20thinserver%E2%84%A2</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5989</link>
      <description>Due to an improper input validation, an unauthenticated threat actor can send a malicious message to invoke SQL injection into the program and cause a remote code execution condition on the Rockwell Automation ThinManager® ThinServer™.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5989|2024-06-25T16:01:39.103Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 16:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5988|2024-06-25T16:03:05.556Z -- rockwell%20automation -- thinmanager%C2%AE%20thinserver%E2%84%A2</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5988</link>
      <description>Due to an improper input validation, an unauthenticated threat actor can send a malicious message to invoke a local or remote executable and cause a remote code execution condition on the Rockwell Automation ThinManager® ThinServer™.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5988|2024-06-25T16:03:05.556Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 15:53:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5989|2024-06-25T17:44:59.233Z -- rockwell%20automation -- thinmanager%C2%AE%20thinserver%E2%84%A2</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5989</link>
      <description>Due to an improper input validation, an unauthenticated threat actor can send a malicious message to invoke SQL injection into the program and cause a remote code execution condition on the Rockwell Automation ThinManager® ThinServer™.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5989|2024-06-25T17:44:59.233Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 16:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6326|2024-07-16T16:51:18.320Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20system%20services%20%28installed%20via%20ftpm%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6326</link>
      <description>An exposure of sensitive information vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® System Service. A malicious user could exploit this vulnerability by starting a back-up or restore process, which temporarily exposes private keys, passwords, pre-shared keys, and database folders when they are temporarily copied to an interim folder. This vulnerability is due to the lack of explicit permissions set on the backup folder. If private keys are obtained by a malicious user, they could impersonate resources on the secured network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6326|2024-07-16T16:51:18.320Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 16:51:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6325|2024-07-16T16:43:44.494Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20system%20services%20%28installed%20via%20ftpm%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6325</link>
      <description>The v6.40 release of Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® Policy Manager CVE-2021-22681 https://www.rockwellautomation.com/en-us/trust-center/security-advisories/advisory.PN1550.html  and  CVE-2022-1161 https://www.rockwellautomation.com/en-us/trust-center/security-advisories/advisory.PN1585.html  by implementing CIP security and did not update to the versions of the software CVE-2022-1161 https://www.rockwellautomation.com/en-us/trust-center/security-advisories/advisory.PN1585.html  and  CVE-2022-1161. https://www.rockwellautomation.com/en-us/trust-center/security-advisories/advisory.PN1585.html</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6325|2024-07-16T16:43:44.494Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 16:43:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6089|2024-07-17T14:57:56.133Z -- rockwell%20automation -- 5015%20-%20aenftxt</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6089</link>
      <description>An input validation vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation 5015 - AENFTXT when a manipulated PTP packet is sent, causing the secondary adapter to result in a major nonrecoverable fault. If exploited, a power cycle is required to recover the product.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6089|2024-07-17T14:57:56.133Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 17:10:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6325|2024-07-17T15:47:32.018Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20system%20services%20%28installed%20via%20ftpm%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6325</link>
      <description>The v6.40 release of Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® Policy Manager CVE-2021-22681 https://www.rockwellautomation.com/en-us/trust-center/security-advisories/advisory.PN1550.html  and  CVE-2022-1161 https://www.rockwellautomation.com/en-us/trust-center/security-advisories/advisory.PN1585.html  by implementing CIP security and did not update to the versions of the software CVE-2022-1161 https://www.rockwellautomation.com/en-us/trust-center/security-advisories/advisory.PN1585.html  and  CVE-2022-1161. https://www.rockwellautomation.com/en-us/trust-center/security-advisories/advisory.PN1585.html</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6325|2024-07-17T15:47:32.018Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 16:43:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6242|2024-08-01T15:15:32.220Z -- rockwell%20automation -- controllogix%C2%AE%205580%20%281756-l8z%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6242</link>
      <description>A vulnerability exists in Rockwell Automation affected products that allows a threat actor to bypass the Trusted® Slot feature in a ControlLogix® controller. If exploited on any affected module in a 1756 chassis, a threat actor could potentially execute CIP commands that modify user projects and/or device configuration on a Logix controller in the chassis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6242|2024-08-01T15:15:32.220Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 15:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2426|2024-08-01T19:11:53.564Z -- rockwell%20automation -- powerflex%C2%AE%20527</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2426</link>
      <description>A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation PowerFlex® 527 due to improper input validation in the device. If exploited, a disruption in the CIP communication will occur and a manual restart will be required by the user to recover it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2426|2024-08-01T19:11:53.564Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 20:17:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2424|2024-08-01T19:11:53.521Z -- rockwell%20automation -- 5015-aenftxt</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2424</link>
      <description>An input validation vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation 5015-AENFTXT that causes the secondary adapter to result in a major nonrecoverable fault (MNRF) when malicious input is entered. If exploited, the availability of the device will be impacted, and a manual restart is required. Additionally, a malformed PTP packet is needed to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2424|2024-08-01T19:11:53.521Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 21:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2929|2024-08-01T19:32:41.647Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2929</link>
      <description>A memory corruption vulnerability in Rockwell Automation Arena Simulation software could potentially allow a malicious user to insert unauthorized code to the software by corrupting the memory triggering an access violation.  Once inside, the threat actor can run harmful code on the system. This affects the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the product. To trigger this, the user would unwittingly need to open a malicious file shared by the threat actor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2929|2024-08-01T19:32:41.647Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 15:56:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2427|2024-08-01T19:11:53.547Z -- rockwell%20automation -- powerflex%C2%AE%20527</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2427</link>
      <description>A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation PowerFlex® 527 due to improper traffic throttling in the device. If multiple data packets are sent to the device repeatedly the device will crash and require a manual restart to recover.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2427|2024-08-01T19:11:53.547Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 20:20:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2425|2024-08-01T19:11:53.614Z -- rockwell%20automation -- powerflex%C2%AE%20527</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2425</link>
      <description>A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation PowerFlex® 527 due to improper input validation in the device. If exploited, the web server will crash and need a manual restart to recover it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2425|2024-08-01T19:11:53.614Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 20:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5989|2024-08-01T21:25:03.287Z -- rockwell%20automation -- thinmanager%C2%AE%20thinserver%E2%84%A2</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5989</link>
      <description>Due to an improper input validation, an unauthenticated threat actor can send a malicious message to invoke SQL injection into the program and cause a remote code execution condition on the Rockwell Automation ThinManager® ThinServer™.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5989|2024-08-01T21:25:03.287Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 16:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6325|2024-08-01T21:33:05.423Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20system%20services%20%28installed%20via%20ftpm%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6325</link>
      <description>The v6.40 release of Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® Policy Manager CVE-2021-22681 https://www.rockwellautomation.com/en-us/trust-center/security-advisories/advisory.PN1550.html  and  CVE-2022-1161 https://www.rockwellautomation.com/en-us/trust-center/security-advisories/advisory.PN1585.html  by implementing CIP security and did not update to the versions of the software CVE-2022-1161 https://www.rockwellautomation.com/en-us/trust-center/security-advisories/advisory.PN1585.html  and  CVE-2022-1161. https://www.rockwellautomation.com/en-us/trust-center/security-advisories/advisory.PN1585.html</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6325|2024-08-01T21:33:05.423Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 16:43:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5988|2024-08-01T21:25:03.324Z -- rockwell%20automation -- thinmanager%C2%AE%20thinserver%E2%84%A2</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5988</link>
      <description>Due to an improper input validation, an unauthenticated threat actor can send a malicious message to invoke a local or remote executable and cause a remote code execution condition on the Rockwell Automation ThinManager® ThinServer™.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5988|2024-08-01T21:25:03.324Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 15:53:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5659|2024-08-01T21:18:06.865Z -- rockwell%20automation -- controllogix%C2%AE%205580</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5659</link>
      <description>Rockwell Automation was made aware of a vulnerability that causes all affected controllers on the same network to result in a major nonrecoverable fault(MNRF/Assert). This vulnerability could be exploited by sending abnormal packets to the mDNS port. If exploited, the availability of the device would be compromised.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5659|2024-08-01T21:18:06.865Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 16:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6435|2024-08-01T21:41:03.349Z -- rockwell%20automation -- pavilion8%C2%AE</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6435</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the affected products which could allow a malicious user with basic privileges to access functions which should only be available to users with administrative level privileges. If exploited, an attacker could read sensitive data, and create users. For example, a malicious user with basic privileges could perform critical functions such as creating a user with elevated privileges and reading sensitive information in the “views” section.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6435|2024-08-01T21:41:03.349Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 13:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6089|2024-08-01T21:33:04.327Z -- rockwell%20automation -- 5015%20-%20aenftxt</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6089</link>
      <description>An input validation vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation 5015 - AENFTXT when a manipulated PTP packet is sent, causing the secondary adapter to result in a major nonrecoverable fault. If exploited, a power cycle is required to recover the product.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6089|2024-08-01T21:33:04.327Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 17:10:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5990|2024-08-01T21:25:03.210Z -- rockwell%20automation -- thinmanager%C2%AE%20thinserver%E2%84%A2</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5990</link>
      <description>Due to an improper input validation, an unauthenticated threat actor can send a malicious message to a monitor thread within Rockwell Automation ThinServer™ and cause a denial-of-service condition on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5990|2024-08-01T21:25:03.210Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 16:11:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6326|2024-08-01T21:33:05.450Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20system%20services%20%28installed%20via%20ftpm%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6326</link>
      <description>An exposure of sensitive information vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® System Service. A malicious user could exploit this vulnerability by starting a back-up or restore process, which temporarily exposes private keys, passwords, pre-shared keys, and database folders when they are temporarily copied to an interim folder. This vulnerability is due to the lack of explicit permissions set on the backup folder. If private keys are obtained by a malicious user, they could impersonate resources on the secured network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6326|2024-08-01T21:33:05.450Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 16:51:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37368|2024-08-02T03:50:56.219Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20view%20se</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37368</link>
      <description>A user authentication vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® View SE. The vulnerability allows a user from a remote system with FTView to send a packet to the customer’s server to view an HMI project. Due to the lack of proper authentication, this action is allowed without proper authentication verification.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37368|2024-08-02T03:50:56.219Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37369|2024-08-02T03:50:56.129Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20view%20se</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37369</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the affected product. The vulnerability allows low-privilege users to edit scripts, bypassing Access Control Lists, and potentially gaining further access within the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37369|2024-08-02T03:50:56.129Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 16:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37367|2024-08-02T03:50:56.151Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20view%20se</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37367</link>
      <description>A user authentication vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® View SE v12. The vulnerability allows a user from a remote system with FTView to send a packet to the customer’s server to view an HMI project.  This action is allowed without proper authentication verification.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37367|2024-08-02T03:50:56.151Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:17:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21919|2024-08-02T17:55:57.699Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21919</link>
      <description>An uninitialized pointer in Rockwell Automation Arena Simulation software could potentially allow a malicious user to insert unauthorized code to the software by leveraging the pointer after it is properly.  Once inside, the threat actor can run harmful code on the system. This affects the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the product. To trigger this, the user would unwittingly need to open a malicious file shared by the threat actor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21919|2024-08-02T17:55:57.699Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 15:46:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
