<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Rockwell Automation -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/rockwell%20automation/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Rockwell Automation -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 17:22:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0755|2024-08-02T05:24:34.155Z -- rockwell%20automation -- kepserver%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0755</link>
      <description>
The affected products are vulnerable to an improper validation of array index, which could allow an attacker to crash the server and remotely execute arbitrary code.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0755|2024-08-02T05:24:34.155Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 21:23:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29026|2024-08-02T14:00:14.665Z -- rockwell%20automation -- armorstart%20st
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29026</link>
      <description>
A cross site scripting vulnerability was discovered in Rockwell Automation's ArmorStart ST product 

that could potentially allow a malicious user with admin privileges and network access to view user data and modify the web interface. Additionally, a malicious user could potentially cause interruptions to the availability of the web page.



</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29026|2024-08-02T14:00:14.665Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 17:47:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27856|2024-08-02T12:23:30.592Z -- rockwell%20automation -- thinmanager%20thinserver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27856</link>
      <description>


In affected versions, path traversal exists when processing a message of type 8

 in Rockwell Automation's ThinManager ThinServer. 

An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit this vulnerability to download arbitrary files on the disk drive where ThinServer.exe is installed.

 

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27856|2024-08-02T12:23:30.592Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 23:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29463|2024-08-02T14:07:46.424Z -- rockwell%20automation -- pavilion8
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29463</link>
      <description>
The JMX Console within the Rockwell Automation Pavilion8 is exposed to application users and does not require authentication. If exploited, a malicious user could potentially retrieve other application users’ session data and or log users out of their session.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29463|2024-08-02T14:07:46.424Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 16:42:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2262|2024-08-02T06:19:14.686Z -- rockwell%20automation -- 1756-en2t%20series%20a%2C%20b%2C%20c
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2262</link>
      <description>


A buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation select 1756-EN* communication devices. If exploited, a threat actor could potentially leverage this vulnerability to perform a remote code execution. To exploit this vulnerability, a threat actor would have to send a maliciously crafted CIP request to device.



</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2262|2024-08-02T06:19:14.686Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 15:20:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5909|2024-08-02T08:14:24.693Z -- rockwell%20automation -- kepserver%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5909</link>
      <description>








KEPServerEX does not properly validate certificates from clients which may allow unauthenticated users to connect.







</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5909|2024-08-02T08:14:24.693Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 22:05:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29025|2024-08-02T14:00:14.643Z -- rockwell%20automation -- armorstart%20st
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29025</link>
      <description>
A cross site scripting vulnerability was discovered in Rockwell Automation's ArmorStart ST product 

that could potentially allow a malicious user with admin privileges and network access to view user data and modify the web interface. Additionally, a malicious user could potentially cause interruptions to the availability of the web page.



</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29025|2024-08-02T14:00:14.643Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 17:45:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2423|2024-08-02T06:19:15.092Z -- rockwell%20automation -- armor%20powerflex
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2423</link>
      <description>
A vulnerability was discovered in the Rockwell Automation Armor PowerFlex device when the product sends communications to the local event log. Threat actors could exploit this vulnerability by sending an influx of network commands, causing the product to generate an influx of event log traffic at a high rate. If exploited, the product would stop normal operations and self-reset creating a denial-of-service condition. The error code would need to be cleared prior to resuming normal operations.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2423|2024-08-02T06:19:15.092Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 14:24:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2072|2024-08-02T06:12:19.922Z -- rockwell%20automation -- powermonitor%201000
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2072</link>
      <description>The Rockwell Automation PowerMonitor 1000 contains stored cross-site scripting vulnerabilities within the web page of the product.  The vulnerable pages do not require privileges to access and can be injected with code by an attacker which could be used to leverage an attack on an authenticated user resulting in remote code execution and potentially the complete loss of confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the product.


</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2072|2024-08-02T06:12:19.922Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 13:05:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0754|2024-08-02T05:24:34.053Z -- rockwell%20automation -- kepserver%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0754</link>
      <description>
The affected products are vulnerable to an integer
overflow or wraparound, which could  allow an attacker to crash the server and remotely
execute arbitrary code.















</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0754|2024-08-02T05:24:34.053Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 21:27:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29031|2024-08-02T14:00:14.782Z -- rockwell%20automation -- armorstart%20st
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29031</link>
      <description>
A cross site scripting vulnerability was discovered in Rockwell Automation's ArmorStart ST product that could potentially allow a malicious user to view and modify sensitive data or make the web page unavailable. User interaction, such as a phishing attack, is required for successful exploitation of this vulnerability.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29031|2024-08-02T14:00:14.782Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 17:38:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2914|2024-08-02T06:41:03.723Z -- rockwell%20automation -- thinmanager%20thinserver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2914</link>
      <description>The Rockwell Automation Thinmanager Thinserver is impacted by an improper input validation vulnerability, an integer overflow condition exists in the affected products. When the ThinManager processes incoming messages, a read access violation occurs and terminates the process. A malicious user could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted synchronization protocol message and causing a denial of service condition in the software.  </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2914|2024-08-02T06:41:03.723Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 15:01:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29024|2024-08-02T14:00:14.659Z -- rockwell%20automation -- armorstart%20st
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29024</link>
      <description>
A cross site scripting vulnerability was discovered in Rockwell Automation's ArmorStart ST product 

A cross site scripting vulnerability was discovered that could potentially allow a malicious user to view and modify sensitive data or make the web page unavailable. User interaction, such as a phishing attack, is required for successful exploitation of this vulnerability.



</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29024|2024-08-02T14:00:14.659Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 17:42:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2639|2024-08-02T06:26:09.863Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%20system%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2639</link>
      <description>The underlying feedback mechanism of 

Rockwell Automation's FactoryTalk System Services that transfers the FactoryTalk Policy Manager rules to relevant devices on the network does not verify that the origin of the communication is from a legitimate local client device.  This may allow a threat actor to craft a malicious website that, when visited, will send a malicious script that can connect to the local WebSocket endpoint and wait for events as if it was a valid client device. If successfully exploited, this would allow a threat actor to receive information including whether FactoryTalk Policy Manager is installed and potentially the entire security policy. 


</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2639|2024-08-02T06:26:09.863Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 20:28:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2913|2024-08-02T06:41:03.654Z -- rockwell%20automation -- thinmanager%20thinserver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2913</link>
      <description>
An executable used in Rockwell Automation ThinManager ThinServer can be configured to enable an API feature in the HTTPS Server Settings. This feature is disabled by default. When the API is enabled and handling requests, a path traversal vulnerability exists that allows a remote actor to leverage the privileges of the server’s file system and read arbitrary files stored in it. A malicious user could exploit this vulnerability by executing a path that contains manipulating variables.


</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2913|2024-08-02T06:41:03.654Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 19:52:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2443|2024-08-02T06:26:09.005Z -- rockwell%20automation -- thinmanager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2443</link>
      <description>
Rockwell Automation ThinManager product allows the use of medium strength ciphers.  If the client requests an insecure cipher, a malicious actor could potentially decrypt traffic sent between the client and server API.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2443|2024-08-02T06:26:09.005Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 18:08:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29462|2024-08-02T14:07:46.223Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29462</link>
      <description>An arbitrary code execution vulnerability contained in Rockwell Automation's Arena Simulation software was reported that could potentially allow a malicious user to commit unauthorized arbitrary code to the software by using a memory buffer overflow in the heap. 

 potentially resulting in a complete loss of confidentiality, integrity, and availability.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29462|2024-08-02T14:07:46.223Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 13:27:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2638|2024-08-02T06:26:09.833Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%20system%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2638</link>
      <description>
Rockwell Automation's FactoryTalk System Services does not verify that a backup configuration archive is password protected.

 

Improper authorization in FTSSBackupRestore.exe may lead to the loading of malicious configuration archives.  This vulnerability may allow a local, authenticated non-admin user to craft a malicious backup archive, without password protection, that will be loaded by FactoryTalk System Services as a valid backup when a restore procedure takes places. User interaction is required for this vulnerability to be successfully exploited.


</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2638|2024-08-02T06:26:09.833Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 20:25:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2071|2024-08-02T06:12:19.927Z -- rockwell%20automation -- fa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2071</link>
      <description>
Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk View Machine Edition on the PanelView Plus, improperly verifies user’s input, which allows unauthenticated attacker to achieve remote code executed via crafted malicious packets.  The device has the functionality, through a CIP class, to execute exported functions from libraries.  There is a routine that restricts it to execute specific functions from two dynamic link library files.  By using a CIP class, an attacker can upload a self-made library to the device which allows the attacker to bypass the security check and execute any code written in the function.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2071|2024-08-02T06:12:19.927Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 13:12:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27855|2024-08-02T12:23:29.345Z -- rockwell%20automation -- thinmanager%20thinserver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27855</link>
      <description>
In affected versions, a path traversal exists when processing a message in Rockwell Automation's ThinManager ThinServer. An unauthenticated remote attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability to upload arbitrary files to any directory on the disk drive where ThinServer.exe is installed. The attacker could overwrite existing executable files with attacker-controlled, malicious contents, potentially causing remote code execution. 

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27855|2024-08-02T12:23:29.345Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 23:48:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3596|2024-08-02T07:01:56.685Z -- rockwell%20automation -- 1756-en4tr%20series%20a
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3596</link>
      <description>
Where this vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation 1756-EN4* Ethernet/IP communication products, it could allow a malicious user to cause a denial of service by asserting the target system through maliciously crafted CIP messages.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3596|2024-08-02T07:01:56.685Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 12:51:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3595|2024-08-02T07:01:57.031Z -- rockwell%20automation -- 1756-en2t%20series%20a%2C%20b%2C%20c
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3595</link>
      <description>
Where this vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation 1756 EN2* and 1756 EN3* ControlLogix communication products, it could allow a malicious user to perform remote code execution with persistence on the target system through maliciously crafted CIP messages. This includes the ability to modify, deny, and exfiltrate data passing through the device.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3595|2024-08-02T07:01:57.031Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 12:37:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2778|2024-08-02T06:33:05.706Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%20transaction%20manager
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2778</link>
      <description>
A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk Transaction Manager. This vulnerability can be exploited by sending a modified packet to port 400. If exploited, the application could potentially crash or experience a high CPU or memory usage condition, causing intermittent application functionality issues. The application would need to be restarted to recover from the DoS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2778|2024-08-02T06:33:05.706Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 20:35:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2746|2024-08-02T06:33:05.556Z -- rockwell%20automation -- enhanced%20him
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2746</link>
      <description>The Rockwell Automation Enhanced HIM software contains 

an API that the application uses that is not protected sufficiently and uses incorrect Cross-Origin Resource Sharing (CORS) settings and, as a result, is vulnerable to a Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) attack. To exploit this vulnerability, a malicious user would have to convince a user to click on an untrusted link through a social engineering attack or successfully perform a Cross Site Scripting Attack (XSS). Exploitation of a CSRF could potentially lead to sensitive information disclosure and full remote access to the affected products.




</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2746|2024-08-02T06:33:05.556Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 13:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29030|2024-08-02T14:00:14.600Z -- rockwell%20automation -- armorstart%20st
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29030</link>
      <description>
A cross site scripting vulnerability was discovered in Rockwell Automation's ArmorStart ST product that could potentially allow a malicious user to view and modify sensitive data or make the web page unavailable. User interaction, such as a phishing attack, is required for successful exploitation of this vulnerability.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29030|2024-08-02T14:00:14.600Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 17:41:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29461|2024-08-02T14:07:46.307Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29461</link>
      <description>An arbitrary code execution vulnerability contained in Rockwell Automation's Arena Simulation software was reported that could potentially allow a malicious user to commit unauthorized arbitrary code to the software by using a memory buffer overflow in the heap. 

 potentially resulting in a complete loss of confidentiality, integrity, and availability.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29461|2024-08-02T14:07:46.307Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 13:26:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27854|2024-08-02T12:23:30.381Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27854</link>
      <description>
An arbitrary code execution vulnerability was reported to Rockwell Automation in Arena Simulation that could potentially allow a malicious user to commit unauthorized arbitrary code to the software by using a memory buffer overflow.  The threat-actor could then execute malicious code on the system affecting the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the product.  The user would need to open a malicious file provided to them by the attacker for the code to execute.


</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27854|2024-08-02T12:23:30.381Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 18:51:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1834|2024-08-02T06:05:26.633Z -- rockwell%20automation -- kinetix%205500%20ethernet%2Fip%20servo%20drive
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1834</link>
      <description>
Rockwell Automation was made aware that Kinetix 5500 drives, manufactured between May 2022 and January 2023, and are running v7.13 may have the telnet and FTP ports open by default.  This could potentially allow attackers unauthorized access to the device through the open ports.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1834|2024-08-02T06:05:26.633Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 18:01:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29028|2024-08-02T14:00:14.630Z -- rockwell%20automation -- armorstart%20st
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29028</link>
      <description>
A cross site scripting vulnerability was discovered in Rockwell Automation's ArmorStart ST product 

that could potentially allow a malicious user with admin privileges and network access to view user data and modify the web interface. Additionally, a malicious user could potentially cause interruptions to the availability of the web page.



</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29028|2024-08-02T14:00:14.630Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 17:50:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2263|2024-08-02T06:19:14.499Z -- rockwell%20automation -- kinetix%205700%20dc%20bus%20power%20supply%20series%20a
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2263</link>
      <description>
The Rockwell Automation Kinetix 5700 DC Bus Power Supply Series A is vulnerable to CIP fuzzing.  The new ENIP connections cannot be established if impacted by this vulnerability,  which prohibits operational capabilities of the device resulting in a denial-of-service attack.


</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2263|2024-08-02T06:19:14.499Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 15:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2915|2024-08-02T06:41:03.650Z -- rockwell%20automation -- thinmanager%20thinserver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2915</link>
      <description>The Rockwell Automation Thinmanager Thinserver is impacted by an improper input validation vulnerability, Due to improper input validation, a path traversal vulnerability exists when the ThinManager software processes a certain function. If exploited, an unauthenticated remote threat actor can delete arbitrary files with system privileges.   A malicious user could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specifically crafted synchronization protocol message resulting in a denial-of-service condition.  </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2915|2024-08-02T06:41:03.650Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 15:05:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29464|2024-08-02T14:07:46.248Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%20linx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29464</link>
      <description>
FactoryTalk Linx, in the Rockwell Automation PanelView Plus, allows an unauthenticated threat actor to read data from memory via crafted malicious packets. Sending a size larger than the buffer size results in leakage of data from memory resulting in an information disclosure. If the size is large enough, it causes communications over the common industrial protocol to become unresponsive to any type of packet, resulting in a denial-of-service to FactoryTalk Linx over the common industrial protocol.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29464|2024-08-02T14:07:46.248Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 12:57:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29029|2024-08-02T14:00:14.631Z -- rockwell%20automation -- armorstart%20st
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29029</link>
      <description>
A cross site scripting vulnerability was discovered in Rockwell Automation's ArmorStart ST product 

that could potentially allow a malicious user with admin privileges and network access to view user data and modify the web interface. Additionally, a malicious user could potentially cause interruptions to the availability of the web page.



</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29029|2024-08-02T14:00:14.631Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 17:51:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29460|2024-08-02T14:07:46.291Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29460</link>
      <description>An arbitrary code execution vulnerability contained in Rockwell Automation's Arena Simulation software was reported that could potentially allow a malicious user to commit unauthorized arbitrary code to the software by using a memory buffer overflow potentially resulting in a complete loss of confidentiality, integrity, and availability.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29460|2024-08-02T14:07:46.291Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 13:19:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29023|2024-08-02T14:00:14.750Z -- rockwell%20automation -- armorstart%20st
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29023</link>
      <description>
A cross site scripting vulnerability was discovered in Rockwell Automation's ArmorStart ST product that could potentially allow a malicious user to view and modify sensitive data or make the web page unavailable. User interaction, such as a phishing attack, is required for successful exploitation of this vulnerability.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29023|2024-08-02T14:00:14.750Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 17:41:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27858|2024-08-02T12:23:30.373Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27858</link>
      <description>
Rockwell Automation Arena Simulation contains an arbitrary code execution vulnerability that could potentially allow a malicious user to commit unauthorized code to the software by using an uninitialized pointer in the application.  The threat-actor could then execute malicious code on the system affecting the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the product.  The user would need to open a malicious file provided to them by the attacker for the code to execute.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27858|2024-08-02T12:23:30.373Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 18:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2637|2024-08-02T06:26:09.908Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%20system%20services
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2637</link>
      <description>
Rockwell Automation's FactoryTalk System Services uses a hard-coded cryptographic key to generate administrator cookies.  Hard-coded cryptographic key may lead to privilege escalation.  This vulnerability may allow a local, authenticated non-admin user to generate an invalid administrator cookie giving them administrative privileges to the FactoryTalk Policy Manger database. This may allow the threat actor to make malicious changes to the database that will be deployed when a legitimate FactoryTalk Policy Manager user deploys a security policy model. User interaction is required for this vulnerability to be successfully exploited.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2637|2024-08-02T06:26:09.908Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 20:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-27857|2024-08-02T12:23:29.231Z -- rockwell%20automation -- thinmanager%20thinserver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27857</link>
      <description>
 In affected versions, a heap-based buffer over-read condition occurs when the message field indicates more data than is present in the message field



 in Rockwell Automation's ThinManager ThinServer.  An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit this vulnerability to crash ThinServer.exe due to a read access violation.



 

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-27857|2024-08-02T12:23:29.231Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 00:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0027|2024-08-02T04:54:32.559Z -- rockwell%20automation -- modbus%20tcp%20server%20add%20on%20instructions
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0027</link>
      <description>Rockwell Automation Modbus TCP Server AOI prior to 2.04.00 is vulnerable to an unauthorized user sending a malformed message that could cause the controller to respond with a copy of the most recent response to the last valid request. If exploited, an unauthorized user could read the connected device’s Modbus TCP Server AOI information.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0027|2024-08-02T04:54:32.559Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 16:52:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2444|2024-08-02T06:26:08.927Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%20vantagepoint
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2444</link>
      <description>
A cross site request forgery vulnerability exists in Rockwell Automation's FactoryTalk Vantagepoint. This vulnerability can be exploited in two ways. If an attacker sends a malicious link to a computer that is on the same domain as the FactoryTalk Vantagepoint server and a user clicks the link, the attacker could impersonate the legitimate user and send requests to the affected product.  Additionally, if an attacker sends an untrusted link to a computer that is not on the same domain as the server and a user opens the FactoryTalk Vantagepoint website, enters credentials for the FactoryTalk Vantagepoint server, and clicks on the malicious link a cross site request forgery attack would be successful as well.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2444|2024-08-02T06:26:08.927Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 18:12:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29027|2024-08-02T14:00:14.656Z -- rockwell%20automation -- armorstart%20st
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29027</link>
      <description>
A cross site scripting vulnerability was discovered in Rockwell Automation's ArmorStart ST product 

that could potentially allow a malicious user with admin privileges and network access to view user data and modify the web interface. Additionally, a malicious user could potentially cause interruptions to the availability of the web page.



</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29027|2024-08-02T14:00:14.656Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 17:47:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-29022|2024-08-02T14:00:14.779Z -- rockwell%20automation -- armorstart%20st
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29022</link>
      <description>
A cross site scripting vulnerability was discovered in Rockwell Automation's ArmorStart ST product 

that could potentially allow a malicious user with admin privileges and network access to view user data and modify the web interface. Additionally, a malicious user could potentially cause interruptions to the availability of the web page.



</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-29022|2024-08-02T14:00:14.779Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 17:51:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5908|2024-08-02T08:14:24.586Z -- rockwell%20automation -- kepserver%20enterprise
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5908</link>
      <description>




KEPServerEX is vulnerable to a buffer overflow which may allow an attacker to crash the product being accessed or leak information.




</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5908|2024-08-02T08:14:24.586Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 22:03:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2917|2024-08-02T06:41:04.162Z -- rockwell%20automation -- thinmanager%20thinserver
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2917</link>
      <description>The Rockwell Automation Thinmanager Thinserver is impacted by an improper input validation vulnerability.  Due to an improper input validation, a path traversal vulnerability exists, via the filename field, when the ThinManager processes a certain function. If exploited, an unauthenticated remote attacker can upload arbitrary files to any directory on the disk drive where ThinServer.exe is installed.  A malicious user could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted synchronization protocol message and potentially gain remote code execution abilities.

  </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2917|2024-08-02T06:41:04.162Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 15:10:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21914|2024-08-01T22:35:34.456Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20view%20me</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21914</link>
      <description>A vulnerability exists in the affected product that allows a malicious user to restart the Rockwell Automation PanelView™ Plus 7 terminal remotely without security protections. If the vulnerability is exploited, it could lead to the loss of view or control of the PanelView™ product.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21914|2024-08-01T22:35:34.456Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 21:27:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21912|2024-08-01T22:35:34.363Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21912</link>
      <description>An arbitrary code execution vulnerability in Rockwell Automation Arena Simulation could let a malicious user insert unauthorized code into the software. This is done by writing beyond the designated memory area, which causes an access violation. Once inside, the threat actor can run harmful code on the system. This affects the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the product. To trigger this, the user would unwittingly need to open a malicious file shared by the threat actor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21912|2024-08-01T22:35:34.363Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 15:34:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21919|2024-08-01T22:35:34.615Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21919</link>
      <description>An uninitialized pointer in Rockwell Automation Arena Simulation software could potentially allow a malicious user to insert unauthorized code to the software by leveraging the pointer after it is properly.  Once inside, the threat actor can run harmful code on the system. This affects the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the product. To trigger this, the user would unwittingly need to open a malicious file shared by the threat actor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21919|2024-08-01T22:35:34.615Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 15:46:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21920|2024-08-01T22:35:34.484Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21920</link>
      <description>A memory buffer vulnerability in Rockwell Automation Arena Simulation could potentially let a threat actor read beyond the intended memory boundaries. This could reveal sensitive information and even cause the application to crash, resulting in a denial-of-service condition. To trigger this, the user would unwittingly need to open a malicious file shared by the threat actor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21920|2024-08-01T22:35:34.484Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 15:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21915|2024-08-01T22:35:34.363Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20service%20platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21915</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® Service Platform (FTSP). If exploited, a malicious user with basic user group privileges could potentially sign into the software and receive FTSP Administrator Group privileges. A threat actor could potentially read and modify sensitive data, delete data and render the FTSP system unavailable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21915|2024-08-01T22:35:34.363Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 18:20:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21913|2024-08-01T22:35:34.486Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21913</link>
      <description>A heap-based memory buffer overflow vulnerability in Rockwell Automation Arena Simulation software could potentially allow a malicious user to insert unauthorized code into the software by overstepping the memory boundaries, which triggers an access violation.  Once inside, the threat actor can run harmful code on the system. This affects the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the product. To trigger this, the user would unwittingly need to open a malicious file shared by the threat actor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21913|2024-08-01T22:35:34.486Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 15:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21918|2024-08-01T22:35:34.549Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21918</link>
      <description>A memory buffer vulnerability in Rockwell Automation Arena Simulation software could potentially allow a malicious user to insert unauthorized code to the software by corrupting the memory and triggering an access violation.  Once inside, the threat actor can run harmful code on the system. This affects the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the product. To trigger this, the user would unwittingly need to open a malicious file shared by the threat actor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21918|2024-08-01T22:35:34.549Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 15:44:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4609|2024-08-01T20:47:41.128Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20view%20se</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4609</link>
      <description>A vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® View SE Datalog function that could allow a threat actor to inject a malicious SQL statement if the SQL database has no authentication in place or if legitimate credentials were stolen. If exploited, the attack could result in information exposure, revealing sensitive information. Additionally, a threat actor could potentially modify and delete the data in a remote database. An attack would only affect the HMI design time, not runtime.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4609|2024-08-01T20:47:41.128Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 15:13:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3640|2024-08-01T20:20:00.578Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20remote%20access%E2%84%A2</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3640</link>
      <description>An unquoted executable path exists in the Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® Remote Access™ possibly resulting in remote code execution if exploited. While running the FTRA installer package, the executable path is not properly quoted, which could allow a threat actor to enter a malicious executable and run it as a System user. A threat actor needs admin privileges to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3640|2024-08-01T20:20:00.578Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 15:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3493|2024-08-01T20:12:07.675Z -- rockwell%20automation -- controllogix%205580</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3493</link>
      <description>A specific malformed fragmented packet type (fragmented packets may be generated automatically by devices that send large amounts of data) can cause a major nonrecoverable fault (MNRF) Rockwell Automation's ControlLogix 5580, Guard Logix 5580, CompactLogix 5380, and 1756-EN4TR. If exploited, the affected product will become unavailable and require a manual restart to recover it. Additionally, an MNRF could result in a loss of view and/or control of connected devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3493|2024-08-01T20:12:07.675Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 21:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6242|2024-08-01T18:01:01.646Z -- rockwell%20automation -- controllogix%C2%AE%205580%20%281756-l8z%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6242</link>
      <description>A vulnerability exists in Rockwell Automation affected products that allows a threat actor to bypass the Trusted® Slot feature in a ControlLogix® controller. If exploited on any affected module in a 1756 chassis, a threat actor could potentially execute CIP commands that modify user projects and/or device configuration on a Logix controller in the chassis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6242|2024-08-01T18:01:01.646Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 15:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6435|2024-07-19T17:34:25.778Z -- rockwell%20automation -- pavilion8%C2%AE</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6435</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the affected products which could allow a malicious user with basic privileges to access functions which should only be available to users with administrative level privileges. If exploited, an attacker could read sensitive data, and create users. For example, a malicious user with basic privileges could perform critical functions such as creating a user with elevated privileges and reading sensitive information in the “views” section.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6435|2024-07-19T17:34:25.778Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 13:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6326|2024-07-16T17:50:07.305Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20system%20services%20%28installed%20via%20ftpm%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6326</link>
      <description>An exposure of sensitive information vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® System Service. A malicious user could exploit this vulnerability by starting a back-up or restore process, which temporarily exposes private keys, passwords, pre-shared keys, and database folders when they are temporarily copied to an interim folder. This vulnerability is due to the lack of explicit permissions set on the backup folder. If private keys are obtained by a malicious user, they could impersonate resources on the secured network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6326|2024-07-16T17:50:07.305Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 16:51:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6089|2024-07-16T17:10:21.810Z -- rockwell%20automation -- 5015%20-%20aenftxt</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6089</link>
      <description>An input validation vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation 5015 - AENFTXT when a manipulated PTP packet is sent, causing the secondary adapter to result in a major nonrecoverable fault. If exploited, a power cycle is required to recover the product.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6089|2024-07-16T17:10:21.810Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 17:10:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6435|2024-07-16T13:00:42.859Z -- rockwell%20automation -- pavilion8%C2%AE</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6435</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the affected products which could allow a malicious user with basic privileges to access functions which should only be available to users with administrative level privileges. If exploited, an attacker could read sensitive data, and create users. For example, a malicious user with basic privileges could perform critical functions such as creating a user with elevated privileges and reading sensitive information in the “views” section.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6435|2024-07-16T13:00:42.859Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 13:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5988|2024-06-26T17:05:32.829Z -- rockwell%20automation -- thinmanager%C2%AE%20thinserver%E2%84%A2</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5988</link>
      <description>Due to an improper input validation, an unauthenticated threat actor can send a malicious message to invoke a local or remote executable and cause a remote code execution condition on the Rockwell Automation ThinManager® ThinServer™.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5988|2024-06-26T17:05:32.829Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 15:53:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5989|2024-06-26T17:06:20.972Z -- rockwell%20automation -- thinmanager%C2%AE%20thinserver%E2%84%A2</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5989</link>
      <description>Due to an improper input validation, an unauthenticated threat actor can send a malicious message to invoke SQL injection into the program and cause a remote code execution condition on the Rockwell Automation ThinManager® ThinServer™.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5989|2024-06-26T17:06:20.972Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 16:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5990|2024-06-26T17:01:59.269Z -- rockwell%20automation -- thinmanager%C2%AE%20thinserver%E2%84%A2</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5990</link>
      <description>Due to an improper input validation, an unauthenticated threat actor can send a malicious message to a monitor thread within Rockwell Automation ThinServer™ and cause a denial-of-service condition on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5990|2024-06-26T17:01:59.269Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 16:11:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5990|2024-06-25T16:11:01.407Z -- rockwell%20automation -- thinmanager%C2%AE%20thinserver%E2%84%A2</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5990</link>
      <description>Due to an improper input validation, an unauthenticated threat actor can send a malicious message to a monitor thread within Rockwell Automation ThinServer™ and cause a denial-of-service condition on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5990|2024-06-25T16:11:01.407Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 16:11:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37368|2024-06-18T16:33:16.826Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20view%20se</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37368</link>
      <description>A user authentication vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® View SE. The vulnerability allows a user from a remote system with FTView to send a packet to the customer’s server to view an HMI project. Due to the lack of proper authentication, this action is allowed without proper authentication verification.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37368|2024-06-18T16:33:16.826Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5659|2024-06-15T20:23:20.243Z -- rockwell%20automation -- controllogix%C2%AE%205580</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5659</link>
      <description>Rockwell Automation was made aware of a vulnerability that causes all affected controllers on the same network to result in a major nonrecoverable fault(MNRF/Assert). This vulnerability could be exploited by sending abnormal packets to the mDNS port. If exploited, the availability of the device would be compromised.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5659|2024-06-15T20:23:20.243Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 16:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5659|2024-06-14T16:42:20.699Z -- rockwell%20automation -- controllogix%C2%AE%205580</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5659</link>
      <description>Rockwell Automation was made aware of a vulnerability that causes all affected controllers on the same network to result in a major nonrecoverable fault(MNRF/Assert). This vulnerability could be exploited by sending abnormal packets to the mDNS port. If exploited, the availability of the device would be compromised.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5659|2024-06-14T16:42:20.699Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 16:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37369|2024-06-14T16:50:20.187Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20view%20se</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37369</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the affected product. The vulnerability allows low-privilege users to edit scripts, bypassing Access Control Lists, and potentially gaining further access within the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37369|2024-06-14T16:50:20.187Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 16:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4609|2024-06-04T17:53:40.228Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20view%20se</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4609</link>
      <description>A vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® View SE Datalog function that could allow a threat actor to inject a malicious SQL statement if the SQL database has no authentication in place or if legitimate credentials were stolen. If exploited, the attack could result in information exposure, revealing sensitive information. Additionally, a threat actor could potentially modify and delete the data in a remote database. An attack would only affect the HMI design time, not runtime.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4609|2024-06-04T17:53:40.228Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 15:13:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21920|2024-03-26T15:48:59.735Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21920</link>
      <description>A memory buffer vulnerability in Rockwell Automation Arena Simulation could potentially let a threat actor read beyond the intended memory boundaries. This could reveal sensitive information and even cause the application to crash, resulting in a denial-of-service condition. To trigger this, the user would unwittingly need to open a malicious file shared by the threat actor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21920|2024-03-26T15:48:59.735Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 15:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21915|2024-02-16T18:20:43.862Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20service%20platform</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21915</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® Service Platform (FTSP). If exploited, a malicious user with basic user group privileges could potentially sign into the software and receive FTSP Administrator Group privileges. A threat actor could potentially read and modify sensitive data, delete data and render the FTSP system unavailable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21915|2024-02-16T18:20:43.862Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 18:20:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21919|2024-03-26T15:46:38.129Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21919</link>
      <description>An uninitialized pointer in Rockwell Automation Arena Simulation software could potentially allow a malicious user to insert unauthorized code to the software by leveraging the pointer after it is properly.  Once inside, the threat actor can run harmful code on the system. This affects the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the product. To trigger this, the user would unwittingly need to open a malicious file shared by the threat actor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21919|2024-03-26T15:46:38.129Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 15:46:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21918|2024-03-26T15:44:33.835Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21918</link>
      <description>A memory buffer vulnerability in Rockwell Automation Arena Simulation software could potentially allow a malicious user to insert unauthorized code to the software by corrupting the memory and triggering an access violation.  Once inside, the threat actor can run harmful code on the system. This affects the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the product. To trigger this, the user would unwittingly need to open a malicious file shared by the threat actor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21918|2024-03-26T15:44:33.835Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 15:44:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21914|2024-03-25T21:27:18.975Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20view%20me</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21914</link>
      <description>A vulnerability exists in the affected product that allows a malicious user to restart the Rockwell Automation PanelView™ Plus 7 terminal remotely without security protections. If the vulnerability is exploited, it could lead to the loss of view or control of the PanelView™ product.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21914|2024-03-25T21:27:18.975Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 21:27:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21913|2024-03-26T15:38:23.962Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21913</link>
      <description>A heap-based memory buffer overflow vulnerability in Rockwell Automation Arena Simulation software could potentially allow a malicious user to insert unauthorized code into the software by overstepping the memory boundaries, which triggers an access violation.  Once inside, the threat actor can run harmful code on the system. This affects the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the product. To trigger this, the user would unwittingly need to open a malicious file shared by the threat actor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21913|2024-03-26T15:38:23.962Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 15:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21912|2024-03-26T15:34:35.837Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21912</link>
      <description>An arbitrary code execution vulnerability in Rockwell Automation Arena Simulation could let a malicious user insert unauthorized code into the software. This is done by writing beyond the designated memory area, which causes an access violation. Once inside, the threat actor can run harmful code on the system. This affects the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the product. To trigger this, the user would unwittingly need to open a malicious file shared by the threat actor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21912|2024-03-26T15:34:35.837Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 15:34:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3493|2024-04-15T21:29:33.269Z -- rockwell%20automation -- controllogix%205580</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3493</link>
      <description>A specific malformed fragmented packet type (fragmented packets may be generated automatically by devices that send large amounts of data) can cause a major nonrecoverable fault (MNRF) Rockwell Automation's ControlLogix 5580, Guard Logix 5580, CompactLogix 5380, and 1756-EN4TR. If exploited, the affected product will become unavailable and require a manual restart to recover it. Additionally, an MNRF could result in a loss of view and/or control of connected devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3493|2024-04-15T21:29:33.269Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 21:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3640|2024-06-04T17:31:28.680Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20remote%20access%E2%84%A2</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3640</link>
      <description>An unquoted executable path exists in the Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® Remote Access™ possibly resulting in remote code execution if exploited. While running the FTRA installer package, the executable path is not properly quoted, which could allow a threat actor to enter a malicious executable and run it as a System user. A threat actor needs admin privileges to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3640|2024-06-04T17:31:28.680Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 15:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2425|2024-06-04T17:30:25.436Z -- rockwell%20automation -- powerflex%C2%AE%20527</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2425</link>
      <description>A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation PowerFlex® 527 due to improper input validation in the device. If exploited, the web server will crash and need a manual restart to recover it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2425|2024-06-04T17:30:25.436Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 20:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2424|2024-06-04T17:29:58.099Z -- rockwell%20automation -- 5015-aenftxt</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2424</link>
      <description>An input validation vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation 5015-AENFTXT that causes the secondary adapter to result in a major nonrecoverable fault (MNRF) when malicious input is entered. If exploited, the availability of the device will be impacted, and a manual restart is required. Additionally, a malformed PTP packet is needed to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2424|2024-06-04T17:29:58.099Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 21:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2427|2024-03-25T20:20:41.295Z -- rockwell%20automation -- powerflex%C2%AE%20527</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2427</link>
      <description>A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation PowerFlex® 527 due to improper traffic throttling in the device. If multiple data packets are sent to the device repeatedly the device will crash and require a manual restart to recover.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2427|2024-03-25T20:20:41.295Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 20:20:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2426|2024-03-25T20:18:33.240Z -- rockwell%20automation -- powerflex%C2%AE%20527</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2426</link>
      <description>A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation PowerFlex® 527 due to improper input validation in the device. If exploited, a disruption in the CIP communication will occur and a manual restart will be required by the user to recover it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2426|2024-03-25T20:18:33.240Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 20:17:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2929|2024-03-26T15:56:31.967Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2929</link>
      <description>A memory corruption vulnerability in Rockwell Automation Arena Simulation software could potentially allow a malicious user to insert unauthorized code to the software by corrupting the memory triggering an access violation.  Once inside, the threat actor can run harmful code on the system. This affects the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the product. To trigger this, the user would unwittingly need to open a malicious file shared by the threat actor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2929|2024-03-26T15:56:31.967Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 15:56:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37368|2024-06-14T14:30:53.422Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20view%20se</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37368</link>
      <description>A user authentication vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® View SE. The vulnerability allows a user from a remote system with FTView to send a packet to the customer’s server to view an HMI project. Due to the lack of proper authentication, this action is allowed without proper authentication verification.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37368|2024-06-14T14:30:53.422Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37367|2024-06-14T14:17:54.951Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20view%20se</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37367</link>
      <description>A user authentication vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® View SE v12. The vulnerability allows a user from a remote system with FTView to send a packet to the customer’s server to view an HMI project.  This action is allowed without proper authentication verification.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37367|2024-06-14T14:17:54.951Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:17:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37369|2024-06-14T18:13:03.399Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20view%20se</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37369</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the affected product. The vulnerability allows low-privilege users to edit scripts, bypassing Access Control Lists, and potentially gaining further access within the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37369|2024-06-14T18:13:03.399Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 16:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37367|2024-06-17T15:37:26.533Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20view%20se</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37367</link>
      <description>A user authentication vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® View SE v12. The vulnerability allows a user from a remote system with FTView to send a packet to the customer’s server to view an HMI project.  This action is allowed without proper authentication verification.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37367|2024-06-17T15:37:26.533Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:17:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5989|2024-06-25T16:01:39.103Z -- rockwell%20automation -- thinmanager%C2%AE%20thinserver%E2%84%A2</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5989</link>
      <description>Due to an improper input validation, an unauthenticated threat actor can send a malicious message to invoke SQL injection into the program and cause a remote code execution condition on the Rockwell Automation ThinManager® ThinServer™.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5989|2024-06-25T16:01:39.103Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 16:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5988|2024-06-25T16:03:05.556Z -- rockwell%20automation -- thinmanager%C2%AE%20thinserver%E2%84%A2</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5988</link>
      <description>Due to an improper input validation, an unauthenticated threat actor can send a malicious message to invoke a local or remote executable and cause a remote code execution condition on the Rockwell Automation ThinManager® ThinServer™.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5988|2024-06-25T16:03:05.556Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 15:53:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5989|2024-06-25T17:44:59.233Z -- rockwell%20automation -- thinmanager%C2%AE%20thinserver%E2%84%A2</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5989</link>
      <description>Due to an improper input validation, an unauthenticated threat actor can send a malicious message to invoke SQL injection into the program and cause a remote code execution condition on the Rockwell Automation ThinManager® ThinServer™.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5989|2024-06-25T17:44:59.233Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 16:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6326|2024-07-16T16:51:18.320Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20system%20services%20%28installed%20via%20ftpm%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6326</link>
      <description>An exposure of sensitive information vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® System Service. A malicious user could exploit this vulnerability by starting a back-up or restore process, which temporarily exposes private keys, passwords, pre-shared keys, and database folders when they are temporarily copied to an interim folder. This vulnerability is due to the lack of explicit permissions set on the backup folder. If private keys are obtained by a malicious user, they could impersonate resources on the secured network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6326|2024-07-16T16:51:18.320Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 16:51:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6325|2024-07-16T16:43:44.494Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20system%20services%20%28installed%20via%20ftpm%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6325</link>
      <description>The v6.40 release of Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® Policy Manager CVE-2021-22681 https://www.rockwellautomation.com/en-us/trust-center/security-advisories/advisory.PN1550.html  and  CVE-2022-1161 https://www.rockwellautomation.com/en-us/trust-center/security-advisories/advisory.PN1585.html  by implementing CIP security and did not update to the versions of the software CVE-2022-1161 https://www.rockwellautomation.com/en-us/trust-center/security-advisories/advisory.PN1585.html  and  CVE-2022-1161. https://www.rockwellautomation.com/en-us/trust-center/security-advisories/advisory.PN1585.html</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6325|2024-07-16T16:43:44.494Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 16:43:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6089|2024-07-17T14:57:56.133Z -- rockwell%20automation -- 5015%20-%20aenftxt</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6089</link>
      <description>An input validation vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation 5015 - AENFTXT when a manipulated PTP packet is sent, causing the secondary adapter to result in a major nonrecoverable fault. If exploited, a power cycle is required to recover the product.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6089|2024-07-17T14:57:56.133Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 17:10:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6325|2024-07-17T15:47:32.018Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20system%20services%20%28installed%20via%20ftpm%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6325</link>
      <description>The v6.40 release of Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® Policy Manager CVE-2021-22681 https://www.rockwellautomation.com/en-us/trust-center/security-advisories/advisory.PN1550.html  and  CVE-2022-1161 https://www.rockwellautomation.com/en-us/trust-center/security-advisories/advisory.PN1585.html  by implementing CIP security and did not update to the versions of the software CVE-2022-1161 https://www.rockwellautomation.com/en-us/trust-center/security-advisories/advisory.PN1585.html  and  CVE-2022-1161. https://www.rockwellautomation.com/en-us/trust-center/security-advisories/advisory.PN1585.html</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6325|2024-07-17T15:47:32.018Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 16:43:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6242|2024-08-01T15:15:32.220Z -- rockwell%20automation -- controllogix%C2%AE%205580%20%281756-l8z%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6242</link>
      <description>A vulnerability exists in Rockwell Automation affected products that allows a threat actor to bypass the Trusted® Slot feature in a ControlLogix® controller. If exploited on any affected module in a 1756 chassis, a threat actor could potentially execute CIP commands that modify user projects and/or device configuration on a Logix controller in the chassis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6242|2024-08-01T15:15:32.220Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 15:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2426|2024-08-01T19:11:53.564Z -- rockwell%20automation -- powerflex%C2%AE%20527</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2426</link>
      <description>A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation PowerFlex® 527 due to improper input validation in the device. If exploited, a disruption in the CIP communication will occur and a manual restart will be required by the user to recover it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2426|2024-08-01T19:11:53.564Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 20:17:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2424|2024-08-01T19:11:53.521Z -- rockwell%20automation -- 5015-aenftxt</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2424</link>
      <description>An input validation vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation 5015-AENFTXT that causes the secondary adapter to result in a major nonrecoverable fault (MNRF) when malicious input is entered. If exploited, the availability of the device will be impacted, and a manual restart is required. Additionally, a malformed PTP packet is needed to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2424|2024-08-01T19:11:53.521Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 21:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2929|2024-08-01T19:32:41.647Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2929</link>
      <description>A memory corruption vulnerability in Rockwell Automation Arena Simulation software could potentially allow a malicious user to insert unauthorized code to the software by corrupting the memory triggering an access violation.  Once inside, the threat actor can run harmful code on the system. This affects the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the product. To trigger this, the user would unwittingly need to open a malicious file shared by the threat actor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2929|2024-08-01T19:32:41.647Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 15:56:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2427|2024-08-01T19:11:53.547Z -- rockwell%20automation -- powerflex%C2%AE%20527</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2427</link>
      <description>A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation PowerFlex® 527 due to improper traffic throttling in the device. If multiple data packets are sent to the device repeatedly the device will crash and require a manual restart to recover.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2427|2024-08-01T19:11:53.547Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 20:20:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2425|2024-08-01T19:11:53.614Z -- rockwell%20automation -- powerflex%C2%AE%20527</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2425</link>
      <description>A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation PowerFlex® 527 due to improper input validation in the device. If exploited, the web server will crash and need a manual restart to recover it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2425|2024-08-01T19:11:53.614Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 20:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5989|2024-08-01T21:25:03.287Z -- rockwell%20automation -- thinmanager%C2%AE%20thinserver%E2%84%A2</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5989</link>
      <description>Due to an improper input validation, an unauthenticated threat actor can send a malicious message to invoke SQL injection into the program and cause a remote code execution condition on the Rockwell Automation ThinManager® ThinServer™.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5989|2024-08-01T21:25:03.287Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 16:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6325|2024-08-01T21:33:05.423Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20system%20services%20%28installed%20via%20ftpm%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6325</link>
      <description>The v6.40 release of Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® Policy Manager CVE-2021-22681 https://www.rockwellautomation.com/en-us/trust-center/security-advisories/advisory.PN1550.html  and  CVE-2022-1161 https://www.rockwellautomation.com/en-us/trust-center/security-advisories/advisory.PN1585.html  by implementing CIP security and did not update to the versions of the software CVE-2022-1161 https://www.rockwellautomation.com/en-us/trust-center/security-advisories/advisory.PN1585.html  and  CVE-2022-1161. https://www.rockwellautomation.com/en-us/trust-center/security-advisories/advisory.PN1585.html</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6325|2024-08-01T21:33:05.423Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 16:43:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5988|2024-08-01T21:25:03.324Z -- rockwell%20automation -- thinmanager%C2%AE%20thinserver%E2%84%A2</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5988</link>
      <description>Due to an improper input validation, an unauthenticated threat actor can send a malicious message to invoke a local or remote executable and cause a remote code execution condition on the Rockwell Automation ThinManager® ThinServer™.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5988|2024-08-01T21:25:03.324Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 15:53:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5659|2024-08-01T21:18:06.865Z -- rockwell%20automation -- controllogix%C2%AE%205580</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5659</link>
      <description>Rockwell Automation was made aware of a vulnerability that causes all affected controllers on the same network to result in a major nonrecoverable fault(MNRF/Assert). This vulnerability could be exploited by sending abnormal packets to the mDNS port. If exploited, the availability of the device would be compromised.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5659|2024-08-01T21:18:06.865Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 16:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6435|2024-08-01T21:41:03.349Z -- rockwell%20automation -- pavilion8%C2%AE</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6435</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the affected products which could allow a malicious user with basic privileges to access functions which should only be available to users with administrative level privileges. If exploited, an attacker could read sensitive data, and create users. For example, a malicious user with basic privileges could perform critical functions such as creating a user with elevated privileges and reading sensitive information in the “views” section.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6435|2024-08-01T21:41:03.349Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 13:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6089|2024-08-01T21:33:04.327Z -- rockwell%20automation -- 5015%20-%20aenftxt</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6089</link>
      <description>An input validation vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation 5015 - AENFTXT when a manipulated PTP packet is sent, causing the secondary adapter to result in a major nonrecoverable fault. If exploited, a power cycle is required to recover the product.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6089|2024-08-01T21:33:04.327Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 17:10:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5990|2024-08-01T21:25:03.210Z -- rockwell%20automation -- thinmanager%C2%AE%20thinserver%E2%84%A2</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5990</link>
      <description>Due to an improper input validation, an unauthenticated threat actor can send a malicious message to a monitor thread within Rockwell Automation ThinServer™ and cause a denial-of-service condition on the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5990|2024-08-01T21:25:03.210Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 16:11:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6326|2024-08-01T21:33:05.450Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20system%20services%20%28installed%20via%20ftpm%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6326</link>
      <description>An exposure of sensitive information vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® System Service. A malicious user could exploit this vulnerability by starting a back-up or restore process, which temporarily exposes private keys, passwords, pre-shared keys, and database folders when they are temporarily copied to an interim folder. This vulnerability is due to the lack of explicit permissions set on the backup folder. If private keys are obtained by a malicious user, they could impersonate resources on the secured network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6326|2024-08-01T21:33:05.450Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 16:51:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37368|2024-08-02T03:50:56.219Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20view%20se</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37368</link>
      <description>A user authentication vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® View SE. The vulnerability allows a user from a remote system with FTView to send a packet to the customer’s server to view an HMI project. Due to the lack of proper authentication, this action is allowed without proper authentication verification.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37368|2024-08-02T03:50:56.219Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37369|2024-08-02T03:50:56.129Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20view%20se</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37369</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the affected product. The vulnerability allows low-privilege users to edit scripts, bypassing Access Control Lists, and potentially gaining further access within the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37369|2024-08-02T03:50:56.129Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 16:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37367|2024-08-02T03:50:56.151Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20view%20se</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37367</link>
      <description>A user authentication vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® View SE v12. The vulnerability allows a user from a remote system with FTView to send a packet to the customer’s server to view an HMI project.  This action is allowed without proper authentication verification.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37367|2024-08-02T03:50:56.151Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:17:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
