<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Rockwell Automation -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/rockwell%20automation/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Rockwell Automation -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 16:23:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37367|2024-06-17T15:37:26.533Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20view%20se
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37367</link>
      <description>A user authentication vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® View SE v12. The vulnerability allows a user from a remote system with FTView to send a packet to the customer’s server to view an HMI project.  This action is allowed without proper authentication verification.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37367|2024-06-17T15:37:26.533Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:17:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37369|2024-06-14T18:13:03.399Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20view%20se</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37369</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the affected product. The vulnerability allows low-privilege users to edit scripts, bypassing Access Control Lists, and potentially gaining further access within the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37369|2024-06-14T18:13:03.399Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 16:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37367|2024-06-14T14:17:54.951Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20view%20se</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37367</link>
      <description>A user authentication vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® View SE v12. The vulnerability allows a user from a remote system with FTView to send a packet to the customer’s server to view an HMI project.  This action is allowed without proper authentication verification.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37367|2024-06-14T14:17:54.951Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:17:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37368|2024-06-14T14:30:53.422Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20view%20se</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37368</link>
      <description>A user authentication vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® View SE. The vulnerability allows a user from a remote system with FTView to send a packet to the customer’s server to view an HMI project. Due to the lack of proper authentication, this action is allowed without proper authentication verification.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37368|2024-06-14T14:30:53.422Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2929|2024-03-26T15:56:31.967Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2929</link>
      <description>A memory corruption vulnerability in Rockwell Automation Arena Simulation software could potentially allow a malicious user to insert unauthorized code to the software by corrupting the memory triggering an access violation.  Once inside, the threat actor can run harmful code on the system. This affects the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the product. To trigger this, the user would unwittingly need to open a malicious file shared by the threat actor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2929|2024-03-26T15:56:31.967Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 15:56:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2426|2024-03-25T20:18:33.240Z -- rockwell%20automation -- powerflex%C2%AE%20527</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2426</link>
      <description>A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation PowerFlex® 527 due to improper input validation in the device. If exploited, a disruption in the CIP communication will occur and a manual restart will be required by the user to recover it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2426|2024-03-25T20:18:33.240Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 20:17:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2427|2024-03-25T20:20:41.295Z -- rockwell%20automation -- powerflex%C2%AE%20527</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2427</link>
      <description>A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation PowerFlex® 527 due to improper traffic throttling in the device. If multiple data packets are sent to the device repeatedly the device will crash and require a manual restart to recover.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2427|2024-03-25T20:20:41.295Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 20:20:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2424|2024-06-04T17:29:58.099Z -- rockwell%20automation -- 5015-aenftxt</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2424</link>
      <description>An input validation vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation 5015-AENFTXT that causes the secondary adapter to result in a major nonrecoverable fault (MNRF) when malicious input is entered. If exploited, the availability of the device will be impacted, and a manual restart is required. Additionally, a malformed PTP packet is needed to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2424|2024-06-04T17:29:58.099Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 21:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2425|2024-06-04T17:30:25.436Z -- rockwell%20automation -- powerflex%C2%AE%20527</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2425</link>
      <description>A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation PowerFlex® 527 due to improper input validation in the device. If exploited, the web server will crash and need a manual restart to recover it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2425|2024-06-04T17:30:25.436Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 20:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3640|2024-06-04T17:31:28.680Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20remote%20access%E2%84%A2</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3640</link>
      <description>An unquoted executable path exists in the Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® Remote Access™ possibly resulting in remote code execution if exploited. While running the FTRA installer package, the executable path is not properly quoted, which could allow a threat actor to enter a malicious executable and run it as a System user. A threat actor needs admin privileges to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3640|2024-06-04T17:31:28.680Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 15:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3493|2024-04-15T21:29:33.269Z -- rockwell%20automation -- controllogix%205580</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3493</link>
      <description>A specific malformed fragmented packet type (fragmented packets may be generated automatically by devices that send large amounts of data) can cause a major nonrecoverable fault (MNRF) Rockwell Automation's ControlLogix 5580, Guard Logix 5580, CompactLogix 5380, and 1756-EN4TR. If exploited, the affected product will become unavailable and require a manual restart to recover it. Additionally, an MNRF could result in a loss of view and/or control of connected devices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3493|2024-04-15T21:29:33.269Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 21:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21912|2024-03-26T15:34:35.837Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21912</link>
      <description>An arbitrary code execution vulnerability in Rockwell Automation Arena Simulation could let a malicious user insert unauthorized code into the software. This is done by writing beyond the designated memory area, which causes an access violation. Once inside, the threat actor can run harmful code on the system. This affects the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the product. To trigger this, the user would unwittingly need to open a malicious file shared by the threat actor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21912|2024-03-26T15:34:35.837Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 15:34:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21913|2024-03-26T15:38:23.962Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21913</link>
      <description>A heap-based memory buffer overflow vulnerability in Rockwell Automation Arena Simulation software could potentially allow a malicious user to insert unauthorized code into the software by overstepping the memory boundaries, which triggers an access violation.  Once inside, the threat actor can run harmful code on the system. This affects the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the product. To trigger this, the user would unwittingly need to open a malicious file shared by the threat actor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21913|2024-03-26T15:38:23.962Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 15:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21914|2024-03-25T21:27:18.975Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20view%20me</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21914</link>
      <description>A vulnerability exists in the affected product that allows a malicious user to restart the Rockwell Automation PanelView™ Plus 7 terminal remotely without security protections. If the vulnerability is exploited, it could lead to the loss of view or control of the PanelView™ product.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21914|2024-03-25T21:27:18.975Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 21:27:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21918|2024-03-26T15:44:33.835Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21918</link>
      <description>A memory buffer vulnerability in Rockwell Automation Arena Simulation software could potentially allow a malicious user to insert unauthorized code to the software by corrupting the memory and triggering an access violation.  Once inside, the threat actor can run harmful code on the system. This affects the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the product. To trigger this, the user would unwittingly need to open a malicious file shared by the threat actor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21918|2024-03-26T15:44:33.835Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 15:44:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21919|2024-03-26T15:46:38.129Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21919</link>
      <description>An uninitialized pointer in Rockwell Automation Arena Simulation software could potentially allow a malicious user to insert unauthorized code to the software by leveraging the pointer after it is properly.  Once inside, the threat actor can run harmful code on the system. This affects the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the product. To trigger this, the user would unwittingly need to open a malicious file shared by the threat actor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21919|2024-03-26T15:46:38.129Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 15:46:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21915|2024-02-16T18:20:43.862Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20service%20platform</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21915</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® Service Platform (FTSP). If exploited, a malicious user with basic user group privileges could potentially sign into the software and receive FTSP Administrator Group privileges. A threat actor could potentially read and modify sensitive data, delete data and render the FTSP system unavailable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21915|2024-02-16T18:20:43.862Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 18:20:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21916|2024-01-31T18:28:59.715Z -- rockwell%20automation -- controllogix%C2%AE%205570</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21916</link>
      <description>A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in specific Rockwell Automation ControlLogix ang GuardLogix controllers. If exploited, the product could potentially experience a major nonrecoverable fault (MNRF). The device will restart itself to recover from the MNRF.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21916|2024-01-31T18:28:59.715Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 18:28:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21920|2024-03-26T15:48:59.735Z -- rockwell%20automation -- arena%20simulation</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21920</link>
      <description>A memory buffer vulnerability in Rockwell Automation Arena Simulation could potentially let a threat actor read beyond the intended memory boundaries. This could reveal sensitive information and even cause the application to crash, resulting in a denial-of-service condition. To trigger this, the user would unwittingly need to open a malicious file shared by the threat actor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21920|2024-03-26T15:48:59.735Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 15:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21917|2024-01-31T18:16:27.949Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20service%20platform</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21917</link>
      <description>A vulnerability exists in Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® Service Platform that allows a malicious user to obtain the service token and use it for authentication on another FTSP directory. This is due to the lack of digital signing between the FTSP service token and directory.  If exploited, a malicious user could potentially retrieve user information and modify settings without any authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21917|2024-01-31T18:16:27.949Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 18:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4609|2024-06-04T17:53:40.228Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20view%20se</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4609</link>
      <description>A vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® View SE Datalog function that could allow a threat actor to inject a malicious SQL statement if the SQL database has no authentication in place or if legitimate credentials were stolen. If exploited, the attack could result in information exposure, revealing sensitive information. Additionally, a threat actor could potentially modify and delete the data in a remote database. An attack would only affect the HMI design time, not runtime.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4609|2024-06-04T17:53:40.228Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 15:13:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37369|2024-06-14T16:50:20.187Z -- rockwell%20automation -- factorytalk%C2%AE%20view%20se</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37369</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the affected product. The vulnerability allows low-privilege users to edit scripts, bypassing Access Control Lists, and potentially gaining further access within the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37369|2024-06-14T16:50:20.187Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 16:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5659|2024-06-14T16:42:20.699Z -- rockwell%20automation -- controllogix%C2%AE%205580</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5659</link>
      <description>Rockwell Automation was made aware of a vulnerability that causes all affected controllers on the same network to result in a major nonrecoverable fault(MNRF/Assert). This vulnerability could be exploited by sending abnormal packets to the mDNS port. If exploited, the availability of the device would be compromised.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5659|2024-06-14T16:42:20.699Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 16:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5659|2024-06-15T20:23:20.243Z -- rockwell%20automation -- controllogix%C2%AE%205580</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5659</link>
      <description>Rockwell Automation was made aware of a vulnerability that causes all affected controllers on the same network to result in a major nonrecoverable fault(MNRF/Assert). This vulnerability could be exploited by sending abnormal packets to the mDNS port. If exploited, the availability of the device would be compromised.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5659|2024-06-15T20:23:20.243Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 16:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
