<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Rockwell Automation -- ISaGRAF Runtime</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/rockwell%20automation/isagraf%20runtime.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Rockwell Automation -- ISaGRAF Runtime</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:22:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-25176|2024-08-04T15:26:10.174Z -- rockwell%20automation -- isagraf%20runtime
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-25176</link>
      <description>Some commands used by the Rockwell Automation ISaGRAF Runtime Versions 4.x and 5.x eXchange Layer (IXL) protocol perform various file operations in the file system. Since the parameter pointing to the file name is not checked for reserved characters, it is possible for a remote, unauthenticated attacker to traverse an application’s directory, which could lead to remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-25176|2024-08-04T15:26:10.174Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 18:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-25182|2024-08-04T15:26:09.509Z -- rockwell%20automation -- isagraf%20runtime
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-25182</link>
      <description>Rockwell Automation ISaGRAF Runtime Versions 4.x and 5.x searches for and loads DLLs as dynamic libraries. Uncontrolled loading of dynamic libraries could allow a local, unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code. This vulnerability only affects ISaGRAF Runtime when running on Microsoft Windows systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-25182|2024-08-04T15:26:09.509Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 18:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-25184|2024-08-04T15:26:10.252Z -- rockwell%20automation -- isagraf%20runtime
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-25184</link>
      <description>Rockwell Automation ISaGRAF Runtime Versions 4.x and 5.x stores the password in plaintext in a file that is in the same directory as the executable file. ISaGRAF Runtime reads the file and saves the data in a variable without any additional modification. A local, unauthenticated attacker could compromise the user passwords, resulting in information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-25184|2024-08-04T15:26:10.252Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 18:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-25178|2024-08-04T15:26:09.783Z -- rockwell%20automation -- isagraf%20runtime
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-25178</link>
      <description>ISaGRAF Workbench communicates with Rockwell Automation ISaGRAF Runtime Versions 4.x and 5.x using TCP/IP. This communication protocol provides various file system operations, as well as the uploading of applications. Data is transferred over this protocol unencrypted, which could allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to upload, read, and delete files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-25178|2024-08-04T15:26:09.783Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 18:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-25180|2024-08-04T15:26:09.581Z -- rockwell%20automation -- isagraf%20runtime
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-25180</link>
      <description>Rockwell Automation ISaGRAF Runtime Versions 4.x and 5.x includes the functionality of setting a password that is required to execute privileged commands. The password value passed to ISaGRAF Runtime is the result of encryption performed with a fixed key value using the tiny encryption algorithm (TEA) on an entered or saved password. A remote, unauthenticated attacker could pass their own encrypted password to the ISaGRAF 5 Runtime, which may result in information disclosure on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-25180|2024-08-04T15:26:09.581Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 18:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
