<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for SanDisk -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sandisk/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for SanDisk -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22818|2023-11-15T20:03:57.085Z -- sandisk -- sandisk%20security%20installer%20for%20windows
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-22818</link>
      <description>Multiple DLL Search Order Hijack vulnerabilities were addressed in the SanDisk Security Installer for
Windows that could allow attackers with local access to execute arbitrary code by executing the installer
in the same folder as the malicious DLL. This can lead to the execution of arbitrary
code with the privileges of the vulnerable application or obtain a certain level of persistence
on the compromised host. </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22818|2023-11-15T20:03:57.085Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 20:03:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22819|2024-06-07T16:00:24.870Z -- sandisk -- ibi
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-22819</link>
      <description>An uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability issue that could arise by sending crafted requests to a service to consume a large amount of memory, eventually resulting in the service being stopped and restarted was discovered in Western Digital My Cloud Home, My Cloud Home Duo, SanDisk ibi and Western Digital My Cloud OS 5 devices. This issue requires the attacker to already have root privileges in order to exploit this vulnerability. This issue affects My Cloud Home and My Cloud Home Duo: before 9.5.1-104; ibi: before 9.5.1-104; My Cloud OS 5: before 5.27.161.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22819|2024-06-07T16:00:24.870Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:26:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22812|2023-10-23T17:06:36.560Z -- sandisk -- privateaccess
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-22812</link>
      <description>SanDisk PrivateAccess versions prior to 6.4.9 support insecure TLS 1.0 and TLS 1.1 protocols which are susceptible to man-in-the-middle attacks thereby compromising confidentiality and integrity of data. 
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22812|2023-10-23T17:06:36.560Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22813|2023-05-10T21:57:39.906Z -- sandisk -- ibi%20mobile%20app
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-22813</link>
      <description>









A device API
endpoint was missing access controls on Western Digital My Cloud OS 5 iOS and Anroid Mobile Apps, My Cloud Home iOS and Android Mobile Apps, SanDisk ibi iOS and Android Mobile Apps, My Cloud OS 5 Web App, My Cloud Home Web App and the SanDisk ibi Web App. Due to a permissive CORS policy
and missing authentication requirement for private IPs, a remote attacker on
the same network as the device could obtain device information by convincing a
victim user to visit an attacker-controlled server and issue a cross-site
request.



This issue affects
My Cloud OS 5 Mobile App: before 4.21.0; My Cloud Home Mobile App: before 4.21.0; ibi Mobile App: before 4.21.0; My
Cloud OS 5 Web App: before 4.26.0-6126; My Cloud Home Web App: before 4.26.0-6126;
ibi Web App: before 4.26.0-6126.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22813|2023-05-10T21:57:39.906Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 22:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22817|2024-02-05T21:26:42.020Z -- sandisk -- ibi
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-22817</link>
      <description>Server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability that could allow a rogue server on the local network to modify its URL using another DNS address to point back to the loopback adapter. This could then allow the URL to exploit other vulnerabilities on the local server. This was addressed by fixing DNS addresses that refer to loopback. This issue affects My Cloud OS 5 devices before 5.27.161, My Cloud Home, My Cloud Home Duo and SanDisk ibi devices before 9.5.1-104. 
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22817|2024-02-05T21:26:42.020Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:26:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22167|2024-03-13T20:43:06.776Z -- sandisk -- privateaccess%20windows%20app
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22167</link>
      <description>A potential DLL hijacking vulnerability in the SanDisk PrivateAccess application for Windows that could lead to arbitrary code execution in the context of the system user. This vulnerability is only exploitable locally if an attacker has access to a copy of the user's vault or has already gained access into a user's system. This attack is limited to the system in context and cannot be propagated. 
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22167|2024-03-13T20:43:06.776Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 20:43:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
