<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Unknown -- Accept Donations with PayPal</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/unknown/accept%20donations%20with%20paypal.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Unknown -- Accept Donations with PayPal</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 23:22:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-24572|2024-08-03T19:35:20.165Z -- unknown -- accept%20donations%20with%20paypal
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-24572</link>
      <description>The Accept Donations with PayPal WordPress plugin before 1.3.1 provides a function to create donation buttons which are internally stored as posts. The deletion of a button is not CSRF protected and there is no control to check if the deleted post was a button post. As a result, an attacker could make logged in admins delete arbitrary posts</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-24572|2024-08-03T19:35:20.165Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 08:46:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-24570|2024-08-03T19:35:20.193Z -- unknown -- accept%20donations%20with%20paypal
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-24570</link>
      <description>The Accept Donations with PayPal WordPress plugin before 1.3.1 offers a function to create donation buttons, which internally are posts. The process to create a new button is lacking a CSRF check. An attacker could use this to make an authenticated admin create a new button. Furthermore, one of the Button field is not escaped before being output in an attribute when editing a Button, leading to a Stored Cross-Site Scripting issue as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-24570|2024-08-03T19:35:20.193Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 08:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-24989|2024-08-03T19:49:14.541Z -- unknown -- accept%20donations%20with%20paypal
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-24989</link>
      <description>The Accept Donations with PayPal WordPress plugin before 1.3.4 does not have CSRF check in place and does not ensure that the post to be deleted belongs to the plugin, allowing attackers to make a logged in admin delete arbitrary posts from the blog</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-24989|2024-08-03T19:49:14.541Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 08:01:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-24815|2024-08-03T19:42:17.342Z -- unknown -- accept%20donations%20with%20paypal
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-24815</link>
      <description>The Accept Donations with PayPal WordPress plugin before 1.3.2 does not escape the Amount Menu Name field of created Buttons, which could allow a high privilege users to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-24815|2024-08-03T19:42:17.342Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 10:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
