<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Unknown -- Custom Content Shortcode</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/unknown/custom%20content%20shortcode.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Unknown -- Custom Content Shortcode</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 20:22:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-24826|2024-08-03T19:42:17.327Z -- unknown -- custom%20content%20shortcode
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-24826</link>
      <description>The Custom Content Shortcode WordPress plugin before 4.0.2 does not escape custom fields before outputting them, which could allow Contributor+ (v &lt; 4.0.1) or Admin+ (v &lt; 4.0.2) users to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html is disallowed. Please note that such attack is still possible by admin+ in single site blogs by default (but won't be when the unfiltered_html is disallowed)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-24826|2024-08-03T19:42:17.327Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 08:16:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-24825|2024-08-03T19:42:17.342Z -- unknown -- custom%20content%20shortcode
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-24825</link>
      <description>The Custom Content Shortcode WordPress plugin before 4.0.2 does not validate the data passed to its load shortcode, which could allow Contributor+ (v &lt; 4.0.1) or Admin+ (v &lt; 4.0.2) users to display arbitrary files from the filesystem (such as logs, .htaccess etc), as well as perform Local File Inclusion attacks as PHP files will be executed. Please note that such attack is still possible by admin+ in single site blogs by default (but won't be when either the unfiltered_html or file_edit is disallowed)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-24825|2024-08-03T19:42:17.342Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 08:16:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-24824|2024-08-03T19:42:17.203Z -- unknown -- custom%20content%20shortcode
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-24824</link>
      <description>The [field] shortcode included with the Custom Content Shortcode WordPress plugin before 4.0.1, allows authenticated users with a role as low as contributor, to access arbitrary post metadata. This could lead to sensitive data disclosure, for example when used in combination with WooCommerce, the email address of orders can be retrieved</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-24824|2024-08-03T19:42:17.203Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 08:16:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
