<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for unknown -- InduSoft Web Studio, and InTouch Edge HMI (formerly InTouch Machine Edition)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/unknown/indusoft%20web%20studio%2C%20and%20intouch%20edge%20hmi%20%28formerly%20intouch%20machine%20edition%29.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for unknown -- InduSoft Web Studio, and InTouch Edge HMI (formerly InTouch Machine Edition)</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:22:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17916|2024-08-05T11:01:14.594Z -- unknown -- indusoft%20web%20studio%2C%20and%20intouch%20edge%20hmi%20%28formerly%20intouch%20machine%20edition%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17916</link>
      <description>InduSoft Web Studio versions prior to 8.1 SP2, and InTouch Edge HMI (formerly InTouch Machine Edition) versions prior to 2017 SP2. A remote attacker could send a carefully crafted packet to exploit a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability during tag, alarm, or event related actions such as read and write, with potential for code to be executed. If InduSoft Web Studio remote communication security was not enabled, or a password was left blank, a remote user could send a carefully crafted packet to invoke an arbitrary process, with potential for code to be executed. The code would be executed under the privileges of the InduSoft Web Studio or InTouch Edge HMI runtime and could lead to a compromise of the InduSoft Web Studio or InTouch Edge HMI server machine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17916|2024-08-05T11:01:14.594Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17914|2024-08-05T11:01:14.684Z -- unknown -- indusoft%20web%20studio%2C%20and%20intouch%20edge%20hmi%20%28formerly%20intouch%20machine%20edition%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17914</link>
      <description>InduSoft Web Studio versions prior to 8.1 SP2, and InTouch Edge HMI (formerly InTouch Machine Edition) versions prior to 2017 SP2. This vulnerability could allow an unauthenticated user to remotely execute code with the same privileges as that of the InduSoft Web Studio or InTouch Edge HMI (formerly InTouch Machine Edition) runtime.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17914|2024-08-05T11:01:14.684Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
