<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Unknown -- Patreon WordPress</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/unknown/patreon%20wordpress.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Unknown -- Patreon WordPress</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 23:23:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-24231|2024-08-03T19:21:18.660Z -- unknown -- patreon%20wordpress
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-24231</link>
      <description>The Jetpack Scan team identified a Cross-Site Request Forgery vulnerability in the Patreon WordPress plugin before 1.7.0, allowing attackers to make a logged administrator disconnect the site from Patreon by visiting a specially crafted link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-24231|2024-08-03T19:21:18.660Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 14:06:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-24228|2024-08-03T19:21:19.050Z -- unknown -- patreon%20wordpress
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-24228</link>
      <description>The Jetpack Scan team identified a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting in the Login Form of the Patreon WordPress plugin before 1.7.2. The WordPress login form (wp-login.php) is hooked by the plugin and offers to allow users to authenticate on the site using their Patreon account. Unfortunately, some of the error logging logic behind the scene allowed user-controlled input to be reflected on the login page, unsanitized.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-24228|2024-08-03T19:21:19.050Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 14:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-24227|2024-08-03T19:21:18.863Z -- unknown -- patreon%20wordpress
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-24227</link>
      <description>The Jetpack Scan team identified a Local File Disclosure vulnerability in the Patreon WordPress plugin before 1.7.0 that could be abused by anyone visiting the site. Using this attack vector, an attacker could leak important internal files like wp-config.php, which contains database credentials and cryptographic keys used in the generation of nonces and cookies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-24227|2024-08-03T19:21:18.863Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 14:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-24230|2024-08-03T19:21:18.743Z -- unknown -- patreon%20wordpress
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-24230</link>
      <description>The Jetpack Scan team identified a Cross-Site Request Forgery vulnerability in the Patreon WordPress plugin before 1.7.0, allowing attackers to make a logged in user overwrite or create arbitrary user metadata on the victim’s account once visited. If exploited, this bug can be used to overwrite the “wp_capabilities” meta, which contains the affected user account’s roles and privileges. Doing this would essentially lock them out of the site, blocking them from accessing paid content.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-24230|2024-08-03T19:21:18.743Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 14:06:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25026|2024-08-03T19:49:14.659Z -- unknown -- patreon%20wordpress
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25026</link>
      <description>The Patreon WordPress plugin before 1.8.2 does not sanitise and escape the field "Custom Patreon Page name", which could allow high privilege users to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25026|2024-08-03T19:49:14.659Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 14:41:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-24229|2024-08-03T19:21:18.861Z -- unknown -- patreon%20wordpress
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-24229</link>
      <description>The Jetpack Scan team identified a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the patreon_save_attachment_patreon_level AJAX action of the Patreon WordPress plugin before 1.7.2. This AJAX hook is used to update the pledge level required by Patreon subscribers to access a given attachment. This action is accessible for user accounts with the ‘manage_options’ privilege (i.e.., only administrators). Unfortunately, one of the parameters used in this AJAX endpoint is not sanitized before being printed back to the user, so the risk it represents is the same as the previous XSS vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-24229|2024-08-03T19:21:18.861Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 14:05:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
