<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Unknown -- Workreap</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/unknown/workreap.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Unknown -- Workreap</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:22:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-24500|2024-08-03T19:35:19.928Z -- unknown -- workreap
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-24500</link>
      <description>Several AJAX actions available in the Workreap WordPress theme before 2.2.2 lacked CSRF protections, as well as allowing insecure direct object references that were not validated. This allows an attacker to trick a logged in user to submit a POST request to the vulnerable site, potentially modifying or deleting arbitrary objects on the target site.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-24500|2024-08-03T19:35:19.928Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 10:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-24501|2024-08-03T19:35:19.963Z -- unknown -- workreap
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-24501</link>
      <description>The Workreap WordPress theme before 2.2.2 had several AJAX actions missing authorization checks to verify that a user was authorized to perform critical operations such as modifying or deleting objects. This allowed a logged in user to modify or delete objects belonging to other users on the site.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-24501|2024-08-03T19:35:19.963Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 10:04:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3846|2024-08-03T01:20:58.635Z -- unknown -- workreap
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3846</link>
      <description>The Workreap WordPress theme before 2.6.3 has a vulnerability with the notifications feature as it's possible to read any user's notification (employer or freelancer) as the notification ID is brute-forceable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3846|2024-08-03T01:20:58.635Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 16:51:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-24499|2024-08-03T19:35:19.868Z -- unknown -- workreap
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-24499</link>
      <description>The Workreap WordPress theme before 2.2.2 AJAX actions workreap_award_temp_file_uploader and workreap_temp_file_uploader did not perform nonce checks, or validate that the request is from a valid user in any other way. The endpoints allowed for uploading arbitrary files to the uploads/workreap-temp directory. Uploaded files were neither sanitized nor validated, allowing an unauthenticated visitor to upload executable code such as php scripts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-24499|2024-08-03T19:35:19.868Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-4239|2024-08-03T01:34:49.603Z -- unknown -- workreap
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4239</link>
      <description>The Workreap WordPress theme before 2.6.4 does not verify that an addon service belongs to the user issuing the request, or indeed that it is an addon service, when processing the workreap_addons_service_remove action, allowing any user to delete any post by knowing or guessing the id.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-4239|2024-08-03T01:34:49.603Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 12:28:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
