<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Unknown -- YOP Poll</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/unknown/yop%20poll.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Unknown -- YOP Poll</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 20:21:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-1600|2024-08-03T00:10:03.637Z -- unknown -- yop%20poll
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1600</link>
      <description>The YOP Poll WordPress plugin before 6.4.3 prioritizes getting a visitor's IP from certain HTTP headers over PHP's REMOTE_ADDR, which makes it possible to bypass IP-based limitations to vote in certain situations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-1600|2024-08-03T00:10:03.637Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 12:48:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-24833|2024-08-03T19:42:17.229Z -- unknown -- yop%20poll
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-24833</link>
      <description>The YOP Poll WordPress plugin before 6.3.1 is affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability, which exists in the Admin preview module where a user with a role as low as author is allowed to execute arbitrary script code within the context of the application. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of question and answer text parameters in Create Poll module.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-24833|2024-08-03T19:42:17.229Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 10:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-24454|2024-08-03T19:35:18.675Z -- unknown -- yop%20poll
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-24454</link>
      <description>In the YOP Poll WordPress plugin before 6.2.8, when a pool is created with the options "Allow other answers", "Display other answers in the result list" and "Show results", it can lead to Stored Cross-Site Scripting issues as the 'Other' answer is not sanitised before being output in the page. The execution of the XSS payload depends on the 'Show results' option selected, which could be before or after sending the vote for example.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-24454|2024-08-03T19:35:18.675Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 19:21:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-24834|2024-08-03T19:42:17.214Z -- unknown -- yop%20poll
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-24834</link>
      <description>The YOP Poll WordPress plugin before 6.3.1 is affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability which exists in the Create Poll - Options module where a user with a role as low as author is allowed to execute arbitrary script code within the context of the application. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of custom label parameters - vote button label , results link label and back to vote caption label.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-24834|2024-08-03T19:42:17.214Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 10:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-24885|2024-08-03T19:49:12.695Z -- unknown -- yop%20poll
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-24885</link>
      <description>The YOP Poll WordPress plugin before 6.1.2 does not escape the perpage parameter before outputting it back in an attribute, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-24885|2024-08-03T19:49:12.695Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 13:21:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
