<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for vercel -- ms</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/vercel/ms.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for vercel -- ms</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:23:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-20162|2024-08-05T21:45:25.992Z -- vercel -- ms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20162</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in vercel ms up to 1.x. This issue affects the function parse of the file index.js. The manipulation of the argument str leads to inefficient regular expression complexity. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 2.0.0 is able to address this issue. The patch is named caae2988ba2a37765d055c4eee63d383320ee662. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-217451.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in vercel ms bis 1.x entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um die Funktion parse der Datei index.js. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments str mit unbekannten Daten kann eine inefficient regular expression complexity-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 2.0.0 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als caae2988ba2a37765d055c4eee63d383320ee662 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-20162|2024-08-05T21:45:25.992Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 11:49:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
