<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Apache Software Foundation -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/apache%20software%20foundation/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Apache Software Foundation -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 15:23:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-26031|2024-07-29T13:09:24.015Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20hadoop
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26031</link>
      <description>Relative library resolution in linux container-executor binary in Apache Hadoop 3.3.1-3.3.4 on Linux allows local user to gain root privileges. If the YARN cluster is accepting work from remote (authenticated) users, this MAY permit remote users to gain root privileges.

Hadoop 3.3.0 updated the " YARN Secure Containers https://hadoop.apache.org/docs/stable/hadoop-yarn/hadoop-yarn-site/SecureContainer.html " to add a feature for executing user-submitted applications in isolated linux containers.

The native binary HADOOP_HOME/bin/container-executor is used to launch these containers; it must be owned by root and have the suid bit set in order for the YARN processes to run the containers as the specific users submitting the jobs.

The patch " YARN-10495 https://issues.apache.org/jira/browse/YARN-10495 . make the rpath of container-executor configurable" modified the library loading path for loading .so files from "$ORIGIN/" to ""$ORIGIN/:../lib/native/". This is the a path through which libcrypto.so is located. Thus it is is possible for a user with reduced privileges to install a malicious libcrypto library into a path to which they have write access, invoke the container-executor command, and have their modified library executed as root.
If the YARN cluster is accepting work from remote (authenticated) users, and these users' submitted job are executed in the physical host, rather than a container, then the CVE permits remote users to gain root privileges.

The fix for the vulnerability is to revert the change, which is done in  YARN-11441 https://issues.apache.org/jira/browse/YARN-11441 , "Revert YARN-10495". This patch is in hadoop-3.3.5.

To determine whether a version of container-executor is vulnerable, use the readelf command. If the RUNPATH or RPATH value contains the relative path "./lib/native/" then it  is at risk

$ readelf -d container-executor|grep 'RUNPATH\|RPATH' 
0x000000000000001d (RUNPATH)            Library runpath: [$ORIGIN/:../lib/native/]

If it does not, then it is safe:

$ readelf -d container-executor|grep 'RUNPATH\|RPATH' 
0x000000000000001d (RUNPATH)            Library runpath: [$ORIGIN/]

For an at-risk version of container-executor to enable privilege escalation, the owner must be root and the suid bit must be set

$ ls -laF /opt/hadoop/bin/container-executor
---Sr-s---. 1 root hadoop 802968 May 9 20:21 /opt/hadoop/bin/container-executor

A safe installation lacks the suid bit; ideally is also not owned by root.

$ ls -laF /opt/hadoop/bin/container-executor
-rwxr-xr-x. 1 yarn hadoop 802968 May 9 20:21 /opt/hadoop/bin/container-executor

This configuration does not support Yarn Secure Containers, but all other hadoop services, including YARN job execution outside secure containers continue to work.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-26031|2024-07-29T13:09:24.015Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 08:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-35296|2024-07-26T20:18:13.746Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20traffic%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35296</link>
      <description>Invalid Accept-Encoding header can cause Apache Traffic Server to fail cache lookup and force forwarding requests.

This issue affects Apache Traffic Server: from 8.0.0 through 8.1.10, from 9.0.0 through 9.2.4.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 8.1.11 or 9.2.5, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-35296|2024-07-26T20:18:13.746Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 09:11:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-24772|2024-07-26T17:55:25.646Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20superset</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24772</link>
      <description>A guest user could exploit a chart data REST API and send arbitrary SQL statements that on error could leak information from the underlying analytics database.This issue affects Apache Superset: before 3.0.4, from 3.1.0 before 3.1.1.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.1.1 or 3.0.4, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24772|2024-07-26T17:55:25.646Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 11:26:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25090|2024-07-26T17:40:11.844Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20roller</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25090</link>
      <description>Insufficient input validation and sanitation in Profile name &amp; screenname, Bookmark name &amp; description and blogroll name features in all versions of Apache Roller on all platforms allows an authenticated user to perform an XSS attack. Mitigation: if you do not have Roller configured for untrusted users, then you need to do nothing because you trust your users to author raw HTML and other web content. If you are running with untrusted users then you should upgrade to Roller 6.1.3.

This issue affects Apache Roller: from 5.0.0 before 6.1.3.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 6.1.3, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25090|2024-07-26T17:40:11.844Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 08:36:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38522|2024-07-26T13:37:33.033Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20traffic%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38522</link>
      <description>Apache Traffic Server accepts characters that are not allowed for HTTP field names and forwards malformed requests to origin servers. This can be utilized for request smuggling and may also lead cache poisoning if the origin servers are vulnerable.

This issue affects Apache Traffic Server: from 8.0.0 through 8.1.10, from 9.0.0 through 9.2.4.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 8.1.11 or 9.2.5, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38522|2024-07-26T13:37:33.033Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 09:11:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25090|2024-07-26T08:36:47.021Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20roller</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25090</link>
      <description>Insufficient input validation and sanitation in Profile name &amp; screenname, Bookmark name &amp; description and blogroll name features in all versions of Apache Roller on all platforms allows an authenticated user to perform an XSS attack. Mitigation: if you do not have Roller configured for untrusted users, then you need to do nothing because you trust your users to author raw HTML and other web content. If you are running with untrusted users then you should upgrade to Roller 6.1.3.

This issue affects Apache Roller: from 5.0.0 before 6.1.3.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 6.1.3, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25090|2024-07-26T08:36:47.021Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 08:36:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22393|2024-07-25T18:23:19.530Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20answer</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22393</link>
      <description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Apache Answer.This issue affects Apache Answer: through 1.2.1.

Pixel Flood Attack by uploading large pixel files will cause server out of memory. A logged-in user can cause such an attack by uploading an image when posting content.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version [1.2.5], which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22393|2024-07-25T18:23:19.530Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 09:51:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-41178|2024-07-25T15:25:05.283Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20arrow%20rust%20object%20store</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41178</link>
      <description>Exposure of temporary credentials in logs in Apache Arrow Rust Object Store (`object_store` crate), version 0.10.1 and earlier on all platforms using AWS WebIdentityTokens. 

On certain error conditions, the logs may contain the OIDC token passed to  AssumeRoleWithWebIdentity https://docs.aws.amazon.com/STS/latest/APIReference/API_AssumeRoleWithWebIdentity.html . This allows someone with access to the logs to impersonate that identity, including performing their own calls to AssumeRoleWithWebIdentity, until the OIDC token expires. Typically OIDC tokens are valid for up to an hour, although this will vary depending on the issuer.

Users are recommended to use a different AWS authentication mechanism, disable logging or upgrade to version 0.10.2, which fixes this issue.

Details:

When using AWS WebIdentityTokens with the object_store crate, in the event of a failure and automatic retry, the underlying reqwest error, including the full URL with the credentials, potentially in the parameters, is written to the logs. 

Thanks to Paul Hatcherian for reporting this vulnerability</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-41178|2024-07-25T15:25:05.283Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 16:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-41172|2024-07-24T18:59:47.054Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20cxf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41172</link>
      <description>In versions of Apache CXF before 3.6.4 and 4.0.5 (3.5.x and lower versions are not impacted), a CXF HTTP client conduit may prevent HTTPClient instances from being garbage collected and it is possible that memory consumption will continue to increase, eventually causing the application to run  out of memory</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-41172|2024-07-24T18:59:47.054Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 08:50:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39676|2024-07-24T14:03:53.907Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20pinot</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39676</link>
      <description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Apache Pinot.

This issue affects Apache Pinot: from 0.1 before 1.0.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.0.0 and configure RBAC, which fixes the issue.

Details: 

When using a request to path “/appconfigs” to the controller, it can lead to the disclosure of sensitive information such as system information (e.g. arch, os version), environment information (e.g. maxHeapSize) and Pinot configurations (e.g. zookeeper path). This issue was addressed by the  Role-based Access Control https://docs.pinot.apache.org/operators/tutorials/authentication/basic-auth-access-control , so that /appConfigs` and all other APIs can be access controlled. Only authorized users have access to it. Note the user needs to add the admin role accordingly to the RBAC guide to control access to this endpoint, and in the future version of Pinot, a default admin role is planned to be added.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39676|2024-07-24T14:03:53.907Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 07:41:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38473|2024-07-24T14:02:38.927Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20http%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38473</link>
      <description>Encoding problem in mod_proxy in Apache HTTP Server 2.4.59 and earlier allows request URLs with incorrect encoding to be sent to backend services, potentially bypassing authentication via crafted requests.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.60, which fixes this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-38473|2024-07-24T14:02:38.927Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:14:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-48362|2024-07-24T07:45:43.686Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20drill</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48362</link>
      <description>XXE in the XML Format Plugin in Apache Drill version 1.19.0 and greater allows a user to read any file on a remote file system or execute commands via a malicious XML file.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.21.2, which fixes this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-48362|2024-07-24T07:45:43.686Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 07:45:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39676|2024-07-24T07:41:09.856Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20pinot</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39676</link>
      <description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Apache Pinot.

This issue affects Apache Pinot: from 0.1 before 1.0.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.0.0 and configure RBAC, which fixes the issue.

Details: 

When using a request to path “/appconfigs” to the controller, it can lead to the disclosure of sensitive information such as system information (e.g. arch, os version), environment information (e.g. maxHeapSize) and Pinot configurations (e.g. zookeeper path). This issue was addressed by the  Role-based Access Control https://docs.pinot.apache.org/operators/tutorials/authentication/basic-auth-access-control , so that /appConfigs` and all other APIs can be access controlled. Only authorized users have access to it. Note the user needs to add the admin role accordingly to the RBAC guide to control access to this endpoint, and in the future version of Pinot, a default admin role is planned to be added.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39676|2024-07-24T07:41:09.856Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 07:41:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-41178|2024-07-23T17:07:59.561Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20arrow%20rust%20object%20store</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41178</link>
      <description>Exposure of temporary credentials in logs in Apache Arrow Rust Object Store (`object_store` crate), version 0.10.1 and earlier on all platforms using AWS WebIdentityTokens. 

On certain error conditions, the logs may contain the OIDC token passed to  AssumeRoleWithWebIdentity https://docs.aws.amazon.com/STS/latest/APIReference/API_AssumeRoleWithWebIdentity.html . This allows someone with access to the logs to impersonate that identity, including performing their own calls to AssumeRoleWithWebIdentity, until the OIDC token expires. Typically OIDC tokens are valid for up to an hour, although this will vary depending on the issuer.

Users are recommended to use a different AWS authentication mechanism, disable logging or upgrade to version 0.10.2, which fixes this issue.

Details:

When using AWS WebIdentityTokens with the object_store crate, in the event of a failure and automatic retry, the underlying reqwest error, including the full URL with the credentials, potentially in the parameters, is written to the logs. 

Thanks to Paul Hatcherian for reporting this vulnerability</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-41178|2024-07-23T17:07:59.561Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 16:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31869|2024-07-23T17:44:12.951Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20airflow</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31869</link>
      <description>Airflow versions 2.7.0 through 2.8.4 have a vulnerability that allows an authenticated user to see sensitive provider configuration via the "configuration" UI page when "non-sensitive-only" was set as "webserver.expose_config" configuration (The celery provider is the only community provider currently that has sensitive configurations). You should migrate to Airflow 2.9 or change your "expose_config" configuration to False as a workaround. This is similar, but different to  CVE-2023-46288 https://github.com/advisories/GHSA-9qqg-mh7c-chfq  which concerned API, not UI configuration page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31869|2024-07-23T17:44:12.951Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 07:19:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-40725|2024-07-23T15:11:02.015Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20http%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40725</link>
      <description>A partial fix for  CVE-2024-39884 in the core of Apache HTTP Server 2.4.61 ignores some use of the legacy content-type based configuration of handlers. "AddType" and similar configuration, under some circumstances where files are requested indirectly, result in source code disclosure of local content. For example, PHP scripts may be served instead of interpreted.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.62, which fixes this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-40725|2024-07-23T15:11:02.015Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 09:32:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23321|2024-07-23T13:46:38.314Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20rocketmq</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23321</link>
      <description>For RocketMQ versions 5.2.0 and below, under certain conditions, there is a risk of exposure of sensitive Information to an unauthorized actor even if RocketMQ is enabled with authentication and authorization functions.

An attacker, possessing regular user privileges or listed in the IP whitelist, could potentially acquire the administrator's account and password through specific interfaces. Such an action would grant them full control over RocketMQ, provided they have access to the broker IP address list.

To mitigate these security threats, it is strongly advised that users upgrade to version 5.3.0 or newer. Additionally, we recommend users to use RocketMQ ACL 2.0 instead of the original RocketMQ ACL when upgrading to version Apache RocketMQ 5.3.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23321|2024-07-23T13:46:38.314Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:24:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38503|2024-07-22T18:24:30.812Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20syncope</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38503</link>
      <description>When editing a user, group or any object in the Syncope Console, HTML tags could be added to any text field and could lead to potential exploits.
The same vulnerability was found in the Syncope Enduser, when editing “Personal Information” or “User Requests”.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.0.8, which fixes this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-38503|2024-07-22T18:24:30.812Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:46:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38477|2024-07-22T16:23:33.260Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20http%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38477</link>
      <description>null pointer dereference in mod_proxy in Apache HTTP Server 2.4.59 and earlier allows an attacker to crash the server via a malicious request.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.60, which fixes this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-38477|2024-07-22T16:23:33.260Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-36387|2024-07-22T16:22:16.714Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20http%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36387</link>
      <description>Serving WebSocket protocol upgrades over a HTTP/2 connection could result in a Null Pointer dereference, leading to a crash of the server process, degrading performance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-36387|2024-07-22T16:22:16.714Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-40898|2024-07-22T14:29:06.016Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20http%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40898</link>
      <description>SSRF in Apache HTTP Server on Windows with mod_rewrite in server/vhost context, allows to potentially leak NTML hashes to a malicious server via SSRF and malicious requests.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.62 which fixes this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-40898|2024-07-22T14:29:06.016Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 09:32:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34457|2024-07-22T09:48:23.130Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20streampark</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34457</link>
      <description>On versions before 2.1.4, after a regular user successfully logs in, they can manually make a request using the authorization token to view everyone's user flink information, including executeSQL and config.

Mitigation:

all users should upgrade to 2.1.4</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34457|2024-07-22T09:48:23.130Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:48:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38503|2024-07-22T09:54:13.388Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20syncope</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38503</link>
      <description>When editing a user, group or any object in the Syncope Console, HTML tags could be added to any text field and could lead to potential exploits.
The same vulnerability was found in the Syncope Enduser, when editing “Personal Information” or “User Requests”.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.0.8, which fixes this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-38503|2024-07-22T09:54:13.388Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:46:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23321|2024-07-22T09:24:15.807Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20rocketmq</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23321</link>
      <description>For RocketMQ versions 5.2.0 and below, under certain conditions, there is a risk of exposure of sensitive Information to an unauthorized actor even if RocketMQ is enabled with authentication and authorization functions.

An attacker, possessing regular user privileges or listed in the IP whitelist, could potentially acquire the administrator's account and password through specific interfaces. Such an action would grant them full control over RocketMQ, provided they have access to the broker IP address list.

To mitigate these security threats, it is strongly advised that users upgrade to version 5.3.0 or newer. Additionally, we recommend users to use RocketMQ ACL 2.0 instead of the original RocketMQ ACL when upgrading to version Apache RocketMQ 5.3.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23321|2024-07-22T09:24:15.807Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:24:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28752|2024-07-20T03:55:32.595Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20cxf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28752</link>
      <description>A SSRF vulnerability using the Aegis DataBinding in versions of Apache CXF before 4.0.4, 3.6.3 and 3.5.8 allows an attacker to perform SSRF style attacks on webservices that take at least one parameter of any type. Users of other data bindings (including the default databinding) are not impacted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28752|2024-07-20T03:55:32.595Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 10:27:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-40898|2024-07-20T03:55:31.007Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20http%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40898</link>
      <description>SSRF in Apache HTTP Server on Windows with mod_rewrite in server/vhost context, allows to potentially leak NTML hashes to a malicious server via SSRF and malicious requests.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.62 which fixes this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-40898|2024-07-20T03:55:31.007Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 09:32:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32007|2024-07-19T17:02:50.657Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20cxf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32007</link>
      <description>An improper input validation of the p2c parameter in the Apache CXF JOSE code before 4.0.5, 3.6.4 and 3.5.9 allows an attacker to perform a denial of service attack by specifying a large value for this parameter in a token.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32007|2024-07-19T17:02:50.657Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 08:50:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39877|2024-07-19T03:55:41.953Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20airflow</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39877</link>
      <description>Apache Airflow 2.4.0, and versions before 2.9.3, has a vulnerability that allows authenticated DAG authors to craft a doc_md parameter in a way that could execute arbitrary code in the scheduler context, which should be forbidden according to the Airflow Security model. Users should upgrade to version 2.9.3 or later which has removed the vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39877|2024-07-19T03:55:41.953Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 07:54:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-40898|2024-07-18T18:48:40.387Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20http%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40898</link>
      <description>SSRF in Apache HTTP Server on Windows with mod_rewrite in server/vhost context, allows to potentially leak NTML hashes to a malicious server via SSRF and malicious requests.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.62 which fixes this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-40898|2024-07-18T18:48:40.387Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 09:32:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29178|2024-07-18T13:37:53.581Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20streampark</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29178</link>
      <description>On versions before 2.1.4, a user could log in and perform a template injection attack resulting in Remote Code Execution on the server, The attacker must successfully log into the system to launch an attack, so this is a moderate-impact vulnerability.

Mitigation:

all users should upgrade to 2.1.4</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29178|2024-07-18T13:37:53.581Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-40725|2024-07-18T09:32:43.929Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20http%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40725</link>
      <description>A partial fix for  CVE-2024-39884 in the core of Apache HTTP Server 2.4.61 ignores some use of the legacy content-type based configuration of handlers. "AddType" and similar configuration, under some circumstances where files are requested indirectly, result in source code disclosure of local content. For example, PHP scripts may be served instead of interpreted.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.62, which fixes this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-40725|2024-07-18T09:32:43.929Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 09:32:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-40898|2024-07-18T09:32:06.990Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20http%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40898</link>
      <description>SSRF in Apache HTTP Server on Windows with mod_rewrite in server/vhost context, allows to potentially leak NTML hashes to a malicious server via SSRF and malicious requests.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.62 which fixes this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-40898|2024-07-18T09:32:06.990Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 09:32:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23807|2024-07-17T19:12:48.404Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20xerces%20c%2B%2B</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23807</link>
      <description>The Apache Xerces C++ XML parser on versions 3.0.0 before 3.2.5 contains a use-after-free error triggered during the scanning of external DTDs.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.2.5 which fixes the issue, or mitigate the issue by disabling DTD processing. This can be accomplished via the DOM using a standard parser feature, or via SAX using the XERCES_DISABLE_DTD environment variable.

This issue has been disclosed before as CVE-2018-1311, but unfortunately that advisory incorrectly stated the issue would be fixed in version 3.2.3 or 3.2.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23807|2024-07-17T19:12:48.404Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 13:50:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27438|2024-07-17T17:40:16.663Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20doris</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27438</link>
      <description>Download of Code Without Integrity Check vulnerability in Apache Doris.
The jdbc driver files used for JDBC catalog is not checked and may resulting in remote command execution.
Once the attacker is authorized to create a JDBC catalog, he/she can use arbitrary driver jar file with unchecked code snippet. This code snippet will be run when catalog is initializing without any check.
This issue affects Apache Doris: from 1.2.0 through 2.0.4.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.0.5 or 2.1.x, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27438|2024-07-17T17:40:16.663Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 09:39:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39877|2024-07-17T13:26:58.909Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20airflow</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39877</link>
      <description>Apache Airflow 2.4.0, and versions before 2.9.3, has a vulnerability that allows authenticated DAG authors to craft a doc_md parameter in a way that could execute arbitrary code in the scheduler context, which should be forbidden according to the Airflow Security model. Users should upgrade to version 2.9.3 or later which has removed the vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39877|2024-07-17T13:26:58.909Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 07:54:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39863|2024-07-17T13:30:13.238Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20airflow</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39863</link>
      <description>Apache Airflow versions before 2.9.3 have a vulnerability that allows an authenticated attacker to inject a malicious link when installing a provider. Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.9.3, which fixes this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39863|2024-07-17T13:30:13.238Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 07:53:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29737|2024-07-17T08:21:12.035Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20streampark%20%28incubating%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29737</link>
      <description>In streampark, the project module integrates Maven's compilation capabilities. The input parameter validation is not strict, allowing attackers to insert commands for remote command execution, The prerequisite for a successful attack is that the user needs to log in to the streampark system and have system-level permissions. Generally, only users of that system have the authorization to log in, and users would not manually input a dangerous operation command. Therefore, the risk level of this vulnerability is very low.

Mitigation:

all users should upgrade to 2.1.4

Background info:

Log in to Streampark using the default username (e.g. test1, test2, test3) and the default password (streampark). Navigate to the Project module, then add a new project. Enter the git repository address of the project and input `touch /tmp/success_2.1.2` as the "Build Argument". Note that there is no verification and interception of the special character "`". As a result, you will find that this injection command will be successfully executed after executing the build.

In the latest version, the special symbol ` is intercepted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29737|2024-07-17T08:21:12.035Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 08:21:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-52291|2024-07-17T08:16:12.520Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20streampark%20%28incubating%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52291</link>
      <description>In streampark, the project module integrates Maven's compilation capabilities. The input parameter validation is not strict, allowing attackers to insert commands for remote command execution, The prerequisite for a successful attack is that the user needs to log in to the streampark system and have system-level permissions. Generally, only users of that system have the authorization to log in, and users would not manually input a dangerous operation command. Therefore, the risk level of this vulnerability is very low.

Background:

In the "Project" module, the maven build args  “&lt;” operator causes command injection. e.g : “&lt; (curl  http://xxx.com )” will be executed as a command injection,

Mitigation:

all users should upgrade to 2.1.4,  The "&lt;" operator will blocked。</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-52291|2024-07-17T08:16:12.520Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 08:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39887|2024-07-16T17:48:52.676Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20superset</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39887</link>
      <description>An SQL Injection vulnerability in Apache Superset exists due to improper neutralization of special elements used in SQL commands. Specifically, certain engine-specific functions are not checked, which allows attackers to bypass Apache Superset's SQL authorization. To mitigate this, a new configuration key named DISALLOWED_SQL_FUNCTIONS has been introduced. This key disallows the use of the following PostgreSQL functions: version, query_to_xml, inet_server_addr, and inet_client_addr. Additional functions can be added to this list for increased protection.

This issue affects Apache Superset: before 4.0.2.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.0.2, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39887|2024-07-16T17:48:52.676Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 09:20:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39887|2024-07-16T09:20:10.688Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20superset</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39887</link>
      <description>An SQL Injection vulnerability in Apache Superset exists due to improper neutralization of special elements used in SQL commands. Specifically, certain engine-specific functions are not checked, which allows attackers to bypass Apache Superset's SQL authorization. To mitigate this, a new configuration key named DISALLOWED_SQL_FUNCTIONS has been introduced. This key disallows the use of the following PostgreSQL functions: version, query_to_xml, inet_server_addr, and inet_client_addr. Additional functions can be added to this list for increased protection.

This issue affects Apache Superset: before 4.0.2.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.0.2, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39887|2024-07-16T09:20:10.688Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 09:20:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-49566|2024-07-15T20:23:10.817Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20linkis%20datasource</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49566</link>
      <description>In Apache Linkis &lt;=1.5.0, due to the lack of effective filtering
of parameters, an attacker configuring malicious 

db2

 parameters in the DataSource Manager Module will result in jndi injection. Therefore, the parameters in the DB2 URL should be blacklisted. 

This attack requires the attacker to obtain an authorized account from Linkis before it can be carried out.

 Versions of Apache Linkis 

&lt;=1.5.0

 will be affected.
We recommend users upgrade the version of Linkis to version 1.6.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-49566|2024-07-15T20:23:10.817Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 07:56:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-49566|2024-07-15T07:56:51.500Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20linkis%20datasource</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49566</link>
      <description>In Apache Linkis &lt;=1.5.0, due to the lack of effective filtering
of parameters, an attacker configuring malicious 

db2

 parameters in the DataSource Manager Module will result in jndi injection. Therefore, the parameters in the DB2 URL should be blacklisted. 

This attack requires the attacker to obtain an authorized account from Linkis before it can be carried out.

 Versions of Apache Linkis 

&lt;=1.5.0

 will be affected.
We recommend users upgrade the version of Linkis to version 1.6.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-49566|2024-07-15T07:56:51.500Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 07:56:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41916|2024-07-15T07:53:57.843Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20linkis%20datasource</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41916</link>
      <description>In Apache Linkis =1.4.0, due to the lack of effective filtering
of parameters, an attacker configuring malicious Mysql JDBC parameters in the DataSource Manager Module will trigger arbitrary file reading. Therefore, the parameters in the Mysql JDBC URL should be blacklisted. This attack requires the attacker to obtain an authorized account from Linkis before it can be carried out. Versions of Apache Linkis = 1.4.0 will be affected. 
We recommend users upgrade the version of Linkis to version 1.5.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41916|2024-07-15T07:53:57.843Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 07:53:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-46801|2024-07-15T07:55:29.702Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20linkis%20datasource</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46801</link>
      <description>In Apache Linkis &lt;= 1.5.0, data source management module, when adding Mysql data source, exists remote code execution vulnerability for java version &lt; 1.8.0_241. The deserialization vulnerability exploited through jrmp can inject malicious files into the server and execute them. 

This attack requires the attacker to obtain an authorized account from Linkis before it can be carried out.  We recommend that users upgrade the java version to &gt;= 1.8.0_241. Or users upgrade Linkis to version 1.6.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-46801|2024-07-15T07:55:29.702Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 07:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-36522|2024-07-12T12:13:51.884Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20wicket</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36522</link>
      <description>The default configuration of XSLTResourceStream.java is vulnerable to remote code execution via XSLT injection when processing input from an untrusted source without validation.
Users are recommended to upgrade to versions 10.1.0, 9.18.0 or 8.16.0, which fix this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-36522|2024-07-12T12:13:51.884Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 12:13:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50740|2024-07-09T20:29:34.134Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20linkis%20datasource</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50740</link>
      <description>In Apache Linkis &lt;=1.4.0, The password is printed to the log when using the Oracle data source of the Linkis data source module. 
We recommend users upgrade the version of Linkis to version 1.5.0</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50740|2024-07-09T20:29:34.134Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 13:44:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38472|2024-07-09T15:19:22.367Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20http%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38472</link>
      <description>SSRF in Apache HTTP Server on Windows allows to potentially leak NTML hashes to a malicious server via SSRF and malicious requests or content 
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.60 which fixes this issue.  Note: Existing configurations that access UNC paths will have to configure new directive "UNCList" to allow access during request processing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-38472|2024-07-09T15:19:22.367Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:12:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34750|2024-07-08T16:54:49.822Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20tomcat</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34750</link>
      <description>Improper Handling of Exceptional Conditions, Uncontrolled Resource Consumption vulnerability in Apache Tomcat. When processing an HTTP/2 stream, Tomcat did not handle some cases of excessive HTTP headers correctly. This led to a miscounting of active HTTP/2 streams which in turn led to the use of an incorrect infinite timeout which allowed connections to remain open which should have been closed.

This issue affects Apache Tomcat: from 11.0.0-M1 through 11.0.0-M20, from 10.1.0-M1 through 10.1.24, from 9.0.0-M1 through 9.0.89.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 11.0.0-M21, 10.1.25 or 9.0.90, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34750|2024-07-08T16:54:49.822Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 19:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37389|2024-07-08T07:29:00.146Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20nifi</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37389</link>
      <description>Apache NiFi 1.10.0 through 1.26.0 and 2.0.0-M1 through 2.0.0-M3 support a description field in the Parameter Context configuration that is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. An authenticated user, authorized to configure a Parameter Context, can enter arbitrary JavaScript code, which the client browser will execute within the session context of the authenticated user. Upgrading to Apache NiFi 1.27.0 or 2.0.0-M4 is the recommended mitigation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37389|2024-07-08T07:29:00.146Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 07:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25710|2024-07-05T17:21:44.416Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20commons%20compress</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25710</link>
      <description>Loop with Unreachable Exit Condition ('Infinite Loop') vulnerability in Apache Commons Compress.This issue affects Apache Commons Compress: from 1.3 through 1.25.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.26.0 which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25710|2024-07-05T17:21:44.416Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 08:33:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51437|2024-07-05T17:22:56.108Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20pulsar</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51437</link>
      <description>Observable timing discrepancy vulnerability in Apache Pulsar SASL Authentication Provider can allow an attacker to forge a SASL Role Token that will pass signature verification.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.11.3, 3.0.2, or 3.1.1 which fixes the issue. Users should also consider updating the configured secret in the `saslJaasServerRoleTokenSignerSecretPath` file.

Any component matching an above version running the SASL Authentication Provider is affected. That includes the Pulsar Broker, Proxy, Websocket Proxy, or Function Worker.

2.11 Pulsar users should upgrade to at least 2.11.3.
3.0 Pulsar users should upgrade to at least 3.0.2.
3.1 Pulsar users should upgrade to at least 3.1.1.
Any users running Pulsar 2.8, 2.9, 2.10, and earlier should upgrade to one of the above patched versions.

For additional details on this attack vector, please refer to  https://codahale.com/a-lesson-in-timing-attacks/ .</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51437|2024-07-05T17:22:56.108Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 09:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22369|2024-07-05T17:21:47.970Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20camel</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22369</link>
      <description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Apache Camel SQL ComponentThis issue affects Apache Camel: from 3.0.0 before 3.21.4, from 3.22.0 before 3.22.1, from 4.0.0 before 4.0.4, from 4.1.0 before 4.4.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.4.0, which fixes the issue. If users are on the 4.0.x LTS releases stream, then they are suggested to upgrade to 4.0.4. If users are on 3.x, they are suggested to move to 3.21.4 or 3.22.1</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22369|2024-07-05T17:21:47.970Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 14:58:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-26308|2024-07-05T17:21:56.918Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20commons%20compress</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26308</link>
      <description>Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling vulnerability in Apache Commons Compress.This issue affects Apache Commons Compress: from 1.21 before 1.26.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.26, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-26308|2024-07-05T17:21:56.918Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 08:31:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23452|2024-07-05T17:20:45.348Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20brpc</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23452</link>
      <description>Request smuggling vulnerability in HTTP server in Apache bRPC 0.9.5~1.7.0 on all platforms allows attacker to smuggle request.

Vulnerability Cause Description：

The http_parser does not comply with the RFC-7230 HTTP 1.1 specification.

Attack scenario:
If a message is received with both a Transfer-Encoding and a Content-Length header field, such a message might indicate an attempt to perform request smuggling or response splitting.
One particular attack scenario is that a bRPC made http server on the backend receiving requests in one persistent connection from frontend server that uses TE to parse request with the logic that 'chunk' is contained in the TE field. in that case an attacker can smuggle a request into the connection to the backend server. 

Solution:
You can choose one solution from below:
1. Upgrade bRPC to version 1.8.0, which fixes this issue. Download link:  https://github.com/apache/brpc/releases/tag/1.8.0
 2. Apply this patch:  https://github.com/apache/brpc/pull/2518</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23452|2024-07-05T17:20:45.348Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 09:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-26578|2024-07-05T17:21:57.385Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20answer</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26578</link>
      <description>Concurrent Execution using Shared Resource with Improper Synchronization ('Race Condition') vulnerability in Apache Answer.This issue affects Apache Answer: through 1.2.1.

Repeated submission during registration resulted in the registration of the same user. When users register, if they rapidly submit multiple registrations using scripts, it can result in the creation of multiple user accounts simultaneously with the same name.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version [1.2.5], which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-26578|2024-07-05T17:21:57.385Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 09:28:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23349|2024-07-05T17:21:55.309Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20answer</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23349</link>
      <description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Apache Answer.This issue affects Apache Answer: through 1.2.1.

XSS attack when user enters summary. A logged-in user, when modifying their own submitted question, can input malicious code in the summary to create such an attack.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version [1.2.5], which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23349|2024-07-05T17:21:55.309Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 09:48:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39884|2024-07-04T08:36:49.772Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20http%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39884</link>
      <description>A regression in the core of Apache HTTP Server 2.4.60 ignores some use of the legacy content-type based configuration of handlers.   "AddType" and similar configuration, under some circumstances where files are requested indirectly, result in source code disclosure of local content. For example, PHP scripts may be served instead of interpreted.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.61, which fixes this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39884|2024-07-04T08:36:49.772Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 08:36:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38476|2024-07-02T18:27:03.011Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20http%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38476</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in core of Apache HTTP Server 2.4.59 and earlier are vulnerably to information disclosure, SSRF or local script execution via backend applications whose response headers are malicious or exploitable.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.60, which fixes this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-38476|2024-07-02T18:27:03.011Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39573|2024-07-01T20:44:44.754Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20http%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39573</link>
      <description>Potential SSRF in mod_rewrite in Apache HTTP Server 2.4.59 and earlier allows an attacker to cause unsafe RewriteRules to unexpectedly setup URL's to be handled by mod_proxy.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.60, which fixes this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39573|2024-07-01T20:44:44.754Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27135|2024-06-24T19:41:30.721Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20pulsar</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27135</link>
      <description>Improper input validation in the Pulsar Function Worker allows a malicious authenticated user to execute arbitrary Java code on the Pulsar Function worker, outside of the sandboxes designated for running user-provided functions. This vulnerability also applies to the Pulsar Broker when it is configured with "functionsWorkerEnabled=true".

This issue affects Apache Pulsar versions from 2.4.0 to 2.10.5, from 2.11.0 to 2.11.3, from 3.0.0 to 3.0.2, from 3.1.0 to 3.1.2, and 3.2.0. 

2.10 Pulsar Function Worker users should upgrade to at least 2.10.6.
2.11 Pulsar Function Worker users should upgrade to at least 2.11.4.
3.0 Pulsar Function Worker users should upgrade to at least 3.0.3.
3.1 Pulsar Function Worker users should upgrade to at least 3.1.3.
3.2 Pulsar Function Worker users should upgrade to at least 3.2.1.

Users operating versions prior to those listed above should upgrade to the aforementioned patched versions or newer versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27135|2024-06-24T19:41:30.721Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 18:18:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29868|2024-06-24T09:59:39.941Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20streampipes</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29868</link>
      <description>Use of Cryptographically Weak Pseudo-Random Number Generator (PRNG) vulnerability in Apache StreamPipes user self-registration and password recovery mechanism.
This allows an attacker to guess the recovery token in a reasonable time and thereby to take over the attacked user's account.
This issue affects Apache StreamPipes: from 0.69.0 through 0.93.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 0.95.0, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29868|2024-06-24T09:59:39.941Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 09:59:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38379|2024-06-22T16:26:16.752Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20allura</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38379</link>
      <description>Apache Allura's neighborhood settings are vulnerable to a stored XSS attack.  Only neighborhood admins can access these settings, so the scope of risk is limited to configurations where neighborhood admins are not fully trusted.

This issue affects Apache Allura: from 1.4.0 through 1.17.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.17.1, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-38379|2024-06-22T16:26:16.752Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 09:09:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34693|2024-06-20T12:55:55.620Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20superset</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34693</link>
      <description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Apache Superset, allows for an authenticated attacker to create a MariaDB connection with local_infile enabled. If both the MariaDB server (off by default) and the local mysql client on the web server are set to allow for local infile, it's possible for the attacker to execute a specific MySQL/MariaDB SQL command that is able to read files from the server and insert their content on a MariaDB database table.This issue affects Apache Superset: before 3.1.3 and version 4.0.0

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.0.1 or 3.1.3, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34693|2024-06-20T12:55:55.620Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 08:51:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35701|2024-06-17T19:53:00.987Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20hive</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35701</link>
      <description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Apache Hive.

The vulnerability affects the Hive JDBC driver component and it can potentially lead to arbitrary code execution on the machine/endpoint that the JDBC driver (client) is running. The malicious user must have sufficient permissions to specify/edit JDBC URL(s) in an endpoint relying on the Hive JDBC driver and the JDBC client process must run under a privileged user to fully exploit the vulnerability. 

The attacker can setup a malicious HTTP server and specify a JDBC URL pointing towards this server. When a JDBC connection is attempted, the malicious HTTP server can provide a special response with customized payload that can trigger the execution of certain commands in the JDBC client.This issue affects Apache Hive: from 4.0.0-alpha-1 before 4.0.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.0.0, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35701|2024-06-17T19:53:00.987Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 08:11:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25142|2024-06-14T08:25:35.633Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20airflow</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25142</link>
      <description>Use of Web Browser Cache Containing Sensitive Information vulnerability in Apache Airflow. 

Airflow did not return "Cache-Control" header for dynamic content, which in case of some browsers could result in potentially storing sensitive data in local cache of the browser.

This issue affects Apache Airflow: before 2.9.2.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.9.2, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25142|2024-06-14T08:25:35.633Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 08:25:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23672|2024-03-13T15:48:42.610Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20tomcat</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23672</link>
      <description>Denial of Service via incomplete cleanup vulnerability in Apache Tomcat. It was possible for WebSocket clients to keep WebSocket connections open leading to increased resource consumption.This issue affects Apache Tomcat: from 11.0.0-M1 through 11.0.0-M16, from 10.1.0-M1 through 10.1.18, from 9.0.0-M1 through 9.0.85, from 8.5.0 through 8.5.98.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 11.0.0-M17, 10.1.19, 9.0.86 or 8.5.99 which fix the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23672|2024-03-13T15:48:42.610Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:48:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-24549|2024-03-13T15:46:53.085Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20tomcat</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-24549</link>
      <description>Denial of Service due to improper input validation vulnerability for HTTP/2 requests in Apache Tomcat. When processing an HTTP/2 request, if the request exceeded any of the configured limits for headers, the associated HTTP/2 stream was not reset until after all of the headers had been processed.This issue affects Apache Tomcat: from 11.0.0-M1 through 11.0.0-M16, from 10.1.0-M1 through 10.1.18, from 9.0.0-M1 through 9.0.85, from 8.5.0 through 8.5.98.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 11.0.0-M17, 10.1.19, 9.0.86 or 8.5.99 which fix the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24549|2024-03-13T15:46:53.085Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:46:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-36265|2024-06-12T14:12:11.078Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20submarine%20server%20core</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-36265</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in Apache Submarine Server Core.

This issue affects Apache Submarine Server Core: from 0.8.0.

As this project is retired, we do not plan to release a version that fixes this issue. Users are recommended to find an alternative or restrict access to the instance to trusted users.

NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-36265|2024-06-12T14:12:11.078Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 14:12:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-36264|2024-06-12T14:06:31.545Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20submarine%20commons%20utils</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-36264</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** Improper Authentication vulnerability in Apache Submarine Commons Utils.

This issue affects Apache Submarine Commons Utils: from 0.8.0.

As this project is retired, we do not plan to release a version that fixes this issue. Users are recommended to find an alternative or restrict access to the instance to trusted users.

NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-36264|2024-06-12T14:06:31.545Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 14:06:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-36263|2024-06-12T14:05:00.096Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20submarine%20server%20core</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-36263</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Apache Submarine Server Core.

This issue affects Apache Submarine Server Core: all versions.

As this project is retired, we do not plan to release a version that fixes this issue. Users are recommended to find an alternative or restrict access to the instance to trusted users.

NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-36263|2024-06-12T14:05:00.096Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25141|2024-02-20T20:30:28.924Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20airflow%20mongo%20provider</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25141</link>
      <description>When ssl was enabled for Mongo Hook, default settings included "allow_insecure" which caused that certificates were not validated. This was unexpected and undocumented.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.0.0, which fixes this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25141|2024-02-20T20:30:28.924Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 20:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25710|2024-02-19T08:33:40.627Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20commons%20compress</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25710</link>
      <description>Loop with Unreachable Exit Condition ('Infinite Loop') vulnerability in Apache Commons Compress.This issue affects Apache Commons Compress: from 1.3 through 1.25.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.26.0 which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25710|2024-02-19T08:33:40.627Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 08:33:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25065|2024-02-28T15:42:50.448Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20ofbiz</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25065</link>
      <description>Possible path traversal in Apache OFBiz allowing authentication bypass.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 18.12.12, that fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25065|2024-02-28T15:42:50.448Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 15:42:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31861|2024-06-04T17:35:55.604Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20zeppelin</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31861</link>
      <description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Apache Zeppelin.

The attackers can use Shell interpreter as a code generation gateway, and execute the generated code as a normal way.
This issue affects Apache Zeppelin: from 0.10.1 before 0.11.1.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 0.11.1, which doesn't have Shell interpreter by default.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31861|2024-06-04T17:35:55.604Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 08:19:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31860|2024-06-04T17:36:17.512Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20zeppelin</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31860</link>
      <description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Apache Zeppelin.

By adding relative path indicators(E.g ..), attackers can see the contents for any files in the filesystem that the server account can access. 
This issue affects Apache Zeppelin: from 0.9.0 before 0.11.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 0.11.0, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31860|2024-06-04T17:36:17.512Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 09:08:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31867|2024-06-04T17:36:25.273Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20zeppelin</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31867</link>
      <description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Apache Zeppelin.

The attackers can execute malicious queries by setting improper configuration properties to LDAP search filter.
This issue affects Apache Zeppelin: from 0.8.2 before 0.11.1.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 0.11.1, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31867|2024-06-04T17:36:25.273Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 16:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31866|2024-04-09T16:09:12.117Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20zeppelin</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31866</link>
      <description>Improper Encoding or Escaping of Output vulnerability in Apache Zeppelin.

The attackers can execute shell scripts or malicious code by overriding configuration like ZEPPELIN_INTP_CLASSPATH_OVERRIDES.
This issue affects Apache Zeppelin: from 0.8.2 before 0.11.1.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 0.11.1, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31866|2024-04-09T16:09:12.117Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 16:09:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31309|2024-06-04T17:36:32.885Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20traffic%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31309</link>
      <description>HTTP/2 CONTINUATION DoS attack can cause Apache Traffic Server to consume more resources on the server.  Version from 8.0.0 through 8.1.9, from 9.0.0 through 9.2.3 are affected.

Users can set a new setting (proxy.config.http2.max_continuation_frames_per_minute) to limit the number of CONTINUATION frames per minute.  ATS does have a fixed amount of memory a request can use and ATS adheres to these limits in previous releases.
Users are recommended to upgrade to versions 8.1.10 or 9.2.4 which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31309|2024-06-04T17:36:32.885Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 12:07:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31391|2024-06-04T17:36:34.613Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20solr%20operator</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31391</link>
      <description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in the Apache Solr Operator.

This issue affects all versions of the Apache Solr Operator from 0.3.0 through 0.8.0.

When asked to bootstrap Solr security, the operator will enable basic authentication and create several accounts for accessing Solr: including the "solr" and "admin" accounts for use by end-users, and a "k8s-oper" account which the operator uses for its own requests to Solr.
One common source of these operator requests is healthchecks: liveness, readiness, and startup probes are all used to determine Solr's health and ability to receive traffic.
By default, the operator configures the Solr APIs used for these probes to be exempt from authentication, but users may specifically request that authentication be required on probe endpoints as well.
Whenever one of these probes would fail, if authentication was in use, the Solr Operator would create a Kubernetes "event" containing the username and password of the "k8s-oper" account.

Within the affected version range, this vulnerability affects any solrcloud resource which (1) bootstrapped security through use of the `.solrOptions.security.authenticationType=basic` option, and (2) required authentication be used on probes by setting `.solrOptions.security.probesRequireAuth=true`.

Users are recommended to upgrade to Solr Operator version 0.8.1, which fixes this issue by ensuring that probes no longer print the credentials used for Solr requests.  Users may also mitigate the vulnerability by disabling authentication on their healthcheck probes using the setting `.solrOptions.security.probesRequireAuth=false`.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31391|2024-06-04T17:36:34.613Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31869|2024-04-18T07:19:05.033Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20airflow</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31869</link>
      <description>Airflow versions 2.7.0 through 2.8.4 have a vulnerability that allows an authenticated user to see sensitive provider configuration via the "configuration" UI page when "non-sensitive-only" was set as "webserver.expose_config" configuration (The celery provider is the only community provider currently that has sensitive configurations). You should migrate to Airflow 2.9 or change your "expose_config" configuration to False as a workaround. This is similar, but different to  CVE-2023-46288 https://github.com/advisories/GHSA-9qqg-mh7c-chfq  which concerned API, not UI configuration page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31869|2024-04-18T07:19:05.033Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 07:19:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31865|2024-06-04T17:36:49.248Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20zeppelin</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31865</link>
      <description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Apache Zeppelin.

The attackers can call updating cron API with invalid or improper privileges so that the notebook can run with the privileges.

This issue affects Apache Zeppelin: from 0.8.2 before 0.11.1.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 0.11.1, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31865|2024-06-04T17:36:49.248Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 16:07:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31864|2024-04-11T07:52:02.800Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20zeppelin</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31864</link>
      <description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Apache Zeppelin.

The attacker can inject sensitive configuration or malicious code when connecting MySQL database via JDBC driver.
This issue affects Apache Zeppelin: before 0.11.1.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 0.11.1, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31864|2024-04-11T07:52:02.800Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 16:05:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31868|2024-06-04T17:36:56.200Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20zeppelin</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31868</link>
      <description>Improper Encoding or Escaping of Output vulnerability in Apache Zeppelin.

The attackers can modify helium.json and exposure XSS attacks to normal users.
This issue affects Apache Zeppelin: from 0.8.2 before 0.11.1.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 0.11.1, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31868|2024-06-04T17:36:56.200Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 16:10:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31863|2024-04-09T10:25:29.449Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20zeppelin</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31863</link>
      <description>Authentication Bypass by Spoofing vulnerability by replacing to exsiting notes in Apache Zeppelin.This issue affects Apache Zeppelin: from 0.10.1 before 0.11.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 0.11.0, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31863|2024-04-09T10:25:29.449Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 10:25:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31862|2024-04-09T09:40:39.495Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20zeppelin</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31862</link>
      <description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Apache Zeppelin when creating a new note from Zeppelin's UI.This issue affects Apache Zeppelin: from 0.10.1 before 0.11.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 0.11.0, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31862|2024-04-09T09:40:39.495Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 09:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21742|2024-06-04T17:37:41.315Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20james%20mime4j</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-21742</link>
      <description>Improper input validation allows for header injection in MIME4J library when using MIME4J DOM for composing message.
This can be exploited by an attacker to add unintended headers to MIME messages.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-21742|2024-06-04T17:37:41.315Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 16:21:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34365|2024-05-09T06:49:05.239Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20karaf%20cave</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-34365</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Apache Karaf Cave.This issue affects all versions of Apache Karaf Cave.

As this project is retired, we do not plan to release a version that fixes this issue. Users are recommended to find an alternative or restrict access to the instance to trusted users.NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34365|2024-05-09T06:49:05.239Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 06:49:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-24746|2024-04-10T08:38:37.008Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20nimble</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-24746</link>
      <description>Loop with Unreachable Exit Condition ('Infinite Loop') vulnerability in Apache NimBLE. 

Specially crafted GATT operation can cause infinite loop in GATT server leading to denial of service in Bluetooth stack or device.

This issue affects Apache NimBLE: through 1.6.0.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.7.0, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24746|2024-04-10T08:38:37.008Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 11:56:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-24795|2024-04-04T19:20:48.803Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20http%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-24795</link>
      <description>HTTP Response splitting in multiple modules in Apache HTTP Server allows an attacker that can inject malicious response headers into backend applications to cause an HTTP desynchronization attack.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.59, which fixes this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24795|2024-04-04T19:20:48.803Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 19:20:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-24779|2024-06-04T17:43:17.870Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20superset</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-24779</link>
      <description>Apache Superset with custom roles that include `can write on dataset` and without all data access permissions, allows for users to create virtual datasets to data they don't have access to. These users could then use those virtual datasets to get access to unauthorized data.
This issue affects Apache Superset: before 3.0.4, from 3.1.0 before 3.1.1.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.1.1 or 3.0.4, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24779|2024-06-04T17:43:17.870Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 11:28:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-24773|2024-06-04T17:43:31.824Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20superset</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-24773</link>
      <description>Improper parsing of nested SQL statements on SQLLab would allow authenticated users to surpass their data authorization scope.
This issue affects Apache Superset: before 3.0.4, from 3.1.0 before 3.1.1.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.1.1, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24773|2024-06-04T17:43:31.824Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 11:24:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-24683|2024-06-04T17:43:35.304Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20hop%20engine</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-24683</link>
      <description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Apache Hop Engine.This issue affects Apache Hop Engine: before 2.8.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.8.0, which fixes the issue.

When Hop Server writes links to the PrepareExecutionPipelineServlet page one of the parameters provided to the user was not properly escaped.
The variable not properly escaped is the "id", which is not directly accessible by users creating pipelines making the risk of exploiting this low.

This issue only affects users using the Hop Server component and does not directly affect the client.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24683|2024-06-04T17:43:35.304Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 08:20:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-24549|2024-06-04T17:43:38.348Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20tomcat</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-24549</link>
      <description>Denial of Service due to improper input validation vulnerability for HTTP/2 requests in Apache Tomcat. When processing an HTTP/2 request, if the request exceeded any of the configured limits for headers, the associated HTTP/2 stream was not reset until after all of the headers had been processed.This issue affects Apache Tomcat: from 11.0.0-M1 through 11.0.0-M16, from 10.1.0-M1 through 10.1.18, from 9.0.0-M1 through 9.0.85, from 8.5.0 through 8.5.98.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 11.0.0-M17, 10.1.19, 9.0.86 or 8.5.99 which fix the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24549|2024-06-04T17:43:38.348Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:46:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-24772|2024-02-28T11:26:45.745Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20superset</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-24772</link>
      <description>A guest user could exploit a chart data REST API and send arbitrary SQL statements that on error could leak information from the underlying analytics database.This issue affects Apache Superset: before 3.0.4, from 3.1.0 before 3.1.1.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.1.1 or 3.0.4, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24772|2024-02-28T11:26:45.745Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 11:26:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23807|2024-02-28T13:50:39.904Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20xerces%20c%2B%2B</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23807</link>
      <description>The Apache Xerces C++ XML parser on versions 3.0.0 before 3.2.5 contains a use-after-free error triggered during the scanning of external DTDs.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.2.5 which fixes the issue, or mitigate the issue by disabling DTD processing. This can be accomplished via the DOM using a standard parser feature, or via SAX using the XERCES_DISABLE_DTD environment variable.

This issue has been disclosed before as CVE-2018-1311, but unfortunately that advisory incorrectly stated the issue would be fixed in version 3.2.3 or 3.2.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23807|2024-02-28T13:50:39.904Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 13:50:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23539|2024-03-29T14:36:57.919Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20fineract</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23539</link>
      <description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Apache Fineract.This issue affects Apache Fineract: &lt;1.8.5.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.8.5 or 1.9.0, which fix the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23539|2024-03-29T14:36:57.919Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 14:36:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23538|2024-03-29T14:37:40.374Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20fineract</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23538</link>
      <description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Apache Fineract.This issue affects Apache Fineract: &lt;1.8.5.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.8.5 or 1.9.0, which fix the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23538|2024-03-29T14:37:40.374Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 14:37:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23349|2024-02-22T09:48:20.873Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20answer</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23349</link>
      <description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Apache Answer.This issue affects Apache Answer: through 1.2.1.

XSS attack when user enters summary. A logged-in user, when modifying their own submitted question, can input malicious code in the summary to create such an attack.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version [1.2.5], which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23349|2024-02-22T09:48:20.873Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 09:48:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23944|2024-06-04T17:45:46.353Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20zookeeper</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23944</link>
      <description>Information disclosure in persistent watchers handling in Apache ZooKeeper due to missing ACL check. It allows an attacker to monitor child znodes by attaching a persistent watcher (addWatch command) to a parent which the attacker has already access to. ZooKeeper server doesn't do ACL check when the persistent watcher is triggered and as a consequence, the full path of znodes that a watch event gets triggered upon is exposed to the owner of the watcher. It's important to note that only the path is exposed by this vulnerability, not the data of znode, but since znode path can contain sensitive information like user name or login ID, this issue is potentially critical.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.9.2, 3.8.4 which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23944|2024-06-04T17:45:46.353Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 10:26:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23114|2024-02-20T14:59:38.326Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20camel</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23114</link>
      <description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Apache Camel CassandraQL Component AggregationRepository which is vulnerable to unsafe deserialization. Under specific conditions it is possible to deserialize malicious payload.This issue affects Apache Camel: from 3.0.0 before 3.21.4, from 3.22.0 before 3.22.1, from 4.0.0 before 4.0.4, from 4.1.0 before 4.4.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.4.0, which fixes the issue. If users are on the 4.0.x LTS releases stream, then they are suggested to upgrade to 4.0.4. If users are on 3.x, they are suggested to move to 3.21.4 or 3.22.1</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23114|2024-02-20T14:59:38.326Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 14:59:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23952|2024-02-14T11:09:47.113Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20superset</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23952</link>
      <description>This is a duplicate for CVE-2023-46104. With correct CVE version ranges for affected Apache Superset.
 
Uncontrolled resource consumption can be triggered by authenticated attacker that uploads a malicious ZIP to import database, dashboards or datasets.  
This vulnerability exists in Apache Superset versions up to and including 2.1.2 and versions 3.0.0, 3.0.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23952|2024-02-14T11:09:47.113Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 11:09:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23946|2024-02-28T15:44:41.714Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20ofbiz</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23946</link>
      <description>Possible path traversal in Apache OFBiz allowing file inclusion.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 18.12.12, that fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23946|2024-02-28T15:44:41.714Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 15:44:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23320|2024-02-23T16:57:09.741Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20dolphinscheduler</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23320</link>
      <description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Apache DolphinScheduler. An authenticated user can cause arbitrary, unsandboxed javascript to be executed on the server.

This issue is a legacy of CVE-2023-49299. We didn't fix it completely in CVE-2023-49299, and we added one more patch to fix it.

This issue affects Apache DolphinScheduler: until 3.2.1.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.2.1, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23320|2024-02-23T16:57:09.741Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 16:57:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23537|2024-03-29T14:38:05.738Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20fineract</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23537</link>
      <description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in Apache Fineract.This issue affects Apache Fineract: &lt;1.8.5.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.9.0, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23537|2024-03-29T14:38:05.738Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 14:38:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23673|2024-02-06T10:04:21.294Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20sling%20servlets%20resolver</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23673</link>
      <description>Malicious code execution via path traversal in Apache Software Foundation Apache Sling Servlets Resolver.This issue affects all version of Apache Sling Servlets Resolver before 2.11.0. However, whether a system is vulnerable to this attack depends on the exact configuration of the system.
If the system is vulnerable, a user with write access to the repository might be able to trick the Sling Servlet Resolver to load a previously uploaded script. 

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.11.0, which fixes this issue. It is recommended to upgrade, regardless of whether your system configuration currently allows this attack or not.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23673|2024-02-06T10:04:21.294Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 10:04:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23452|2024-02-08T09:00:04.809Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20brpc</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23452</link>
      <description>Request smuggling vulnerability in HTTP server in Apache bRPC 0.9.5~1.7.0 on all platforms allows attacker to smuggle request.

Vulnerability Cause Description：

The http_parser does not comply with the RFC-7230 HTTP 1.1 specification.

Attack scenario:
If a message is received with both a Transfer-Encoding and a Content-Length header field, such a message might indicate an attempt to perform request smuggling or response splitting.
One particular attack scenario is that a bRPC made http server on the backend receiving requests in one persistent connection from frontend server that uses TE to parse request with the logic that 'chunk' is contained in the TE field. in that case an attacker can smuggle a request into the connection to the backend server. 

Solution:
You can choose one solution from below:
1. Upgrade bRPC to version 1.8.0, which fixes this issue. Download link:  https://github.com/apache/brpc/releases/tag/1.8.0
 2. Apply this patch:  https://github.com/apache/brpc/pull/2518</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23452|2024-02-08T09:00:04.809Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 09:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23672|2024-06-04T17:46:12.648Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20tomcat</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23672</link>
      <description>Denial of Service via incomplete cleanup vulnerability in Apache Tomcat. It was possible for WebSocket clients to keep WebSocket connections open leading to increased resource consumption.This issue affects Apache Tomcat: from 11.0.0-M1 through 11.0.0-M16, from 10.1.0-M1 through 10.1.18, from 9.0.0-M1 through 9.0.85, from 8.5.0 through 8.5.98.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 11.0.0-M17, 10.1.19, 9.0.86 or 8.5.99 which fix the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23672|2024-06-04T17:46:12.648Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:48:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27347|2024-06-04T17:46:33.643Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20hugegraph-hubble</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27347</link>
      <description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Apache HugeGraph-Hubble.This issue affects Apache HugeGraph-Hubble: from 1.0.0 before 1.3.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.3.0, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27347|2024-06-04T17:46:33.643Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 14:07:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27439|2024-03-19T11:07:47.648Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20wicket</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27439</link>
      <description>An error in the evaluation of the fetch metadata headers could allow a bypass of the CSRF protection in Apache Wicket.
This issue affects Apache Wicket: from 9.1.0 through 9.16.0, and the milestone releases for the 10.0 series.
Apache Wicket 8.x does not support CSRF protection via the fetch metadata headers and as such is not affected.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 9.17.0 or 10.0.0, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27439|2024-03-19T11:07:47.648Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 11:07:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27317|2024-03-12T18:18:52.650Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20pulsar</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27317</link>
      <description>In Pulsar Functions Worker, authenticated users can upload functions in jar or nar files. These files, essentially zip files, are extracted by the Functions Worker. However, if a malicious file is uploaded, it could exploit a directory traversal vulnerability. This occurs when the filenames in the zip files, which aren't properly validated, contain special elements like "..", altering the directory path. This could allow an attacker to create or modify files outside of the designated extraction directory, potentially influencing system behavior. This vulnerability also applies to the Pulsar Broker when it is configured with "functionsWorkerEnabled=true".

This issue affects Apache Pulsar versions from 2.4.0 to 2.10.5, from 2.11.0 to 2.11.3, from 3.0.0 to 3.0.2, from 3.1.0 to 3.1.2, and 3.2.0. 

2.10 Pulsar Function Worker users should upgrade to at least 2.10.6.
2.11 Pulsar Function Worker users should upgrade to at least 2.11.4.
3.0 Pulsar Function Worker users should upgrade to at least 3.0.3.
3.1 Pulsar Function Worker users should upgrade to at least 3.1.3.
3.2 Pulsar Function Worker users should upgrade to at least 3.2.1.

Users operating versions prior to those listed above should upgrade to the aforementioned patched versions or newer versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27317|2024-03-12T18:18:52.650Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 18:18:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27316|2024-04-04T19:21:41.984Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20http%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27316</link>
      <description>HTTP/2 incoming headers exceeding the limit are temporarily buffered in nghttp2 in order to generate an informative HTTP 413 response. If a client does not stop sending headers, this leads to memory exhaustion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27316|2024-04-04T19:21:41.984Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 19:21:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27438|2024-03-21T09:39:21.894Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20doris</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27438</link>
      <description>Download of Code Without Integrity Check vulnerability in Apache Doris.
The jdbc driver files used for JDBC catalog is not checked and may resulting in remote command execution.
Once the attacker is authorized to create a JDBC catalog, he/she can use arbitrary driver jar file with unchecked code snippet. This code snippet will be run when catalog is initializing without any check.
This issue affects Apache Doris: from 1.2.0 through 2.0.4.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.0.5 or 2.1.x, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27438|2024-03-21T09:39:21.894Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 09:39:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27140|2024-03-01T15:40:08.456Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20archiva</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27140</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED **

Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Apache Archiva.

This issue affects Apache Archiva: from 2.0.0.

As this project is retired, we do not plan to release a version that fixes this issue. Users are recommended to find an alternative or restrict access to the instance to trusted users. Alternatively, you could configure a HTTP proxy in front of your Archiva instance to only forward requests that do not have malicious characters in the URL.

NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27140|2024-03-01T15:40:08.456Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 15:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27906|2024-06-04T17:47:00.639Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20airflow</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27906</link>
      <description>Apache Airflow, versions before 2.8.2, has a vulnerability that allows authenticated users to view DAG code and import errors of DAGs they do not have permission to view through the API and the UI.

Users of Apache Airflow are recommended to upgrade to version 2.8.2 or newer to mitigate the risk associated with this vulnerability</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27906|2024-06-04T17:47:00.639Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 11:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27138|2024-03-01T15:41:12.677Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20archiva</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27138</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in Apache Archiva.

Apache Archiva has a setting to disable user registration, however this restriction can be bypassed. As Apache Archiva has been retired, we do not expect to release a version of Apache Archiva that fixes this issue. You are recommended to look into migrating to a different solution, or isolate your instance from any untrusted users.

NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27138|2024-03-01T15:41:12.677Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 15:41:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27315|2024-02-28T10:06:48.685Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20superset</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27315</link>
      <description>An authenticated user with privileges to create Alerts on Alerts &amp; Reports has the capability to generate a specially crafted SQL statement that triggers an error on the database. This error is not properly handled by Apache Superset and may inadvertently surface in the error log of the Alert exposing possibly sensitive data.

This issue affects Apache Superset: before 3.0.4, from 3.1.0 before 3.1.1.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.1.1 or 3.0.4, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27315|2024-02-28T10:06:48.685Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 10:06:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27905|2024-02-27T14:29:22.497Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20aurora</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27905</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Apache Aurora.

An endpoint exposing internals to unauthenticated users can be used as a "padding oracle" allowing an anonymous attacker to construct a valid authentication cookie. Potentially this could be combined with vulnerabilities in other components to achieve remote code execution.

As this project is retired, we do not plan to release a version that fixes this issue. Users are recommended to find an alternative or restrict access to the instance to trusted users.

NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27905|2024-02-27T14:29:22.497Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 14:29:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27135|2024-03-12T18:18:06.720Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20pulsar</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27135</link>
      <description>Improper input validation in the Pulsar Function Worker allows a malicious authenticated user to execute arbitrary Java code on the Pulsar Function worker, outside of the sandboxes designated for running user-provided functions. This vulnerability also applies to the Pulsar Broker when it is configured with "functionsWorkerEnabled=true".

This issue affects Apache Pulsar versions from 2.4.0 to 2.10.5, from 2.11.0 to 2.11.3, from 3.0.0 to 3.0.2, from 3.1.0 to 3.1.2, and 3.2.0. 

2.10 Pulsar Function Worker users should upgrade to at least 2.10.6.
2.11 Pulsar Function Worker users should upgrade to at least 2.11.4.
3.0 Pulsar Function Worker users should upgrade to at least 3.0.3.
3.1 Pulsar Function Worker users should upgrade to at least 3.1.3.
3.2 Pulsar Function Worker users should upgrade to at least 3.2.1.

Users operating versions prior to those listed above should upgrade to the aforementioned patched versions or newer versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27135|2024-03-12T18:18:06.720Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 18:18:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27894|2024-06-04T17:47:12.905Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20pulsar</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27894</link>
      <description>The Pulsar Functions Worker includes a capability that permits authenticated users to create functions where the function's implementation is referenced by a URL. The supported URL schemes include "file", "http", and "https". When a function is created using this method, the Functions Worker will retrieve the implementation from the URL provided by the user. However, this feature introduces a vulnerability that can be exploited by an attacker to gain unauthorized access to any file that the Pulsar Functions Worker process has permissions to read. This includes reading the process environment which potentially includes sensitive information, such as secrets. Furthermore, an attacker could leverage this vulnerability to use the Pulsar Functions Worker as a proxy to access the content of remote HTTP and HTTPS endpoint URLs. This could also be used to carry out denial of service attacks.
This vulnerability also applies to the Pulsar Broker when it is configured with "functionsWorkerEnabled=true".

This issue affects Apache Pulsar versions from 2.4.0 to 2.10.5, from 2.11.0 to 2.11.3, from 3.0.0 to 3.0.2, from 3.1.0 to 3.1.2, and 3.2.0. 

2.10 Pulsar Function Worker users should upgrade to at least 2.10.6.
2.11 Pulsar Function Worker users should upgrade to at least 2.11.4.
3.0 Pulsar Function Worker users should upgrade to at least 3.0.3.
3.1 Pulsar Function Worker users should upgrade to at least 3.1.3.
3.2 Pulsar Function Worker users should upgrade to at least 3.2.1.

Users operating versions prior to those listed above should upgrade to the aforementioned patched versions or newer versions.

The updated versions of Pulsar Functions Worker will, by default, impose restrictions on the creation of functions using URLs. For users who rely on this functionality, the Function Worker configuration provides two configuration keys: "additionalEnabledConnectorUrlPatterns" and "additionalEnabledFunctionsUrlPatterns". These keys allow users to specify a set of URL patterns that are permitted, enabling the creation of functions using URLs that match the defined patterns. This approach ensures that the feature remains available to those who require it, while limiting the potential for unauthorized access and exploitation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27894|2024-06-04T17:47:12.905Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 18:19:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27139|2024-03-01T15:40:49.893Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20archiva</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27139</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED **

Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in Apache Archiva: a vulnerability in Apache Archiva allows an unauthenticated attacker to modify account data, potentially leading to account takeover.

This issue affects Apache Archiva: from 2.0.0.

As this project is retired, we do not plan to release a version that fixes this issue. Users are recommended to find an alternative or restrict access to the instance to trusted users.

NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27139|2024-03-01T15:40:49.893Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 15:40:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27309|2024-04-12T06:58:45.134Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20kafka</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27309</link>
      <description>While an Apache Kafka cluster is being migrated from ZooKeeper mode to KRaft mode, in some cases ACLs will not be correctly enforced.

Two preconditions are needed to trigger the bug:
1. The administrator decides to remove an ACL
2. The resource associated with the removed ACL continues to have two or more other ACLs associated with it after the removal.

When those two preconditions are met, Kafka will treat the resource as if it had only one ACL associated with it after the removal, rather than the two or more that would be correct.

The incorrect condition is cleared by removing all brokers in ZK mode, or by adding a new ACL to the affected resource. Once the migration is completed, there is no metadata loss (the ACLs all remain).

The full impact depends on the ACLs in use. If only ALLOW ACLs were configured during the migration, the impact would be limited to availability impact. if DENY ACLs were configured, the impact could include confidentiality and integrity impact depending on the ACLs configured, as the DENY ACLs might be ignored due to this vulnerability during the migration period.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27309|2024-04-12T06:58:45.134Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 06:58:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27348|2024-04-22T14:08:06.294Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20hugegraph-server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27348</link>
      <description>RCE-Remote Command Execution vulnerability in Apache HugeGraph-Server.This issue affects Apache HugeGraph-Server: from 1.0.0 before 1.3.0 in Java8 &amp; Java11

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.3.0 with Java11 &amp; enable the Auth system, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27348|2024-04-22T14:08:06.294Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 14:08:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27349|2024-06-04T17:47:33.283Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20hugegraph-server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27349</link>
      <description>Authentication Bypass by Spoofing vulnerability in Apache HugeGraph-Server.This issue affects Apache HugeGraph-Server: from 1.0.0 before 1.3.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.3.0, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27349|2024-06-04T17:47:33.283Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 14:08:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-36471|2024-06-11T17:34:55.238Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20allura</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-36471</link>
      <description>Import functionality is vulnerable to DNS rebinding attacks between verification and processing of the URL.  Project administrators can run these imports, which could cause Allura to read from internal services and expose them.

This issue affects Apache Allura from 1.0.1 through 1.16.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.17.0, which fixes the issue.  If you are unable to upgrade, set "disable_entry_points.allura.importers = forge-tracker, forge-discussion" in your .ini config file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-36471|2024-06-11T17:34:55.238Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:55:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-36104|2024-06-04T07:25:07.746Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20ofbiz</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-36104</link>
      <description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Apache OFBiz. This issue affects Apache OFBiz: before 18.12.14.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 18.12.14, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-36104|2024-06-04T07:25:07.746Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 07:25:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-26280|2024-06-04T17:48:21.926Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20airflow</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-26280</link>
      <description>Apache Airflow, versions before 2.8.2, has a vulnerability that allows authenticated Ops and Viewers users to view all information on audit logs, including dag names and usernames they were not permitted to view. With 2.8.2 and newer, Ops and Viewer users do not have audit log permission by default, they need to be explicitly granted permissions to see the logs. Only admin users have audit log permission by default.

Users of Apache Airflow are recommended to upgrade to version 2.8.2 or newer to mitigate the risk associated with this vulnerability</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-26280|2024-06-04T17:48:21.926Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 11:05:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-26307|2024-06-04T17:48:28.523Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20doris</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-26307</link>
      <description>Possible race condition vulnerability in Apache Doris.
Some of code using `chmod()` method. This method run the risk of someone renaming the file out from under user and chmodding the wrong file.
This could theoretically happen, but the impact would be minimal.
This issue affects Apache Doris: before 1.2.8, before 2.0.4.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.0.4, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-26307|2024-06-04T17:48:28.523Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 09:38:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-26308|2024-02-19T08:31:50.192Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20commons%20compress</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-26308</link>
      <description>Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling vulnerability in Apache Commons Compress.This issue affects Apache Commons Compress: from 1.21 before 1.26.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.26, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-26308|2024-02-19T08:31:50.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 08:31:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-26579|2024-05-08T15:06:23.829Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20inlong</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-26579</link>
      <description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Apache InLong.This issue affects Apache InLong: from 1.7.0 through 1.11.0, 

 the attackers can bypass using malicious parameters.

Users are advised to upgrade to Apache InLong's 1.12.0 or cherry-pick [1], [2] to solve it.

[1]  https://github.com/apache/inlong/pull/9694 

[2]  https://github.com/apache/inlong/pull/9707</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-26579|2024-05-08T15:06:23.829Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:06:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-26580|2024-03-06T12:07:28.140Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20inlong</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-26580</link>
      <description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Apache InLong.This issue affects Apache InLong: from 1.8.0 through 1.10.0, the attackers can 

use the specific payload to read from an arbitrary file. Users are advised to upgrade to Apache InLong's 1.11.0 or cherry-pick [1] to solve it.

[1]  https://github.com/apache/inlong/pull/9673</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-26580|2024-03-06T12:07:28.140Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 12:07:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-26578|2024-02-22T09:28:15.274Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20answer</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-26578</link>
      <description>Concurrent Execution using Shared Resource with Improper Synchronization ('Race Condition') vulnerability in Apache Answer.This issue affects Apache Answer: through 1.2.1.

Repeated submission during registration resulted in the registration of the same user. When users register, if they rapidly submit multiple registrations using scripts, it can result in the creation of multiple user accounts simultaneously with the same name.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version [1.2.5], which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-26578|2024-02-22T09:28:15.274Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 09:28:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-26016|2024-06-04T17:49:34.048Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20superset</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-26016</link>
      <description>A low privilege authenticated user could import an existing dashboard or chart that they do not have access to and then modify its metadata, thereby gaining ownership of the object. However, it's important to note that access to the analytical data of these charts and dashboards would still be subject to validation based on data access privileges.

This issue affects Apache Superset: before 3.0.4, from 3.1.0 before 3.1.1.Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.1.1, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-26016|2024-06-04T17:49:34.048Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 11:28:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32113|2024-05-08T14:50:07.272Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20ofbiz</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-32113</link>
      <description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Apache OFBiz.This issue affects Apache OFBiz: before 18.12.13.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 18.12.13, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32113|2024-05-08T14:50:07.272Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 14:50:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32077|2024-05-14T10:43:20.299Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20airflow</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-32077</link>
      <description>Apache Airflow version 2.9.0 has a vulnerability that allows an authenticated attacker to inject malicious data into the task instance logs. 
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.9.1, which fixes this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32077|2024-05-14T10:43:20.299Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 10:43:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32114|2024-06-04T17:50:57.920Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20activemq</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-32114</link>
      <description>In Apache ActiveMQ 6.x, the default configuration doesn't secure the API web context (where the Jolokia JMX REST API and the Message REST API are located).
It means that anyone can use these layers without any required authentication. Potentially, anyone can interact with the broker (using Jolokia JMX REST API) and/or produce/consume messages or purge/delete destinations (using the Message REST API).

To mitigate, users can update the default conf/jetty.xml configuration file to add authentication requirement:

  
  


Or we encourage users to upgrade to Apache ActiveMQ 6.1.2 where the default configuration has been updated with authentication by default.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32114|2024-06-04T17:50:57.920Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 08:29:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32638|2024-06-04T17:51:36.154Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20apisix</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-32638</link>
      <description>Inconsistent Interpretation of HTTP Requests ('HTTP Request Smuggling') vulnerability in Apache APISIX when using `forward-auth` plugin.This issue affects Apache APISIX: from 3.8.0, 3.9.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.8.1, 3.9.1 or higher, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32638|2024-06-04T17:51:36.154Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 09:20:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22369|2024-02-20T14:58:36.291Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20camel</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22369</link>
      <description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Apache Camel SQL ComponentThis issue affects Apache Camel: from 3.0.0 before 3.21.4, from 3.22.0 before 3.22.1, from 4.0.0 before 4.0.4, from 4.1.0 before 4.4.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.4.0, which fixes the issue. If users are on the 4.0.x LTS releases stream, then they are suggested to upgrade to 4.0.4. If users are on 3.x, they are suggested to move to 3.21.4 or 3.22.1</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22369|2024-02-20T14:58:36.291Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 14:58:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22371|2024-02-26T09:22:38.384Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20camel</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22371</link>
      <description>Exposure of sensitive data by by crafting a malicious EventFactory and providing a custom ExchangeCreatedEvent that exposes sensitive data. Vulnerability in Apache Camel.This issue affects Apache Camel: from 3.21.X through 3.21.3, from 3.22.X through 3.22.0, from 4.0.X through 4.0.3, from 4.X through 4.3.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.21.4, 3.22.1, 4.0.4 or 4.4.0, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22371|2024-02-26T09:22:38.384Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 09:22:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22393|2024-02-22T09:51:43.432Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20answer</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22393</link>
      <description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Apache Answer.This issue affects Apache Answer: through 1.2.1.

Pixel Flood Attack by uploading large pixel files will cause server out of memory. A logged-in user can cause such an attack by uploading an image when posting content.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version [1.2.5], which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22393|2024-02-22T09:51:43.432Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 09:51:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29006|2024-06-04T17:56:43.725Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20cloudstack</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-29006</link>
      <description>By default the CloudStack management server honours the x-forwarded-for HTTP header and logs it as the source IP of an API request. This could lead to authentication bypass and other operational problems should an attacker decide to spoof their IP address this way. Users are recommended to upgrade to CloudStack version 4.18.1.1 or 4.19.0.1, which fixes this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29006|2024-06-04T17:56:43.725Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 07:48:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29733|2024-06-04T17:56:57.291Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20airflow%20ftp%20provider</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-29733</link>
      <description>Improper Certificate Validation vulnerability in Apache Airflow FTP Provider.

The FTP hook lacks complete certificate validation in FTP_TLS connections, which can potentially be leveraged. Implementing proper certificate validation by passing context=ssl.create_default_context() during FTP_TLS instantiation is used as mitigation to validate the certificates properly.

This issue affects Apache Airflow FTP Provider: before 3.7.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.7.0, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29733|2024-06-04T17:56:57.291Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 17:21:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29007|2024-04-04T07:49:57.831Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20cloudstack</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-29007</link>
      <description>The CloudStack management server and secondary storage VM could be tricked into making requests to restricted or random resources by means of following 301 HTTP redirects presented by external servers when downloading templates or ISOs. Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.18.1.1 or 4.19.0.1, which fixes this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29007|2024-04-04T07:49:57.831Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 07:49:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29217|2024-06-04T17:57:20.166Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20answer</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-29217</link>
      <description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Apache Answer.This issue affects Apache Answer: before 1.3.0.

XSS attack when user changes personal website. A logged-in user, when modifying their personal website, can input malicious code in the website to create such an attack.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version [1.3.0], which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29217|2024-06-04T17:57:20.166Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 16:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29133|2024-06-04T17:57:30.067Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20commons%20configuration</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-29133</link>
      <description>Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in Apache Commons Configuration.This issue affects Apache Commons Configuration: from 2.0 before 2.10.1.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.10.1, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29133|2024-06-04T17:57:30.067Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 09:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29735|2024-03-26T16:52:40.770Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20airflow</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-29735</link>
      <description>Improper Preservation of Permissions vulnerability in Apache Airflow.This issue affects Apache Airflow from 2.8.2 through 2.8.3.

Airflow's local file task handler in Airflow incorrectly set permissions for all parent folders of log folder, in default configuration adding write access to Unix group of the folders. In the case Airflow is run with the root user (not recommended) it added group write permission to all folders up to the root of the filesystem.

If your log files are stored in the home directory, these permission changes might impact your ability to run SSH operations after your home directory becomes group-writeable.

This issue does not affect users who use or extend Airflow using Official Airflow Docker reference images ( https://hub.docker.com/r/apache/airflow/ ) - those images require to have group write permission set anyway.

You are affected only if you install Airflow using local installation / virtualenv or other Docker images, but the issue has no impact if docker containers are used as intended, i.e. where Airflow components do not share containers with other applications and users.

Also you should not be affected if your umask is 002 (group write enabled) - this is the default on many linux systems.

Recommendation for users using Airflow outside of the containers:

  *  if you are using root to run Airflow, change your Airflow user to use non-root
  *  upgrade Apache Airflow to 2.8.4 or above
  *  If you prefer not to upgrade, you can change the  https://airflow.apache.org/docs/apache-airflow/stable/configurations-ref.html#file-task-handler-new-folder-permissions  to 0o755 (original value 0o775).
  *  if you already ran Airflow tasks before and your default umask is 022 (group write disabled) you should stop Airflow components, check permissions of AIRFLOW_HOME/logs in all your components and all parent directories of this directory and remove group write access for all the parent directories</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29735|2024-03-26T16:52:40.770Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 16:52:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29131|2024-03-21T09:07:13.627Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20commons%20configuration</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-29131</link>
      <description>Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in Apache Commons Configuration.This issue affects Apache Commons Configuration: from 2.0 before 2.10.1.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.10.1, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29131|2024-03-21T09:07:13.627Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 09:07:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29008|2024-04-04T07:51:05.423Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20cloudstack</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-29008</link>
      <description>A problem has been identified in the CloudStack additional VM configuration (extraconfig) feature which can be misused by anyone who has privilege to deploy a VM instance or configure settings of an already deployed VM instance, to configure additional VM configuration even when the feature is not explicitly enabled by the administrator. In a KVM based CloudStack environment, an attacker can exploit this issue to attach host devices such as storage disks, and PCI and USB devices such as network adapters and GPUs, in a regular VM instance that can be further exploited to gain access to the underlying network and storage infrastructure resources, and access any VM instance disks on the local storage.

Users are advised to upgrade to version 4.18.1.1 or 4.19.0.1, which fixes this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29008|2024-04-04T07:51:05.423Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 07:51:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29834|2024-04-02T19:24:46.473Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20pulsar</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-29834</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows authenticated users with produce or consume permissions to perform unauthorized operations on partitioned topics, such as unloading topics and triggering compaction. These management operations should be restricted to users with the tenant admin role or superuser role. An authenticated user with produce permission can create subscriptions and update subscription properties on partitioned topics, even though this should be limited to users with consume permissions. This impact analysis assumes that Pulsar has been configured with the default authorization provider. For custom authorization providers, the impact could be slightly different. Additionally, the vulnerability allows an authenticated user to read, create, modify, and delete namespace properties in any namespace in any tenant. In Pulsar, namespace properties are reserved for user provided metadata about the namespace.

This issue affects Apache Pulsar versions from 2.7.1 to 2.10.6, from 2.11.0 to 2.11.4, from 3.0.0 to 3.0.3, from 3.1.0 to 3.1.3, and from 3.2.0 to 3.2.1. 

3.0 Apache Pulsar users should upgrade to at least 3.0.4.
3.1 and 3.2 Apache Pulsar users should upgrade to at least 3.2.2.

Users operating versions prior to those listed above should upgrade to the aforementioned patched versions or newer versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29834|2024-04-02T19:24:46.473Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 19:24:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28752|2024-03-15T10:27:30.083Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20cxf</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-28752</link>
      <description>A SSRF vulnerability using the Aegis DataBinding in versions of Apache CXF before 4.0.4, 3.6.3 and 3.5.8 allows an attacker to perform SSRF style attacks on webservices that take at least one parameter of any type. Users of other data bindings (including the default databinding) are not impacted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28752|2024-03-15T10:27:30.083Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 10:27:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28148|2024-06-04T18:03:19.183Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20superset</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-28148</link>
      <description>An authenticated user could potentially access metadata for a datasource they are not authorized to view by submitting a targeted REST API request.This issue affects Apache Superset: before 3.1.2.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.1.2 or above, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28148|2024-06-04T18:03:19.183Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 13:33:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28098|2024-06-04T18:03:35.775Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20pulsar</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-28098</link>
      <description>The vulnerability allows authenticated users with only produce or consume permissions to modify topic-level policies, such as retention, TTL, and offloading settings. These management operations should be restricted to users with the tenant admin role or super user role.

This issue affects Apache Pulsar versions from 2.7.1 to 2.10.5, from 2.11.0 to 2.11.3, from 3.0.0 to 3.0.2, from 3.1.0 to 3.1.2, and 3.2.0. 

2.10 Apache Pulsar users should upgrade to at least 2.10.6.
2.11 Apache Pulsar users should upgrade to at least 2.11.4.
3.0 Apache Pulsar users should upgrade to at least 3.0.3.
3.1 Apache Pulsar users should upgrade to at least 3.1.3.
3.2 Apache Pulsar users should upgrade to at least 3.2.1.

Users operating versions prior to those listed above should upgrade to the aforementioned patched versions or newer versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28098|2024-06-04T18:03:35.775Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 18:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28746|2024-06-04T18:03:56.047Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20airflow</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-28746</link>
      <description>Apache Airflow, versions 2.8.0 through 2.8.2, has a vulnerability that allows an authenticated user with limited permissions to access resources such as variables, connections, etc from the UI which they do not have permission to access. 

Users of Apache Airflow are recommended to upgrade to version 2.8.3 or newer to mitigate the risk associated with this vulnerability</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28746|2024-06-04T18:03:56.047Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 08:41:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50378|2024-06-04T17:17:39.090Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20ambari</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50378</link>
      <description>Lack of proper input validation and constraint enforcement in Apache Ambari prior to 2.7.8  

 Impact : As it will be stored XSS, Could be exploited to perform unauthorized actions, varying from data access to session hijacking and delivering malicious payloads. 

Users are recommended to upgrade to version  2.7.8 which fixes this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50378|2024-06-04T17:17:39.090Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 14:38:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50270|2024-02-23T10:17:35.425Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20dolphinscheduler</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50270</link>
      <description>Session Fixation Apache DolphinScheduler before version 3.2.0, which session is still valid after the password change.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.2.1, which fixes this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50270|2024-02-23T10:17:35.425Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 10:01:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50379|2024-02-27T08:27:03.120Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20ambari</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50379</link>
      <description>Malicious code injection in Apache Ambari in prior to 2.7.8. Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.7.8, which fixes this issue.

Impact:
A Cluster Operator can manipulate the request by adding a malicious code injection and gain a root over the cluster main host.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50379|2024-02-27T08:27:03.120Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 08:27:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50292|2024-02-09T17:29:21.249Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20solr</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50292</link>
      <description>Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource, Improper Control of Dynamically-Managed Code Resources vulnerability in Apache Solr.

This issue affects Apache Solr: from 8.10.0 through 8.11.2, from 9.0.0 before 9.3.0.

The Schema Designer was introduced to allow users to more easily configure and test new Schemas and configSets.
However, when the feature was created, the "trust" (authentication) of these configSets was not considered.
External library loading is only available to configSets that are "trusted" (created by authenticated users), thus non-authenticated users are unable to perform Remote Code Execution.
Since the Schema Designer loaded configSets without taking their "trust" into account, configSets that were created by unauthenticated users were allowed to load external libraries when used in the Schema Designer.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 9.3.0, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50292|2024-02-09T17:29:21.249Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 17:29:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50380|2024-02-27T16:51:33.978Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20ambari</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50380</link>
      <description>XML External Entity injection in apache ambari versions &lt;= 2.7.7, Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.7.8, which fixes this issue.

More Details:

Oozie Workflow Scheduler had a vulnerability that allowed for root-level file reading and privilege escalation from low-privilege users. The vulnerability was caused through lack of proper user input validation.

This vulnerability is known as an XML External Entity (XXE) injection attack. Attackers can exploit XXE vulnerabilities to read arbitrary files on the server, including sensitive system files. In theory, it might be possible to use this to escalate privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50380|2024-02-27T16:51:33.978Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 16:51:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50386|2024-06-04T17:17:47.000Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20solr</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50386</link>
      <description>Improper Control of Dynamically-Managed Code Resources, Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type, Inclusion of Functionality from Untrusted Control Sphere vulnerability in Apache Solr.This issue affects Apache Solr: from 6.0.0 through 8.11.2, from 9.0.0 before 9.4.1.

In the affected versions, Solr ConfigSets accepted Java jar and class files to be uploaded through the ConfigSets API.
When backing up Solr Collections, these configSet files would be saved to disk when using the LocalFileSystemRepository (the default for backups).
If the backup was saved to a directory that Solr uses in its ClassPath/ClassLoaders, then the jar and class files would be available to use with any ConfigSet, trusted or untrusted.

When Solr is run in a secure way (Authorization enabled), as is strongly suggested, this vulnerability is limited to extending the Backup permissions with the ability to add libraries.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 8.11.3 or 9.4.1, which fix the issue.
In these versions, the following protections have been added:

  *  Users are no longer able to upload files to a configSet that could be executed via a Java ClassLoader.
  *  The Backup API restricts saving backups to directories that are used in the ClassLoader.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50386|2024-06-04T17:17:47.000Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 17:28:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50298|2024-02-09T17:29:07.889Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20solr</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50298</link>
      <description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Apache Solr.This issue affects Apache Solr: from 6.0.0 through 8.11.2, from 9.0.0 before 9.4.1.

Solr Streaming Expressions allows users to extract data from other Solr Clouds, using a "zkHost" parameter.
When original SolrCloud is setup to use ZooKeeper credentials and ACLs, they will be sent to whatever "zkHost" the user provides.
An attacker could setup a server to mock ZooKeeper, that accepts ZooKeeper requests with credentials and ACLs and extracts the sensitive information,
then send a streaming expression using the mock server's address in "zkHost".
Streaming Expressions are exposed via the "/streaming" handler, with "read" permissions.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 8.11.3 or 9.4.1, which fix the issue.
From these versions on, only zkHost values that have the same server address (regardless of chroot), will use the given ZooKeeper credentials and ACLs when connecting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50298|2024-02-09T17:29:07.889Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 17:29:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50740|2024-03-06T13:44:53.867Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20linkis%20datasource</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50740</link>
      <description>In Apache Linkis &lt;=1.4.0, The password is printed to the log when using the Oracle data source of the Linkis data source module. 
We recommend users upgrade the version of Linkis to version 1.5.0</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50740|2024-03-06T13:44:53.867Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 13:44:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50291|2024-02-09T17:29:32.882Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20solr</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50291</link>
      <description>Insufficiently Protected Credentials vulnerability in Apache Solr.

This issue affects Apache Solr: from 6.0.0 through 8.11.2, from 9.0.0 before 9.3.0.
One of the two endpoints that publishes the Solr process' Java system properties, /admin/info/properties, was only setup to hide system properties that had "password" contained in the name.
There are a number of sensitive system properties, such as "basicauth" and "aws.secretKey" do not contain "password", thus their values were published via the "/admin/info/properties" endpoint.
This endpoint populates the list of System Properties on the home screen of the Solr Admin page, making the exposed credentials visible in the UI.

This /admin/info/properties endpoint is protected under the "config-read" permission.
Therefore, Solr Clouds with Authorization enabled will only be vulnerable through logged-in users that have the "config-read" permission.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 9.3.0 or 8.11.3, which fixes the issue.
A single option now controls hiding Java system property for all endpoints, "-Dsolr.hiddenSysProps".
By default all known sensitive properties are hidden (including "-Dbasicauth"), as well as any property with a name containing "secret" or "password".

Users who cannot upgrade can also use the following Java system property to fix the issue:
  '-Dsolr.redaction.system.pattern=.*(password|secret|basicauth).*'</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50291|2024-02-09T17:29:32.882Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 17:29:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-35701|2024-05-03T08:11:08.215Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20hive</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-35701</link>
      <description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Apache Hive.

The vulnerability affects the Hive JDBC driver component and it can potentially lead to arbitrary code execution on the machine/endpoint that the JDBC driver (client) is running. The malicious user must have sufficient permissions to specify/edit JDBC URL(s) in an endpoint relying on the Hive JDBC driver and the JDBC client process must run under a privileged user to fully exploit the vulnerability. 

The attacker can setup a malicious HTTP server and specify a JDBC URL pointing towards this server. When a JDBC connection is attempted, the malicious HTTP server can provide a special response with customized payload that can trigger the execution of certain commands in the JDBC client.This issue affects Apache Hive: from 4.0.0-alpha-1 before 4.0.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.0.0, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-35701|2024-05-03T08:11:08.215Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 08:11:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51437|2024-02-07T09:18:19.080Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20pulsar</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51437</link>
      <description>Observable timing discrepancy vulnerability in Apache Pulsar SASL Authentication Provider can allow an attacker to forge a SASL Role Token that will pass signature verification.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.11.3, 3.0.2, or 3.1.1 which fixes the issue. Users should also consider updating the configured secret in the `saslJaasServerRoleTokenSignerSecretPath` file.

Any component matching an above version running the SASL Authentication Provider is affected. That includes the Pulsar Broker, Proxy, Websocket Proxy, or Function Worker.

2.11 Pulsar users should upgrade to at least 2.11.3.
3.0 Pulsar users should upgrade to at least 3.0.2.
3.1 Pulsar users should upgrade to at least 3.1.1.
Any users running Pulsar 2.8, 2.9, 2.10, and earlier should upgrade to one of the above patched versions.

For additional details on this attack vector, please refer to  https://codahale.com/a-lesson-in-timing-attacks/ .</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51437|2024-02-07T09:18:19.080Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 09:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51518|2024-02-27T09:09:31.579Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20james%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51518</link>
      <description>Apache James prior to version 3.7.5 and 3.8.0 exposes a JMX endpoint on localhost subject to pre-authentication deserialisation of untrusted data.
Given a deserialisation gadjet, this could be leveraged as part of an exploit chain that could result in privilege escalation.
Note that by default JMX endpoint is only bound locally.

We recommend users to:
 - Upgrade to a non-vulnerable Apache James version

 - Run Apache James isolated from other processes (docker - dedicated virtual machine)
 - If possible turn off JMX</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51518|2024-02-27T09:09:31.579Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 09:09:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51770|2024-06-04T17:20:55.794Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20dolphinscheduler</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51770</link>
      <description>Arbitrary File Read Vulnerability in Apache Dolphinscheduler.

This issue affects Apache DolphinScheduler: before 3.2.1. 

We recommend users to upgrade Apache DolphinScheduler to version 3.2.1, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51770|2024-06-04T17:20:55.794Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 10:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51747|2024-06-04T17:21:01.826Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20james%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51747</link>
      <description>Apache James prior to versions 3.8.1 and 3.7.5 is vulnerable to SMTP smuggling.

A lenient behaviour in line delimiter handling might create a difference of interpretation between the sender and the receiver which can be exploited by an attacker to forge an SMTP envelop, allowing for instance to bypass SPF checks.

The patch implies enforcement of CRLF as a line delimiter as part of the DATA transaction.

We recommend James users to upgrade to non vulnerable versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51747|2024-06-04T17:21:01.826Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 13:08:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41313|2024-03-12T10:16:23.638Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20doris</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-41313</link>
      <description>The authentication method in Apache Doris versions before 2.0.0 was vulnerable to timing attacks.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.0.0 + or 1.2.8, which fixes this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41313|2024-03-12T10:16:23.638Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 10:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39196|2024-02-07T12:56:29.534Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20ozone</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39196</link>
      <description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in Apache Ozone.

The vulnerability allows an attacker to download metadata internal to the Storage Container Manager service without proper authentication.
The attacker is not allowed to do any modification within the Ozone Storage Container Manager service using this vulnerability.
The accessible metadata does not contain sensitive information that can be used to exploit the system later on, and the accessible data does not make it possible to gain access to actual user data within Ozone.
This issue affects Apache Ozone: 1.2.0 and subsequent releases up until 1.3.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.4.0, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39196|2024-02-07T12:56:29.534Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 12:56:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-49250|2024-02-20T10:00:06.733Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20dolphinscheduler</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-49250</link>
      <description>Because the HttpUtils class did not verify certificates, an attacker that could perform a Man-in-the-Middle (MITM) attack on outgoing https connections could impersonate the server.

This issue affects Apache DolphinScheduler: before 3.2.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.2.1, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-49250|2024-02-20T10:00:06.733Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 10:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-49109|2024-02-20T09:58:56.779Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20dolphinscheduler</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-49109</link>
      <description>Exposure of Remote Code Execution in Apache Dolphinscheduler.

This issue affects Apache DolphinScheduler: before 3.2.1. 

We recommend users to upgrade Apache DolphinScheduler to version 3.2.1, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-49109|2024-02-20T09:58:56.779Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 09:58:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38709|2024-04-04T19:19:35.467Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20http%20server</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38709</link>
      <description>Faulty input validation in the core of Apache allows malicious or exploitable backend/content generators to split HTTP responses.

This issue affects Apache HTTP Server: through 2.4.58.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38709|2024-04-04T19:19:35.467Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 19:19:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34365|2024-06-12T19:21:08.705Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20karaf%20cave</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-34365</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Apache Karaf Cave.This issue affects all versions of Apache Karaf Cave.

As this project is retired, we do not plan to release a version that fixes this issue. Users are recommended to find an alternative or restrict access to the instance to trusted users.NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34365|2024-06-12T19:21:08.705Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 06:49:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-36264|2024-06-12T19:20:39.505Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20submarine%20commons%20utils</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-36264</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** Improper Authentication vulnerability in Apache Submarine Commons Utils.

This issue affects Apache Submarine Commons Utils: from 0.8.0.

As this project is retired, we do not plan to release a version that fixes this issue. Users are recommended to find an alternative or restrict access to the instance to trusted users.

NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-36264|2024-06-12T19:20:39.505Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 14:06:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-36265|2024-06-13T20:07:05.232Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20submarine%20server%20core</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36265</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in Apache Submarine Server Core.

This issue affects Apache Submarine Server Core: from 0.8.0.

As this project is retired, we do not plan to release a version that fixes this issue. Users are recommended to find an alternative or restrict access to the instance to trusted users.

NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-36265|2024-06-13T20:07:05.232Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 14:12:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25142|2024-06-14T18:06:10.366Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20airflow</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25142</link>
      <description>Use of Web Browser Cache Containing Sensitive Information vulnerability in Apache Airflow. 

Airflow did not return "Cache-Control" header for dynamic content, which in case of some browsers could result in potentially storing sensitive data in local cache of the browser.

This issue affects Apache Airflow: before 2.9.2.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.9.2, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25142|2024-06-14T18:06:10.366Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 08:25:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34693|2024-06-20T08:51:55.329Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20superset</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34693</link>
      <description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Apache Superset, allows for an authenticated attacker to create a MariaDB connection with local_infile enabled. If both the MariaDB server (off by default) and the local mysql client on the web server are set to allow for local infile, it's possible for the attacker to execute a specific MySQL/MariaDB SQL command that is able to read files from the server and insert their content on a MariaDB database table.This issue affects Apache Superset: before 3.1.3 and version 4.0.0

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.0.1 or 3.1.3, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34693|2024-06-20T08:51:55.329Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 08:51:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38379|2024-06-22T09:09:32.464Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20allura</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38379</link>
      <description>Apache Allura's neighborhood settings are vulnerable to a stored XSS attack.  Only neighborhood admins can access these settings, so the scope of risk is limited to configurations where neighborhood admins are not fully trusted.

This issue affects Apache Allura: from 1.4.0 through 1.17.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.17.1, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-38379|2024-06-22T09:09:32.464Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 09:09:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27136|2024-06-24T07:44:30.732Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20jspwiki</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27136</link>
      <description>XSS in Upload page in Apache JSPWiki 2.12.1 and priors allows the attacker to execute javascript in the victim's browser and get some sensitive information about the victim.  Apache JSPWiki users should upgrade to 2.12.2 or later.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27136|2024-06-24T07:44:30.732Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 07:44:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29868|2024-06-24T13:27:04.364Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20streampipes</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29868</link>
      <description>Use of Cryptographically Weak Pseudo-Random Number Generator (PRNG) vulnerability in Apache StreamPipes user self-registration and password recovery mechanism.
This allows an attacker to guess the recovery token in a reasonable time and thereby to take over the attacked user's account.
This issue affects Apache StreamPipes: from 0.69.0 through 0.93.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 0.95.0, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29868|2024-06-24T13:27:04.364Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 09:59:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27136|2024-06-24T13:27:32.693Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20jspwiki</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27136</link>
      <description>XSS in Upload page in Apache JSPWiki 2.12.1 and priors allows the attacker to execute javascript in the victim's browser and get some sensitive information about the victim.  Apache JSPWiki users should upgrade to 2.12.2 or later.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27136|2024-06-24T13:27:32.693Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 07:44:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38473|2024-07-01T18:14:21.520Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20http%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38473</link>
      <description>Encoding problem in mod_proxy in Apache HTTP Server 2.4.59 and earlier allows request URLs with incorrect encoding to be sent to backend services, potentially bypassing authentication via crafted requests.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.60, which fixes this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-38473|2024-07-01T18:14:21.520Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:14:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38474|2024-07-01T18:14:47.004Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20http%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38474</link>
      <description>Substitution encoding issue in mod_rewrite in Apache HTTP Server 2.4.59 and earlier allows attacker to execute scripts in
directories permitted by the configuration but not directly reachable by any URL or source disclosure of scripts meant to only to be executed as CGI.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.60, which fixes this issue.

Some RewriteRules that capture and substitute unsafely will now fail unless rewrite flag "UnsafeAllow3F" is specified.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-38474|2024-07-01T18:14:47.004Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:14:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-36387|2024-07-01T18:10:25.512Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20http%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36387</link>
      <description>Serving WebSocket protocol upgrades over a HTTP/2 connection could result in a Null Pointer dereference, leading to a crash of the server process, degrading performance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-36387|2024-07-01T18:10:25.512Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38472|2024-07-01T18:12:27.616Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20http%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38472</link>
      <description>SSRF in Apache HTTP Server on Windows allows to potentially leak NTML hashes to a malicious server via SSRF and malicious requests or content 
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.60 which fixes this issue.  Note: Existing configurations that access UNC paths will have to configure new directive "UNCList" to allow access during request processing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-38472|2024-07-01T18:12:27.616Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:12:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39573|2024-07-01T18:16:44.297Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20http%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39573</link>
      <description>Potential SSRF in mod_rewrite in Apache HTTP Server 2.4.59 and earlier allows an attacker to cause unsafe RewriteRules to unexpectedly setup URL's to be handled by mod_proxy.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.60, which fixes this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39573|2024-07-01T18:16:44.297Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38477|2024-07-01T18:16:11.935Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20http%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38477</link>
      <description>null pointer dereference in mod_proxy in Apache HTTP Server 2.4.59 and earlier allows an attacker to crash the server via a malicious request.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.60, which fixes this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-38477|2024-07-01T18:16:11.935Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38475|2024-07-01T18:15:12.292Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20http%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38475</link>
      <description>Improper escaping of output in mod_rewrite in Apache HTTP Server 2.4.59 and earlier allows an attacker to map URLs to filesystem locations that are permitted to be served by the server but are not intentionally/directly reachable by any URL, resulting in code execution or source code disclosure. 

Substitutions in server context that use a backreferences or variables as the first segment of the substitution are affected.  Some unsafe RewiteRules will be broken by this change and the rewrite flag "UnsafePrefixStat" can be used to opt back in once ensuring the substitution is appropriately constrained.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-38475|2024-07-01T18:15:12.292Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:15:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38476|2024-07-01T18:15:40.071Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20http%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38476</link>
      <description>Vulnerability in core of Apache HTTP Server 2.4.59 and earlier are vulnerably to information disclosure, SSRF or local script execution via backend applications whose response headers are malicious or exploitable.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.60, which fixes this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-38476|2024-07-01T18:15:40.071Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-36387|2024-07-02T10:05:15.503Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20http%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36387</link>
      <description>Serving WebSocket protocol upgrades over a HTTP/2 connection could result in a Null Pointer dereference, leading to a crash of the server process, degrading performance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-36387|2024-07-02T10:05:15.503Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34750|2024-07-03T19:32:34.695Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20tomcat</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34750</link>
      <description>Improper Handling of Exceptional Conditions, Uncontrolled Resource Consumption vulnerability in Apache Tomcat. When processing an HTTP/2 stream, Tomcat did not handle some cases of excessive HTTP headers correctly. This led to a miscounting of active HTTP/2 streams which in turn led to the use of an incorrect infinite timeout which allowed connections to remain open which should have been closed.

This issue affects Apache Tomcat: from 11.0.0-M1 through 11.0.0-M20, from 10.1.0-M1 through 10.1.24, from 9.0.0-M1 through 9.0.89.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 11.0.0-M21, 10.1.25 or 9.0.90, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34750|2024-07-03T19:32:34.695Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 19:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38346|2024-07-05T13:40:57.246Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20cloudstack</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38346</link>
      <description>The CloudStack cluster service runs on unauthenticated port (default 9090) that can be misused to run arbitrary commands on targeted hypervisors and CloudStack management server hosts. Some of these commands were found to have command injection vulnerabilities that can result in arbitrary code execution via agents on the hosts that may run as a privileged user. An attacker that can reach the cluster service on the unauthenticated port (default 9090), can exploit this to perform remote code execution on CloudStack managed hosts and result in complete compromise of the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of CloudStack managed infrastructure.

Users are recommended to restrict the network access to the cluster service port (default 9090) on a CloudStack management server host to only its peer CloudStack management server hosts. Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.18.2.1, 4.19.0.2 or later, which addresses this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-38346|2024-07-05T13:40:57.246Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 13:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39864|2024-07-05T13:40:37.937Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20cloudstack</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39864</link>
      <description>The CloudStack integration API service allows running its unauthenticated API server (usually on port 8096 when configured and enabled via integration.api.port global setting) for internal portal integrations and for testing purposes. By default, the integration API service port is disabled and is considered disabled when integration.api.port is set to 0 or negative. Due to an improper initialisation logic, the integration API service would listen on a random port when its port value is set to 0 (default value). An attacker that can access the CloudStack management network could scan and find the randomised integration API service port and exploit it to perform unauthorised administrative actions and perform remote code execution on CloudStack managed hosts and result in complete compromise of the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of CloudStack managed infrastructure.

Users are recommended to restrict the network access on the CloudStack management server hosts to only essential ports. Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.18.2.1, 4.19.0.2 or later, which addresses this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39864|2024-07-05T13:40:37.937Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 13:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38475|2024-07-05T18:03:48.637Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20http%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38475</link>
      <description>Improper escaping of output in mod_rewrite in Apache HTTP Server 2.4.59 and earlier allows an attacker to map URLs to filesystem locations that are permitted to be served by the server but are not intentionally/directly reachable by any URL, resulting in code execution or source code disclosure. 

Substitutions in server context that use a backreferences or variables as the first segment of the substitution are affected.  Some unsafe RewiteRules will be broken by this change and the rewrite flag "UnsafePrefixStat" can be used to opt back in once ensuring the substitution is appropriately constrained.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-38475|2024-07-05T18:03:48.637Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:15:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37389|2024-07-08T13:39:29.650Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20nifi</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37389</link>
      <description>Apache NiFi 1.10.0 through 1.26.0 and 2.0.0-M1 through 2.0.0-M3 support a description field in the Parameter Context configuration that is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. An authenticated user, authorized to configure a Parameter Context, can enter arbitrary JavaScript code, which the client browser will execute within the session context of the authenticated user. Upgrading to Apache NiFi 1.27.0 or 2.0.0-M4 is the recommended mitigation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37389|2024-07-08T13:39:29.650Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 07:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38346|2024-07-08T13:54:00.246Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20cloudstack</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38346</link>
      <description>The CloudStack cluster service runs on unauthenticated port (default 9090) that can be misused to run arbitrary commands on targeted hypervisors and CloudStack management server hosts. Some of these commands were found to have command injection vulnerabilities that can result in arbitrary code execution via agents on the hosts that may run as a privileged user. An attacker that can reach the cluster service on the unauthenticated port (default 9090), can exploit this to perform remote code execution on CloudStack managed hosts and result in complete compromise of the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of CloudStack managed infrastructure.

Users are recommended to restrict the network access to the cluster service port (default 9090) on a CloudStack management server host to only its peer CloudStack management server hosts. Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.18.2.1, 4.19.0.2 or later, which addresses this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-38346|2024-07-08T13:54:00.246Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 13:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39864|2024-07-08T13:44:39.748Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20cloudstack</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39864</link>
      <description>The CloudStack integration API service allows running its unauthenticated API server (usually on port 8096 when configured and enabled via integration.api.port global setting) for internal portal integrations and for testing purposes. By default, the integration API service port is disabled and is considered disabled when integration.api.port is set to 0 or negative. Due to an improper initialisation logic, the integration API service would listen on a random port when its port value is set to 0 (default value). An attacker that can access the CloudStack management network could scan and find the randomised integration API service port and exploit it to perform unauthorised administrative actions and perform remote code execution on CloudStack managed hosts and result in complete compromise of the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of CloudStack managed infrastructure.

Users are recommended to restrict the network access on the CloudStack management server hosts to only essential ports. Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.18.2.1, 4.19.0.2 or later, which addresses this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39864|2024-07-08T13:44:39.748Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 13:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23539|2024-07-08T20:07:58.442Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20fineract</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23539</link>
      <description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Apache Fineract.This issue affects Apache Fineract: &lt;1.8.5.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.8.5 or 1.9.0, which fix the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23539|2024-07-08T20:07:58.442Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 14:36:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27309|2024-07-08T20:13:14.394Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20kafka</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27309</link>
      <description>While an Apache Kafka cluster is being migrated from ZooKeeper mode to KRaft mode, in some cases ACLs will not be correctly enforced.

Two preconditions are needed to trigger the bug:
1. The administrator decides to remove an ACL
2. The resource associated with the removed ACL continues to have two or more other ACLs associated with it after the removal.

When those two preconditions are met, Kafka will treat the resource as if it had only one ACL associated with it after the removal, rather than the two or more that would be correct.

The incorrect condition is cleared by removing all brokers in ZK mode, or by adding a new ACL to the affected resource. Once the migration is completed, there is no metadata loss (the ACLs all remain).

The full impact depends on the ACLs in use. If only ALLOW ACLs were configured during the migration, the impact would be limited to availability impact. if DENY ACLs were configured, the impact could include confidentiality and integrity impact depending on the ACLs configured, as the DENY ACLs might be ignored due to this vulnerability during the migration period.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27309|2024-07-08T20:13:14.394Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 06:58:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23537|2024-07-08T20:06:52.390Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20fineract</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23537</link>
      <description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in Apache Fineract.This issue affects Apache Fineract: &lt;1.8.5.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.9.0, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23537|2024-07-08T20:06:52.390Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 14:38:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38474|2024-07-09T18:02:49.344Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20http%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38474</link>
      <description>Substitution encoding issue in mod_rewrite in Apache HTTP Server 2.4.59 and earlier allows attacker to execute scripts in
directories permitted by the configuration but not directly reachable by any URL or source disclosure of scripts meant to only to be executed as CGI.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.60, which fixes this issue.

Some RewriteRules that capture and substitute unsafely will now fail unless rewrite flag "UnsafeAllow3F" is specified.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-38474|2024-07-09T18:02:49.344Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:14:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38475|2024-07-10T03:55:18.150Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20http%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38475</link>
      <description>Improper escaping of output in mod_rewrite in Apache HTTP Server 2.4.59 and earlier allows an attacker to map URLs to filesystem locations that are permitted to be served by the server but are not intentionally/directly reachable by any URL, resulting in code execution or source code disclosure. 

Substitutions in server context that use a backreferences or variables as the first segment of the substitution are affected.  Some unsafe RewiteRules will be broken by this change and the rewrite flag "UnsafePrefixStat" can be used to opt back in once ensuring the substitution is appropriately constrained.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-38475|2024-07-10T03:55:18.150Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:15:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-36522|2024-07-12T17:17:44.301Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20wicket</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36522</link>
      <description>The default configuration of XSLTResourceStream.java is vulnerable to remote code execution via XSLT injection when processing input from an untrusted source without validation.
Users are recommended to upgrade to versions 10.1.0, 9.18.0 or 8.16.0, which fix this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-36522|2024-07-12T17:17:44.301Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 12:13:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-46801|2024-07-15T13:16:09.548Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20linkis%20datasource</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46801</link>
      <description>In Apache Linkis &lt;= 1.5.0, data source management module, when adding Mysql data source, exists remote code execution vulnerability for java version &lt; 1.8.0_241. The deserialization vulnerability exploited through jrmp can inject malicious files into the server and execute them. 

This attack requires the attacker to obtain an authorized account from Linkis before it can be carried out.  We recommend that users upgrade the java version to &gt;= 1.8.0_241. Or users upgrade Linkis to version 1.6.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-46801|2024-07-15T13:16:09.548Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 07:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-52290|2024-07-16T07:37:38.660Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20streampark%20%28incubating%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52290</link>
      <description>In streampark-console the list pages(e.g: application pages), users can sort page by field. This sort field is sent from the front-end to the back-end, and the SQL query is generated using this field. However, because this sort field isn't validated, there is a risk of SQL injection vulnerability. The attacker must successfully log into the system to launch an attack, which may cause data leakage. Since no data will be written, so this is a low-impact vulnerability.

Mitigation:

all users should upgrade to 2.1.4,  Such parameters will be blocked.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-52290|2024-07-16T07:37:38.660Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 07:37:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-52290|2024-07-16T13:18:13.487Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20streampark%20%28incubating%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52290</link>
      <description>In streampark-console the list pages(e.g: application pages), users can sort page by field. This sort field is sent from the front-end to the back-end, and the SQL query is generated using this field. However, because this sort field isn't validated, there is a risk of SQL injection vulnerability. The attacker must successfully log into the system to launch an attack, which may cause data leakage. Since no data will be written, so this is a low-impact vulnerability.

Mitigation:

all users should upgrade to 2.1.4,  Such parameters will be blocked.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-52290|2024-07-16T13:18:13.487Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 07:37:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-41916|2024-07-16T13:19:59.665Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20linkis%20datasource</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41916</link>
      <description>In Apache Linkis =1.4.0, due to the lack of effective filtering
of parameters, an attacker configuring malicious Mysql JDBC parameters in the DataSource Manager Module will trigger arbitrary file reading. Therefore, the parameters in the Mysql JDBC URL should be blacklisted. This attack requires the attacker to obtain an authorized account from Linkis before it can be carried out. Versions of Apache Linkis = 1.4.0 will be affected. 
We recommend users upgrade the version of Linkis to version 1.5.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-41916|2024-07-16T13:19:59.665Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 07:53:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29007|2024-07-16T19:54:52.441Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20cloudstack</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29007</link>
      <description>The CloudStack management server and secondary storage VM could be tricked into making requests to restricted or random resources by means of following 301 HTTP redirects presented by external servers when downloading templates or ISOs. Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.18.1.1 or 4.19.0.1, which fixes this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29007|2024-07-16T19:54:52.441Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 07:49:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39863|2024-07-17T07:53:31.820Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20airflow</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39863</link>
      <description>Apache Airflow versions before 2.9.3 have a vulnerability that allows an authenticated attacker to inject a malicious link when installing a provider. Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.9.3, which fixes this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39863|2024-07-17T07:53:31.820Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 07:53:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39877|2024-07-17T07:54:24.338Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20airflow</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39877</link>
      <description>Apache Airflow 2.4.0, and versions before 2.9.3, has a vulnerability that allows authenticated DAG authors to craft a doc_md parameter in a way that could execute arbitrary code in the scheduler context, which should be forbidden according to the Airflow Security model. Users should upgrade to version 2.9.3 or later which has removed the vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39877|2024-07-17T07:54:24.338Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 07:54:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30471|2024-07-17T09:01:52.214Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20streampipes</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30471</link>
      <description>Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) Race Condition vulnerability in Apache StreamPipes in user self-registration.
This allows an attacker to potentially request the creation of multiple accounts with the same email address until the email address is registered, creating many identical users and corrupting StreamPipe's user management.
This issue affects Apache StreamPipes: through 0.93.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 0.95.0, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30471|2024-07-17T09:01:52.214Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 09:01:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31979|2024-07-17T09:04:47.677Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20streampipes</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31979</link>
      <description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Apache StreamPipes during installation process of pipeline elements.
Previously, StreamPipes allowed users to configure custom endpoints from which to install additional pipeline elements. 
These endpoints were not properly validated, allowing an attacker to get StreamPipes to send an HTTP GET request to an arbitrary address.
This issue affects Apache StreamPipes: through 0.93.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 0.95.0, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31979|2024-07-17T09:04:47.677Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 09:04:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31411|2024-07-17T09:22:08.507Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20streampipes</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31411</link>
      <description>Unrestricted Upload of File with dangerous type vulnerability in Apache StreamPipes.
Such a dangerous type might be an executable file that may lead to a remote code execution (RCE).
The unrestricted upload is only possible for authenticated and authorized users.
This issue affects Apache StreamPipes: through 0.93.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 0.95.0, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31411|2024-07-17T09:22:08.507Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 09:22:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29120|2024-07-17T14:59:04.540Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20streampark</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29120</link>
      <description>In Streampark (version &lt; 2.1.4), when a user logged in successfully, the Backend service would return "Authorization" as the front-end authentication credential.  User can use this credential to request other users' information, including the administrator's username, password, salt value, etc. 

Mitigation:

all users should upgrade to 2.1.4</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29120|2024-07-17T14:59:04.540Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 14:59:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31979|2024-07-17T15:45:08.448Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20streampipes</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31979</link>
      <description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Apache StreamPipes during installation process of pipeline elements.
Previously, StreamPipes allowed users to configure custom endpoints from which to install additional pipeline elements. 
These endpoints were not properly validated, allowing an attacker to get StreamPipes to send an HTTP GET request to an arbitrary address.
This issue affects Apache StreamPipes: through 0.93.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 0.95.0, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31979|2024-07-17T15:45:08.448Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 09:04:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29120|2024-07-17T18:16:16.172Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20streampark</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29120</link>
      <description>In Streampark (version &lt; 2.1.4), when a user logged in successfully, the Backend service would return "Authorization" as the front-end authentication credential.  User can use this credential to request other users' information, including the administrator's username, password, salt value, etc. 

Mitigation:

all users should upgrade to 2.1.4</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29120|2024-07-17T18:16:16.172Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 14:59:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31411|2024-07-17T18:43:54.091Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20streampipes</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31411</link>
      <description>Unrestricted Upload of File with dangerous type vulnerability in Apache StreamPipes.
Such a dangerous type might be an executable file that may lead to a remote code execution (RCE).
The unrestricted upload is only possible for authenticated and authorized users.
This issue affects Apache StreamPipes: through 0.93.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 0.95.0, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31411|2024-07-17T18:43:54.091Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 09:22:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-30471|2024-07-17T20:14:46.205Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20streampipes</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30471</link>
      <description>Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) Race Condition vulnerability in Apache StreamPipes in user self-registration.
This allows an attacker to potentially request the creation of multiple accounts with the same email address until the email address is registered, creating many identical users and corrupting StreamPipe's user management.
This issue affects Apache StreamPipes: through 0.93.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 0.95.0, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-30471|2024-07-17T20:14:46.205Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 09:01:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29178|2024-07-18T11:15:56.706Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20streampark</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29178</link>
      <description>On versions before 2.1.4, a user could log in and perform a template injection attack resulting in Remote Code Execution on the server, The attacker must successfully log into the system to launch an attack, so this is a moderate-impact vulnerability.

Mitigation:

all users should upgrade to 2.1.4</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29178|2024-07-18T11:15:56.706Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29736|2024-07-19T08:50:08.265Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20cxf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29736</link>
      <description>A SSRF vulnerability in WADL service description in versions of Apache CXF before 4.0.5, 3.6.4 and 3.5.9 allows an attacker to perform SSRF style attacks on REST webservices. The attack only applies if a custom stylesheet parameter is configured.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29736|2024-07-19T08:50:08.265Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 08:50:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32007|2024-07-19T08:50:31.832Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20cxf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32007</link>
      <description>An improper input validation of the p2c parameter in the Apache CXF JOSE code before 4.0.5, 3.6.4 and 3.5.9 allows an attacker to perform a denial of service attack by specifying a large value for this parameter in a token.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32007|2024-07-19T08:50:31.832Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 08:50:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-41172|2024-07-19T08:50:43.766Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20cxf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41172</link>
      <description>In versions of Apache CXF before 3.6.4 and 4.0.5 (3.5.x and lower versions are not impacted), a CXF HTTP client conduit may prevent HTTPClient instances from being garbage collected and it is possible that memory consumption will continue to increase, eventually causing the application to run  out of memory</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-41172|2024-07-19T08:50:43.766Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 08:50:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-41107|2024-07-19T10:19:53.995Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20cloudstack</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41107</link>
      <description>The CloudStack SAML authentication (disabled by default) does not enforce signature check. In CloudStack environments where SAML authentication is enabled, an attacker that initiates CloudStack SAML single sign-on authentication can bypass SAML authentication by submitting a spoofed SAML response with no signature and known or guessed username and other user details of a SAML-enabled CloudStack user-account. In such environments, this can result in a complete compromise of the resources owned and/or accessible by a SAML enabled user-account.

Affected users are recommended to disable the SAML authentication plugin by setting the "saml2.enabled" global setting to "false", or upgrade to version 4.18.2.2, 4.19.1.0 or later, which addresses this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-41107|2024-07-19T10:19:53.995Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 10:19:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-41107|2024-07-19T14:49:16.846Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20cloudstack</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41107</link>
      <description>The CloudStack SAML authentication (disabled by default) does not enforce signature check. In CloudStack environments where SAML authentication is enabled, an attacker that initiates CloudStack SAML single sign-on authentication can bypass SAML authentication by submitting a spoofed SAML response with no signature and known or guessed username and other user details of a SAML-enabled CloudStack user-account. In such environments, this can result in a complete compromise of the resources owned and/or accessible by a SAML enabled user-account.

Affected users are recommended to disable the SAML authentication plugin by setting the "saml2.enabled" global setting to "false", or upgrade to version 4.18.2.2, 4.19.1.0 or later, which addresses this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-41107|2024-07-19T14:49:16.846Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 10:19:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29736|2024-07-19T16:02:00.261Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20cxf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29736</link>
      <description>A SSRF vulnerability in WADL service description in versions of Apache CXF before 4.0.5, 3.6.4 and 3.5.9 allows an attacker to perform SSRF style attacks on REST webservices. The attack only applies if a custom stylesheet parameter is configured.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29736|2024-07-19T16:02:00.261Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 08:50:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51437|2024-07-22T08:38:36.247Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20pulsar</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51437</link>
      <description>Observable timing discrepancy vulnerability in Apache Pulsar SASL Authentication Provider can allow an attacker to forge a SASL Role Token that will pass signature verification.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.11.3, 3.0.2, or 3.1.1 which fixes the issue. Users should also consider updating the configured secret in the `saslJaasServerRoleTokenSignerSecretPath` file.

Any component matching an above version running the SASL Authentication Provider is affected. That includes the Pulsar Broker, Proxy, Websocket Proxy, or Function Worker.

2.11 Pulsar users should upgrade to at least 2.11.3.
3.0 Pulsar users should upgrade to at least 3.0.2.
3.1 Pulsar users should upgrade to at least 3.1.1.
Any users running Pulsar 2.8, 2.9, 2.10, and earlier should upgrade to one of the above patched versions.

For additional details on this attack vector, please refer to  https://codahale.com/a-lesson-in-timing-attacks/ .</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51437|2024-07-22T08:38:36.247Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 09:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39863|2024-07-22T08:50:07.217Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20airflow</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39863</link>
      <description>Apache Airflow versions before 2.9.3 have a vulnerability that allows an authenticated attacker to inject a malicious link when installing a provider. Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.9.3, which fixes this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39863|2024-07-22T08:50:07.217Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 07:53:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27316|2024-07-22T08:42:14.089Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20http%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27316</link>
      <description>HTTP/2 incoming headers exceeding the limit are temporarily buffered in nghttp2 in order to generate an informative HTTP 413 response. If a client does not stop sending headers, this leads to memory exhaustion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27316|2024-07-22T08:42:14.089Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 19:21:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28752|2024-07-22T13:59:26.146Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20cxf</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28752</link>
      <description>A SSRF vulnerability using the Aegis DataBinding in versions of Apache CXF before 4.0.4, 3.6.3 and 3.5.8 allows an attacker to perform SSRF style attacks on webservices that take at least one parameter of any type. Users of other data bindings (including the default databinding) are not impacted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28752|2024-07-22T13:59:26.146Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 10:27:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-52291|2024-07-22T15:31:31.956Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20streampark%20%28incubating%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52291</link>
      <description>In streampark, the project module integrates Maven's compilation capabilities. The input parameter validation is not strict, allowing attackers to insert commands for remote command execution, The prerequisite for a successful attack is that the user needs to log in to the streampark system and have system-level permissions. Generally, only users of that system have the authorization to log in, and users would not manually input a dangerous operation command. Therefore, the risk level of this vulnerability is very low.

Background:

In the "Project" module, the maven build args  “&lt;” operator causes command injection. e.g : “&lt; (curl  http://xxx.com )” will be executed as a command injection,

Mitigation:

all users should upgrade to 2.1.4,  The "&lt;" operator will blocked。</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-52291|2024-07-22T15:31:31.956Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 08:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29737|2024-07-22T15:29:56.839Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20streampark%20%28incubating%29</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29737</link>
      <description>In streampark, the project module integrates Maven's compilation capabilities. The input parameter validation is not strict, allowing attackers to insert commands for remote command execution, The prerequisite for a successful attack is that the user needs to log in to the streampark system and have system-level permissions. Generally, only users of that system have the authorization to log in, and users would not manually input a dangerous operation command. Therefore, the risk level of this vulnerability is very low.

Mitigation:

all users should upgrade to 2.1.4

Background info:

Log in to Streampark using the default username (e.g. test1, test2, test3) and the default password (streampark). Navigate to the Project module, then add a new project. Enter the git repository address of the project and input `touch /tmp/success_2.1.2` as the "Build Argument". Note that there is no verification and interception of the special character "`". As a result, you will find that this injection command will be successfully executed after executing the build.

In the latest version, the special symbol ` is intercepted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29737|2024-07-22T15:29:56.839Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 08:21:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-34457|2024-07-22T17:57:24.474Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20streampark</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34457</link>
      <description>On versions before 2.1.4, after a regular user successfully logs in, they can manually make a request using the authorization token to view everyone's user flink information, including executeSQL and config.

Mitigation:

all users should upgrade to 2.1.4</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-34457|2024-07-22T17:57:24.474Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 09:48:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29070|2024-07-23T08:13:41.408Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20streampark</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29070</link>
      <description>On versions before 2.1.4, session is not invalidated after logout. When the user logged in successfully, the Backend service returns "Authorization" as the front-end authentication credential. "Authorization" can still initiate requests and access data even after logout.

Mitigation:

all users should upgrade to 2.1.4</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29070|2024-07-23T08:13:41.408Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 08:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29070|2024-07-23T14:47:17.230Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20streampark</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29070</link>
      <description>On versions before 2.1.4, session is not invalidated after logout. When the user logged in successfully, the Backend service returns "Authorization" as the front-end authentication credential. "Authorization" can still initiate requests and access data even after logout.

Mitigation:

all users should upgrade to 2.1.4</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29070|2024-07-23T14:47:17.230Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 08:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-41178|2024-07-23T16:50:10.093Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20arrow%20rust%20object%20store</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41178</link>
      <description>Exposure of temporary credentials in logs in Apache Arrow Rust Object Store, version 0.10.1 and earlier on all platforms using AWS WebIdentityTokens. 

On certain error conditions, the logs may contain the OIDC token passed to  AssumeRoleWithWebIdentity https://docs.aws.amazon.com/STS/latest/APIReference/API_AssumeRoleWithWebIdentity.html . This allows someone with access to the logs to impersonate that identity, including performing their own calls to AssumeRoleWithWebIdentity, until the OIDC token expires. Typically OIDC tokens are valid for up to an hour, although this will vary depending on the issuer.

Users are recommended to use a different AWS authentication mechanism, disable logging or upgrade to version 0.10.2, which fixes this issue.

Details:

When using AWS WebIdentityTokens with the object_store crate, in the event of a failure and automatic retry, the underlying reqwest error, including the full URL with the credentials, potentially in the parameters, is written to the logs. 

Thanks to Paul Hatcherian for reporting this vulnerability</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-41178|2024-07-23T16:50:10.093Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 16:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-39884|2024-07-23T18:53:16.539Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20http%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39884</link>
      <description>A regression in the core of Apache HTTP Server 2.4.60 ignores some use of the legacy content-type based configuration of handlers.   "AddType" and similar configuration, under some circumstances where files are requested indirectly, result in source code disclosure of local content. For example, PHP scripts may be served instead of interpreted.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.61, which fixes this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-39884|2024-07-23T18:53:16.539Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 08:36:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-48362|2024-07-24T13:10:24.774Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20drill</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48362</link>
      <description>XXE in the XML Format Plugin in Apache Drill version 1.19.0 and greater allows a user to read any file on a remote file system or execute commands via a malicious XML file.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.21.2, which fixes this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-48362|2024-07-24T13:10:24.774Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 07:45:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27348|2024-07-24T18:41:43.732Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20hugegraph-server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27348</link>
      <description>RCE-Remote Command Execution vulnerability in Apache HugeGraph-Server.This issue affects Apache HugeGraph-Server: from 1.0.0 before 1.3.0 in Java8 &amp; Java11

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.3.0 with Java11 &amp; enable the Auth system, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27348|2024-07-24T18:41:43.732Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 14:08:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27139|2024-07-25T14:19:12.809Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20archiva</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27139</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED **

Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in Apache Archiva: a vulnerability in Apache Archiva allows an unauthenticated attacker to modify account data, potentially leading to account takeover.

This issue affects Apache Archiva: from 2.0.0.

As this project is retired, we do not plan to release a version that fixes this issue. Users are recommended to find an alternative or restrict access to the instance to trusted users.

NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27139|2024-07-25T14:19:12.809Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 15:40:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27905|2024-07-25T15:59:06.396Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20aurora</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27905</link>
      <description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Apache Aurora.

An endpoint exposing internals to unauthenticated users can be used as a "padding oracle" allowing an anonymous attacker to construct a valid authentication cookie. Potentially this could be combined with vulnerabilities in other components to achieve remote code execution.

As this project is retired, we do not plan to release a version that fixes this issue. Users are recommended to find an alternative or restrict access to the instance to trusted users.

NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27905|2024-07-25T15:59:06.396Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 14:29:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38472|2024-07-26T03:55:30.695Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20http%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38472</link>
      <description>SSRF in Apache HTTP Server on Windows allows to potentially leak NTML hashes to a malicious server via SSRF and malicious requests or content 
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.60 which fixes this issue.  Note: Existing configurations that access UNC paths will have to configure new directive "UNCList" to allow access during request processing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-38472|2024-07-26T03:55:30.695Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:12:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-35161|2024-07-26T09:10:56.281Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20traffic%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35161</link>
      <description>Apache Traffic Server forwards malformed HTTP chunked trailer section to origin servers. This can be utilized for request smuggling and may also lead cache poisoning if the origin servers are vulnerable.

This issue affects Apache Traffic Server: from 8.0.0 through 8.1.10, from 9.0.0 through 9.2.4.

Users can set a new setting (proxy.config.http.drop_chunked_trailers) not to forward chunked trailer section.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 8.1.11 or 9.2.5, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-35161|2024-07-26T09:10:56.281Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 09:10:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38522|2024-07-26T09:11:20.419Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20traffic%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38522</link>
      <description>Apache Traffic Server accepts characters that are not allowed for HTTP field names and forwards malformed requests to origin servers. This can be utilized for request smuggling and may also lead cache poisoning if the origin servers are vulnerable.

This issue affects Apache Traffic Server: from 8.0.0 through 8.1.10, from 9.0.0 through 9.2.4.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 8.1.11 or 9.2.5, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38522|2024-07-26T09:11:20.419Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 09:11:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-35296|2024-07-26T09:11:11.221Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20traffic%20server</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35296</link>
      <description>Invalid Accept-Encoding header can cause Apache Traffic Server to fail cache lookup and force forwarding requests.

This issue affects Apache Traffic Server: from 8.0.0 through 8.1.10, from 9.0.0 through 9.2.4.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 8.1.11 or 9.2.5, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-35296|2024-07-26T09:11:11.221Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 09:11:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-26580|2024-07-26T15:09:14.088Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20inlong</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26580</link>
      <description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Apache InLong.This issue affects Apache InLong: from 1.8.0 through 1.10.0, the attackers can 

use the specific payload to read from an arbitrary file. Users are advised to upgrade to Apache InLong's 1.11.0 or cherry-pick [1] to solve it.

[1]  https://github.com/apache/inlong/pull/9673</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-26580|2024-07-26T15:09:14.088Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 12:07:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23320|2024-07-26T18:29:05.387Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20dolphinscheduler</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23320</link>
      <description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Apache DolphinScheduler. An authenticated user can cause arbitrary, unsandboxed javascript to be executed on the server.

This issue is a legacy of CVE-2023-49299. We didn't fix it completely in CVE-2023-49299, and we added one more patch to fix it.

This issue affects Apache DolphinScheduler: until 3.2.1.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.2.1, which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23320|2024-07-26T18:29:05.387Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 16:57:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
