<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache OpenOffice</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/apache%20software%20foundation/apache%20openoffice.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache OpenOffice</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 21:23:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11790|2024-08-05T08:17:09.226Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20openoffice
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11790</link>
      <description>When loading a document with Apache Open Office 4.1.5 and earlier with smaller end line termination than the operating system uses, the defect occurs. In this case OpenOffice runs into an Arithmetic Overflow at a string length calculation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11790|2024-08-05T08:17:09.226Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12608|2024-08-05T18:43:56.098Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20openoffice
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12608</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Apache OpenOffice Writer DOC file parser before 4.1.4, and specifically in ImportOldFormatStyles, allows attackers to craft malicious documents that cause denial of service (memory corruption and application crash) potentially resulting in arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12608|2024-08-05T18:43:56.098Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-9806|2024-08-05T17:18:02.109Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20openoffice
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-9806</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the OpenOffice Writer DOC file parser before 4.1.4, and specifically in the WW8Fonts Constructor, allows attackers to craft malicious documents that cause denial of service (memory corruption and application crash) potentially resulting in arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-9806|2024-08-05T17:18:02.109Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-3157|2024-08-05T14:16:28.361Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20openoffice
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-3157</link>
      <description>By exploiting the way Apache OpenOffice before 4.1.4 renders embedded objects, an attacker could craft a document that allows reading in a file from the user's filesystem. Information could be retrieved by the attacker by, e.g., using hidden sections to store the information, tricking the user into saving the document and convincing the user to send the document back to the attacker. The vulnerability is mitigated by the need for the attacker to know the precise file path in the target system, and the need to trick the user into saving the document and sending it back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-3157|2024-08-05T14:16:28.361Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12607|2024-08-05T18:43:56.134Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20openoffice
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12607</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in OpenOffice's PPT file parser before 4.1.4, and specifically in PPTStyleSheet, allows attackers to craft malicious documents that cause denial of service (memory corruption and application crash) potentially resulting in arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12607|2024-08-05T18:43:56.134Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
