<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache CouchDB</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/apache%20software%20foundation/apache%20couchdb.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache CouchDB</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 22:23:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-8742|2024-09-17T00:26:42.742Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20couchdb
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-8742</link>
      <description>The Windows installer that the Apache CouchDB team provides was vulnerable to local privilege escalation. All files in the install inherit the file permissions of the parent directory and therefore a non-privileged user can substitute any executable for the nssm.exe service launcher, or CouchDB batch or binary files. A subsequent service or server restart will then run that binary with administrator privilege. This issue affected CouchDB 2.0.0 (Windows platform only) and was addressed in CouchDB 2.0.0.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-8742|2024-09-17T00:26:42.742Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12635|2024-09-17T01:31:53.828Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20couchdb
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12635</link>
      <description>Due to differences in the Erlang-based JSON parser and JavaScript-based JSON parser, it is possible in Apache CouchDB before 1.7.0 and 2.x before 2.1.1 to submit _users documents with duplicate keys for 'roles' used for access control within the database, including the special case '_admin' role, that denotes administrative users. In combination with CVE-2017-12636 (Remote Code Execution), this can be used to give non-admin users access to arbitrary shell commands on the server as the database system user. The JSON parser differences result in behaviour that if two 'roles' keys are available in the JSON, the second one will be used for authorising the document write, but the first 'roles' key is used for subsequent authorization for the newly created user. By design, users can not assign themselves roles. The vulnerability allows non-admin users to give themselves admin privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12635|2024-09-17T01:31:53.828Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
