<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache OpenOffice</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/apache%20software%20foundation/apache%20openoffice.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache OpenOffice</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 23:23:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-37400|2024-08-03T10:29:20.978Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20openoffice
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-37400</link>
      <description>Apache OpenOffice supports the storage of passwords for web connections in the user's configuration database. The stored passwords are encrypted with a single master key provided by the user. A flaw in OpenOffice existed where the required initialization vector for encryption was always the same which weakens the security of the encryption making them vulnerable if an attacker has access to the user's configuration data. This issue affects: Apache OpenOffice versions prior to 4.1.13. Reference: CVE-2022-26306 - LibreOffice</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-37400|2024-08-03T10:29:20.978Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 06:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-37401|2024-08-03T10:29:21.020Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20openoffice
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-37401</link>
      <description>Apache OpenOffice supports the storage of passwords for web connections in the user's configuration database. The stored passwords are encrypted with a single master key provided by the user. A flaw in OpenOffice existed where master key was poorly encoded resulting in weakening its entropy from 128 to 43 bits making the stored passwords vulnerable to a brute force attack if an attacker has access to the users stored config. This issue affects: Apache OpenOffice versions prior to 4.1.13. Reference: CVE-2022-26307 - LibreOffice</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-37401|2024-08-03T10:29:21.020Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 06:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-28129|2024-08-03T21:33:17.499Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20openoffice
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-28129</link>
      <description>While working on Apache OpenOffice 4.1.8 a developer discovered that the DEB package did not install using root, but instead used a userid and groupid of 500. This both caused issues with desktop integration and could allow a crafted attack on files owned by that user or group if they exist. Users who installed the Apache OpenOffice 4.1.8 DEB packaging should upgrade to the latest version of Apache OpenOffice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-28129|2024-08-03T21:33:17.499Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 15:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-30245|2024-08-03T22:24:59.592Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20openoffice
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-30245</link>
      <description>The project received a report that all versions of Apache OpenOffice through 4.1.8 can open non-http(s) hyperlinks. The problem has existed since about 2006 and the issue is also in 4.1.9. If the link is specifically crafted this could lead to untrusted code execution. It is always best practice to be careful opening documents from unknown and unverified sources. The mitigation in Apache OpenOffice 4.1.10 (unreleased) assures that a security warning is displayed giving the user the option of continuing to open the hyperlink.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-30245|2024-08-03T22:24:59.592Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 19:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38745|2024-08-03T11:02:14.478Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20openoffice
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38745</link>
      <description>Apache OpenOffice versions before 4.1.14 may be configured to add an empty entry to the Java class path. This may lead to run arbitrary Java code from the current directory.


</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38745|2024-08-03T11:02:14.478Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 15:56:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-47502|2024-08-03T14:55:08.175Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20openoffice
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-47502</link>
      <description>Apache OpenOffice documents can contain links that call internal macros with arbitrary arguments. Several URI Schemes are defined for this purpose.


Links can be activated by clicks, or by automatic document events.

The execution of such links must be subject to user approval.

In the affected versions of OpenOffice, approval for certain links is not   requested; when activated, such links could therefore result in arbitrary script execution.


</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-47502|2024-08-03T14:55:08.175Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 15:57:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
