<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache ZooKeeper</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/apache%20software%20foundation/apache%20zookeeper.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache ZooKeeper</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 22:22:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-8012|2024-08-05T06:46:11.492Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20zookeeper
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-8012</link>
      <description>No authentication/authorization is enforced when a server attempts to join a quorum in Apache ZooKeeper before 3.4.10, and 3.5.0-alpha through 3.5.3-beta. As a result an arbitrary end point could join the cluster and begin propagating counterfeit changes to the leader.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-8012|2024-08-05T06:46:11.492Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-5637|2024-08-05T15:04:15.426Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20zookeeper
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-5637</link>
      <description>Two four letter word commands "wchp/wchc" are CPU intensive and could cause spike of CPU utilization on Apache ZooKeeper server if abused, which leads to the server unable to serve legitimate client requests. Apache ZooKeeper thru version 3.4.9 and 3.5.2 suffer from this issue, fixed in 3.4.10, 3.5.3, and later.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-5637|2024-08-05T15:04:15.426Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-23944|2024-06-04T17:45:46.353Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20zookeeper</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-23944</link>
      <description>Information disclosure in persistent watchers handling in Apache ZooKeeper due to missing ACL check. It allows an attacker to monitor child znodes by attaching a persistent watcher (addWatch command) to a parent which the attacker has already access to. ZooKeeper server doesn't do ACL check when the persistent watcher is triggered and as a consequence, the full path of znodes that a watch event gets triggered upon is exposed to the owner of the watcher. It's important to note that only the path is exposed by this vulnerability, not the data of znode, but since znode path can contain sensitive information like user name or login ID, this issue is potentially critical.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.9.2, 3.8.4 which fixes the issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-23944|2024-06-04T17:45:46.353Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 10:26:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
