<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache CouchDB</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/apache%20software%20foundation/apache%20couchdb.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache CouchDB</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 20:23:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11769|2024-09-16T17:59:21.214Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20couchdb
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11769</link>
      <description>CouchDB administrative users before 2.2.0 can configure the database server via HTTP(S). Due to insufficient validation of administrator-supplied configuration settings via the HTTP API, it is possible for a CouchDB administrator user to escalate their privileges to that of the operating system's user under which CouchDB runs, by bypassing the blacklist of configuration settings that are not allowed to be modified via the HTTP API. This privilege escalation effectively allows a CouchDB admin user to gain arbitrary remote code execution, bypassing CVE-2017-12636 and CVE-2018-8007.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11769|2024-09-16T17:59:21.214Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-8007|2024-09-16T17:04:00.488Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20couchdb
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-8007</link>
      <description>Apache CouchDB administrative users can configure the database server via HTTP(S). Due to insufficient validation of administrator-supplied configuration settings via the HTTP API, it is possible for a CouchDB administrator user to escalate their privileges to that of the operating system's user that CouchDB runs under, by bypassing the blacklist of configuration settings that are not allowed to be modified via the HTTP API. This privilege escalation effectively allows an existing CouchDB admin user to gain arbitrary remote code execution, bypassing already disclosed CVE-2017-12636. Mitigation: All users should upgrade to CouchDB releases 1.7.2 or 2.1.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-8007|2024-09-16T17:04:00.488Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12636|2024-09-16T18:48:31.205Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20couchdb
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12636</link>
      <description>CouchDB administrative users can configure the database server via HTTP(S). Some of the configuration options include paths for operating system-level binaries that are subsequently launched by CouchDB. This allows an admin user in Apache CouchDB before 1.7.0 and 2.x before 2.1.1 to execute arbitrary shell commands as the CouchDB user, including downloading and executing scripts from the public internet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12636|2024-09-16T18:48:31.205Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
