<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache Airflow Hive Provider</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/apache%20software%20foundation/apache%20airflow%20hive%20provider.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache Airflow Hive Provider</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 15:23:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-46421|2024-08-03T14:31:46.305Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20airflow%20hive%20provider
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-46421</link>
      <description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command ('Command Injection') vulnerability in Apache Software Foundation Apache Airflow Hive Provider.This issue affects Apache Airflow Hive Provider: before 5.0.0.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-46421|2024-08-03T14:31:46.305Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 10:20:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-41131|2024-08-03T12:35:49.376Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20airflow%20hive%20provider
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41131</link>
      <description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in Apache Airflow Hive Provider, Apache Airflow allows an attacker to execute arbtrary commands in the task execution context, without write access to DAG files. This issue affects Hive Provider versions prior to 4.1.0. It also impacts any Apache Airflow versions prior to 2.3.0 in case HIve Provider is installed (Hive Provider 4.1.0 can only be installed for Airflow 2.3.0+). Note that you need to manually install the HIve Provider version 4.1.0 in order to get rid of the vulnerability on top of Airflow 2.3.0+ version that has lower version of the Hive Provider installed).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-41131|2024-08-03T12:35:49.376Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
