<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache Airflow CNCF Kubernetes provider</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/apache%20software%20foundation/apache%20airflow%20cncf%20kubernetes%20provider.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache Airflow CNCF Kubernetes provider</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33234|2023-05-30T10:56:56.139Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20airflow%20cncf%20kubernetes%20provider
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-33234</link>
      <description>Arbitrary code execution in Apache Airflow CNCF Kubernetes provider version 5.0.0 allows user to change xcom sidecar image and resources via Airflow connection.

In order to exploit this weakness, a user would already need elevated permissions (Op or Admin) to change the connection object in this manner.  Operators should upgrade to provider version 7.0.0 which has removed the vulnerability.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33234|2023-05-30T10:56:56.139Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 10:56:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51702|2024-01-24T12:56:17.869Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20airflow%20cncf%20kubernetes%20provider
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51702</link>
      <description>Since version 5.2.0, when using deferrable mode with the path of a Kubernetes configuration file for authentication, the Airflow worker serializes this configuration file as a dictionary and sends it to the triggerer by storing it in metadata without any encryption. Additionally, if used with an Airflow version between 2.3.0 and 2.6.0, the configuration dictionary will be logged as plain text in the triggerer service without masking. This allows anyone with access to the metadata or triggerer log to obtain the configuration file and use it to access the Kubernetes cluster.

This behavior was changed in version 7.0.0, which stopped serializing the file contents and started providing the file path instead to read the contents into the trigger. Users are recommended to upgrade to version 7.0.0, which fixes this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51702|2024-01-24T12:56:17.869Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 12:56:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
