<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache Qpid Proton-J</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/apache%20software%20foundation/apache%20qpid%20proton-j.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache Qpid Proton-J</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 22:22:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17187|2024-08-05T10:39:59.671Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20qpid%20proton-j
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17187</link>
      <description>The Apache Qpid Proton-J transport includes an optional wrapper layer to perform TLS, enabled by use of the 'transport.ssl(...)' methods. Unless a verification mode was explicitly configured, client and server modes previously defaulted as documented to not verifying a peer certificate, with options to configure this explicitly or select a certificate verification mode with or without hostname verification being performed. The latter hostname verifying mode was not implemented in Apache Qpid Proton-J versions 0.3 to 0.29.0, with attempts to use it resulting in an exception. This left only the option to verify the certificate is trusted, leaving such a client vulnerable to Man In The Middle (MITM) attack. Uses of the Proton-J protocol engine which do not utilise the optional transport TLS wrapper are not impacted, e.g. usage within Qpid JMS. Uses of Proton-J utilising the optional transport TLS wrapper layer that wish to enable hostname verification must be upgraded to version 0.30.0 or later and utilise the VerifyMode#VERIFY_PEER_NAME configuration, which is now the default for client mode usage unless configured otherwise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17187|2024-08-05T10:39:59.671Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
