<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache James</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/apache%20software%20foundation/apache%20james.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache James</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 06:24:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-38542|2024-08-04T01:44:23.485Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20james
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38542</link>
      <description>Apache James prior to release 3.6.1 is vulnerable to a buffering attack relying on the use of the STARTTLS command. This can result in Man-in -the-middle command injection attacks, leading potentially to leakage of sensible information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-38542|2024-08-04T01:44:23.485Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 08:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40111|2024-08-04T02:27:31.847Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20james
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40111</link>
      <description>In Apache James, while fuzzing with Jazzer the IMAP parsing stack, we discover that crafted APPEND and STATUS IMAP command could be used to trigger infinite loops resulting in expensive CPU computations and OutOfMemory exceptions. This can be used for a Denial Of Service attack. The IMAP user needs to be authenticated to exploit this vulnerability. This affected Apache James prior to version 3.6.1. This vulnerability had been patched in Apache James 3.6.1 and higher. We recommend the upgrade.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40111|2024-08-04T02:27:31.847Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 08:55:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40110|2024-08-04T02:27:31.846Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20james
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40110</link>
      <description>In Apache James, using Jazzer fuzzer, we identified that an IMAP user can craft IMAP LIST commands to orchestrate a Denial Of Service using a vulnerable Regular expression. This affected Apache James prior to 3.6.1 We recommend upgrading to Apache James 3.6.1 or higher , which enforce the use of RE2J regular expression engine to execute regex in linear time without back-tracking.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40110|2024-08-04T02:27:31.846Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 08:55:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-40525|2024-08-04T02:44:10.863Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20james
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40525</link>
      <description>Apache James ManagedSieve implementation alongside with the file storage for sieve scripts is vulnerable to path traversal, allowing reading and writing any file. This vulnerability had been patched in Apache James 3.6.1 and higher. We recommend the upgrade. Distributed and Cassandra based products are also not impacted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-40525|2024-08-04T02:44:10.863Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 08:55:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
