<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache RocketMQ</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/apache%20software%20foundation/apache%20rocketmq.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache RocketMQ</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-37582|2023-07-12T09:26:18.652Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20rocketmq
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-37582</link>
      <description>The RocketMQ NameServer component still has a remote command execution vulnerability as the CVE-2023-33246 issue was not completely fixed in version 5.1.1. 

When NameServer address are leaked on the extranet and lack permission verification, an attacker can exploit this vulnerability by using the update configuration function on the NameServer component to execute commands as the system users that RocketMQ is running as. 

It is recommended for users to upgrade their NameServer version to 5.1.2 or above for RocketMQ 5.x or 4.9.7 or above for RocketMQ 4.x to prevent these attacks.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-37582|2023-07-12T09:26:18.652Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 09:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-33246|2023-05-24T14:45:25.684Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20rocketmq
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-33246</link>
      <description>For RocketMQ versions 5.1.0 and below, under certain conditions, there is a risk of remote command execution. 

Several components of RocketMQ, including NameServer, Broker, and Controller, are leaked on the extranet and lack permission verification, an attacker can exploit this vulnerability by using the update configuration function to execute commands as the system users that RocketMQ is running as. Additionally, an attacker can achieve the same effect by forging the RocketMQ protocol content. 

To prevent these attacks, users are recommended to upgrade to version 5.1.1 or above for using RocketMQ 5.x or 4.9.6 or above for using RocketMQ 4.x .











</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-33246|2023-05-24T14:45:25.684Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 14:45:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
