<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache Dubbo</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/apache%20software%20foundation/apache%20dubbo.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache Dubbo</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 23:23:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39198|2024-08-03T12:00:43.797Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20dubbo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39198</link>
      <description>A deserialization vulnerability existed in dubbo hessian-lite 3.2.12 and its earlier versions, which could lead to malicious code execution. This issue affects Apache Dubbo 2.7.x version 2.7.17 and prior versions; Apache Dubbo 3.0.x version 3.0.11 and prior versions; Apache Dubbo 3.1.x version 3.1.0 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39198|2024-08-03T12:00:43.797Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25640|2024-08-03T20:11:27.531Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20dubbo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25640</link>
      <description>In Apache Dubbo prior to 2.6.9 and 2.7.9, the usage of parseURL method will lead to the bypass of white host check which can cause open redirect or SSRF vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25640|2024-08-03T20:11:27.531Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 07:25:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24969|2024-08-03T04:29:01.633Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20dubbo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24969</link>
      <description>bypass CVE-2021-25640 &gt; In Apache Dubbo prior to 2.6.12 and 2.7.15, the usage of parseURL method will lead to the bypass of the white host check which can cause open redirect or SSRF vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24969|2024-08-03T04:29:01.633Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 22:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-30181|2024-08-03T22:24:59.650Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20dubbo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-30181</link>
      <description>Apache Dubbo prior to 2.6.9 and 2.7.9 supports Script routing which will enable a customer to route the request to the right server. These rules are used by the customers when making a request in order to find the right endpoint. When parsing these rules, Dubbo customers use ScriptEngine and run the rule provided by the script which by default may enable executing arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-30181|2024-08-03T22:24:59.650Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 07:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-30180|2024-08-03T22:24:59.649Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20dubbo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-30180</link>
      <description>Apache Dubbo prior to 2.7.9 support Tag routing which will enable a customer to route the request to the right server. These rules are used by the customers when making a request in order to find the right endpoint. When parsing these YAML rules, Dubbo customers may enable calling arbitrary constructors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-30180|2024-08-03T22:24:59.649Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 07:25:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-30179|2024-08-03T22:24:59.625Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20dubbo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-30179</link>
      <description>Apache Dubbo prior to 2.6.9 and 2.7.9 by default supports generic calls to arbitrary methods exposed by provider interfaces. These invocations are handled by the GenericFilter which will find the service and method specified in the first arguments of the invocation and use the Java Reflection API to make the final call. The signature for the $invoke or $invokeAsync methods is Ljava/lang/String;[Ljava/lang/String;[Ljava/lang/Object; where the first argument is the name of the method to invoke, the second one is an array with the parameter types for the method being invoked and the third one is an array with the actual call arguments. In addition, the caller also needs to set an RPC attachment specifying that the call is a generic call and how to decode the arguments. The possible values are: - true - raw.return - nativejava - bean - protobuf-json An attacker can control this RPC attachment and set it to nativejava to force the java deserialization of the byte array located in the third argument.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-30179|2024-08-03T22:24:59.625Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 07:25:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-25641|2024-08-03T20:11:27.972Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20dubbo
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-25641</link>
      <description>Each Apache Dubbo server will set a serialization id to tell the clients which serialization protocol it is working on. But for Dubbo versions before 2.7.8 or 2.6.9, an attacker can choose which serialization id the Provider will use by tampering with the byte preamble flags, aka, not following the server's instruction. This means that if a weak deserializer such as the Kryo and FST are somehow in code scope (e.g. if Kryo is somehow a part of a dependency), a remote unauthenticated attacker can tell the Provider to use the weak deserializer, and then proceed to exploit it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-25641|2024-08-03T20:11:27.972Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 07:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
