<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache CouchDB</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/apache%20software%20foundation/apache%20couchdb.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache CouchDB</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 12:26:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-8007|2024-08-05T06:46:11.455Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20couchdb
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-8007</link>
      <description>Apache CouchDB administrative users can configure the database server via HTTP(S). Due to insufficient validation of administrator-supplied configuration settings via the HTTP API, it is possible for a CouchDB administrator user to escalate their privileges to that of the operating system's user that CouchDB runs under, by bypassing the blacklist of configuration settings that are not allowed to be modified via the HTTP API. This privilege escalation effectively allows an existing CouchDB admin user to gain arbitrary remote code execution, bypassing already disclosed CVE-2017-12636. Mitigation: All users should upgrade to CouchDB releases 1.7.2 or 2.1.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-8007|2024-08-05T06:46:11.455Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17188|2024-08-05T10:39:59.575Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20couchdb
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17188</link>
      <description>Prior to CouchDB version 2.3.0, CouchDB allowed for runtime-configuration of key components of the database. In some cases, this lead to vulnerabilities where CouchDB admin users could access the underlying operating system as the CouchDB user. Together with other vulnerabilities, it allowed full system entry for unauthenticated users. Rather than waiting for new vulnerabilities to be discovered, and fixing them as they come up, the CouchDB development team decided to make changes to avoid this entire class of vulnerabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17188|2024-08-05T10:39:59.575Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11769|2024-08-05T08:17:09.231Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20couchdb
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11769</link>
      <description>CouchDB administrative users before 2.2.0 can configure the database server via HTTP(S). Due to insufficient validation of administrator-supplied configuration settings via the HTTP API, it is possible for a CouchDB administrator user to escalate their privileges to that of the operating system's user under which CouchDB runs, by bypassing the blacklist of configuration settings that are not allowed to be modified via the HTTP API. This privilege escalation effectively allows a CouchDB admin user to gain arbitrary remote code execution, bypassing CVE-2017-12636 and CVE-2018-8007.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11769|2024-08-05T08:17:09.231Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
