<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache Spark</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/apache%20software%20foundation/apache%20spark.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache Spark</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 21:21:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-33891|2024-08-03T08:09:22.687Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20spark
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-33891</link>
      <description>The Apache Spark UI offers the possibility to enable ACLs via the configuration option spark.acls.enable. With an authentication filter, this checks whether a user has access permissions to view or modify the application. If ACLs are enabled, a code path in HttpSecurityFilter can allow someone to perform impersonation by providing an arbitrary user name. A malicious user might then be able to reach a permission check function that will ultimately build a Unix shell command based on their input, and execute it. This will result in arbitrary shell command execution as the user Spark is currently running as. This affects Apache Spark versions 3.0.3 and earlier, versions 3.1.1 to 3.1.2, and versions 3.2.0 to 3.2.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-33891|2024-08-03T08:09:22.687Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31777|2024-08-03T07:26:01.073Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20spark
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31777</link>
      <description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Apache Spark 3.2.1 and earlier, and 3.3.0, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the web browser of a user, by including a malicious payload into the logs which would be returned in logs rendered in the UI.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31777|2024-08-03T07:26:01.073Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
