<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache Kylin</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/apache%20software%20foundation/apache%20kylin.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache Kylin</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 11:20:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-45458|2024-08-04T04:39:21.117Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20kylin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-45458</link>
      <description>Apache Kylin provides encryption classes PasswordPlaceholderConfigurer to help users encrypt their passwords. In the encryption algorithm used by this encryption class, the cipher is initialized with a hardcoded key and IV. If users use class PasswordPlaceholderConfigurer to encrypt their password and configure it into kylin's configuration file, there is a risk that the password may be decrypted. This issue affects Apache Kylin 2 version 2.6.6 and prior versions; Apache Kylin 3 version 3.1.2 and prior versions; Apache Kylin 4 version 4.0.0 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-45458|2024-08-04T04:39:21.117Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 12:35:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-45457|2024-08-04T04:39:21.127Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20kylin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-45457</link>
      <description>In Apache Kylin, Cross-origin requests with credentials are allowed to be sent from any origin. This issue affects Apache Kylin 2 version 2.6.6 and prior versions; Apache Kylin 3 version 3.1.2 and prior versions; Apache Kylin 4 version 4.0.0 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-45457|2024-08-04T04:39:21.127Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 12:35:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-45456|2024-08-04T04:39:21.067Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20kylin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-45456</link>
      <description>Apache kylin checks the legitimacy of the project before executing some commands with the project name passed in by the user. There is a mismatch between what is being checked and what is being used as the shell command argument in DiagnosisService. This may cause an illegal project name to pass the check and perform the following steps, resulting in a command injection vulnerability. This issue affects Apache Kylin 4.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-45456|2024-08-04T04:39:21.067Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 12:35:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-36774|2024-08-04T01:01:59.491Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20kylin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-36774</link>
      <description>Apache Kylin allows users to read data from other database systems using JDBC. The MySQL JDBC driver supports certain properties, which, if left unmitigated, can allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code from a hacker-controlled malicious MySQL server within Kylin server processes. This issue affects Apache Kylin 2 version 2.6.6 and prior versions; Apache Kylin 3 version 3.1.2 and prior versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-36774|2024-08-04T01:01:59.491Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 12:35:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
