<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache Geode</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/apache%20software%20foundation/apache%20geode.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache Geode</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 18:24:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-5649|2024-08-05T15:11:47.417Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20geode
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-5649</link>
      <description>Apache Geode before 1.1.1, when a cluster has enabled security by setting the security-manager property, allows remote authenticated users with CLUSTER:READ but not DATA:READ permission to access the data browser page in Pulse and consequently execute an OQL query that exposes data stored in the cluster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-5649|2024-08-05T15:11:47.417Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2017 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-9794|2024-08-05T17:18:02.182Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20geode
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-9794</link>
      <description>When a cluster is operating in secure mode, a user with read privileges for specific data regions can use the gfsh command line utility to execute queries. In Apache Geode before 1.2.1, the query results may contain data from another user's concurrently executing gfsh query, potentially revealing data that the user is not authorized to view.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-9794|2024-08-05T17:18:02.182Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-9796|2024-08-05T17:18:02.187Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20geode
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-9796</link>
      <description>When an Apache Geode cluster before v1.3.0 is operating in secure mode, a user with read access to specific regions within a Geode cluster may execute OQL queries containing a region name as a bind parameter that allow read access to objects within unauthorized regions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-9796|2024-08-05T17:18:02.187Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-9797|2024-08-05T17:18:01.974Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20geode
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-9797</link>
      <description>When an Apache Geode cluster before v1.2.1 is operating in secure mode, an unauthenticated client can enter multi-user authentication mode and send metadata messages. These metadata operations could leak information about application data types. In addition, an attacker could perform a denial of service attack on the cluster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-9797|2024-08-05T17:18:01.974Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-9795|2024-08-05T17:18:02.193Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20geode
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-9795</link>
      <description>When an Apache Geode cluster before v1.3.0 is operating in secure mode, a user with read access to specific regions within a Geode cluster may execute OQL queries that allow read and write access to objects within unauthorized regions. In addition a user could invoke methods that allow remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-9795|2024-08-05T17:18:02.193Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
