<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache Mesos</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/apache%20software%20foundation/apache%20mesos.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache Mesos</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 22:22:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11793|2024-09-16T16:27:53.700Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20mesos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11793</link>
      <description>When parsing a JSON payload with deeply nested JSON structures, the parser in Apache Mesos versions pre-1.4.x, 1.4.0 to 1.4.2, 1.5.0 to 1.5.1, 1.6.0 to 1.6.1, and 1.7.0 might overflow the stack due to unbounded recursion. A malicious actor can therefore cause a denial of service of Mesos masters rendering the Mesos-controlled cluster inoperable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11793|2024-09-16T16:27:53.700Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1330|2024-09-16T20:42:57.117Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20mesos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1330</link>
      <description>When parsing a malformed JSON payload, libprocess in Apache Mesos versions 1.4.0 to 1.5.0 might crash due to an uncaught exception. Parsing chunked HTTP requests with trailers can lead to a libprocess crash too because of the mistakenly planted assertion. A malicious actor can therefore cause a denial of service of Mesos masters rendering the Mesos-controlled cluster inoperable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1330|2024-09-16T20:42:57.117Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7687|2024-09-16T16:43:52.011Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20mesos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7687</link>
      <description>When handling a decoding failure for a malformed URL path of an HTTP request, libprocess in Apache Mesos before 1.1.3, 1.2.x before 1.2.2, 1.3.x before 1.3.1, and 1.4.0-dev might crash because the code accidentally calls inappropriate function. A malicious actor can therefore cause a denial of service of Mesos masters rendering the Mesos-controlled cluster inoperable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7687|2024-09-16T16:43:52.011Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-8023|2024-09-16T16:58:25.082Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20mesos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-8023</link>
      <description>Apache Mesos can be configured to require authentication to call the Executor HTTP API using JSON Web Token (JWT). In Apache Mesos versions pre-1.4.2, 1.5.0, 1.5.1, 1.6.0 the comparison of the generated HMAC value against the provided signature in the JWT implementation used is vulnerable to a timing attack because instead of a constant-time string comparison routine a standard `==` operator has been used. A malicious actor can therefore abuse the timing difference of when the JWT validation function returns to reveal the correct HMAC value.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-8023|2024-09-16T16:58:25.082Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
