<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache NiFi</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/apache%20software%20foundation/apache%20nifi.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache NiFi</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 18:24:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-33140|2024-08-03T08:01:19.873Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20nifi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-33140</link>
      <description>The optional ShellUserGroupProvider in Apache NiFi 1.10.0 to 1.16.2 and Apache NiFi Registry 0.6.0 to 1.16.2 does not neutralize arguments for group resolution commands, allowing injection of operating system commands on Linux and macOS platforms. The ShellUserGroupProvider is not included in the default configuration. Command injection requires ShellUserGroupProvider to be one of the enabled User Group Providers in the Authorizers configuration. Command injection also requires an authenticated user with elevated privileges. Apache NiFi requires an authenticated user with authorization to modify access policies in order to execute the command. Apache NiFi Registry requires an authenticated user with authorization to read user groups in order to execute the command. The resolution removes command formatting based on user-provided arguments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-33140|2024-08-03T08:01:19.873Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 14:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29265|2024-08-03T06:17:54.476Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20nifi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29265</link>
      <description>Multiple components in Apache NiFi 0.0.1 to 1.16.0 do not restrict XML External Entity references in the default configuration. The Standard Content Viewer service attempts to resolve XML External Entity references when viewing formatted XML files. The following Processors attempt to resolve XML External Entity references when configured with default property values: - EvaluateXPath - EvaluateXQuery - ValidateXml Apache NiFi flow configurations that include these Processors are vulnerable to malicious XML documents that contain Document Type Declarations with XML External Entity references. The resolution disables Document Type Declarations in the default configuration for these Processors, and disallows XML External Entity resolution in standard services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29265|2024-08-03T06:17:54.476Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 08:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-26850|2024-08-03T05:11:45.347Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20nifi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26850</link>
      <description>When creating or updating credentials for single-user access, Apache NiFi wrote a copy of the Login Identity Providers configuration to the operating system temporary directory. On most platforms, the operating system temporary directory has global read permissions. NiFi immediately moved the temporary file to the final configuration directory, which significantly limited the window of opportunity for access. NiFi 1.16.0 includes updates to replace the Login Identity Providers configuration without writing a file to the operating system temporary directory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-26850|2024-08-03T05:11:45.347Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 17:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37389|2024-08-02T03:50:56.177Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20nifi</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37389</link>
      <description>Apache NiFi 1.10.0 through 1.26.0 and 2.0.0-M1 through 2.0.0-M3 support a description field in the Parameter Context configuration that is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. An authenticated user, authorized to configure a Parameter Context, can enter arbitrary JavaScript code, which the client browser will execute within the session context of the authenticated user. Upgrading to Apache NiFi 1.27.0 or 2.0.0-M4 is the recommended mitigation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37389|2024-08-02T03:50:56.177Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 07:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37389|2024-07-08T07:29:00.146Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20nifi</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37389</link>
      <description>Apache NiFi 1.10.0 through 1.26.0 and 2.0.0-M1 through 2.0.0-M3 support a description field in the Parameter Context configuration that is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. An authenticated user, authorized to configure a Parameter Context, can enter arbitrary JavaScript code, which the client browser will execute within the session context of the authenticated user. Upgrading to Apache NiFi 1.27.0 or 2.0.0-M4 is the recommended mitigation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37389|2024-07-08T07:29:00.146Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 07:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37389|2024-07-08T13:39:29.650Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20nifi</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37389</link>
      <description>Apache NiFi 1.10.0 through 1.26.0 and 2.0.0-M1 through 2.0.0-M3 support a description field in the Parameter Context configuration that is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. An authenticated user, authorized to configure a Parameter Context, can enter arbitrary JavaScript code, which the client browser will execute within the session context of the authenticated user. Upgrading to Apache NiFi 1.27.0 or 2.0.0-M4 is the recommended mitigation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37389|2024-07-08T13:39:29.650Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 07:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
