<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache Airflow Spark Provider</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/apache%20software%20foundation/apache%20airflow%20spark%20provider.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache Airflow Spark Provider</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28710|2023-06-12T14:16:06.937Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20airflow%20spark%20provider
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-28710</link>
      <description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Apache Software Foundation Apache Airflow Spark Provider.This issue affects Apache Airflow Spark Provider: before 4.0.1.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28710|2023-06-12T14:16:06.937Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 14:55:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40195|2023-08-28T07:50:01.211Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20airflow%20spark%20provider
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40195</link>
      <description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data, Inclusion of Functionality from Untrusted Control Sphere vulnerability in Apache Software Foundation Apache Airflow Spark Provider.

When the Apache Spark provider is installed on an Airflow deployment, an Airflow user that is authorized to configure Spark hooks can effectively run arbitrary code on the Airflow node by pointing it at a malicious Spark server. Prior to version 4.1.3, this was not called out in the documentation explicitly, so it is possible that administrators provided authorizations to configure Spark hooks without taking this into account. We recommend administrators to review their configurations to make sure the authorization to configure Spark hooks is only provided to fully trusted users.

To view the warning in the docs please visit  https://airflow.apache.org/docs/apache-airflow-providers-apache-spark/4.1.3/connections/spark.html 

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40195|2023-08-28T07:50:01.211Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 07:50:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40272|2023-08-17T13:52:30.647Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20airflow%20spark%20provider
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40272</link>
      <description>Apache Airflow Spark Provider, versions before 4.1.3, is affected by a vulnerability that allows an attacker to pass in malicious parameters when establishing a connection giving an opportunity to read files on the Airflow server.
It is recommended to upgrade to a version that is not affected.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40272|2023-08-17T13:52:30.647Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 13:52:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
