<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache Maven</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/apache%20software%20foundation/apache%20maven.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Apache Software Foundation -- Apache Maven</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 23:23:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29599|2024-08-03T06:26:06.558Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20maven
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29599</link>
      <description>In Apache Maven maven-shared-utils prior to version 3.3.3, the Commandline class can emit double-quoted strings without proper escaping, allowing shell injection attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29599|2024-08-03T06:26:06.558Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 10:25:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-26291|2024-08-03T20:19:20.126Z -- apache%20software%20foundation -- apache%20maven
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26291</link>
      <description>Apache Maven will follow repositories that are defined in a dependency’s Project Object Model (pom) which may be surprising to some users, resulting in potential risk if a malicious actor takes over that repository or is able to insert themselves into a position to pretend to be that repository. Maven is changing the default behavior in 3.8.1+ to no longer follow http (non-SSL) repository references by default. More details available in the referenced urls. If you are currently using a repository manager to govern the repositories used by your builds, you are unaffected by the risks present in the legacy behavior, and are unaffected by this vulnerability and change to default behavior. See this link for more information about repository management: https://maven.apache.org/repository-management.html</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-26291|2024-08-03T20:19:20.126Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 14:20:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
