<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Ydalb -- mapicoin</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ydalb/mapicoin.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Ydalb -- mapicoin</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 04:23:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2016-15029|2024-08-06T03:47:34.725Z -- ydalb -- mapicoin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-15029</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Ydalb mapicoin up to 1.9.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file webroot/stats.php. The manipulation of the argument link/search leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 1.10.0 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as 67e87f0f0c1ac238fcd050f4c3db298229bc9679. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-223402 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In Ydalb mapicoin bis 1.9.0 wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle gefunden. Betroffen ist eine unbekannte Verarbeitung der Datei webroot/stats.php. Durch die Manipulation des Arguments link/search mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 1.10.0 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als 67e87f0f0c1ac238fcd050f4c3db298229bc9679 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2016-15029|2024-08-06T03:47:34.725Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
