<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for deislabs -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/deislabs/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for deislabs -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 20:22:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-21272|2024-08-03T18:09:15.220Z -- deislabs -- oras
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21272</link>
      <description>ORAS is open source software which enables a way to push OCI Artifacts to OCI Conformant registries. ORAS is both a CLI for initial testing and a Go Module. In ORAS from version 0.4.0 and before version 0.9.0, there is a "zip-slip" vulnerability. The directory support feature allows the downloaded gzipped tarballs to be automatically extracted to the user-specified directory where the tarball can have symbolic links and hard links. A well-crafted tarball or tarballs allow malicious artifact providers linking, writing, or overwriting specific files on the host filesystem outside of the user-specified directory unexpectedly with the same permissions as the user who runs `oras pull`. Users of the affected versions are impacted if they are `oras` CLI users who runs `oras pull`, or if they are Go programs, which invoke `github.com/deislabs/oras/pkg/content.FileStore`. The problem has been fixed in version 0.9.0. For `oras` CLI users, there is no workarounds other than pulling from a trusted artifact provider. For `oras` package users, the workaround is to not use `github.com/deislabs/oras/pkg/content.FileStore`, and use other content stores instead, or pull from a trusted artifact provider.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-21272|2024-08-03T18:09:15.220Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 18:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
