<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Biscom -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/biscom/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Biscom -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 17:22:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-5246|2024-08-05T14:55:35.789Z -- biscom -- secure%20file%20transfer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-5246</link>
      <description>Biscom Secure File Transfer is vulnerable to AngularJS expression injection in the Display Name field. An authenticated user can populate this field with a valid AngularJS expression, wrapped in double curly-braces ({{ }}). This expression will be evaluated by any other authenticated user who views the attacker's display name. Affected versions are 5.0.0000 through 5.1.1026. The Issue is fixed in 5.1.1028.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-5246|2024-08-05T14:55:35.789Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-5241|2024-08-05T14:55:35.822Z -- biscom -- secure%20file%20transfer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-5241</link>
      <description>Biscom Secure File Transfer versions 5.0.0.0 trough 5.1.1024 are vulnerable to post-authentication persistent cross-site scripting (XSS) in the "Name" and "Description" fields of a Workspace, as well as the "Description" field of a File Details pane of a file stored in a Workspace. This issue has been resolved in version 5.1.1025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-5241|2024-08-05T14:55:35.822Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-5247|2024-08-05T14:55:35.883Z -- biscom -- secure%20file%20transfer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-5247</link>
      <description>Biscom Secure File Transfer is vulnerable to cross-site scripting in the File Name field. An authenticated user with permissions to upload or send files can populate this field with a filename that contains standard HTML scripting tags. The resulting script will evaluated by any other authenticated user who views the attacker-supplied file name. All versions of SFT prior to 5.1.1028 are affected. The fix version is 5.1.1028.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-5247|2024-08-05T14:55:35.883Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
