<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for smackcoders -- Import All Pages, Post types, Products, Orders, and Users as XML &amp; CSV</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/smackcoders/import%20all%20pages%2C%20post%20types%2C%20products%2C%20orders%2C%20and%20users%20as%20xml%20%26%20csv.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for smackcoders -- Import All Pages, Post types, Products, Orders, and Users as XML &amp; CSV</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4139|2023-08-04T02:04:27.318Z -- smackcoders -- import%20all%20pages%2C%20post%20types%2C%20products%2C%20orders%2C%20and%20users%20as%20xml%20%26%20csv
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4139</link>
      <description>The WP Ultimate CSV Importer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure  via Directory Listing due to missing restriction in export folder indexing in versions up to, and including, 7.9.8. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to list and view exported files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4139|2023-08-04T02:04:27.318Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 02:04:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4142|2023-08-04T02:04:30.714Z -- smackcoders -- import%20all%20pages%2C%20post%20types%2C%20products%2C%20orders%2C%20and%20users%20as%20xml%20%26%20csv
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4142</link>
      <description>The WP Ultimate CSV Importer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in versions up to, and including, 7.9.8 via the '-&gt;cus1' parameter. This allows authenticated attackers with author-level permissions or above, if the administrator previously grants access in the plugin settings, to execute code on the server. The author resolved this vulnerability by removing the ability for authors and editors to import files, please note that this means remote code execution is still possible for site administrators, use the plugin with caution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4142|2023-08-04T02:04:30.714Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 02:04:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4141|2023-08-04T02:04:28.826Z -- smackcoders -- import%20all%20pages%2C%20post%20types%2C%20products%2C%20orders%2C%20and%20users%20as%20xml%20%26%20csv
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4141</link>
      <description>The WP Ultimate CSV Importer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in versions up to, and including, 7.9.8 via the '-&gt;cus2' parameter. This allows authenticated attackers with author-level permissions or above, if the administrator previously grants access in the plugin settings, to create a PHP file and execute code on the server. The author resolved this vulnerability by removing the ability for authors and editors to import files, please note that this means php file creation is still allowed for site administrators, use the plugin with caution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4141|2023-08-04T02:04:28.826Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 02:04:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-4140|2023-08-04T02:04:24.655Z -- smackcoders -- import%20all%20pages%2C%20post%20types%2C%20products%2C%20orders%2C%20and%20users%20as%20xml%20%26%20csv
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-4140</link>
      <description>The WP Ultimate CSV Importer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in versions up to, and including, 7.9.8 due to insufficient restriction on the 'get_header_values' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with minimal permissions such as an author, if the administrator previously grants access in the plugin settings, to modify their user role by supplying the 'wp_capabilities-&gt;cus1' parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-4140|2023-08-04T02:04:24.655Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 02:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
