<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Weidmüller -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/weidm%C3%BCller/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Weidmüller -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:21:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-33528|2024-09-16T20:02:22.419Z -- weidm%C3%BCller -- ie-wl%28t%29-bl-ap-cl-xx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-33528</link>
      <description>In Weidmueller Industrial WLAN devices in multiple versions an exploitable privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the iw_console functionality. A specially crafted menu selection string can cause an escape from the restricted console, resulting in system access as the root user. An attacker can send commands while authenticated as a low privilege user to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-33528|2024-09-16T20:02:22.419Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 18:25:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-33529|2024-09-16T17:52:51.853Z -- weidm%C3%BCller -- ie-wl%28t%29-bl-ap-cl-xx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-33529</link>
      <description>In Weidmueller Industrial WLAN devices in multiple versions the usage of hard-coded cryptographic keys within the service agent binary allows for the decryption of captured traffic across the network from or to the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-33529|2024-09-16T17:52:51.853Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 18:25:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-33539|2024-09-16T17:43:21.621Z -- weidm%C3%BCller -- ie-wl%28t%29-bl-ap-cl-xx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-33539</link>
      <description>In Weidmueller Industrial WLAN devices in multiple versions an exploitable authentication bypass vulnerability exists in the hostname processing. A specially configured device hostname can cause the device to interpret selected remote traffic as local traffic, resulting in a bypass of web authentication. An attacker can send authenticated SNMP requests to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-33539|2024-09-16T17:43:21.621Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 18:26:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
