<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Weidmüller -- IE-WL(T)-BL-AP-CL-XX</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/weidm%C3%BCller/ie-wl%28t%29-bl-ap-cl-xx.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Weidmüller -- IE-WL(T)-BL-AP-CL-XX</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 22:22:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-33535|2024-09-17T01:15:45.850Z -- weidm%C3%BCller -- ie-wl%28t%29-bl-ap-cl-xx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-33535</link>
      <description>In Weidmueller Industrial WLAN devices in multiple versions an exploitable format string vulnerability exists in the iw_console conio_writestr functionality. A specially crafted time server entry can cause an overflow of the time server buffer, resulting in remote code execution. An attacker can send commands while authenticated as a low privilege user to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-33535|2024-09-17T01:15:45.850Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 18:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-33536|2024-09-17T03:38:31.151Z -- weidm%C3%BCller -- ie-wl%28t%29-bl-ap-cl-xx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-33536</link>
      <description>In Weidmueller Industrial WLAN devices in multiple versions an exploitable denial-of-service vulnerability exists in ServiceAgent functionality. A specially crafted packet can cause an integer underflow, triggering a large memcpy that will access unmapped or out-of-bounds memory. An attacker can send this packet while unauthenticated to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-33536|2024-09-17T03:38:31.151Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 18:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-33534|2024-09-17T04:20:16.498Z -- weidm%C3%BCller -- ie-wl%28t%29-bl-ap-cl-xx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-33534</link>
      <description>In Weidmueller Industrial WLAN devices in multiple versions an exploitable command injection vulnerability exists in the hostname functionality. A specially crafted entry to network configuration information can cause execution of arbitrary system commands, resulting in full control of the device. An attacker can send various requests while authenticated as a high privilege user to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-33534|2024-09-17T04:20:16.498Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 18:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-33537|2024-09-17T02:57:37.665Z -- weidm%C3%BCller -- ie-wl%28t%29-bl-ap-cl-xx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-33537</link>
      <description>In Weidmueller Industrial WLAN devices in multiple versions an exploitable remote code execution vulnerability exists in the iw_webs configuration parsing functionality. A specially crafted user name entry can cause an overflow of an error message buffer, resulting in remote code execution. An attacker can send commands while authenticated as a low privilege user to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-33537|2024-09-17T02:57:37.665Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 18:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-33533|2024-09-17T02:07:08.701Z -- weidm%C3%BCller -- ie-wl%28t%29-bl-ap-cl-xx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-33533</link>
      <description>In Weidmueller Industrial WLAN devices in multiple versions an exploitable command injection vulnerability exists in the iw_webs functionality. A specially crafted iw_serverip parameter can cause user input to be reflected in a subsequent iw_system call, resulting in remote control over the device. An attacker can send commands while authenticated as a low privilege user to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-33533|2024-09-17T02:07:08.701Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 18:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-33530|2024-09-17T02:01:49.357Z -- weidm%C3%BCller -- ie-wl%28t%29-bl-ap-cl-xx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-33530</link>
      <description>In Weidmueller Industrial WLAN devices in multiple versions an exploitable command injection vulnerability exists in encrypted diagnostic script functionality of the devices. A specially crafted diagnostic script file can cause arbitrary busybox commands to be executed, resulting in remote control over the device. An attacker can send diagnostic while authenticated as a low privilege user to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-33530|2024-09-17T02:01:49.357Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 18:25:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-33532|2024-09-17T01:25:59.161Z -- weidm%C3%BCller -- ie-wl%28t%29-bl-ap-cl-xx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-33532</link>
      <description>In Weidmueller Industrial WLAN devices in multiple versions an exploitable command injection vulnerability exists in the iw_webs functionality. A specially crafted diagnostic script file name can cause user input to be reflected in a subsequent iw_system call, resulting in remote control over the device. An attacker can send commands while authenticated as a low privilege user to trigger this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-33532|2024-09-17T01:25:59.161Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 18:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
