<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for chrisy -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/chrisy/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for chrisy -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 18:24:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2015-10131|2024-07-05T17:22:22.697Z -- chrisy -- tfo%20graphviz%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-10131</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in chrisy TFO Graphviz Plugin up to 1.9 on WordPress and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function admin_page_load/admin_page of the file tfo-graphviz-admin.php. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 1.10 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is 594c953a345f79e26003772093b0caafc14b92c2. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-258620.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in chrisy TFO Graphviz Plugin bis 1.9 für WordPress gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist die Funktion admin_page_load/admin_page der Datei tfo-graphviz-admin.php. Durch Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 1.10 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als 594c953a345f79e26003772093b0caafc14b92c2 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2015-10131|2024-07-05T17:22:22.697Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 06:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
