<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Lespeed -- WiseCleaner Wise System Monitor</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/lespeed/wisecleaner%20wise%20system%20monitor.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Lespeed -- WiseCleaner Wise System Monitor</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 19:20:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1488|2024-08-02T05:49:11.698Z -- lespeed -- wisecleaner%20wise%20system%20monitor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1488</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Lespeed WiseCleaner Wise System Monitor 1.5.3.54. Affected is the function 0x9C40A0D8/0x9C40A0DC/0x9C40A0E0 in the library WiseHDInfo64.dll of the component IoControlCode Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-223374 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Es wurde eine Schwachstelle in Lespeed WiseCleaner Wise System Monitor 1.5.3.54 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen hiervon ist die Funktion 0x9C40A0D8/0x9C40A0DC/0x9C40A0E0 in der Bibliothek WiseHDInfo64.dll der Komponente IoControlCode Handler. Durch Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine denial of service-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff hat dabei lokal zu erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1488|2024-08-02T05:49:11.698Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 21:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1489|2024-08-02T05:49:11.683Z -- lespeed -- wisecleaner%20wise%20system%20monitor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1489</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Lespeed WiseCleaner Wise System Monitor 1.5.3.54 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function 0x9C402088 in the library WiseHDInfo64.dll of the component IoControlCode Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-223375.
In Lespeed WiseCleaner Wise System Monitor 1.5.3.54 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht um die Funktion 0x9C402088 in der Bibliothek WiseHDInfo64.dll der Komponente IoControlCode Handler. Durch das Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine improper access controls-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff muss lokal angegangen werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1489|2024-08-02T05:49:11.683Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 21:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1487|2024-08-02T05:49:11.668Z -- lespeed -- wisecleaner%20wise%20system%20monitor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1487</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Lespeed WiseCleaner Wise System Monitor 1.5.3.54. This issue affects the function 0x9C40208C/0x9C402000/0x9C402084/0x9C402088/0x9C402004/0x9C4060C4/0x9C4060CC/0x9C4060D0/0x9C4060D4/0x9C40A0DC/0x9C40A0D8/0x9C40A0DC/0x9C40A0E0 in the library WiseHDInfo64.dll of the component IoControlCode Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-223373 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Lespeed WiseCleaner Wise System Monitor 1.5.3.54 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist die Funktion 0x9C40208C/0x9C402000/0x9C402084/0x9C402088/0x9C402004/0x9C4060C4/0x9C4060CC/0x9C4060D0/0x9C4060D4/0x9C40A0DC/0x9C40A0D8/0x9C40A0DC/0x9C40A0E0 in der Bibliothek WiseHDInfo64.dll der Komponente IoControlCode Handler. Durch das Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine denial of service-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden muss der Angriff lokal. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1487|2024-08-02T05:49:11.668Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 21:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
