<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for crmperks -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/crmperks/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for crmperks -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 21:24:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-1069|2024-01-31T02:35:09.832Z -- crmperks -- Database for Contact Form 7, WPforms, Elementor forms
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1069</link><description>The Contact Form Entries plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient file validation on the 'view_page' function in versions up to, and including, 1.3.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with administrator-level capabilities or above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1069|2024-01-31T02:35:09.832Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 02:35:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3715|2024-05-02T16:52:30.676Z -- crmperks -- Database for Contact Form 7, WPforms, Elementor forms
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3715</link><description>The Database for Contact Form 7, WPforms, Elementor forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3715|2024-05-02T16:52:30.676Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2030|2024-03-13T15:27:13.560Z -- crmperks -- Database for Contact Form 7, WPforms, Elementor forms
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2030</link><description>The Database for Contact Form 7, WPforms, Elementor forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2030|2024-03-13T15:27:13.560Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:27:13 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>