<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for gofiber -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/gofiber/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for gofiber -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 21:21:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38513|2024-07-02T20:31:39.546Z -- gofiber -- fiber
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38513</link>
      <description>Fiber is an Express-inspired web framework written in Go A vulnerability present in versions prior to 2.52.5 is a session middleware issue in GoFiber versions 2 and above. This vulnerability allows users to supply their own session_id value, resulting in the creation of a session with that key. If a website relies on the mere presence of a session for security purposes, this can lead to significant security risks, including unauthorized access and session fixation attacks. All users utilizing GoFiber's session middleware in the affected versions are impacted. The issue has been addressed in version 2.52.5. Users are strongly encouraged to upgrade to version 2.52.5 or higher to mitigate this vulnerability. Users who are unable to upgrade immediately can apply the following workarounds to reduce the risk: Either implement additional validation to ensure session IDs are not supplied by the user and are securely generated by the server, or regularly rotate session IDs and enforce strict session expiration policies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-38513|2024-07-02T20:31:39.546Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22199|2024-01-11T17:39:45.745Z -- gofiber -- template</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22199</link>
      <description>This package provides universal methods to use multiple template engines with the Fiber web framework using the Views interface. This vulnerability specifically impacts web applications that render user-supplied data through this template engine, potentially leading to the execution of malicious scripts in users' browsers when visiting affected web pages. The vulnerability has been addressed, the template engine now defaults to having autoescape set to `true`, effectively mitigating the risk of XSS attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22199|2024-01-11T17:39:45.745Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 17:39:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-25124|2024-02-21T21:01:44.672Z -- gofiber -- fiber</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25124</link>
      <description>Fiber is a web framework written in go. Prior to version 2.52.1, the CORS middleware allows for insecure configurations that could potentially expose the application to multiple CORS-related vulnerabilities. Specifically, it allows setting the Access-Control-Allow-Origin header to a wildcard (`*`) while also having the Access-Control-Allow-Credentials set to true, which goes against recommended security best practices. The impact of this misconfiguration is high as it can lead to unauthorized access to sensitive user data and expose the system to various types of attacks listed in the PortSwigger article linked in the references. Version 2.52.1 contains a patch for this issue. As a workaround, users may manually validate the CORS configurations in their implementation to ensure that they do not allow a wildcard origin when credentials are enabled. The browser fetch api, as well as browsers and utilities that enforce CORS policies, are not affected by this.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25124|2024-02-21T21:01:44.672Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:01:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38513|2024-07-01T18:31:13.028Z -- gofiber -- fiber</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38513</link>
      <description>Fiber is an Express-inspired web framework written in Go A vulnerability present in versions prior to 2.52.5 is a session middleware issue in GoFiber versions 2 and above. This vulnerability allows users to supply their own session_id value, resulting in the creation of a session with that key. If a website relies on the mere presence of a session for security purposes, this can lead to significant security risks, including unauthorized access and session fixation attacks. All users utilizing GoFiber's session middleware in the affected versions are impacted. The issue has been addressed in version 2.52.5. Users are strongly encouraged to upgrade to version 2.52.5 or higher to mitigate this vulnerability. Users who are unable to upgrade immediately can apply the following workarounds to reduce the risk: Either implement additional validation to ensure session IDs are not supplied by the user and are securely generated by the server, or regularly rotate session IDs and enforce strict session expiration policies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-38513|2024-07-01T18:31:13.028Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
