<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Contec Health -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/contec%20health/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Contec Health -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 15:22:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38100|2024-08-03T10:45:52.412Z -- contec%20health -- cms8000%20contec%20icu%20ccu%20vital%20signs%20patient%20monitor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38100</link>
      <description>The CMS800 device fails while attempting to parse malformed network data sent by a threat actor. A threat actor with network access can remotely issue a specially formatted UDP request that will cause the entire device to crash and require a physical reboot. A UDP broadcast request could be sent that causes a mass denial-of-service attack on all CME8000 devices connected to the same network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38100|2024-08-03T10:45:52.412Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38069|2024-08-03T10:45:52.456Z -- contec%20health -- cms8000%20contec%20icu%20ccu%20vital%20signs%20patient%20monitor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38069</link>
      <description>Multiple globally default credentials exist across all CMS8000 devices, that once exposed, allow a threat actor with momentary physical access to gain privileged access to any device. Privileged credential access enables the extraction of sensitive patient information or modification of device parameters</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38069|2024-08-03T10:45:52.456Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36385|2024-08-03T10:00:04.453Z -- contec%20health -- cms8000%20contec%20icu%20ccu%20vital%20signs%20patient%20monitor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36385</link>
      <description>A threat actor with momentary access to the device can plug in a USB drive and perform a malicious firmware update, resulting in permanent changes to device functionality. No authentication or controls are in place to prevent a threat actor from maliciously modifying firmware and performing a drive-by attack to load the firmware on any CMS8000 device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36385|2024-08-03T10:00:04.453Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38453|2024-08-03T10:54:03.773Z -- contec%20health -- cms8000%20contec%20icu%20ccu%20vital%20signs%20patient%20monitor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38453</link>
      <description>Multiple binary application files on the CMS8000 device are compiled with 'not stripped' and 'debug_info' compilation settings. These compiler settings greatly decrease the level of effort for a threat actor to reverse engineer sensitive code and identify additional vulnerabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38453|2024-08-03T10:54:03.773Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3027|2024-08-03T00:53:00.651Z -- contec%20health -- cms8000%20contec%20icu%20ccu%20vital%20signs%20patient%20monitor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3027</link>
      <description>The CMS8000 device does not properly control or sanitize the SSID name of a new Wi-Fi access point. A threat actor could create an SSID with a malicious name, including non-standard characters that, when the device attempts connecting to the malicious SSID, the device can be exploited to write arbitrary files or display incorrect information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3027|2024-08-03T00:53:00.651Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
