<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for portabilis -- i-educar</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/portabilis/i-educar.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for portabilis -- i-educar</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 21:22:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-45058|2024-08-28T20:35:17.069Z -- portabilis -- i-educar
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45058</link>
      <description>i-Educar is free, completely online school management software that allows school secretaries, teachers, coordinators and area managers. An attacker with only minimal viewing privileges in the settings section is able to change their user type to Administrator (or another type with super-permissions). Any user is capable of becoming an administrator, which can lead to account theft, changing administrative tasks, etc. The failure occurs in the file located in ieducar/intranet/educar_usuario_cad.php on line 446 , which does not perform checks on the user's current permission level to make changes.  This issue has not yet been patched. Users are advised to contact the developer and to coordinate an update schedule.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-45058|2024-08-28T20:35:17.069Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 20:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-45059|2024-08-28T20:35:01.466Z -- portabilis -- i-educar
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45059</link>
      <description>i-Educar is free, completely online school management software that allows school secretaries, teachers, coordinators and area managers. In affected versions Creating a SQL query from a concatenation of a user-controlled GET parameter allows an attacker to manipulate the query. Successful exploitation of this flaw allows an attacker to have complete and unrestricted access to the database, with a web user with minimal permissions. This may involve obtaining user information, such as emails, password hashes, etc. This issue has not yet been patched. Users are advised to contact the developer and to coordinate an update schedule.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-45059|2024-08-28T20:35:01.466Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 20:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-45057|2024-08-28T20:36:24.401Z -- portabilis -- i-educar
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45057</link>
      <description>i-Educar is free, completely online school management software that allows school secretaries, teachers, coordinators and area managers. The lack of sanitization of user-controlled parameters for generating HTML field values ​​dynamically leads to XSS (Cross-Site Scripting) attacks. The dynamic generation of HTML fields in the ieducar/intranet/include/clsCampos.inc.php file does not perform the correct validation or sanitization, reflecting the user-controlled values ​​to be shown in the page's HTML. This allows an attacker to inject a specific XSS payload into a parameter. Successful exploitation of this flaw allows an attacker to trick the victim into clicking a vulnerable URL, enabling JavaScript scripts to be executed in the browser. Due to the configuration of session cookies, with the HttpOnly and SameSite=Lax flags being defined, there is little an attacker can do to steal the session or force the victim to perform actions within the application. This issue hast been patched but a new release has not yet been made. Users are advised to contact the developer and to coordinate an update schedule.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-45057|2024-08-28T20:36:24.401Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 20:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
