<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for decidim -- decidim</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/decidim/decidim.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for decidim -- decidim</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 18:23:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-48220|2024-07-26T17:11:07.062Z -- decidim -- decidim
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48220</link>
      <description>Decidim is a participatory democracy framework. Starting in version 0.4.rc3 and prior to version 2.0.9 of the `devise_invitable` gem, the invites feature allows users to accept the invitation for an unlimited amount of time through the password reset functionality. This issue creates vulnerable dependencies starting in version 0.0.1.alpha3 and prior to versions 0.26.9, 0.27.5, and 0.28.0 of the `decidim,` `decidim-admin`, and `decidim-system` gems. When using the password reset functionality, the `devise_invitable` gem always accepts the pending invitation if the user has been invited. The only check done is if the user has been invited but the code does not ensure that the pending invitation is still valid as defined by the `invite_for` expiry period. Decidim sets this configuration to `2.weeks` so this configuration should be respected. The bug is in the `devise_invitable` gem and should be fixed there and the dependency should be upgraded in Decidim once the fix becomes available. `devise_invitable` to version `2.0.9` and above fix this issue. Versions 0.26.9, 0.27.5, and 0.28.0 of the `decidim,` `decidim-admin`, and `decidim-system` gems contain this fix. As a workaround, invitations can be cancelled directly from the database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-48220|2024-07-26T17:11:07.062Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 17:24:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32469|2024-07-11T14:25:47.917Z -- decidim -- decidim</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32469</link>
      <description>Decidim is a participatory democracy framework. The pagination feature used in searches and filters is subject to potential XSS attack through a malformed URL using the GET parameter `per_page`. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.27.6 and 0.28.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32469|2024-07-11T14:25:47.917Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 19:10:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27090|2024-07-10T18:25:26.241Z -- decidim -- decidim</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27090</link>
      <description>Decidim is a participatory democracy framework, written in Ruby on Rails, originally developed for the Barcelona City government online and offline participation website. If an attacker can infer the slug or URL of an unpublished or private resource, and this resource can be embbeded (such as a Participatory Process, an Assembly, a Proposal, a Result, etc), then some data of this resource could be accessed. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.27.6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27090|2024-07-10T18:25:26.241Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:25:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-51447|2024-02-20T17:29:35.677Z -- decidim -- decidim</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-51447</link>
      <description>Decidim is a participatory democracy framework. Starting in version 0.27.0 and prior to versions 0.27.5 and 0.28.0, the dynamic file upload feature is subject to potential cross-site scripting attacks in case the attacker manages to modify the file names of the records being uploaded to the server. This appears in sections where the user controls the file upload dialogs themselves and has the technical knowledge to change the file names through the dynamic upload endpoint. Therefore I believe it would require the attacker to control the whole session of the particular user but in any case, this needs to be fixed. Successful exploit of this vulnerability would require the user to have successfully uploaded a file blob to the server with a malicious file name and then have the possibility to direct the other user to the edit page of the record where the attachment is attached. The users are able to craft the direct upload requests themselves controlling the file name that gets stored to the database. The attacker is able to change the filename e.g. to `&lt;svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;` if they know how to craft these requests themselves. And then enter the returned blob ID to the form inputs manually by modifying the edit page source. Versions 0.27.5 and 0.28.0 contain a patch for this issue. As a workaround, disable dynamic uploads for the instance, e.g. from proposals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-51447|2024-02-20T17:29:35.677Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 17:29:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-47634|2024-06-04T17:26:35.629Z -- decidim -- decidim</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-47634</link>
      <description>Decidim is a participatory democracy framework. Starting in version 0.10.0 and prior to versions 0.26.9, 0.27.5, and 0.28.0, a race condition in the endorsement of resources (for instance, a proposal) allows a user to make more than once endorsement. To exploit this vulnerability, the request to set an endorsement must be sent several times in parallel. Versions 0.26.9, 0.27.5, and 0.28.0 contain a patch for this issue. As a workaround, disable the Endorsement feature in the components.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-47634|2024-06-04T17:26:35.629Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 16:37:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-47635|2024-02-20T17:26:38.896Z -- decidim -- decidim</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-47635</link>
      <description>Decidim is a participatory democracy framework. Starting in version 0.23.0 and prior to versions 0.27.5 and 0.28.0, the CSRF authenticity token check is disabled for the questionnaire templates preview. The issue does not imply a serious security thread as you need to have access also to the session cookie in order to see this resource. This URL does not allow modifying the resource but it may allow attackers to gain access to information which was not meant to be public. The issue is fixed in version 0.27.5 and 0.28.0. As a workaround, disable the templates functionality or remove all available templates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-47635|2024-02-20T17:26:38.896Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 16:45:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-48220|2024-02-20T17:27:26.335Z -- decidim -- decidim</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-48220</link>
      <description>Decidim is a participatory democracy framework. Starting in version 0.4.rc3 and prior to version 2.0.9 of the `devise_invitable` gem, the invites feature allows users to accept the invitation for an unlimited amount of time through the password reset functionality. This issue creates vulnerable dependencies starting in version 0.0.1.alpha3 and prior to versions 0.26.9, 0.27.5, and 0.28.0 of the `decidim,` `decidim-admin`, and `decidim-system` gems. When using the password reset functionality, the `devise_invitable` gem always accepts the pending invitation if the user has been invited. The only check done is if the user has been invited but the code does not ensure that the pending invitation is still valid as defined by the `invite_for` expiry period. Decidim sets this configuration to `2.weeks` so this configuration should be respected. The bug is in the `devise_invitable` gem and should be fixed there and the dependency should be upgraded in Decidim once the fix becomes available. `devise_invitable` to version `2.0.9` and above fix this issue. Versions 0.26.9, 0.27.5, and 0.28.0 of the `decidim,` `decidim-admin`, and `decidim-system` gems contain this fix. As a workaround, invitations can be cancelled directly from the database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-48220|2024-02-20T17:27:26.335Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 17:24:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27095|2024-07-10T19:56:37.741Z -- decidim -- decidim</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27095</link>
      <description>Decidim is a participatory democracy framework. The admin panel is subject to potential XSS attach in case the attacker manages to modify some records being uploaded to the server. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.27.6 and 0.28.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27095|2024-07-10T19:56:37.741Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 19:07:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-32469|2024-07-10T19:10:36.304Z -- decidim -- decidim</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32469</link>
      <description>Decidim is a participatory democracy framework. The pagination feature used in searches and filters is subject to potential XSS attack through a malformed URL using the GET parameter `per_page`. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.27.6 and 0.28.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32469|2024-07-10T19:10:36.304Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 19:10:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27090|2024-07-11T17:44:23.242Z -- decidim -- decidim</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27090</link>
      <description>Decidim is a participatory democracy framework, written in Ruby on Rails, originally developed for the Barcelona City government online and offline participation website. If an attacker can infer the slug or URL of an unpublished or private resource, and this resource can be embbeded (such as a Participatory Process, an Assembly, a Proposal, a Result, etc), then some data of this resource could be accessed. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.27.6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27090|2024-07-11T17:44:23.242Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:25:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
