<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Twister -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/twister/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Twister -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 17:22:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1008|2024-08-02T05:32:46.252Z -- twister -- antivirus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1008</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Twister Antivirus 8.17. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects the function 0x801120E4 in the library filmfd.sys of the component IoControlCode Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-221741 was assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Twister Antivirus 8.17 ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht hierbei um die Funktion 0x801120E4 in der Bibliothek filmfd.sys der Komponente IoControlCode Handler. Durch die Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine denial of service-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden muss der Angriff lokal. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1008|2024-08-02T05:32:46.252Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 10:24:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1007|2024-08-02T05:32:46.463Z -- twister -- antivirus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1007</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Twister Antivirus 8.17. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function 0x801120E4 in the library filmfd.sys of the component IoControlCode Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-221740.
In Twister Antivirus 8.17 wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Es geht um die Funktion 0x801120E4 in der Bibliothek filmfd.sys der Komponente IoControlCode Handler. Mit der Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine improper access controls-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs hat dabei lokal zu erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1007|2024-08-02T05:32:46.463Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 10:23:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2873|2024-08-02T06:33:05.531Z -- twister -- antivirus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2873</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Twister Antivirus 8. This vulnerability affects the function 0x804f2143/0x804f217f/0x804f214b/0x80800043 in the library filppd.sys of the component IoControlCode Handler. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-229852. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
In Twister Antivirus 8 wurde eine Schwachstelle entdeckt. Sie wurde als kritisch eingestuft. Betroffen ist die Funktion 0x804f2143/0x804f217f/0x804f214b/0x80800043 in der Bibliothek filppd.sys der Komponente IoControlCode Handler. Durch das Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine memory corruption-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs hat dabei lokal zu erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2873|2024-08-02T06:33:05.531Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 18:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2874|2024-08-02T06:33:06.075Z -- twister -- antivirus
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2874</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Twister Antivirus 8. This issue affects the function 0x804f2158/0x804f2154/0x804f2150/0x804f215c/0x804f2160/0x80800040/0x804f214c/0x804f2148/0x804f2144/0x801120e4/0x804f213c/0x804f2140 in the library filppd.sys of the component IoControlCode Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-229853 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Twister Antivirus 8 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Betroffen davon ist die Funktion 0x804f2158/0x804f2154/0x804f2150/0x804f215c/0x804f2160/0x80800040/0x804f214c/0x804f2148/0x804f2144/0x801120e4/0x804f213c/0x804f2140 in der Bibliothek filppd.sys der Komponente IoControlCode Handler. Durch Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine denial of service-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden muss der Angriff lokal. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2874|2024-08-02T06:33:06.075Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 18:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
