<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for glpi-project -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/glpi-project/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for glpi-project -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 12:25:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11033|2024-08-04T11:21:14.326Z -- glpi-project -- glpi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11033</link>
      <description>In GLPI from version 9.1 and before version 9.4.6, any API user with READ right on User itemtype will have access to full list of users when querying apirest.php/User. The response contains: - All api_tokens which can be used to do privileges escalations or read/update/delete data normally non accessible to the current user. - All personal_tokens can display another users planning. Exploiting this vulnerability requires the api to be enabled, a technician account. It can be mitigated by adding an application token. This is fixed in version 9.4.6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11033|2024-08-04T11:21:14.326Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 21:15:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11032|2024-08-04T11:21:14.564Z -- glpi-project -- glpi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11032</link>
      <description>In GLPI before version 9.4.6, there is a SQL injection vulnerability for all helpdesk instances. Exploiting this vulnerability requires a technician account. This is fixed in version 9.4.6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11032|2024-08-04T11:21:14.564Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 21:05:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39213|2024-08-04T01:58:18.177Z -- glpi-project -- glpi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39213</link>
      <description>GLPI is a free Asset and IT management software package. Starting in version 9.1 and prior to version 9.5.6, GLPI with API Rest enabled is vulnerable to API bypass with custom header injection. This issue is fixed in version 9.5.6. One may disable API Rest as a workaround.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39213|2024-08-04T01:58:18.177Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 17:05:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39209|2024-08-04T01:58:18.170Z -- glpi-project -- glpi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39209</link>
      <description>GLPI is a free Asset and IT management software package. In versions prior to 9.5.6, a user who is logged in to GLPI can bypass Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) protection in many places. This could allow a malicious actor to perform many actions on GLPI. This issue is fixed in version 9.5.6. There are no workarounds aside from upgrading.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39209|2024-08-04T01:58:18.170Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39211|2024-08-04T01:58:18.247Z -- glpi-project -- glpi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39211</link>
      <description>GLPI is a free Asset and IT management software package. Starting in version 9.2 and prior to version 9.5.6, the telemetry endpoint discloses GLPI and server information. This issue is fixed in version 9.5.6. As a workaround, remove the file `ajax/telemetry.php`, which is not needed for usual functions of GLPI.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39211|2024-08-04T01:58:18.247Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 16:55:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11031|2024-08-04T11:21:14.373Z -- glpi-project -- glpi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11031</link>
      <description>In GLPI before version 9.5.0, the encryption algorithm used is insecure. The security of the data encrypted relies on the password used, if a user sets a weak/predictable password, an attacker could decrypt data. This is fixed in version 9.5.0 by using a more secure encryption library. The library chosen is sodium.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11031|2024-08-04T11:21:14.373Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 15:20:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-39210|2024-08-04T01:58:18.270Z -- glpi-project -- glpi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39210</link>
      <description>GLPI is a free Asset and IT management software package. In versions prior to 9.5.6, the cookie used to store the autologin cookie (when a user uses the "remember me" feature) is accessible by scripts. A malicious plugin that could steal this cookie would be able to use it to autologin. This issue is fixed in version 9.5.6. As a workaround, one may avoid using the "remember me" feature.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-39210|2024-08-04T01:58:18.270Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 16:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11034|2024-08-04T11:21:14.511Z -- glpi-project -- glpi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11034</link>
      <description>In GLPI before version 9.4.6, there is a vulnerability that allows bypassing the open redirect protection based which is based on a regexp. This is fixed in version 9.4.6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11034|2024-08-04T11:21:14.511Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 21:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11035|2024-08-04T11:21:14.511Z -- glpi-project -- glpi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11035</link>
      <description>In GLPI after version 0.83.3 and before version 9.4.6, the CSRF tokens are generated using an insecure algorithm. The implementation uses rand and uniqid and MD5 which does not provide secure values. This is fixed in version 9.4.6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11035|2024-08-04T11:21:14.511Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 21:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11060|2024-08-04T11:21:14.633Z -- glpi-project -- glpi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11060</link>
      <description>In GLPI before 9.4.6, an attacker can execute system commands by abusing the backup functionality. Theoretically, this vulnerability can be exploited by an attacker without a valid account by using a CSRF. Due to the difficulty of the exploitation, the attack is only conceivable by an account having Maintenance privileges and the right to add WIFI networks. This is fixed in version 9.4.6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11060|2024-08-04T11:21:14.633Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 19:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-5248|2024-08-04T08:22:09.092Z -- glpi-project -- glpi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-5248</link>
      <description>GLPI before before version 9.4.6 has a vulnerability involving a default encryption key. GLPIKEY is public and is used on every instance. This means anyone can decrypt sensitive data stored using this key. It is possible to change the key before installing GLPI. But on existing instances, data must be reencrypted with the new key. Problem is we can not know which columns or rows in the database are using that; espcially from plugins. Changing the key without updating data would lend in bad password sent from glpi; but storing them again from the UI will work.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-5248|2024-08-04T08:22:09.092Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 16:05:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-11036|2024-08-04T11:21:14.475Z -- glpi-project -- glpi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11036</link>
      <description>In GLPI before version 9.4.6 there are multiple related stored XSS vulnerabilities. The package is vulnerable to Stored XSS in the comments of items in the Knowledge base. Adding a comment with content "&lt;script&gt;alert(1)&lt;/script&gt;" reproduces the attack. This can be exploited by a user with administrator privileges in the User-Agent field. It can also be exploited by an outside party through the following steps: 1. Create a user with the surname `" onmouseover="alert(document.cookie)` and an empty first name. 2. With this user, create a ticket 3. As an administrator (or other privileged user) open the created ticket 4. On the "last update" field, put your mouse on the name of the user 5. The XSS fires This is fixed in version 9.4.6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-11036|2024-08-04T11:21:14.475Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 21:35:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31456|2024-08-02T01:52:56.947Z -- glpi-project -- glpi</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31456</link>
      <description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package. Prior to 10.0.15, an authenticated user can exploit a SQL injection vulnerability from map search. This vulnerability is fixed in 10.0.15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31456|2024-08-02T01:52:56.947Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:07:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37148|2024-07-15T20:17:53.471Z -- glpi-project -- glpi</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37148</link>
      <description>GLPI is an open-source asset and IT management software package that provides ITIL Service Desk features, licenses tracking and software auditing. An authenticated user can exploit a SQL injection vulnerability in some AJAX scripts to alter another user account data and take control of it. Upgrade to 10.0.16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37148|2024-07-15T20:17:53.471Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 19:18:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37149|2024-07-15T20:18:50.727Z -- glpi-project -- glpi</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37149</link>
      <description>GLPI is an open-source asset and IT management software package that provides ITIL Service Desk features, licenses tracking and software auditing. An authenticated technician user can upload a malicious PHP script and hijack the plugin loader to execute this malicious script. Upgrade to 10.0.16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37149|2024-07-15T20:18:50.727Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 19:20:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37148|2024-07-10T19:18:09.444Z -- glpi-project -- glpi</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37148</link>
      <description>GLPI is an open-source asset and IT management software package that provides ITIL Service Desk features, licenses tracking and software auditing. An authenticated user can exploit a SQL injection vulnerability in some AJAX scripts to alter another user account data and take control of it. Upgrade to 10.0.16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37148|2024-07-10T19:18:09.444Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 19:18:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37149|2024-07-10T19:20:36.161Z -- glpi-project -- glpi</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37149</link>
      <description>GLPI is an open-source asset and IT management software package that provides ITIL Service Desk features, licenses tracking and software auditing. An authenticated technician user can upload a malicious PHP script and hijack the plugin loader to execute this malicious script. Upgrade to 10.0.16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37149|2024-07-10T19:20:36.161Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 19:20:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27937|2024-07-05T17:21:14.396Z -- glpi-project -- glpi</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27937</link>
      <description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package, Data center management, ITIL Service Desk, licenses tracking and software auditing. An authenticated user can obtain the email address of all GLPI users. This issue has been patched in version 10.0.13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27937|2024-07-05T17:21:14.396Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 15:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-31456|2024-06-04T17:36:07.872Z -- glpi-project -- glpi</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-31456</link>
      <description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package. Prior to 10.0.15, an authenticated user can exploit a SQL injection vulnerability from map search. This vulnerability is fixed in 10.0.15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-31456|2024-06-04T17:36:07.872Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:07:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27937|2024-04-24T14:41:40.256Z -- glpi-project -- glpi</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27937</link>
      <description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package, Data center management, ITIL Service Desk, licenses tracking and software auditing. An authenticated user can obtain the email address of all GLPI users. This issue has been patched in version 10.0.13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27937|2024-04-24T14:41:40.256Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 15:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27096|2024-06-04T17:46:29.094Z -- glpi-project -- glpi</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27096</link>
      <description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package, Data center management, ITIL Service Desk, licenses tracking and software auditing. An authenticated user can exploit a SQL injection vulnerability in the search engine to extract data from the database. This issue has been patched in version 10.0.13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27096|2024-06-04T17:46:29.094Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 16:11:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27930|2024-04-24T14:39:50.719Z -- glpi-project -- glpi</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27930</link>
      <description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package, Data center management, ITIL Service Desk, licenses tracking and software auditing. An authenticated user can access sensitive fields data from items on which he has read access. This issue has been patched in version 10.0.13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27930|2024-04-24T14:39:50.719Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 15:29:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27098|2024-06-04T17:47:14.574Z -- glpi-project -- glpi</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27098</link>
      <description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package, Data center management, ITIL Service Desk, licenses tracking and software auditing. An authenticated user can execute a SSRF based attack using Arbitrary Object Instantiation. This issue has been patched in version 10.0.13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27098|2024-06-04T17:47:14.574Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 16:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27104|2024-03-18T16:16:38.709Z -- glpi-project -- glpi</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27104</link>
      <description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package, Data center management, ITIL Service Desk, licenses tracking and software auditing. A user with rights to create and share dashboards can build a dashboard containing javascript code. Any user that will open this dashboard will be subject to an XSS attack. This issue has been patched in version 10.0.13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27104|2024-03-18T16:16:38.709Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 16:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27914|2024-03-18T16:19:00.298Z -- glpi-project -- glpi</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27914</link>
      <description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package, Data center management, ITIL Service Desk, licenses tracking and software auditing. An unauthenticated user can provide a malicious link to a GLPI administrator in order to exploit a reflected XSS  vulnerability. The XSS will only trigger if the administrator navigates through the debug bar. This issue has been patched in version 10.0.13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27914|2024-03-18T16:19:00.298Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 16:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29889|2024-06-06T16:08:34.715Z -- glpi-project -- glpi</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-29889</link>
      <description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package. Prior to 10.0.15, an authenticated user can exploit a SQL injection vulnerability in the saved searches feature to alter another user account data take control of it. This vulnerability is fixed in 10.0.15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29889|2024-06-06T16:08:34.715Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:05:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28241|2024-06-04T18:03:23.300Z -- glpi-project -- glpi-agent</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-28241</link>
      <description>The GLPI Agent is a generic management agent. Prior to version 1.7.2, a local user can modify GLPI-Agent code or used DLLs to modify agent logic and even gain higher privileges. Users should upgrade to GLPI-Agent 1.7.2 to receive a patch. As a workaround, use the default installation folder which involves installed folder is automatically secured by the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28241|2024-06-04T18:03:23.300Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:44:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28240|2024-06-04T18:03:27.642Z -- glpi-project -- glpi-agent</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-28240</link>
      <description>The GLPI Agent is a generic management agent. A vulnerability that only affects GLPI-Agent installed on windows via MSI packaging can allow a local user to cause denial of agent service by replacing GLPI server url with a wrong url or disabling the service. Additionally, in the case the Deploy task is installed, a local malicious user can trigger privilege escalation configuring a malicious server providing its own deploy task payload. GLPI-Agent 1.7.2 contains a patch for this issue. As a workaround, edit GLPI-Agent related key under `HKEY_LOCAL_MACHINE\SOFTWARE\Microsoft\Windows\CurrentVersion\Uninstall` and add `SystemComponent` DWORD value setting it to `1` to hide GLPI-Agent from installed applications.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28240|2024-06-04T18:03:27.642Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:37:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37147|2024-07-10T18:38:37.588Z -- glpi-project -- glpi</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37147</link>
      <description>GLPI is an open-source asset and IT management software package that provides ITIL Service Desk features, licenses tracking and software auditing. An authenticated user can attach a document to any item, even if the user has no write access on it. Upgrade to 10.0.16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37147|2024-07-10T18:38:37.588Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:38:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37147|2024-07-12T20:16:00.630Z -- glpi-project -- glpi</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37147</link>
      <description>GLPI is an open-source asset and IT management software package that provides ITIL Service Desk features, licenses tracking and software auditing. An authenticated user can attach a document to any item, even if the user has no write access on it. Upgrade to 10.0.16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37147|2024-07-12T20:16:00.630Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:38:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28240|2024-08-02T00:48:49.487Z -- glpi-project -- glpi-agent</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28240</link>
      <description>The GLPI Agent is a generic management agent. A vulnerability that only affects GLPI-Agent installed on windows via MSI packaging can allow a local user to cause denial of agent service by replacing GLPI server url with a wrong url or disabling the service. Additionally, in the case the Deploy task is installed, a local malicious user can trigger privilege escalation configuring a malicious server providing its own deploy task payload. GLPI-Agent 1.7.2 contains a patch for this issue. As a workaround, edit GLPI-Agent related key under `HKEY_LOCAL_MACHINE\SOFTWARE\Microsoft\Windows\CurrentVersion\Uninstall` and add `SystemComponent` DWORD value setting it to `1` to hide GLPI-Agent from installed applications.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28240|2024-08-02T00:48:49.487Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:37:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27937|2024-08-02T00:41:55.829Z -- glpi-project -- glpi</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27937</link>
      <description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package, Data center management, ITIL Service Desk, licenses tracking and software auditing. An authenticated user can obtain the email address of all GLPI users. This issue has been patched in version 10.0.13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27937|2024-08-02T00:41:55.829Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 15:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-28241|2024-08-02T00:48:49.650Z -- glpi-project -- glpi-agent</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28241</link>
      <description>The GLPI Agent is a generic management agent. Prior to version 1.7.2, a local user can modify GLPI-Agent code or used DLLs to modify agent logic and even gain higher privileges. Users should upgrade to GLPI-Agent 1.7.2 to receive a patch. As a workaround, use the default installation folder which involves installed folder is automatically secured by the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-28241|2024-08-02T00:48:49.650Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:44:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27098|2024-08-02T00:27:59.073Z -- glpi-project -- glpi</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27098</link>
      <description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package, Data center management, ITIL Service Desk, licenses tracking and software auditing. An authenticated user can execute a SSRF based attack using Arbitrary Object Instantiation. This issue has been patched in version 10.0.13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27098|2024-08-02T00:27:59.073Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 16:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27930|2024-08-02T00:41:55.952Z -- glpi-project -- glpi</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27930</link>
      <description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package, Data center management, ITIL Service Desk, licenses tracking and software auditing. An authenticated user can access sensitive fields data from items on which he has read access. This issue has been patched in version 10.0.13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27930|2024-08-02T00:41:55.952Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 15:29:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27096|2024-08-02T00:27:59.351Z -- glpi-project -- glpi</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27096</link>
      <description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package, Data center management, ITIL Service Desk, licenses tracking and software auditing. An authenticated user can exploit a SQL injection vulnerability in the search engine to extract data from the database. This issue has been patched in version 10.0.13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27096|2024-08-02T00:27:59.351Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 16:11:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-29889|2024-08-02T01:17:58.452Z -- glpi-project -- glpi</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29889</link>
      <description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package. Prior to 10.0.15, an authenticated user can exploit a SQL injection vulnerability in the saved searches feature to alter another user account data take control of it. This vulnerability is fixed in 10.0.15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29889|2024-08-02T01:17:58.452Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:05:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27104|2024-08-02T00:27:59.887Z -- glpi-project -- glpi</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27104</link>
      <description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package, Data center management, ITIL Service Desk, licenses tracking and software auditing. A user with rights to create and share dashboards can build a dashboard containing javascript code. Any user that will open this dashboard will be subject to an XSS attack. This issue has been patched in version 10.0.13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27104|2024-08-02T00:27:59.887Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 16:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27914|2024-08-02T00:41:55.731Z -- glpi-project -- glpi</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27914</link>
      <description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package, Data center management, ITIL Service Desk, licenses tracking and software auditing. An unauthenticated user can provide a malicious link to a GLPI administrator in order to exploit a reflected XSS  vulnerability. The XSS will only trigger if the administrator navigates through the debug bar. This issue has been patched in version 10.0.13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27914|2024-08-02T00:41:55.731Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 16:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37149|2024-08-02T03:50:54.839Z -- glpi-project -- glpi</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37149</link>
      <description>GLPI is an open-source asset and IT management software package that provides ITIL Service Desk features, licenses tracking and software auditing. An authenticated technician user can upload a malicious PHP script and hijack the plugin loader to execute this malicious script. Upgrade to 10.0.16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37149|2024-08-02T03:50:54.839Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 19:20:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37147|2024-08-02T03:50:54.626Z -- glpi-project -- glpi</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37147</link>
      <description>GLPI is an open-source asset and IT management software package that provides ITIL Service Desk features, licenses tracking and software auditing. An authenticated user can attach a document to any item, even if the user has no write access on it. Upgrade to 10.0.16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37147|2024-08-02T03:50:54.626Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:38:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37148|2024-08-02T03:50:55.237Z -- glpi-project -- glpi</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37148</link>
      <description>GLPI is an open-source asset and IT management software package that provides ITIL Service Desk features, licenses tracking and software auditing. An authenticated user can exploit a SQL injection vulnerability in some AJAX scripts to alter another user account data and take control of it. Upgrade to 10.0.16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-37148|2024-08-02T03:50:55.237Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 19:18:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27914|2024-08-02T15:25:55.247Z -- glpi-project -- glpi</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27914</link>
      <description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package, Data center management, ITIL Service Desk, licenses tracking and software auditing. An unauthenticated user can provide a malicious link to a GLPI administrator in order to exploit a reflected XSS  vulnerability. The XSS will only trigger if the administrator navigates through the debug bar. This issue has been patched in version 10.0.13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27914|2024-08-02T15:25:55.247Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 16:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27930|2024-08-02T15:26:25.744Z -- glpi-project -- glpi</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27930</link>
      <description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package, Data center management, ITIL Service Desk, licenses tracking and software auditing. An authenticated user can access sensitive fields data from items on which he has read access. This issue has been patched in version 10.0.13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27930|2024-08-02T15:26:25.744Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 15:29:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
