<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for ThinuTech -- ThinuCMS</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/thinutech/thinucms.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for ThinuTech -- ThinuCMS</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3541|2023-10-23T14:18:22.365Z -- thinutech -- thinucms
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3541</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in ThinuTech ThinuCMS 1.5 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /author_posts.php. The manipulation of the argument author with the input g6g12&lt;script&gt;alert(1)&lt;/script&gt;o8sdm leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The identifier VDB-233293 was assigned to this vulnerability.
In ThinuTech ThinuCMS 1.5 wurde eine Schwachstelle gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Datei /author_posts.php. Mittels dem Manipulieren des Arguments author mit der Eingabe g6g12&lt;script&gt;alert(1)&lt;/script&gt;o8sdm mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Umsetzung des Angriffs kann dabei über das Netzwerk erfolgen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3541|2023-10-23T14:18:22.365Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 15:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3528|2023-10-23T14:07:22.844Z -- thinutech -- thinucms
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3528</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in ThinuTech ThinuCMS 1.5. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /category.php. The manipulation of the argument cat_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-233252.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in ThinuTech ThinuCMS 1.5 ausgemacht. Dies betrifft einen unbekannten Teil der Datei /category.php. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments cat_id mit unbekannten Daten kann eine sql injection-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk passieren.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3528|2023-10-23T14:07:22.844Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 18:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3542|2023-10-23T14:19:35.518Z -- thinutech -- thinucms
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-3542</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in ThinuTech ThinuCMS 1.5 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /contact.php. The manipulation of the argument name/body leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. VDB-233294 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in ThinuTech ThinuCMS 1.5 gefunden. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Datei /contact.php. Mittels Manipulieren des Arguments name/body mit unbekannten Daten kann eine cross site scripting-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Umgesetzt werden kann der Angriff über das Netzwerk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3542|2023-10-23T14:19:35.518Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 16:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
