<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for FUJITSU LIMITED -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/fujitsu%20limited/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for FUJITSU LIMITED -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38433|2023-07-26T07:44:04.302Z -- fujitsu%20limited -- ip-he950e
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38433</link>
      <description>Fujitsu Real-time Video Transmission Gear "IP series" use hard-coded credentials, which may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to initialize or reboot the products, and as a result, terminate the video transmission. Affected products and versions are as follows: IP-HE950E firmware versions V01L001 to V01L053, IP-HE950D firmware versions V01L001 to V01L053, IP-HE900E firmware versions V01L001 to V01L010, IP-HE900D firmware versions V01L001 to V01L004, IP-900E / IP-920E firmware versions V01L001 to V02L061, IP-900D / IP-900ⅡD / IP-920D firmware versions V01L001 to V02L061, IP-90 firmware versions V01L001 to V01L013, and IP-9610 firmware versions V01L001 to V02L007.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38433|2023-07-26T07:44:04.302Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 07:44:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38555|2023-07-26T07:43:21.819Z -- fujitsu%20limited -- si-r%2030b
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-38555</link>
      <description>Authentication bypass vulnerability in Fujitsu network devices Si-R series and SR-M series allows a network-adjacent unauthenticated attacker to obtain, change, and/or reset configuration settings of the affected products. Affected products and versions are as follows: Si-R 30B all versions, Si-R 130B all versions, Si-R 90brin all versions, Si-R570B all versions, Si-R370B all versions, Si-R220D all versions, Si-R G100 V02.54 and earlier, Si-R G200 V02.54 and earlier, Si-R G100B V04.12 and earlier, Si-R G110B V04.12 and earlier, Si-R G200B V04.12 and earlier, Si-R G210 V20.52 and earlier, Si-R G211 V20.52 and earlier, Si-R G120 V20.52 and earlier, Si-R G121 V20.52 and earlier, and SR-M 50AP1 all versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38555|2023-07-26T07:43:21.819Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 07:43:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-39379|2023-08-04T09:43:32.360Z -- fujitsu%20limited -- fujitsu%20software%20infrastructure%20manager%20advanced%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-39379</link>
      <description>Fujitsu Software Infrastructure Manager (ISM) stores sensitive information at the product's maintenance data (ismsnap) in cleartext form. As a result, the password for the proxy server that is configured in ISM may be retrieved. Affected products and versions are as follows: Fujitsu Software Infrastructure Manager Advanced Edition V2.8.0.060, Fujitsu Software Infrastructure Manager Advanced Edition for PRIMEFLEX V2.8.0.060, and Fujitsu Software Infrastructure Manager Essential Edition V2.8.0.060.&#13;
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-39379|2023-08-04T09:43:32.360Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 09:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22377|2023-02-15T00:00:00 -- fujitsu%20limited -- tsclinical%20define.xml%20generator%20and%20tsclinical%20metadata%20desktop%20tools
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-22377</link>
      <description>Improper restriction of XML external entity reference (XXE) vulnerability exists in tsClinical Define.xml Generator all versions (v1.0.0 to v1.4.0) and tsClinical Metadata Desktop Tools Version 1.0.3 to Version 1.1.0. If this vulnerability is exploited, an attacker may obtain an arbitrary file which meets a certain condition by reading a specially crafted XML file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22377|2023-02-15T00:00:00</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
