<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for DIRACGrid -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/diracgrid/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for DIRACGrid -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 22:02:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-29905|2024-04-09T16:49:48.158Z -- DIRACGrid -- DIRAC
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-29905</link><description>DIRAC is an interware, meaning a software framework for distributed computing. Prior to version 8.0.41, during the proxy generation process (e.g., when using `dirac-proxy-init`), it is possible for unauthorized users on the same machine to gain read access to the proxy. This allows the user to then perform any action that is possible with the original proxy. This vulnerability only exists for a short period of time (sub-millsecond) during the generation process. Version 8.0.41 contains a patch for the issue. As a workaround, setting the `X509_USER_PROXY` environment variable to a path that is inside a directory that is only readable to the current user avoids the potential risk. After the file has been written, it can be safely copied to the standard location (`/tmp/x509up_uNNNN`).</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-29905|2024-04-09T16:49:48.158Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 16:49:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24825|2024-02-08T23:39:28.741Z -- DIRACGrid -- DIRAC
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-24825</link><description>DIRAC is a distributed resource framework. In affected versions any user could get a token that has been requested by another user/agent. This may expose resources to unintended parties. This issue has been addressed in release version 8.0.37. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24825|2024-02-08T23:39:28.741Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 23:39:28 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>