<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for sparklemotion -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/sparklemotion/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for sparklemotion -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 18:24:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41098|2024-08-04T02:59:31.455Z -- sparklemotion -- nokogiri
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41098</link>
      <description>Nokogiri is a Rubygem providing HTML, XML, SAX, and Reader parsers with XPath and CSS selector support. In Nokogiri v1.12.4 and earlier, on JRuby only, the SAX parser resolves external entities by default. Users of Nokogiri on JRuby who parse untrusted documents using any of these classes are affected: Nokogiri::XML::SAX::Parse, Nokogiri::HTML4::SAX::Parser or its alias Nokogiri::HTML::SAX::Parser, Nokogiri::XML::SAX::PushParser, and Nokogiri::HTML4::SAX::PushParser or its alias Nokogiri::HTML::SAX::PushParser. JRuby users should upgrade to Nokogiri v1.12.5 or later to receive a patch for this issue. There are no workarounds available for v1.12.4 or earlier. CRuby users are not affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41098|2024-08-04T02:59:31.455Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 19:35:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26247|2024-08-04T15:56:04.939Z -- sparklemotion -- nokogiri
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26247</link>
      <description>Nokogiri is a Rubygem providing HTML, XML, SAX, and Reader parsers with XPath and CSS selector support. In Nokogiri before version 1.11.0.rc4 there is an XXE vulnerability. XML Schemas parsed by Nokogiri::XML::Schema are trusted by default, allowing external resources to be accessed over the network, potentially enabling XXE or SSRF attacks. This behavior is counter to the security policy followed by Nokogiri maintainers, which is to treat all input as untrusted by default whenever possible. This is fixed in Nokogiri version 1.11.0.rc4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26247|2024-08-04T15:56:04.939Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
