<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Silver Peak Systems, Inc. -- ECOS</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/silver%20peak%20systems%2C%20inc./ecos.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Silver Peak Systems, Inc. -- ECOS</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:23:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-12149|2024-08-04T11:48:58.307Z -- silver%20peak%20systems%2C%20inc. -- ecos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12149</link>
      <description>The configuration backup/restore function in Silver Peak Unity ECOSTM (ECOS) appliance software was found to directly incorporate the user-controlled config filename in a subsequent shell command, allowing an attacker to manipulate the resulting command by injecting valid OS command input. This vulnerability can be exploited by an attacker with authenticated access to the Orchestrator UI or EdgeConnect UI. This affects all ECOS versions prior to: 8.1.9.15, 8.3.0.8, 8.3.1.2, 8.3.2.0, 9.0.2.0, and 9.1.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-12149|2024-08-04T11:48:58.307Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-12148|2024-08-04T11:48:58.361Z -- silver%20peak%20systems%2C%20inc. -- ecos
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12148</link>
      <description>A command injection flaw identified in the nslookup API in Silver Peak Unity ECOSTM (ECOS) appliance software could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary commands with the privileges of the web server running on the EdgeConnect appliance. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to establish an interactive channel, effectively taking control of the target system. This vulnerability can be exploited by an attacker with authenticated access to the Orchestrator UI or EdgeConnect UI. This affects all ECOS versions prior to : 8.1.9.15, 8.3.0.8, 8.3.1.2, 8.3.2.0, 9.0.2.0, and 9.1.0.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-12148|2024-08-04T11:48:58.361Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
