<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for xpeedstudio -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/xpeedstudio/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for xpeedstudio -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 08:24:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0084|2024-08-02T05:02:42.970Z -- xpeedstudio -- metform%20elementor%20contact%20form%20builder%20%E2%80%93%20flexible%20and%20design-friendly%20contact%20form%20builder%20plugin%20for%20wordpress
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0084</link>
      <description>The Metform Elementor Contact Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via text areas on forms in versions up to, and including, 3.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page, which is the submissions page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0084|2024-08-02T05:02:42.970Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 18:35:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0689|2024-08-02T05:17:50.357Z -- xpeedstudio -- metform%20elementor%20contact%20form%20builder
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0689</link>
      <description>The Metform Elementor Contact Form Builder for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Disclosure via the 'mf_first_name' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 3.3.1. This allows authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level capabilities or above to obtain sensitive information about arbitrary form submissions, including the submitter's first name.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0689|2024-08-02T05:17:50.357Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 05:33:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0708|2024-08-02T05:17:50.389Z -- xpeedstudio -- metform%20elementor%20contact%20form%20builder%20%E2%80%93%20flexible%20and%20design-friendly%20contact%20form%20builder%20plugin%20for%20wordpress
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0708</link>
      <description>The Metform Elementor Contact Form Builder for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting by using the 'mf_first_name' shortcode to echo unescaped form submissions in versions up to, and including, 3.3.0. This allows authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions or above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute when the victim visits a a page containing the shortcode when the submission id is present in the query string. Note that getting the JavaScript to execute requires user interaction as the victim must visit a crafted link with the form entry id, but the script itself is stored in the site database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0708|2024-08-02T05:17:50.389Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 05:33:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0694|2024-08-02T05:17:50.331Z -- xpeedstudio -- metform%20elementor%20contact%20form%20builder%20%E2%80%93%20flexible%20and%20design-friendly%20contact%20form%20builder%20plugin%20for%20wordpress
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0694</link>
      <description>The Metform Elementor Contact Form Builder for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Disclosure via the 'mf' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 3.3.1. This allows authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level capabilities or above to obtain sensitive information about any standard form field of any form submission.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0694|2024-08-02T05:17:50.331Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 05:33:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0710|2024-08-02T05:17:50.396Z -- xpeedstudio -- metform%20elementor%20contact%20form%20builder%20%E2%80%93%20flexible%20and%20design-friendly%20contact%20form%20builder%20plugin%20for%20wordpress
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0710</link>
      <description>The Metform Elementor Contact Form Builder for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting by using the 'fname' attribute of the 'mf_thankyou' shortcode to echo unescaped form submissions in versions up to, and including, 3.3.0. This allows authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions or above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute when the victim visits a a page containing the shortcode when the submission id is present in the query string. Note that getting the JavaScript to execute requires user interaction as the victim must visit a crafted link with the form entry id, but the script itself is stored in the site database. Additionally this requires successful payment, increasing the complexity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0710|2024-08-02T05:17:50.396Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 05:33:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0695|2024-08-02T05:17:50.389Z -- xpeedstudio -- metform%20elementor%20contact%20form%20builder%20%E2%80%93%20flexible%20and%20design-friendly%20contact%20form%20builder%20plugin%20for%20wordpress
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0695</link>
      <description>The Metform Elementor Contact Form Builder for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting by using the 'mf' shortcode to echo unescaped form submissions in versions up to, and including, 3.3.0. This allows authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions or above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute when the victim visits a specific link. Note that getting the JavaScript to execute still requires user interaction as the victim must visit a crafted link with the form entry id, but the script itself is stored in the site database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0695|2024-08-02T05:17:50.389Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 05:33:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0693|2024-08-02T05:17:50.384Z -- xpeedstudio -- metform%20elementor%20contact%20form%20builder%20%E2%80%93%20flexible%20and%20design-friendly%20contact%20form%20builder%20plugin%20for%20wordpress
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0693</link>
      <description>The Metform Elementor Contact Form Builder for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Disclosure via the 'mf_transaction_id' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 3.3.1. This allows authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level capabilities or above to obtain sensitive information about the transaction ids of arbitrary form submissions that included payment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0693|2024-08-02T05:17:50.384Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 05:33:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0709|2024-08-02T05:17:50.354Z -- xpeedstudio -- metform%20elementor%20contact%20form%20builder%20%E2%80%93%20flexible%20and%20design-friendly%20contact%20form%20builder%20plugin%20for%20wordpress
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0709</link>
      <description>The Metform Elementor Contact Form Builder for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting by using the 'mf_last_name' shortcode to echo unescaped form submissions in versions up to, and including, 3.3.0. This allows authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions or above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute when the victim visits a a page containing the shortcode when the submission id is present in the query string. Note that getting the JavaScript to execute requires user interaction as the victim must visit a crafted link with the form entry id, but the script itself is stored in the site database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0709|2024-08-02T05:17:50.354Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 05:33:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0688|2024-08-02T05:17:50.357Z -- xpeedstudio -- metform%20elementor%20contact%20form%20builder%20%E2%80%93%20flexible%20and%20design-friendly%20contact%20form%20builder%20plugin%20for%20wordpress
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0688</link>
      <description>The Metform Elementor Contact Form Builder for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Disclosure via the 'mf_thankyou' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 3.3.1. This allows authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level capabilities or above to obtain sensitive information about form submissions, including payment status, and transaction ID.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0688|2024-08-02T05:17:50.357Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 05:33:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0085|2024-08-02T05:02:42.994Z -- xpeedstudio -- metform%20elementor%20contact%20form%20builder%20%E2%80%93%20flexible%20and%20design-friendly%20contact%20form%20builder%20plugin%20for%20wordpress
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0085</link>
      <description>The Metform Elementor Contact Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to reCaptcha Bypass in versions up to, and including, 3.2.1. This is due to insufficient server side checking on the captcha value submitted during a form submission. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass Captcha restrictions and for attackers to utilize bots to submit forms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0085|2024-08-02T05:02:42.994Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 16:01:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0692|2024-08-02T05:17:50.345Z -- xpeedstudio -- metform%20elementor%20contact%20form%20builder%20%E2%80%93%20flexible%20and%20design-friendly%20contact%20form%20builder%20plugin%20for%20wordpress
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0692</link>
      <description>The Metform Elementor Contact Form Builder for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Disclosure via the 'mf_payment_status' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 3.3.1. This allows authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level capabilities or above to obtain sensitive information about the payment status of arbitrary form submissions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0692|2024-08-02T05:17:50.345Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 05:33:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0721|2024-08-02T05:24:33.117Z -- xpeedstudio -- metform%20elementor%20contact%20form%20builder%20%E2%80%93%20flexible%20and%20design-friendly%20contact%20form%20builder%20plugin%20for%20wordpress
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0721</link>
      <description>The Metform Elementor Contact Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to CSV injection in versions up to, and including, 3.3.0. This allows unauthenticated attackers to embed untrusted input into exported CSV files, which can result in code execution when these files are downloaded and opened on a local system with a vulnerable configuration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0721|2024-08-02T05:24:33.117Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 05:33:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1843|2024-08-02T06:05:26.826Z -- xpeedstudio -- metform%20elementor%20contact%20form%20builder%20%E2%80%93%20flexible%20and%20design-friendly%20contact%20form%20builder%20plugin%20for%20wordpress
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1843</link>
      <description>The Metform Elementor Contact Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized permalink structure update due to a missing capability check on the permalink_setup function in versions up to, and including, 3.3.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change the permalink structure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1843|2024-08-02T06:05:26.826Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 05:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-2517|2024-08-02T06:26:08.645Z -- xpeedstudio -- metform%20elementor%20contact%20form%20builder
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2517</link>
      <description>The Metform Elementor Contact Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 3.3.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the permalink_setup function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change the permalink structure via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. While nonce verification is implemented, verification only takes place when a nonce is provided.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-2517|2024-08-02T06:26:08.645Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 04:38:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0691|2024-08-02T05:17:50.387Z -- xpeedstudio -- metform%20elementor%20contact%20form%20builder%20%E2%80%93%20flexible%20and%20design-friendly%20contact%20form%20builder%20plugin%20for%20wordpress
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0691</link>
      <description>The Metform Elementor Contact Form Builder for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Disclosure via the 'mf_last_name' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 3.3.1. This allows authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level capabilities or above to obtain sensitive information about arbitrary form submissions, specifically the submitter's last name.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0691|2024-08-02T05:17:50.387Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 05:33:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4266|2024-08-01T20:33:53.023Z -- xpeedstudio -- metform%20%E2%80%93%20contact%20form%2C%20survey%2C%20quiz%2C%20%26%20custom%20form%20builder%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4266</link>
      <description>The MetForm – Contact Form, Survey, Quiz, &amp; Custom Form Builder for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in versions up to, and including, 3.8.8 via the 'handle_file' function. This can allow unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data, such as Personally Identifiable Information, from files uploaded by users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4266|2024-08-01T20:33:53.023Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 07:32:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3650|2024-08-01T20:20:00.573Z -- xpeedstudio -- elementskit%20elementor%20addons%20and%20templates%20library</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3650</link>
      <description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Image Accordion widget in all versions 3.0.7 through 3.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3650|2024-08-01T20:20:00.573Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3499|2024-08-01T20:12:07.692Z -- xpeedstudio -- elementskit%20elementor%20addons%20and%20templates%20library</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3499</link>
      <description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.0 via the generate_navigation_markup function of the Onepage Scroll module. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3499|2024-08-01T20:12:07.692Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1239|2024-08-01T18:33:25.118Z -- xpeedstudio -- elementskit%20elementor%20addons</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1239</link>
      <description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the blog post read more button in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1239|2024-08-01T18:33:25.118Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 02:34:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1585|2024-08-01T18:40:21.405Z -- xpeedstudio -- metform%20elementor%20contact%20form%20builder</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1585</link>
      <description>The Metform Elementor Contact Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1585|2024-08-01T18:40:21.405Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:26:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1238|2024-08-01T18:33:25.337Z -- xpeedstudio -- elementskit%20elementor%20addons</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1238</link>
      <description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the button ID parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1238|2024-08-01T18:33:25.337Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 04:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1763|2024-08-01T18:48:22.004Z -- xpeedstudio -- wp%20social%20login%20and%20register%20social%20counter</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1763</link>
      <description>The Wp Social Login and Register Social Counter plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the /wp_social/v1/ REST API endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to enable and disable certain providers for the social share and login features.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1763|2024-08-01T18:48:22.004Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:26:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6698|2024-08-01T03:29:58.918Z -- xpeedstudio -- fundengine%20%E2%80%93%20donation%20and%20crowdfunding%20platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6698</link>
      <description>The FundEngine plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.0. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying user meta updated through the update_user_meta function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to update their user meta which can be leveraged to update their capabilities to gain administrator access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6698|2024-08-01T03:29:58.918Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 03:29:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6455|2024-07-18T20:32:37.651Z -- xpeedstudio -- elementskit%20elementor%20addons</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6455</link>
      <description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.0 due to a missing capability checks on ekit_widgetarea_content function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view any item created in Elementor, such as posts, pages and templates including drafts, pending and private items.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6455|2024-07-18T20:32:37.651Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 20:32:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1585|2024-06-24T14:51:24.549Z -- xpeedstudio -- metform%20elementor%20contact%20form%20builder</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1585</link>
      <description>The Metform Elementor Contact Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1585|2024-06-24T14:51:24.549Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:26:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2791|2024-06-04T17:29:02.507Z -- xpeedstudio -- metform%20%E2%80%93%20contact%20form%2C%20survey%2C%20quiz%2C%20%26%20custom%20form%20builder%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2791</link>
      <description>The Metform Elementor Contact Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's widgets in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2791|2024-06-04T17:29:02.507Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 05:32:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2047|2024-03-30T04:31:07.657Z -- xpeedstudio -- elementskit%20elementor%20addons</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2047</link>
      <description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.6 via the render_raw function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2047|2024-03-30T04:31:07.657Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 04:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2042|2024-06-04T17:30:13.087Z -- xpeedstudio -- elementskit%20elementor%20addons</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2042</link>
      <description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Image Accordion widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2042|2024-06-04T17:30:13.087Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 02:34:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2803|2024-06-04T17:30:47.856Z -- xpeedstudio -- elementskit%20elementor%20addons</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2803</link>
      <description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the countdown widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2803|2024-06-04T17:30:47.856Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 01:56:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3499|2024-06-04T17:31:09.414Z -- xpeedstudio -- elementskit%20elementor%20addons%20and%20templates%20library</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3499</link>
      <description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.0 via the generate_navigation_markup function of the Onepage Scroll module. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3499|2024-06-04T17:31:09.414Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3650|2024-05-02T16:52:25.574Z -- xpeedstudio -- elementskit%20elementor%20addons%20and%20templates%20library</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3650</link>
      <description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Image Accordion widget in all versions 3.0.7 through 3.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3650|2024-05-02T16:52:25.574Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4266|2024-06-11T15:44:34.740Z -- xpeedstudio -- metform%20%E2%80%93%20contact%20form%2C%20survey%2C%20quiz%2C%20%26%20custom%20form%20builder%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4266</link>
      <description>The MetForm – Contact Form, Survey, Quiz, &amp; Custom Form Builder for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in versions up to, and including, 3.8.8 via the 'handle_file' function. This can allow unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data, such as Personally Identifiable Information, from files uploaded by users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4266|2024-06-11T15:44:34.740Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 07:32:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1763|2024-03-13T15:26:48.783Z -- xpeedstudio -- wp%20social%20login%20and%20register%20social%20counter</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1763</link>
      <description>The Wp Social Login and Register Social Counter plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the /wp_social/v1/ REST API endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to enable and disable certain providers for the social share and login features.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1763|2024-03-13T15:26:48.783Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:26:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1585|2024-03-13T15:26:42.210Z -- xpeedstudio -- metform%20elementor%20contact%20form%20builder</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1585</link>
      <description>The Metform Elementor Contact Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1585|2024-03-13T15:26:42.210Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:26:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1238|2024-06-04T18:01:12.544Z -- xpeedstudio -- elementskit%20elementor%20addons</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1238</link>
      <description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the button ID parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1238|2024-06-04T18:01:12.544Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 04:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1239|2024-06-04T18:01:27.741Z -- xpeedstudio -- elementskit%20elementor%20addons</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1239</link>
      <description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the blog post read more button in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1239|2024-06-04T18:01:27.741Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 02:34:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6525|2024-06-04T17:17:07.306Z -- xpeedstudio -- elementskit%20elementor%20addons</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6525</link>
      <description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the progress bar element attributes in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with editor-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This primarily affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6525|2024-06-04T17:17:07.306Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 02:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3650|2024-07-05T21:08:18.676Z -- xpeedstudio -- elementskit%20elementor%20addons%20and%20templates%20library</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3650</link>
      <description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Image Accordion widget in all versions 3.0.7 through 3.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3650|2024-07-05T21:08:18.676Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6455|2024-07-24T18:35:10.765Z -- xpeedstudio -- elementskit%20elementor%20addons</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6455</link>
      <description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.0 due to a missing capability checks on ekit_widgetarea_content function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view any item created in Elementor, such as posts, pages and templates including drafts, pending and private items.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6455|2024-07-24T18:35:10.765Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 20:32:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6698|2024-08-01T14:10:21.095Z -- xpeedstudio -- fundengine%20%E2%80%93%20donation%20and%20crowdfunding%20platform</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6698</link>
      <description>The FundEngine plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.0. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying user meta updated through the update_user_meta function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to update their user meta which can be leveraged to update their capabilities to gain administrator access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6698|2024-08-01T14:10:21.095Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 03:29:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2791|2024-08-01T19:25:42.156Z -- xpeedstudio -- metform%20%E2%80%93%20contact%20form%2C%20survey%2C%20quiz%2C%20%26%20custom%20form%20builder%20for%20elementor</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2791</link>
      <description>The Metform Elementor Contact Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's widgets in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2791|2024-08-01T19:25:42.156Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 05:32:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2042|2024-08-01T19:03:37.825Z -- xpeedstudio -- elementskit%20elementor%20addons</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2042</link>
      <description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Image Accordion widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2042|2024-08-01T19:03:37.825Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 02:34:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2047|2024-08-01T19:03:38.721Z -- xpeedstudio -- elementskit%20elementor%20addons</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2047</link>
      <description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.6 via the render_raw function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2047|2024-08-01T19:03:38.721Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 04:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2803|2024-08-01T19:25:41.768Z -- xpeedstudio -- elementskit%20elementor%20addons</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2803</link>
      <description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the countdown widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2803|2024-08-01T19:25:41.768Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 01:56:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6455|2024-08-01T21:41:03.300Z -- xpeedstudio -- elementskit%20elementor%20addons</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6455</link>
      <description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.0 due to a missing capability checks on ekit_widgetarea_content function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view any item created in Elementor, such as posts, pages and templates including drafts, pending and private items.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6455|2024-08-01T21:41:03.300Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 20:32:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
