<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Vaerys-Dawn -- DiscordSailv2</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/vaerys-dawn/discordsailv2.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Vaerys-Dawn -- DiscordSailv2</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 19:21:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-25092|2024-08-05T12:33:48.485Z -- vaerys-dawn -- discordsailv2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25092</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Vaerys-Dawn DiscordSailv2 up to 2.10.2. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Command Mention Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. Upgrading to version 2.10.3 is able to address this issue. The patch is named cc12e0be82a5d05d9f359ed8e56088f4f8b8eb69. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-244483.
In Vaerys-Dawn DiscordSailv2 bis 2.10.2 wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Dabei geht es um eine nicht genauer bekannte Funktion der Komponente Command Mention Handler. Durch Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine improper access controls-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 2.10.3 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als cc12e0be82a5d05d9f359ed8e56088f4f8b8eb69 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-25092|2024-08-05T12:33:48.485Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 21:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-25093|2024-08-05T12:33:49.283Z -- vaerys-dawn -- discordsailv2
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25093</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Vaerys-Dawn DiscordSailv2 up to 2.10.2. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Tag Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. Upgrading to version 2.10.3 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is cc12e0be82a5d05d9f359ed8e56088f4f8b8eb69. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-244484.
Eine kritische Schwachstelle wurde in Vaerys-Dawn DiscordSailv2 bis 2.10.2 ausgemacht. Hierbei geht es um eine nicht exakt ausgemachte Funktion der Komponente Tag Handler. Durch das Beeinflussen mit unbekannten Daten kann eine improper access controls-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Ein Aktualisieren auf die Version 2.10.3 vermag dieses Problem zu lösen. Der Patch wird als cc12e0be82a5d05d9f359ed8e56088f4f8b8eb69 bezeichnet. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird das Einspielen eines Upgrades empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-25093|2024-08-05T12:33:49.283Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 01:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
