<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for getkirby -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/getkirby/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for getkirby -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 18:25:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38489|2024-10-23T13:34:03.258Z -- getkirby -- kirby
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38489</link>
      <description>Kirby is a content management system. A vulnerability in versions prior to 3.5.8.3, 3.6.6.3, 3.7.5.2, 3.8.4.1, and 3.9.6 affects all Kirby sites with user accounts (unless Kirby's API and Panel are disabled in the config). It can only be abused if a Kirby user is logged in on a device or browser that is shared with potentially untrusted users or if an attacker already maliciously used a previous password to log in to a Kirby site as the affected user.

Insufficient Session Expiration is when a web site permits an attacker to reuse old session credentials or session IDs for authorization. In the variation described in this advisory, it allows attackers to stay logged in to a Kirby site on another device even if the logged in user has since changed their password. Kirby did not invalidate user sessions that were created with a password that was since changed by the user or by a site admin. If a user changed their password to lock out an attacker who was already in possession of the previous password or of a login session on another device or browser, the attacker would not be reliably prevented from accessing the Kirby site as the affected user.

The problem has been patched in Kirby 3.5.8.3, 3.6.6.3, 3.7.5.2, 3.8.4.1, and 3.9.6. In all of the mentioned releases, the maintainers have updated the authentication implementation to keep track of the hashed password in each active session. If the password changed since the login, the session is invalidated. To enforce this fix even if the vulnerability was previously abused, all users are logged out from the Kirby site after updating to one of the patched releases.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38489|2024-10-23T13:34:03.258Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 14:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-41964|2024-08-29T16:36:08.820Z -- getkirby -- kirby</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41964</link>
      <description>Kirby is a CMS targeting designers and editors. Kirby allows to restrict the permissions of specific user roles. Users of that role can only perform permitted actions. Permissions for creating and deleting languages have already existed and could be configured, but were not enforced by Kirby's frontend or backend code. A permission for updating existing languages has not existed before the patched versions. So disabling the languages.* wildcard permission for a role could not have prohibited updates to existing language definitions. The missing permission checks allowed attackers with Panel access to manipulate the language definitions. The problem has been patched in Kirby 3.6.6.6, Kirby 3.7.5.5, Kirby 3.8.4.4, Kirby 3.9.8.2, Kirby 3.10.1.1, and Kirby 4.3.1. Please update to one of these or a later version to fix the vulnerability. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-41964|2024-08-29T16:36:08.820Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 16:19:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
