<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for getkirby -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/getkirby/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for getkirby -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 19:19:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41252|2024-08-04T03:08:31.511Z -- getkirby -- kirby
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41252</link>
      <description>Kirby is an open source file structured CMS ### Impact Kirby's writer field stores its formatted content as HTML code. Unlike with other field types, it is not possible to escape HTML special characters against cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks, otherwise the formatting would be lost. If the user is logged in to the Panel, a harmful script can for example trigger requests to Kirby's API with the permissions of the victim. Because the writer field did not securely sanitize its contents on save, it was possible to inject malicious HTML code into the content file by sending it to Kirby's API directly without using the Panel. This malicious HTML code would then be displayed on the site frontend and executed in the browsers of site visitors and logged in users who are browsing the site. Attackers must be in your group of authenticated Panel users in order to exploit this weakness. Users who do not make use of the writer field are not affected. This issue has been patched in Kirby 3.5.8 by sanitizing all writer field contents on the backend whenever the content is modified via Kirby's API. Please update to this or a later version to fix the vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41252|2024-08-04T03:08:31.511Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 18:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26255|2024-08-04T15:56:03.743Z -- getkirby -- kirby
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26255</link>
      <description>Kirby is a CMS. In Kirby CMS (getkirby/cms) before version 3.4.5, and Kirby Panel before version 2.5.14 , an editor with full access to the Kirby Panel can upload a PHP .phar file and execute it on the server. This vulnerability is critical if you might have potential attackers in your group of authenticated Panel users, as they can gain access to the server with such a Phar file. Visitors without Panel access *cannot* use this attack vector. The problem has been patched in Kirby 2.5.14 and Kirby 3.4.5. Please update to one of these or a later version to fix the vulnerability. Note: Kirby 2 reaches end of life on December 31, 2020. We therefore recommend to upgrade your Kirby 2 sites to Kirby 3. If you cannot upgrade, we still recommend to update to Kirby 2.5.14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26255|2024-08-04T15:56:03.743Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 14:45:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-26253|2024-08-04T15:56:04.401Z -- getkirby -- kirby
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26253</link>
      <description>Kirby is a CMS. In Kirby CMS (getkirby/cms) before version 3.3.6, and Kirby Panel before version 2.5.14 there is a vulnerability in which the admin panel may be accessed if hosted on a .dev domain. In order to protect new installations on public servers that don't have an admin account for the Panel yet, we block account registration there by default. This is a security feature, which we implemented years ago in Kirby 2. It helps to avoid that you forget registering your first admin account on a public server. In this case – without our security block – someone else might theoretically be able to find your site, find out it's running on Kirby, find the Panel and then register the account first. It's an unlikely situation, but it's still a certain risk. To be able to register the first Panel account on a public server, you have to enforce the installer via a config setting. This helps to push all users to the best practice of registering your first Panel account on your local machine and upload it together with the rest of the site. This installation block implementation in Kirby versions before 3.3.6 still assumed that .dev domains are local domains, which is no longer true. In the meantime, those domains became publicly available. This means that our installation block is no longer working as expected if you use a .dev domain for your Kirby site. Additionally the local installation check may also fail if your site is behind a reverse proxy. You are only affected if you use a .dev domain or your site is behind a reverse proxy and you have not yet registered your first Panel account on the public server and someone finds your site and tries to login at `yourdomain.dev/panel` before you register your first account. You are not affected if you have already created one or multiple Panel accounts (no matter if on a .dev domain or behind a reverse proxy). The problem has been patched in Kirby 3.3.6. Please upgrade to this or a later version to fix the vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-26253|2024-08-04T15:56:04.401Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 01:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41258|2024-08-04T03:08:31.642Z -- getkirby -- kirby
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-41258</link>
      <description>Kirby is an open source file structured CMS. In affected versions Kirby's blocks field stores structured data for each block. This data is then used in block snippets to convert the blocks to HTML for use in your templates. We recommend to escape HTML special characters to protect against cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks. The default snippet for the image block unfortunately did not use our escaping helper. This made it possible to include malicious HTML code in the source, alt and link fields of the image block, which would then be displayed on the site frontend and executed in the browsers of site visitors and logged in users who are browsing the site. Attackers must be in your group of authenticated Panel users in order to exploit this weakness. Users who do not make use of the blocks field are not affected. This issue has been patched in Kirby version 3.5.8 by escaping special HTML characters in the output from the default image block snippet. Please update to this or a later version to fix the vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-41258|2024-08-04T03:08:31.642Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 18:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27087|2024-08-02T00:27:57.813Z -- getkirby -- kirby</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27087</link>
      <description>Kirby is a content management system. The new link field introduced in Kirby 4 allows several different link types that each validate the entered link to the relevant URL format. It also includes a "Custom" link type for advanced use cases that don't fit any of the pre-defined link formats.  As the "Custom" link type is meant to be flexible, it also allows the javascript: URL scheme. In some use cases this can be intended, but it can also be misused by attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript code when a user or visitor clicks on a link that is generated from the contents of the link field. This vulnerability is patched in 4.1.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27087|2024-08-02T00:27:57.813Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 16:44:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27087|2024-02-26T16:44:31.105Z -- getkirby -- kirby</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27087</link>
      <description>Kirby is a content management system. The new link field introduced in Kirby 4 allows several different link types that each validate the entered link to the relevant URL format. It also includes a "Custom" link type for advanced use cases that don't fit any of the pre-defined link formats.  As the "Custom" link type is meant to be flexible, it also allows the javascript: URL scheme. In some use cases this can be intended, but it can also be misused by attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript code when a user or visitor clicks on a link that is generated from the contents of the link field. This vulnerability is patched in 4.1.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27087|2024-02-26T16:44:31.105Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 16:44:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27087|2024-07-05T17:22:00.531Z -- getkirby -- kirby</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27087</link>
      <description>Kirby is a content management system. The new link field introduced in Kirby 4 allows several different link types that each validate the entered link to the relevant URL format. It also includes a "Custom" link type for advanced use cases that don't fit any of the pre-defined link formats.  As the "Custom" link type is meant to be flexible, it also allows the javascript: URL scheme. In some use cases this can be intended, but it can also be misused by attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript code when a user or visitor clicks on a link that is generated from the contents of the link field. This vulnerability is patched in 4.1.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27087|2024-07-05T17:22:00.531Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 16:44:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
