<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for getkirby -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/getkirby/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for getkirby -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 21:23:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38490|2024-10-16T20:31:01.108Z -- getkirby -- kirby
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38490</link>
      <description>Kirby is a content management system. A vulnerability in versions prior to 3.5.8.3, 3.6.6.3, 3.7.5.2, 3.8.4.1, and 3.9.6 only affects Kirby sites that use the `Xml` data handler (e.g. `Data::decode($string, 'xml')`) or the `Xml::parse()` method in site or plugin code. The Kirby core does not use any of the affected methods.

XML External Entities (XXE) is a little used feature in the XML markup language that allows to include data from external files in an XML structure. If the name of the external file can be controlled by an attacker, this becomes a vulnerability that can be abused for various system impacts like the disclosure of internal or confidential data that is stored on the server (arbitrary file disclosure) or to perform network requests on behalf of the server (server-side request forgery, SSRF).

Kirby's `Xml::parse()` method used PHP's `LIBXML_NOENT` constant, which enabled the processing of XML external entities during the parsing operation. The `Xml::parse()` method is used in the `Xml` data handler (e.g. `Data::decode($string, 'xml')`). Both the vulnerable method and the data handler are not used in the Kirby core. However they may be used in site or plugin code, e.g. to parse RSS feeds or other XML files. If those files are of an external origin (e.g. uploaded by a user or retrieved from an external URL), attackers may be able to include an external entity in the XML file that will then be processed in the parsing process. Kirby sites that don't use XML parsing in site or plugin code are *not* affected.

The problem has been patched in Kirby 3.5.8.3, 3.6.6.3, 3.7.5.2, 3.8.4.1, and 3.9.6. In all of the mentioned releases, the maintainers have removed the `LIBXML_NOENT` constant as processing of external entities is out of scope of the parsing logic. This protects all uses of the method against the described vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38490|2024-10-16T20:31:01.108Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 14:46:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-41964|2024-08-29T16:36:08.820Z -- getkirby -- kirby</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41964</link>
      <description>Kirby is a CMS targeting designers and editors. Kirby allows to restrict the permissions of specific user roles. Users of that role can only perform permitted actions. Permissions for creating and deleting languages have already existed and could be configured, but were not enforced by Kirby's frontend or backend code. A permission for updating existing languages has not existed before the patched versions. So disabling the languages.* wildcard permission for a role could not have prohibited updates to existing language definitions. The missing permission checks allowed attackers with Panel access to manipulate the language definitions. The problem has been patched in Kirby 3.6.6.6, Kirby 3.7.5.5, Kirby 3.8.4.4, Kirby 3.9.8.2, Kirby 3.10.1.1, and Kirby 4.3.1. Please update to one of these or a later version to fix the vulnerability. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-41964|2024-08-29T16:36:08.820Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 16:19:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
