<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for getkirby -- kirby</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/getkirby/kirby.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for getkirby -- kirby</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:22:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39315|2024-08-03T12:00:44.153Z -- getkirby -- kirby
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39315</link>
      <description>Kirby is a Content Management System. Prior to versions 3.5.8.2, 3.6.6.2, 3.7.5.1, and 3.8.1, a user enumeration vulnerability affects all Kirby sites with user accounts unless Kirby's API and Panel are disabled in the config. It can only be exploited for targeted attacks because the attack does not scale to brute force. The problem has been patched in Kirby 3.5.8.2, Kirby 3.6.6.2, Kirby 3.7.5.1, and Kirby 3.8.1. In all of the mentioned releases, the maintainers have rewritten the affected code so that the delay is also inserted after the brute force limit is reached.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39315|2024-08-03T12:00:44.153Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36037|2024-08-03T09:51:59.947Z -- getkirby -- kirby
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36037</link>
      <description>kirby is a content management system (CMS) that adapts to many different projects and helps you build your own ideal interface. Cross-site scripting (XSS) is a type of vulnerability that allows execution of any kind of JavaScript code inside the Panel session of the same or other users. In the Panel, a harmful script can for example trigger requests to Kirby's API with the permissions of the victim. If bad actors gain access to your group of authenticated Panel users they can escalate their privileges via the Panel session of an admin user. Depending on your site, other JavaScript-powered attacks are possible. The multiselect field allows selection of tags from an autocompleted list. Unfortunately, the Panel in Kirby 3.5 used HTML rendering for the raw option value. This allowed **attackers with influence on the options source** to store HTML code. The browser of the victim who visited a page with manipulated multiselect options in the Panel will then have rendered this malicious HTML code when the victim opened the autocomplete dropdown. Users are *not* affected by this vulnerability if you don't use the multiselect field or don't use it with options that can be manipulated by attackers. The problem has been patched in Kirby 3.5.8.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36037|2024-08-03T09:51:59.947Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 17:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39314|2024-08-03T12:00:44.030Z -- getkirby -- kirby
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39314</link>
      <description>Kirby is a flat-file CMS. In versions prior to 3.5.8.2, 3.6.6.2, 3.7.5.1, and 3.8.1, Kirby is subject to user enumeration due to Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts. This vulnerability affects you only if you are using the `code` or `password-reset` auth method with the `auth.methods` option or if you have enabled the `debug` option in production. By using two or more IP addresses and multiple login attempts, valid user accounts will lock, but invalid accounts will not, leading to account enumeration. This issue has been patched in versions 3.5.8.2, 3.6.6.2, 3.7.5.1, and 3.8.1. If you cannot update immediately, you can work around the issue by setting the `auth.methods` option to `password`, which disables the code-based login and password reset forms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39314|2024-08-03T12:00:44.030Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27087|2024-07-05T17:22:00.531Z -- getkirby -- kirby</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27087</link>
      <description>Kirby is a content management system. The new link field introduced in Kirby 4 allows several different link types that each validate the entered link to the relevant URL format. It also includes a "Custom" link type for advanced use cases that don't fit any of the pre-defined link formats.  As the "Custom" link type is meant to be flexible, it also allows the javascript: URL scheme. In some use cases this can be intended, but it can also be misused by attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript code when a user or visitor clicks on a link that is generated from the contents of the link field. This vulnerability is patched in 4.1.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27087|2024-07-05T17:22:00.531Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 16:44:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27087|2024-02-26T16:44:31.105Z -- getkirby -- kirby</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27087</link>
      <description>Kirby is a content management system. The new link field introduced in Kirby 4 allows several different link types that each validate the entered link to the relevant URL format. It also includes a "Custom" link type for advanced use cases that don't fit any of the pre-defined link formats.  As the "Custom" link type is meant to be flexible, it also allows the javascript: URL scheme. In some use cases this can be intended, but it can also be misused by attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript code when a user or visitor clicks on a link that is generated from the contents of the link field. This vulnerability is patched in 4.1.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27087|2024-02-26T16:44:31.105Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 16:44:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27087|2024-08-02T00:27:57.813Z -- getkirby -- kirby</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27087</link>
      <description>Kirby is a content management system. The new link field introduced in Kirby 4 allows several different link types that each validate the entered link to the relevant URL format. It also includes a "Custom" link type for advanced use cases that don't fit any of the pre-defined link formats.  As the "Custom" link type is meant to be flexible, it also allows the javascript: URL scheme. In some use cases this can be intended, but it can also be misused by attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript code when a user or visitor clicks on a link that is generated from the contents of the link field. This vulnerability is patched in 4.1.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27087|2024-08-02T00:27:57.813Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 16:44:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
