<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Grafana -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/grafana/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Grafana -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:21:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36062|2024-08-03T09:52:00.539Z -- grafana -- grafana
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36062</link>
      <description>Grafana is an open-source platform for monitoring and observability. In versions prior to 8.5.13, 9.0.9, and 9.1.6, Grafana is subject to Improper Preservation of Permissions resulting in privilege escalation on some folders where Admin is the only used permission. The vulnerability impacts Grafana instances where RBAC was disabled and enabled afterwards, as the migrations which are translating legacy folder permissions to RBAC permissions do not account for the scenario where the only user permission in the folder is Admin, as a result RBAC adds permissions for Editors and Viewers which allow them to edit and view folders accordingly. This issue has been patched in versions 8.5.13, 9.0.9, and 9.1.6. A workaround when the impacted folder/dashboard is known is to remove the additional permissions manually.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36062|2024-08-03T09:52:00.539Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21703|2024-08-03T02:53:35.380Z -- grafana -- grafana
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21703</link>
      <description>Grafana is an open-source platform for monitoring and observability. Affected versions are subject to a cross site request forgery vulnerability which allows attackers to elevate their privileges by mounting cross-origin attacks against authenticated high-privilege Grafana users (for example, Editors or Admins). An attacker can exploit this vulnerability for privilege escalation by tricking an authenticated user into inviting the attacker as a new user with high privileges. Users are advised to upgrade as soon as possible. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21703|2024-08-03T02:53:35.380Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 20:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-35957|2024-08-03T09:51:59.288Z -- grafana -- grafana
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-35957</link>
      <description>Grafana is an open-source platform for monitoring and observability. Versions prior to 9.1.6 and 8.5.13 are vulnerable to an escalation from admin to server admin when auth proxy is used, allowing an admin to take over the server admin account and gain full control of the grafana instance. All installations should be upgraded as soon as possible. As a workaround deactivate auth proxy following the instructions at: https://grafana.com/docs/grafana/latest/setup-grafana/configure-security/configure-authentication/auth-proxy/</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-35957|2024-08-03T09:51:59.288Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39201|2024-08-03T12:00:42.561Z -- grafana -- grafana
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39201</link>
      <description>Grafana is an open source observability and data visualization platform. Starting with version 5.0.0-beta1 and prior to versions 8.5.14 and 9.1.8, Grafana could leak the authentication cookie of users to plugins. The vulnerability impacts data source and plugin proxy endpoints under certain conditions. The destination plugin could receive a user's Grafana authentication cookie. Versions 9.1.8 and 8.5.14 contain a patch for this issue. There are no known workarounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39201|2024-08-03T12:00:42.561Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31130|2024-08-03T07:11:39.569Z -- grafana -- grafana
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31130</link>
      <description>Grafana is an open source observability and data visualization platform. Versions of Grafana for endpoints prior to 9.1.8 and 8.5.14 could leak authentication tokens to some destination plugins under some conditions. The vulnerability impacts data source and plugin proxy endpoints with authentication tokens. The destination plugin could receive a user's Grafana authentication token. Versions 9.1.8 and 8.5.14 contain a patch for this issue. As a workaround, do not use API keys, JWT authentication, or any HTTP Header based authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31130|2024-08-03T07:11:39.569Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21713|2024-08-03T02:53:34.831Z -- grafana -- grafana
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21713</link>
      <description>Grafana is an open-source platform for monitoring and observability. Affected versions of Grafana expose multiple API endpoints which do not properly handle user authorization. `/teams/:teamId` will allow an authenticated attacker to view unintended data by querying for the specific team ID, `/teams/:search` will allow an authenticated attacker to search for teams and see the total number of available teams, including for those teams that the user does not have access to, and `/teams/:teamId/members` when editors_can_admin flag is enabled, an authenticated attacker can see unintended data by querying for the specific team ID. Users are advised to upgrade as soon as possible. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21713|2024-08-03T02:53:34.831Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 20:50:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31107|2024-08-03T07:11:38.479Z -- grafana -- grafana
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31107</link>
      <description>Grafana is an open-source platform for monitoring and observability. In versions 5.3 until 9.0.3, 8.5.9, 8.4.10, and 8.3.10, it is possible for a malicious user who has authorization to log into a Grafana instance via a configured OAuth IdP which provides a login name to take over the account of another user in that Grafana instance. This can occur when the malicious user is authorized to log in to Grafana via OAuth, the malicious user's external user id is not already associated with an account in Grafana, the malicious user's email address is not already associated with an account in Grafana, and the malicious user knows the Grafana username of the target user. If these conditions are met, the malicious user can set their username in the OAuth provider to that of the target user, then go through the OAuth flow to log in to Grafana. Due to the way that external and internal user accounts are linked together during login, if the conditions above are all met then the malicious user will be able to log in to the target user's Grafana account. Versions 9.0.3, 8.5.9, 8.4.10, and 8.3.10 contain a patch for this issue. As a workaround, concerned users can disable OAuth login to their Grafana instance, or ensure that all users authorized to log in via OAuth have a corresponding user account in Grafana linked to their email address.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31107|2024-08-03T07:11:38.479Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 12:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29170|2024-08-03T06:17:54.001Z -- grafana -- grafana
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29170</link>
      <description>Grafana is an open-source platform for monitoring and observability. In Grafana Enterprise, the Request security feature allows list allows to configure Grafana in a way so that the instance doesn’t call or only calls specific hosts. The vulnerability present starting with version 7.4.0-beta1 and prior to versions 7.5.16 and 8.5.3 allows someone to bypass these security configurations if a malicious datasource (running on an allowed host) returns an HTTP redirect to a forbidden host. The vulnerability only impacts Grafana Enterprise when the Request security allow list is used and there is a possibility to add a custom datasource to Grafana which returns HTTP redirects. In this scenario, Grafana would blindly follow the redirects and potentially give secure information to the clients. Grafana Cloud is not impacted by this vulnerability. Versions 7.5.16 and 8.5.3 contain a patch for this issue. There are currently no known workarounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29170|2024-08-03T06:17:54.001Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 16:10:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39307|2024-08-03T12:00:44.036Z -- grafana -- grafana
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39307</link>
      <description>Grafana is an open-source platform for monitoring and observability. When using the forget password on the login page, a POST request is made to the `/api/user/password/sent-reset-email` URL. When the username or email does not exist, a JSON response contains a “user not found” message. This leaks information to unauthenticated users and introduces a security risk. This issue has been patched in 9.2.4 and backported to 8.5.15. There are no known workarounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39307|2024-08-03T12:00:44.036Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21673|2024-08-03T02:46:39.413Z -- grafana -- grafana
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21673</link>
      <description>Grafana is an open-source platform for monitoring and observability. In affected versions when a data source has the Forward OAuth Identity feature enabled, sending a query to that datasource with an API token (and no other user credentials) will forward the OAuth Identity of the most recently logged-in user. This can allow API token holders to retrieve data for which they may not have intended access. This attack relies on the Grafana instance having data sources that support the Forward OAuth Identity feature, the Grafana instance having a data source with the Forward OAuth Identity feature toggled on, the Grafana instance having OAuth enabled, and the Grafana instance having usable API keys. This issue has been patched in versions 7.5.13 and 8.3.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21673|2024-08-03T02:46:39.413Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 21:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39306|2024-08-03T12:00:44.049Z -- grafana -- grafana
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39306</link>
      <description>Grafana is an open-source platform for monitoring and observability. Versions prior to 9.2.4, or 8.5.15 on the 8.X branch, are subject to Improper Input Validation. Grafana admins can invite other members to the organization they are an admin for. When admins add members to the organization, non existing users get an email invite, existing members are added directly to the organization. When an invite link is sent, it allows users to sign up with whatever username/email address the user chooses and become a member of the organization. This introduces a vulnerability which can be used with malicious intent. This issue is patched in version 9.2.4, and has been backported to 8.5.15. There are no known workarounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39306|2024-08-03T12:00:44.049Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39229|2024-08-03T12:00:43.379Z -- grafana -- grafana
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39229</link>
      <description>Grafana is an open source data visualization platform for metrics, logs, and traces. Versions prior to 9.1.8 and 8.5.14 allow one user to block another user's login attempt by registering someone else'e email address as a username. A Grafana user’s username and email address are unique fields, that means no other user can have the same username or email address as another user. A user can have an email address as a username. However, the login system allows users to log in with either username or email address. Since Grafana allows a user to log in with either their username or email address, this creates an usual behavior where `user_1` can register with one email address and `user_2` can register their username as `user_1`’s email address. This prevents `user_1` logging into the application since `user_1`'s password won’t match with `user_2`'s email address. Versions 9.1.8 and 8.5.14 contain a patch. There are no workarounds for this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39229|2024-08-03T12:00:43.379Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-21702|2024-08-03T02:53:34.846Z -- grafana -- grafana
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21702</link>
      <description>Grafana is an open-source platform for monitoring and observability. In affected versions an attacker could serve HTML content thru the Grafana datasource or plugin proxy and trick a user to visit this HTML page using a specially crafted link and execute a Cross-site Scripting (XSS) attack. The attacker could either compromise an existing datasource for a specific Grafana instance or either set up its own public service and instruct anyone to set it up in their Grafana instance. To be impacted, all of the following must be applicable. For the data source proxy: A Grafana HTTP-based datasource configured with Server as Access Mode and a URL set, the attacker has to be in control of the HTTP server serving the URL of above datasource, and a specially crafted link pointing at the attacker controlled data source must be clicked on by an authenticated user. For the plugin proxy: A Grafana HTTP-based app plugin configured and enabled with a URL set, the attacker has to be in control of the HTTP server serving the URL of above app, and a specially crafted link pointing at the attacker controlled plugin must be clocked on by an authenticated user. For the backend plugin resource: An attacker must be able to navigate an authenticated user to a compromised plugin through a crafted link. Users are advised to update to a patched version. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-21702|2024-08-03T02:53:34.846Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 19:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31176|2024-08-03T07:11:39.644Z -- grafana -- grafana-image-renderer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31176</link>
      <description>Grafana Image Renderer is a Grafana backend plugin that handles rendering of panels &amp; dashboards to PNGs using a headless browser (Chromium/Chrome). An internal security review identified an unauthorized file disclosure vulnerability. It is possible for a malicious user to retrieve unauthorized files under some network conditions or via a fake datasource (if user has admin permissions in Grafana). All Grafana installations should be upgraded to version 3.6.1 as soon as possible. As a workaround it is possible to [disable HTTP remote rendering](https://grafana.com/docs/grafana/latest/setup-grafana/configure-grafana/#plugingrafana-image-renderer).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31176|2024-08-03T07:11:39.644Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39324|2024-08-03T12:00:44.040Z -- grafana -- grafana
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39324</link>
      <description>Grafana is an open-source platform for monitoring and observability. Prior to versions 8.5.16 and 9.2.8, malicious user can create a snapshot and arbitrarily choose the `originalUrl` parameter by editing the query, thanks to a web proxy. When another user opens the URL of the snapshot, they will be presented with the regular web interface delivered by the trusted Grafana server. The `Open original dashboard` button no longer points to the to the real original dashboard but to the attacker’s injected URL. This issue is fixed in versions 8.5.16 and 9.2.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39324|2024-08-03T12:00:44.040Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 22:42:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31097|2024-08-03T07:11:38.469Z -- grafana -- grafana
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31097</link>
      <description>Grafana is an open-source platform for monitoring and observability. Versions on the 8.x and 9.x branch prior to 9.0.3, 8.5.9, 8.4.10, and 8.3.10 are vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting via the Unified Alerting feature of Grafana. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability to escalate privilege from editor to admin by tricking an authenticated admin to click on a link. Versions 9.0.3, 8.5.9, 8.4.10, and 8.3.10 contain a patch. As a workaround, it is possible to disable alerting or use legacy alerting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31097|2024-08-03T07:11:38.469Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 12:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23552|2024-08-03T03:43:46.570Z -- grafana -- grafana
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23552</link>
      <description>Grafana is an open-source platform for monitoring and observability. Starting with the 8.1 branch and prior to versions 8.5.16, 9.2.10, and 9.3.4, Grafana had a stored XSS vulnerability affecting the core plugin GeoMap. The stored XSS vulnerability was possible because SVG files weren't properly sanitized and allowed arbitrary JavaScript to be executed in the context of the currently authorized user of the Grafana instance. 

An attacker needs to have the Editor role in order to change a panel to include either an external URL to a SVG-file containing JavaScript, or use the `data:` scheme to load an inline SVG-file containing JavaScript. This means that vertical privilege escalation is possible, where a user with Editor role can change to a known password for a user having Admin role if the user with Admin role executes malicious JavaScript viewing a dashboard.   

Users may upgrade to version 8.5.16, 9.2.10, or 9.3.4 to receive a fix.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23552|2024-08-03T03:43:46.570Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 22:59:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-24812|2024-08-03T04:20:50.621Z -- grafana -- grafana
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24812</link>
      <description>Grafana is an open-source platform for monitoring and observability. When fine-grained access control is enabled and a client uses Grafana API Key to make requests, the permissions for that API Key are cached for 30 seconds for the given organization. Because of the way the cache ID is constructed, the consequent requests with any API Key evaluate to the same permissions as the previous requests. This can lead to an escalation of privileges, when for example a first request is made with Admin permissions, and the second request with different API Key is made with Viewer permissions, the second request will get the cached permissions from the previous Admin, essentially accessing higher privilege than it should. The vulnerability is only impacting Grafana Enterprise when the fine-grained access control beta feature is enabled and there are more than one API Keys in one organization with different roles assigned. All installations after Grafana Enterprise v8.1.0-beta1 should be upgraded as soon as possible. As an alternative, disable fine-grained access control will mitigate the vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-24812|2024-08-03T04:20:50.621Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 17:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-46156|2024-08-03T14:24:03.303Z -- grafana -- synthetic-monitoring-agent
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-46156</link>
      <description>The Synthetic Monitoring Agent for Grafana's Synthetic Monitoring application provides probe functionality and executes network checks for monitoring remote targets. Users running the Synthetic Monitoring agent prior to version 0.12.0 in their local network are impacted. The authentication token used to communicate with the Synthetic Monitoring API is exposed through a debugging endpoint. This token can be used to retrieve the Synthetic Monitoring checks created by the user and assigned to the agent identified with that token. The Synthetic Monitoring API will reject connections from already-connected agents, so access to the token does not guarantee access to the checks. Version 0.12.0 contains a fix. Users are advised to rotate the agent tokens. After upgrading to version v0.12.0 or later, it's recommended that users of distribution packages review the configuration stored in `/etc/synthetic-monitoring/synthetic-monitoring-agent.conf`, specifically the `API_TOKEN` variable which has been renamed to `SM_AGENT_API_TOKEN`. As a workaround for previous versions, it's recommended that users review the agent settings and set the HTTP listening address in a manner that limits the exposure, for example, localhost or a non-routed network, by using the command line parameter `-listen-address`, e.g. `-listen-address localhost:4050`.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-46156|2024-08-03T14:24:03.303Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-31123|2024-08-03T07:11:39.205Z -- grafana -- grafana
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-31123</link>
      <description>Grafana is an open source observability and data visualization platform. Versions prior to 9.1.8 and 8.5.14 are vulnerable to a bypass in the plugin signature verification. An attacker can convince a server admin to download and successfully run a malicious plugin even though unsigned plugins are not allowed. Versions 9.1.8 and 8.5.14 contain a patch for this issue. As a workaround, do not install plugins downloaded from untrusted sources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-31123|2024-08-03T07:11:39.205Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-39328|2024-08-03T12:00:44.037Z -- grafana -- grafana
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-39328</link>
      <description>Grafana is an open-source platform for monitoring and observability. Versions starting with 9.2.0 and less than 9.2.4 contain a race condition in the authentication middlewares logic which may allow an unauthenticated user to query an administration endpoint under heavy load. This issue is patched in 9.2.4. There are no known workarounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-39328|2024-08-03T12:00:44.037Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-23498|2024-08-03T03:43:46.002Z -- grafana -- grafana
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23498</link>
      <description>Grafana is an open-source platform for monitoring and observability. When datasource query caching is enabled, Grafana caches all headers, including `grafana_session`. As a result, any user that queries a datasource where the caching is enabled can acquire another user’s session. To mitigate the vulnerability you can disable datasource query caching for all datasources. This issue has been patched in versions 9.2.10 and 9.3.4.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-23498|2024-08-03T03:43:46.002Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 21:34:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6152|2024-08-02T08:21:17.614Z -- grafana -- grafana</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6152</link>
      <description>A user changing their email after signing up and verifying it can change it without verification in profile settings.

The configuration option "verify_email_enabled" will only validate email only on sign up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6152|2024-08-02T08:21:17.614Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 21:38:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1313|2024-08-01T18:33:25.596Z -- grafana -- grafana</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1313</link>
      <description>It is possible for a user in a different organization from the owner of a snapshot to bypass authorization and delete a snapshot by issuing a DELETE request to /api/snapshots/ using its view key. This functionality is intended to only be available to individuals with the permission to write/edit to the snapshot in question, but due to a bug in the authorization logic, deletion requests issued by an unprivileged user in a different organization than the snapshot owner are treated as authorized.

Grafana Labs would like to thank Ravid Mazon and Jay Chen of Palo 
Alto Research for discovering and disclosing this vulnerability.

This issue affects Grafana: from 9.5.0 before 9.5.18, from 10.0.0 before 10.0.13, from 10.1.0 before 10.1.9, from 10.2.0 before 10.2.6, from 10.3.0 before 10.3.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1313|2024-08-01T18:33:25.596Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 17:24:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1442|2024-08-01T18:40:21.181Z -- grafana -- grafana</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1442</link>
      <description>A user with the permissions to create a data source can use Grafana API to create a data source with UID set to *.
Doing this will grant the user access to read, query, edit and delete all data sources within the organization.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1442|2024-08-01T18:40:21.181Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 17:45:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1442|2024-07-26T14:35:58.049Z -- grafana -- grafana</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1442</link>
      <description>A user with the permissions to create a data source can use Grafana API to create a data source with UID set to *.
Doing this will grant the user access to read, query, edit and delete all data sources within the organization.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1442|2024-07-26T14:35:58.049Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 17:45:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5123|2024-02-14T16:45:44.616Z -- grafana -- grafana-json-datasource</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5123</link>
      <description>The JSON datasource plugin ( https://grafana.com/grafana/plugins/marcusolsson-json-datasource/ https://grafana.com/grafana/plugins/marcusolsson-json-datasource/ ) is a Grafana Labs maintained plugin for Grafana that allows for retrieving and processing JSON data from a remote endpoint (including a specific sub-path) configured by an administrator. Due to inadequate sanitization of the dashboard-supplied path parameter, it was possible to include path traversal characters (../) in the path parameter and send requests to paths on the configured endpoint outside the configured sub-path. 





    
    
            






    
    
            This means that if the datasource was configured by an administrator to point at some sub-path of a domain (e.g.  https://example.com/api/some_safe_api/ https://example.com/api/some_safe_api/ ), it was possible for an editor to create a dashboard referencing the datasource which issues queries containing path traversal characters, which would in turn cause the datasource to instead query arbitrary subpaths on the configured domain (e.g.  https://example.com/api/admin_api/) https://example.com/api/admin_api/) .

In the rare case that this plugin is configured by an administrator to point back at the Grafana instance itself, this vulnerability becomes considerably more severe, as an administrator browsing a maliciously configured panel could be compelled to make requests to Grafana administrative API endpoints with their credentials, resulting in the potential for privilege escalation, hence the high score for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5123|2024-02-14T16:45:44.616Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:06:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5122|2024-06-04T17:28:44.777Z -- grafana -- grafana-csv-datasource</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-5122</link>
      <description>Grafana is an open-source platform for monitoring and observability. The CSV datasource plugin is a Grafana Labs maintained plugin for Grafana that allows for retrieving and processing CSV data from a remote endpoint configured by an administrator. If this plugin was configured to send requests to a bare host with no path (e.g.  https://www.example.com/ https://www.example.com/` ), requests to an endpoint other than the one configured by the administrator could be triggered by a specially crafted request from any user, resulting in an SSRF vector. AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:N https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln-metrics/cvss/v3-calculator</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5122|2024-06-04T17:28:44.777Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:06:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6152|2024-02-13T21:38:01.404Z -- grafana -- grafana</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-6152</link>
      <description>A user changing their email after signing up and verifying it can change it without verification in profile settings.

The configuration option "verify_email_enabled" will only validate email only on sign up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6152|2024-02-13T21:38:01.404Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 21:38:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5526|2024-06-05T13:49:42.734Z -- grafana -- oncall</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5526</link>
      <description>Grafana OnCall is an easy-to-use on-call management tool that will help reduce toil in on-call management through simpler workflows and interfaces that are tailored specifically for engineers.

Grafana OnCall, from version 1.1.37 before 1.5.2 are vulnerable to a Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in the webhook functionallity. 

This issue was fixed in version 1.5.2</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5526|2024-06-05T13:49:42.734Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 11:21:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1442|2024-03-07T17:45:43.993Z -- grafana -- grafana</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1442</link>
      <description>A user with the permissions to create a data source can use Grafana API to create a data source with UID set to *.
Doing this will grant the user access to read, query, edit and delete all data sources within the organization.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1442|2024-03-07T17:45:43.993Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 17:45:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1313|2024-06-10T20:46:07.773Z -- grafana -- grafana</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1313</link>
      <description>It is possible for a user in a different organization from the owner of a snapshot to bypass authorization and delete a snapshot by issuing a DELETE request to /api/snapshots/ using its view key. This functionality is intended to only be available to individuals with the permission to write/edit to the snapshot in question, but due to a bug in the authorization logic, deletion requests issued by an unprivileged user in a different organization than the snapshot owner are treated as authorized.

Grafana Labs would like to thank Ravid Mazon and Jay Chen of Palo 
Alto Research for discovering and disclosing this vulnerability.

This issue affects Grafana: from 9.5.0 before 9.5.18, from 10.0.0 before 10.0.13, from 10.1.0 before 10.1.9, from 10.2.0 before 10.2.6, from 10.3.0 before 10.3.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1313|2024-06-10T20:46:07.773Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 17:24:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5123|2024-06-18T09:26:49.158Z -- grafana -- grafana-json-datasource</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5123</link>
      <description>The JSON datasource plugin ( https://grafana.com/grafana/plugins/marcusolsson-json-datasource/ ) is a Grafana Labs maintained plugin for Grafana that allows for retrieving and processing JSON data from a remote endpoint (including a specific sub-path) configured by an administrator. Due to inadequate sanitization of the dashboard-supplied path parameter, it was possible to include path traversal characters (../) in the path parameter and send requests to paths on the configured endpoint outside the configured sub-path. 





    
    
            






    
    
            This means that if the datasource was configured by an administrator to point at some sub-path of a domain (e.g.  https://example.com/api/some_safe_api/ ), it was possible for an editor to create a dashboard referencing the datasource which issues queries containing path traversal characters, which would in turn cause the datasource to instead query arbitrary subpaths on the configured domain (e.g.  https://example.com/api/admin_api/) .

In the rare case that this plugin is configured by an administrator to point back at the Grafana instance itself, this vulnerability becomes considerably more severe, as an administrator browsing a maliciously configured panel could be compelled to make requests to Grafana administrative API endpoints with their credentials, resulting in the potential for privilege escalation, hence the high score for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5123|2024-06-18T09:26:49.158Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:06:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5526|2024-08-01T21:18:05.358Z -- grafana -- oncall</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5526</link>
      <description>Grafana OnCall is an easy-to-use on-call management tool that will help reduce toil in on-call management through simpler workflows and interfaces that are tailored specifically for engineers.

Grafana OnCall, from version 1.1.37 before 1.5.2 are vulnerable to a Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in the webhook functionallity. 

This issue was fixed in version 1.5.2</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5526|2024-08-01T21:18:05.358Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 11:21:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5123|2024-08-02T07:44:53.814Z -- grafana -- grafana-json-datasource</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5123</link>
      <description>The JSON datasource plugin ( https://grafana.com/grafana/plugins/marcusolsson-json-datasource/ ) is a Grafana Labs maintained plugin for Grafana that allows for retrieving and processing JSON data from a remote endpoint (including a specific sub-path) configured by an administrator. Due to inadequate sanitization of the dashboard-supplied path parameter, it was possible to include path traversal characters (../) in the path parameter and send requests to paths on the configured endpoint outside the configured sub-path. 





    
    
            






    
    
            This means that if the datasource was configured by an administrator to point at some sub-path of a domain (e.g.  https://example.com/api/some_safe_api/ ), it was possible for an editor to create a dashboard referencing the datasource which issues queries containing path traversal characters, which would in turn cause the datasource to instead query arbitrary subpaths on the configured domain (e.g.  https://example.com/api/admin_api/) .

In the rare case that this plugin is configured by an administrator to point back at the Grafana instance itself, this vulnerability becomes considerably more severe, as an administrator browsing a maliciously configured panel could be compelled to make requests to Grafana administrative API endpoints with their credentials, resulting in the potential for privilege escalation, hence the high score for this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5123|2024-08-02T07:44:53.814Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:06:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-5122|2024-08-02T07:44:53.890Z -- grafana -- grafana-csv-datasource</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5122</link>
      <description>Grafana is an open-source platform for monitoring and observability. The CSV datasource plugin is a Grafana Labs maintained plugin for Grafana that allows for retrieving and processing CSV data from a remote endpoint configured by an administrator. If this plugin was configured to send requests to a bare host with no path (e.g.  https://www.example.com/ https://www.example.com/` ), requests to an endpoint other than the one configured by the administrator could be triggered by a specially crafted request from any user, resulting in an SSRF vector. AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:N https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln-metrics/cvss/v3-calculator</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-5122|2024-08-02T07:44:53.890Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:06:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
