<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for parisneo -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/parisneo/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for parisneo -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 04:24:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6281|2024-07-20T03:19:25.663Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6281</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the `apply_settings` function of parisneo/lollms versions prior to 9.5.1. The `sanitize_path` function does not adequately secure the `discussion_db_name` parameter, allowing attackers to manipulate the path and potentially write to important system folders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6281|2024-07-20T03:19:25.663Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 03:19:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1511|2024-07-15T17:01:40.671Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1511</link>
      <description>The parisneo/lollms-webui repository is susceptible to a path traversal vulnerability due to inadequate validation of user-supplied file paths. This flaw allows an unauthenticated attacker to read, write, and in certain configurations execute arbitrary files on the server by exploiting various endpoints. The vulnerability can be exploited even when the service is bound to localhost, through cross-site requests facilitated by malicious HTML/JS pages.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1511|2024-07-15T17:01:40.671Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:08:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1601|2024-07-15T17:00:01.281Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1601</link>
      <description>An SQL injection vulnerability exists in the `delete_discussion()` function of the parisneo/lollms-webui application, allowing an attacker to delete all discussions and message data. The vulnerability is exploitable via a crafted HTTP POST request to the `/delete_discussion` endpoint, which internally calls the vulnerable `delete_discussion()` function. By sending a specially crafted payload in the 'id' parameter, an attacker can manipulate SQL queries to delete all records from the 'discussion' and 'message' tables. This issue is due to improper neutralization of special elements used in an SQL command.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1601|2024-07-15T17:00:01.281Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 00:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3121|2024-07-08T18:08:19.314Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3121</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the create_conda_env function of the parisneo/lollms repository, version 5.9.0. The vulnerability arises from the use of shell=True in the subprocess.Popen function, which allows an attacker to inject arbitrary commands by manipulating the env_name and python_version parameters. This issue could lead to a serious security breach as demonstrated by the ability to execute the 'whoami' command among potentially other harmful commands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3121|2024-07-08T18:08:19.314Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 00:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4897|2024-07-03T20:12:56.422Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4897</link>
      <description>parisneo/lollms-webui, in its latest version, is vulnerable to remote code execution due to an insecure dependency on llama-cpp-python version llama_cpp_python-0.2.61+cpuavx2-cp311-cp311-manylinux_2_31_x86_64. The vulnerability arises from the application's 'binding_zoo' feature, which allows attackers to upload and interact with a malicious model file hosted on hugging-face, leading to remote code execution. The issue is linked to a known vulnerability in llama-cpp-python, CVE-2024-34359, which has not been patched in lollms-webui as of commit b454f40a. The vulnerability is exploitable through the application's handling of model files in the 'bindings_zoo' feature, specifically when processing gguf format model files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4897|2024-07-03T20:12:56.422Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:37:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6139|2024-07-02T16:48:28.625Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6139</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the XTTS server of the parisneo/lollms package version v9.6. This vulnerability allows an attacker to write audio files to arbitrary locations on the system and enumerate file paths. The issue arises from improper validation of user-provided file paths in the `tts_to_file` endpoint.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6139|2024-07-02T16:48:28.625Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:45:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1522|2024-07-01T20:34:39.415Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1522</link>
      <description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the parisneo/lollms-webui project allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on a victim's system. The vulnerability stems from the `/execute_code` API endpoint, which does not properly validate requests, enabling an attacker to craft a malicious webpage that, when visited by a victim, submits a form to the victim's local lollms-webui instance to execute arbitrary OS commands. This issue allows attackers to take full control of the victim's system without requiring direct network access to the vulnerable application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1522|2024-07-01T20:34:39.415Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 18:02:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5824|2024-06-27T18:45:26.668Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5824</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability in the `/set_personality_config` endpoint of parisneo/lollms version 9.4.0 allows an attacker to overwrite the `configs/config.yaml` file. This can lead to remote code execution by changing server configuration properties such as `force_accept_remote_access` and `turn_on_code_validation`.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5824|2024-06-27T18:45:26.668Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5933|2024-06-27T18:46:17.563Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5933</link>
      <description>A Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the chat functionality of parisneo/lollms-webui in the latest version. This vulnerability allows an attacker to inject malicious scripts via chat messages, which are then executed in the context of the user's browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5933|2024-06-27T18:46:17.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:46:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6139|2024-06-27T18:45:54.046Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6139</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the XTTS server of the parisneo/lollms package version v9.6. This vulnerability allows an attacker to write audio files to arbitrary locations on the system and enumerate file paths. The issue arises from improper validation of user-provided file paths in the `tts_to_file` endpoint.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6139|2024-06-27T18:45:54.046Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:45:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6085|2024-06-27T18:45:15.903Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6085</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the XTTS server included in the lollms package, version v9.6. This vulnerability arises from the ability to perform an unauthenticated root folder settings change. Although the read file endpoint is protected against path traversals, this protection can be bypassed by changing the root folder to '/'. This allows attackers to read arbitrary files on the system. Additionally, the output folders can be changed to write arbitrary audio files to any location on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6085|2024-06-27T18:45:15.903Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6250|2024-06-27T18:41:41.259Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6250</link>
      <description>An absolute path traversal vulnerability exists in parisneo/lollms-webui v9.6, specifically in the `open_file` endpoint of `lollms_advanced.py`. The `sanitize_path` function with `allow_absolute_path=True` allows an attacker to access arbitrary files and directories on a Windows system. This vulnerability can be exploited to read any file and list arbitrary directories on the affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6250|2024-06-27T18:41:41.259Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:41:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4315|2024-06-26T14:28:57.314Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4315</link>
      <description>parisneo/lollms version 9.5 is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion (LFI) attacks due to insufficient path sanitization. The `sanitize_path_from_endpoint` function fails to properly sanitize Windows-style paths (backward slash `\`), allowing attackers to perform directory traversal attacks on Windows systems. This vulnerability can be exploited through various routes, including `personalities` and `/del_preset`, to read or delete any file on the Windows filesystem, compromising the system's availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4315|2024-06-26T14:28:57.314Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 00:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4841|2024-06-25T18:08:12.884Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4841</link>
      <description>A Path Traversal vulnerability exists in the parisneo/lollms-webui, specifically within the 'add_reference_to_local_mode' function due to the lack of input sanitization. This vulnerability affects versions v9.6 to the latest. By exploiting this vulnerability, an attacker can predict the folders, subfolders, and files present on the victim's computer. The vulnerability is present in the way the application handles the 'path' parameter in HTTP requests to the '/add_reference_to_local_model' endpoint.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4841|2024-06-25T18:08:12.884Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 14:33:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4839|2024-06-24T12:47:59.441Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4839</link>
      <description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability exists in the 'Servers Configurations' function of the parisneo/lollms-webui, versions 9.6 to the latest. The affected functions include Elastic search Service (under construction), XTTS service, Petals service, vLLM service, and Motion Ctrl service, which lack CSRF protection. This vulnerability allows attackers to deceive users into unwittingly installing the XTTS service among other packages by submitting a malicious installation request. Successful exploitation results in attackers tricking users into performing actions without their consent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4839|2024-06-24T12:47:59.441Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 12:47:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4841|2024-06-23T14:33:33.798Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4841</link>
      <description>A Path Traversal vulnerability exists in the parisneo/lollms-webui, specifically within the 'add_reference_to_local_mode' function due to the lack of input sanitization. This vulnerability affects versions v9.6 to the latest. By exploiting this vulnerability, an attacker can predict the folders, subfolders, and files present on the victim's computer. The vulnerability is present in the way the application handles the 'path' parameter in HTTP requests to the '/add_reference_to_local_model' endpoint.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4841|2024-06-23T14:33:33.798Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 14:33:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4403|2024-06-12T14:19:20.966Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4403</link>
      <description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability exists in the restart_program function of the parisneo/lollms-webui v9.6. This vulnerability allows attackers to trick users into performing unintended actions, such as resetting the program without their knowledge, by sending specially crafted CSRF forms. This issue affects the installation process, including the installation of Binding zoo and Models zoo, by unexpectedly resetting programs. The vulnerability is due to the lack of CSRF protection in the affected function.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4403|2024-06-12T14:19:20.966Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 14:43:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2178|2024-06-07T15:16:42.282Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2178</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the parisneo/lollms-webui, specifically within the 'copy_to_custom_personas' endpoint in the 'lollms_personalities_infos.py' file. This vulnerability allows attackers to read arbitrary files by manipulating the 'category' and 'name' parameters during the 'Copy to custom personas folder for editing' process. By inserting '../' sequences in these parameters, attackers can traverse the directory structure and access files outside of the intended directory. Successful exploitation results in unauthorized access to sensitive information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2178|2024-06-07T15:16:42.282Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 10:52:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2288|2024-06-06T19:59:01.987Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2288</link>
      <description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability exists in the profile picture upload functionality of the Lollms application, specifically in the parisneo/lollms-webui repository, affecting versions up to 7.3.0. This vulnerability allows attackers to change a victim's profile picture without their consent, potentially leading to a denial of service by overloading the filesystem with files. Additionally, this flaw can be exploited to perform a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack, enabling attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of the victim's browser session. The issue is resolved in version 9.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2288|2024-06-06T19:59:01.987Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:24:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2359|2024-06-07T19:14:21.392Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2359</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the parisneo/lollms-webui version 9.3 allows attackers to bypass intended access restrictions and execute arbitrary code. The issue arises from the application's handling of the `/execute_code` endpoint, which is intended to be blocked from external access by default. However, attackers can exploit the `/update_setting` endpoint, which lacks proper access control, to modify the `host` configuration at runtime. By changing the `host` setting to an attacker-controlled value, the restriction on the `/execute_code` endpoint can be bypassed, leading to remote code execution. This vulnerability is due to improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command (`Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command`).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2359|2024-06-07T19:14:21.392Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:55:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2358|2024-06-04T17:29:16.821Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2358</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability in the '/apply_settings' endpoint of parisneo/lollms-webui allows attackers to execute arbitrary code. The vulnerability arises due to insufficient sanitization of user-supplied input in the configuration settings, specifically within the 'extensions' parameter. Attackers can exploit this by crafting a payload that includes relative path traversal sequences ('../../../'), enabling them to navigate to arbitrary directories. This flaw subsequently allows the server to load and execute a malicious '__init__.py' file, leading to remote code execution. The issue affects the latest version of parisneo/lollms-webui.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2358|2024-06-04T17:29:16.821Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2548|2024-06-07T19:35:13.160Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2548</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the parisneo/lollms-webui application, specifically within the `lollms_core/lollms/server/endpoints/lollms_binding_files_server.py` and `lollms_core/lollms/security.py` files. Due to inadequate validation of file paths between Windows and Linux environments using `Path(path).is_absolute()`, attackers can exploit this flaw to read any file on the system. This issue affects the latest version of LoLLMs running on the Windows platform. The vulnerability is triggered when an attacker sends a specially crafted request to the `/user_infos/{path:path}` endpoint, allowing the reading of arbitrary files, as demonstrated with the `win.ini` file. The issue has been addressed in version 9.5 of the software.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2548|2024-06-07T19:35:13.160Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:08:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2362|2024-06-07T19:42:03.438Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2362</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the parisneo/lollms-webui version 9.3 on the Windows platform. Due to improper validation of file paths between Windows and Linux environments, an attacker can exploit this vulnerability to delete any file on the system. The issue arises from the lack of adequate sanitization of user-supplied input in the 'del_preset' endpoint, where the application fails to prevent the use of absolute paths or directory traversal sequences ('..'). As a result, an attacker can send a specially crafted request to the 'del_preset' endpoint to delete files outside of the intended directory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2362|2024-06-07T19:42:03.438Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2299|2024-06-04T17:29:55.921Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2299</link>
      <description>A stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the parisneo/lollms-webui application due to improper validation of uploaded files in the profile picture upload functionality. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability by uploading malicious HTML files containing JavaScript code, which is executed when the file is accessed. This vulnerability is remotely exploitable via Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF), allowing attackers to perform actions on behalf of authenticated users and potentially leading to unauthorized access to sensitive information within the Lollms-webui application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2299|2024-06-04T17:29:55.921Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 20:27:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2366|2024-06-04T17:30:21.229Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2366</link>
      <description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the parisneo/lollms-webui application, specifically within the reinstall_binding functionality in lollms_core/lollms/server/endpoints/lollms_binding_infos.py of the latest version. The vulnerability arises due to insufficient path sanitization, allowing an attacker to exploit path traversal to navigate to arbitrary directories. By manipulating the binding_path to point to a controlled directory and uploading a malicious __init__.py file, an attacker can execute arbitrary code on the server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2366|2024-06-04T17:30:21.229Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:03:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2624|2024-06-07T15:10:34.142Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2624</link>
      <description>A path traversal and arbitrary file upload vulnerability exists in the parisneo/lollms-webui application, specifically within the `@router.get("/switch_personal_path")` endpoint in `./lollms-webui/lollms_core/lollms/server/endpoints/lollms_user.py`. The vulnerability arises due to insufficient sanitization of user-supplied input for the `path` parameter, allowing an attacker to specify arbitrary file system paths. This flaw enables direct arbitrary file uploads, leakage of `personal_data`, and overwriting of configurations in `lollms-webui`-&gt;`configs` by exploiting the same named directory in `personal_data`. The issue affects the latest version of the application and is fixed in version 9.4. Successful exploitation could lead to sensitive information disclosure, unauthorized file uploads, and potentially remote code execution by overwriting critical configuration files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2624|2024-06-07T15:10:34.142Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2361|2024-06-04T17:30:41.590Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2361</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the parisneo/lollms-webui allows for arbitrary file upload and read due to insufficient sanitization of user-supplied input. Specifically, the issue resides in the `install_model()` function within `lollms_core/lollms/binding.py`, where the application fails to properly sanitize the `file://` protocol and other inputs, leading to arbitrary read and upload capabilities. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the `path` and `variant_name` parameters to achieve path traversal, allowing for the reading of arbitrary files and uploading files to arbitrary locations on the server. This vulnerability affects the latest version of parisneo/lollms-webui.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2361|2024-06-04T17:30:41.590Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:03:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2360|2024-06-07T13:28:27.870Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2360</link>
      <description>parisneo/lollms-webui is vulnerable to path traversal attacks that can lead to remote code execution due to insufficient sanitization of user-supplied input in the 'Database path' and 'PDF LaTeX path' settings. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by manipulating these settings to execute arbitrary code on the targeted server. The issue affects the latest version of the software. The vulnerability stems from the application's handling of the 'discussion_db_name' and 'pdf_latex_path' parameters, which do not properly validate file paths, allowing for directory traversal. This vulnerability can also lead to further file exposure and other attack vectors by manipulating the 'discussion_db_name' parameter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2360|2024-06-07T13:28:27.870Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:55:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3322|2024-06-06T18:40:18.402Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3322</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the 'cyber_security/codeguard' native personality of the parisneo/lollms-webui, affecting versions up to 9.5. The vulnerability arises from the improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory in the 'process_folder' function within 'lollms-webui/zoos/personalities_zoo/cyber_security/codeguard/scripts/processor.py'. Specifically, the function fails to properly sanitize user-supplied input for the 'code_folder_path', allowing an attacker to specify arbitrary paths using '../' or absolute paths. This flaw leads to arbitrary file read and overwrite capabilities in specified directories without limitations, posing a significant risk of sensitive information disclosure and unauthorized file manipulation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3322|2024-06-06T18:40:18.402Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3126|2024-06-04T17:32:18.315Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3126</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability exists in the 'run_xtts_api_server' function of the parisneo/lollms-webui application, specifically within the 'lollms_xtts.py' script. The vulnerability arises due to the improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command. The affected function utilizes 'subprocess.Popen' to execute a command constructed with a Python f-string, without adequately sanitizing the 'xtts_base_url' input. This flaw allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands remotely by manipulating the 'xtts_base_url' parameter. The vulnerability affects versions up to and including the latest version before 9.5. Successful exploitation could lead to arbitrary remote code execution (RCE) on the system where the application is deployed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3126|2024-06-04T17:32:18.315Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:03:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3429|2024-06-10T18:18:56.838Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3429</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the parisneo/lollms application, specifically within the `sanitize_path_from_endpoint` and `sanitize_path` functions in `lollms_core\lollms\security.py`. This vulnerability allows for arbitrary file reading when the application is running on Windows. The issue arises due to insufficient sanitization of user-supplied input, enabling attackers to bypass the path traversal protection mechanisms by crafting malicious input. Successful exploitation could lead to unauthorized access to sensitive files, information disclosure, and potentially a denial of service (DoS) condition by including numerous large or resource-intensive files. This vulnerability affects the latest version prior to 9.6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3429|2024-06-10T18:18:56.838Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:44:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3435|2024-06-04T17:33:07.007Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3435</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the 'save_settings' endpoint of the parisneo/lollms-webui application, affecting versions up to the latest release before 9.5. The vulnerability arises due to insufficient sanitization of the 'config' parameter in the 'apply_settings' function, allowing an attacker to manipulate the application's configuration by sending specially crafted JSON payloads. This could lead to remote code execution (RCE) by bypassing existing patches designed to mitigate such vulnerabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3435|2024-06-04T17:33:07.007Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:03:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4330|2024-06-07T19:09:30.278Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4330</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability was identified in the parisneo/lollms-webui repository, specifically within version 9.6. The vulnerability arises due to improper handling of user-supplied input in the 'list_personalities' endpoint. By crafting a malicious HTTP request, an attacker can traverse the directory structure and view the contents of any folder, albeit limited to subfolder names only. This issue was demonstrated via a specific HTTP request that manipulated the 'category' parameter to access arbitrary directories. The vulnerability is present in the code located at the 'endpoints/lollms_advanced.py' file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4330|2024-06-07T19:09:30.278Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 14:43:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4326|2024-06-05T19:09:14.040Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4326</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in parisneo/lollms-webui versions up to 9.3 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code. The vulnerability stems from insufficient protection of the `/apply_settings` and `/execute_code` endpoints. Attackers can bypass protections by setting the host to localhost, enabling code execution, and disabling code validation through the `/apply_settings` endpoint. Subsequently, arbitrary commands can be executed remotely via the `/execute_code` endpoint, exploiting the delay in settings enforcement. This issue was addressed in version 9.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4326|2024-06-05T19:09:14.040Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:03:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4078|2024-05-16T09:03:49.562Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4078</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the parisneo/lollms, specifically in the `/unInstall_binding` endpoint, allows for arbitrary code execution due to insufficient sanitization of user input. The issue arises from the lack of path sanitization when handling the `name` parameter in the `unInstall_binding` function, allowing an attacker to traverse directories and execute arbitrary code by loading a malicious `__init__.py` file. This vulnerability affects the latest version of the software. The exploitation of this vulnerability could lead to remote code execution on the system where parisneo/lollms is deployed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4078|2024-05-16T09:03:49.562Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:03:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4881|2024-06-06T20:03:35.700Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4881</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the parisneo/lollms application, affecting version 9.4.0 and potentially earlier versions, but fixed in version 5.9.0. The vulnerability arises due to improper validation of file paths between Windows and Linux environments, allowing attackers to traverse beyond the intended directory and read any file on the Windows system. Specifically, the application fails to adequately sanitize file paths containing backslashes (`\`), which can be exploited to access the root directory and read, or even delete, sensitive files. This issue was discovered in the context of the `/user_infos` endpoint, where a crafted request using backslashes to reference a file (e.g., `\windows\win.ini`) could result in unauthorized file access. The impact of this vulnerability includes the potential for attackers to access sensitive information such as environment variables, database files, and configuration files, which could lead to further compromise of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4881|2024-06-06T20:03:35.700Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4403|2024-06-10T14:43:21.623Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4403</link>
      <description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability exists in the restart_program function of the parisneo/lollms-webui v9.6. This vulnerability allows attackers to trick users into performing unintended actions, such as resetting the program without their knowledge, by sending specially crafted CSRF forms. This issue affects the installation process, including the installation of Binding zoo and Models zoo, by unexpectedly resetting programs. The vulnerability is due to the lack of CSRF protection in the affected function.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4403|2024-06-10T14:43:21.623Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 14:43:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4320|2024-06-07T19:14:34.341Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4320</link>
      <description>A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability exists in the '/install_extension' endpoint of the parisneo/lollms-webui application, specifically within the `@router.post("/install_extension")` route handler. The vulnerability arises due to improper handling of the `name` parameter in the `ExtensionBuilder().build_extension()` method, which allows for local file inclusion (LFI) leading to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by crafting a malicious `name` parameter that causes the server to load and execute a `__init__.py` file from an arbitrary location, such as the upload directory for discussions. This vulnerability affects the latest version of parisneo/lollms-webui and can lead to remote code execution without requiring user interaction, especially when the application is exposed to an external endpoint or operated in headless mode.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4320|2024-06-07T19:14:34.341Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:22:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4267|2024-06-04T17:55:41.376Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4267</link>
      <description>A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability exists in the parisneo/lollms-webui, specifically within the 'open_file' module, version 9.5. The vulnerability arises due to improper neutralization of special elements used in a command within the 'open_file' function. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by crafting a malicious file path that, when processed by the 'open_file' function, executes arbitrary system commands or reads sensitive file content. This issue is present in the code where subprocess.Popen is used unsafely to open files based on user-supplied paths without adequate validation, leading to potential command injection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4267|2024-06-04T17:55:41.376Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 19:29:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4322|2024-06-04T17:55:42.204Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4322</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the parisneo/lollms-webui application, specifically within the `/list_personalities` endpoint. By manipulating the `category` parameter, an attacker can traverse the directory structure and list any directory on the system. This issue affects the latest version of the application. The vulnerability is due to improper handling of user-supplied input in the `list_personalities` function, where the `category` parameter can be controlled to specify arbitrary directories for listing. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an attacker to list all folders in the drive on the system, potentially leading to information disclosure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4322|2024-06-04T17:55:42.204Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4328|2024-06-10T12:18:56.901Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4328</link>
      <description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability exists in the clear_personality_files_list function of the parisneo/lollms-webui v9.6. The vulnerability arises from the use of a GET request to clear personality files list, which lacks proper CSRF protection. This flaw allows attackers to trick users into performing actions without their consent, such as deleting important files on the system. The issue is present in the application's handling of requests, making it susceptible to CSRF attacks that could lead to unauthorized actions being performed on behalf of the user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4328|2024-06-10T12:18:56.901Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 07:27:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1646|2024-06-04T17:59:30.637Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1646</link>
      <description>parisneo/lollms-webui is vulnerable to authentication bypass due to insufficient protection over sensitive endpoints. The application checks if the host parameter is not '0.0.0.0' to restrict access, which is inadequate when the application is bound to a specific interface, allowing unauthorized access to endpoints such as '/restart_program', '/update_software', '/check_update', '/start_recording', and '/stop_recording'. This vulnerability can lead to denial of service, unauthorized disabling or overriding of recordings, and potentially other impacts if certain features are enabled in the configuration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1646|2024-06-04T17:59:30.637Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 00:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1522|2024-04-16T11:10:26.224Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1522</link>
      <description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the parisneo/lollms-webui project allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on a victim's system. The vulnerability stems from the `/execute_code` API endpoint, which does not properly validate requests, enabling an attacker to craft a malicious webpage that, when visited by a victim, submits a form to the victim's local lollms-webui instance to execute arbitrary OS commands. This issue allows attackers to take full control of the victim's system without requiring direct network access to the vulnerable application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1522|2024-04-16T11:10:26.224Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 18:02:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1601|2024-04-16T11:10:47.905Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1601</link>
      <description>An SQL injection vulnerability exists in the `delete_discussion()` function of the parisneo/lollms-webui application, allowing an attacker to delete all discussions and message data. The vulnerability is exploitable via a crafted HTTP POST request to the `/delete_discussion` endpoint, which internally calls the vulnerable `delete_discussion()` function. By sending a specially crafted payload in the 'id' parameter, an attacker can manipulate SQL queries to delete all records from the 'discussion' and 'message' tables. This issue is due to improper neutralization of special elements used in an SQL command.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1601|2024-04-16T11:10:47.905Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 00:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1569|2024-06-04T18:00:08.316Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1569</link>
      <description>parisneo/lollms-webui is vulnerable to a denial of service (DoS) attack due to uncontrolled resource consumption. Attackers can exploit the `/open_code_in_vs_code` and similar endpoints without authentication by sending repeated HTTP POST requests, leading to the opening of Visual Studio Code or the default folder opener (e.g., File Explorer, xdg-open) multiple times. This can render the host machine unusable by exhausting system resources. The vulnerability is present in the latest version of the software.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1569|2024-06-04T18:00:08.316Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 00:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1600|2024-04-16T11:10:29.015Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1600</link>
      <description>A Local File Inclusion (LFI) vulnerability exists in the parisneo/lollms-webui application, specifically within the `/personalities` route. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by crafting a URL that includes directory traversal sequences (`../../`) followed by the desired system file path, URL encoded. Successful exploitation allows the attacker to read any file on the filesystem accessible by the web server. This issue arises due to improper control of filename for include/require statement in the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1600|2024-04-16T11:10:29.015Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:07:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1511|2024-04-16T11:10:30.829Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1511</link>
      <description>The parisneo/lollms-webui repository is susceptible to a path traversal vulnerability due to inadequate validation of user-supplied file paths. This flaw allows an unauthenticated attacker to read, write, and in certain configurations execute arbitrary files on the server by exploiting various endpoints. The vulnerability can be exploited even when the service is bound to localhost, through cross-site requests facilitated by malicious HTML/JS pages.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1511|2024-04-16T11:10:30.829Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:08:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1602|2024-04-16T11:10:31.851Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1602</link>
      <description>parisneo/lollms-webui is vulnerable to stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) that leads to Remote Code Execution (RCE). The vulnerability arises due to inadequate sanitization and validation of model output data, allowing an attacker to inject malicious JavaScript code. This code can be executed within the user's browser context, enabling the attacker to send a request to the `/execute_code` endpoint and establish a reverse shell to the attacker's host. The issue affects various components of the application, including the handling of user input and model output.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1602|2024-04-16T11:10:31.851Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:08:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1520|2024-04-16T11:10:31.162Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1520</link>
      <description>An OS Command Injection vulnerability exists in the '/open_code_folder' endpoint of the parisneo/lollms-webui application, due to improper validation of user-supplied input in the 'discussion_id' parameter. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious OS commands, leading to unauthorized command execution on the underlying operating system. This could result in unauthorized access, data leakage, or complete system compromise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1520|2024-04-16T11:10:31.162Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:08:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1873|2024-06-07T15:15:45.782Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1873</link>
      <description>parisneo/lollms-webui is vulnerable to path traversal and denial of service attacks due to an exposed `/select_database` endpoint in version a9d16b0. The endpoint improperly handles file paths, allowing attackers to specify absolute paths when interacting with the `DiscussionsDB` instance. This flaw enables attackers to create directories anywhere on the system where the application has permissions, potentially leading to denial of service by creating directories with names of critical files, such as HTTPS certificate files, causing server startup failures. Additionally, attackers can manipulate the database path, resulting in the loss of client data by constantly changing the file location to an attacker-controlled location, scattering the data across the filesystem and making recovery difficult.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1873|2024-06-07T15:15:45.782Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:40:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5482|2024-06-07T15:09:39.896Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5482</link>
      <description>A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability exists in the 'add_webpage' endpoint of the parisneo/lollms-webui application, affecting the latest version. The vulnerability arises because the application does not adequately validate URLs entered by users, allowing them to input arbitrary URLs, including those that target internal resources such as 'localhost' or '127.0.0.1'. This flaw enables attackers to make unauthorized requests to internal or external systems, potentially leading to access to sensitive data, service disruption, network integrity compromise, business logic manipulation, and abuse of third-party resources. The issue is critical and requires immediate attention to maintain the application's security and integrity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5482|2024-06-07T15:09:39.896Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 17:56:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5443|2024-06-22T16:12:32.499Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5443</link>
      <description>CVE-2024-4320 describes a vulnerability in the parisneo/lollms software, specifically within the `ExtensionBuilder().build_extension()` function. The vulnerability arises from the `/mount_extension` endpoint, where a path traversal issue allows attackers to navigate beyond the intended directory structure. This is facilitated by the `data.category` and `data.folder` parameters accepting empty strings (`""`), which, due to inadequate input sanitization, can lead to the construction of a `package_path` that points to the root directory. Consequently, if an attacker can create a `config.yaml` file in a controllable path, this path can be appended to the `extensions` list and trigger the execution of `__init__.py` in the current directory, leading to remote code execution. The vulnerability affects versions up to 5.9.0, and has been addressed in version 9.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5443|2024-06-22T16:12:32.499Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 16:12:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4499|2024-06-24T03:06:46.088Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4499</link>
      <description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability exists in the XTTS server of parisneo/lollms version 9.6 due to a lax CORS policy. The vulnerability allows attackers to perform unauthorized actions by tricking a user into visiting a malicious webpage, which can then trigger arbitrary LoLLMS-XTTS API requests. This issue can lead to the reading and writing of audio files and, when combined with other vulnerabilities, could allow for the reading of arbitrary files on the system and writing files outside the permitted audio file location.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4499|2024-06-24T03:06:46.088Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 03:06:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4499|2024-06-24T14:57:18.658Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4499</link>
      <description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability exists in the XTTS server of parisneo/lollms version 9.6 due to a lax CORS policy. The vulnerability allows attackers to perform unauthorized actions by tricking a user into visiting a malicious webpage, which can then trigger arbitrary LoLLMS-XTTS API requests. This issue can lead to the reading and writing of audio files and, when combined with other vulnerabilities, could allow for the reading of arbitrary files on the system and writing files outside the permitted audio file location.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4499|2024-06-24T14:57:18.658Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 03:06:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5443|2024-06-24T14:51:22.620Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5443</link>
      <description>CVE-2024-4320 describes a vulnerability in the parisneo/lollms software, specifically within the `ExtensionBuilder().build_extension()` function. The vulnerability arises from the `/mount_extension` endpoint, where a path traversal issue allows attackers to navigate beyond the intended directory structure. This is facilitated by the `data.category` and `data.folder` parameters accepting empty strings (`""`), which, due to inadequate input sanitization, can lead to the construction of a `package_path` that points to the root directory. Consequently, if an attacker can create a `config.yaml` file in a controllable path, this path can be appended to the `extensions` list and trigger the execution of `__init__.py` in the current directory, leading to remote code execution. The vulnerability affects versions up to 5.9.0, and has been addressed in version 9.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5443|2024-06-24T14:51:22.620Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 16:12:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4498|2024-06-25T19:55:42.340Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4498</link>
      <description>A Path Traversal and Remote File Inclusion (RFI) vulnerability exists in the parisneo/lollms-webui application, affecting versions v9.7 to the latest. The vulnerability arises from insufficient input validation in the `/apply_settings` function, allowing an attacker to manipulate the `discussion_db_name` parameter to traverse the file system and include arbitrary files. This issue is compounded by the bypass of input filtering in the `install_binding`, `reinstall_binding`, and `unInstall_binding` endpoints, despite the presence of a `sanitize_path_from_endpoint(data.name)` filter. Successful exploitation enables an attacker to upload and execute malicious code on the victim's system, leading to Remote Code Execution (RCE).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4498|2024-06-25T19:55:42.340Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 19:55:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4498|2024-06-26T16:55:20.543Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4498</link>
      <description>A Path Traversal and Remote File Inclusion (RFI) vulnerability exists in the parisneo/lollms-webui application, affecting versions v9.7 to the latest. The vulnerability arises from insufficient input validation in the `/apply_settings` function, allowing an attacker to manipulate the `discussion_db_name` parameter to traverse the file system and include arbitrary files. This issue is compounded by the bypass of input filtering in the `install_binding`, `reinstall_binding`, and `unInstall_binding` endpoints, despite the presence of a `sanitize_path_from_endpoint(data.name)` filter. Successful exploitation enables an attacker to upload and execute malicious code on the victim's system, leading to Remote Code Execution (RCE).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4498|2024-06-26T16:55:20.543Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 19:55:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6250|2024-06-28T15:14:13.182Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6250</link>
      <description>An absolute path traversal vulnerability exists in parisneo/lollms-webui v9.6, specifically in the `open_file` endpoint of `lollms_advanced.py`. The `sanitize_path` function with `allow_absolute_path=True` allows an attacker to access arbitrary files and directories on a Windows system. This vulnerability can be exploited to read any file and list arbitrary directories on the affected system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6250|2024-06-28T15:14:13.182Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:41:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5933|2024-06-28T15:07:33.248Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5933</link>
      <description>A Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the chat functionality of parisneo/lollms-webui in the latest version. This vulnerability allows an attacker to inject malicious scripts via chat messages, which are then executed in the context of the user's browser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5933|2024-06-28T15:07:33.248Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:46:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5824|2024-06-28T15:10:40.789Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5824</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability in the `/set_personality_config` endpoint of parisneo/lollms version 9.4.0 allows an attacker to overwrite the `configs/config.yaml` file. This can lead to remote code execution by changing server configuration properties such as `force_accept_remote_access` and `turn_on_code_validation`.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5824|2024-06-28T15:10:40.789Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4897|2024-07-02T14:37:36.135Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4897</link>
      <description>parisneo/lollms-webui, in its latest version, is vulnerable to remote code execution due to an insecure dependency on llama-cpp-python version llama_cpp_python-0.2.61+cpuavx2-cp311-cp311-manylinux_2_31_x86_64. The vulnerability arises from the application's 'binding_zoo' feature, which allows attackers to upload and interact with a malicious model file hosted on hugging-face, leading to remote code execution. The issue is linked to a known vulnerability in llama-cpp-python, CVE-2024-34359, which has not been patched in lollms-webui as of commit b454f40a. The vulnerability is exploitable through the application's handling of model files in the 'bindings_zoo' feature, specifically when processing gguf format model files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4897|2024-07-02T14:37:36.135Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:37:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1600|2024-07-03T16:47:16.616Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1600</link>
      <description>A Local File Inclusion (LFI) vulnerability exists in the parisneo/lollms-webui application, specifically within the `/personalities` route. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by crafting a URL that includes directory traversal sequences (`../../`) followed by the desired system file path, URL encoded. Successful exploitation allows the attacker to read any file on the filesystem accessible by the web server. This issue arises due to improper control of filename for include/require statement in the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1600|2024-07-03T16:47:16.616Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:07:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1601|2024-07-03T21:04:32.685Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1601</link>
      <description>An SQL injection vulnerability exists in the `delete_discussion()` function of the parisneo/lollms-webui application, allowing an attacker to delete all discussions and message data. The vulnerability is exploitable via a crafted HTTP POST request to the `/delete_discussion` endpoint, which internally calls the vulnerable `delete_discussion()` function. By sending a specially crafted payload in the 'id' parameter, an attacker can manipulate SQL queries to delete all records from the 'discussion' and 'message' tables. This issue is due to improper neutralization of special elements used in an SQL command.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1601|2024-07-03T21:04:32.685Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 00:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-6085|2024-07-09T19:16:52.617Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6085</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the XTTS server included in the lollms package, version v9.6. This vulnerability arises from the ability to perform an unauthenticated root folder settings change. Although the read file endpoint is protected against path traversals, this protection can be bypassed by changing the root folder to '/'. This allows attackers to read arbitrary files on the system. Additionally, the output folders can be changed to write arbitrary audio files to any location on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-6085|2024-07-09T19:16:52.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-1602|2024-07-19T15:29:52.583Z -- parisneo -- parisneo%2Flollms-webui</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1602</link>
      <description>parisneo/lollms-webui is vulnerable to stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) that leads to Remote Code Execution (RCE). The vulnerability arises due to inadequate sanitization and validation of model output data, allowing an attacker to inject malicious JavaScript code. This code can be executed within the user's browser context, enabling the attacker to send a request to the `/execute_code` endpoint and establish a reverse shell to the attacker's host. The issue affects various components of the application, including the handling of user input and model output.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1602|2024-07-19T15:29:52.583Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:08:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
