<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for parisneo -- parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/parisneo/parisneo%2Flollms-webui.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for parisneo -- parisneo/lollms-webui</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 11:19:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-2178|2024-06-02T10:52:32.063Z -- parisneo -- parisneo/lollms-webui
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2178</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the parisneo/lollms-webui, specifically within the 'copy_to_custom_personas' endpoint in the 'lollms_personalities_infos.py' file. This vulnerability allows attackers to read arbitrary files by manipulating the 'category' and 'name' parameters during the 'Copy to custom personas folder for editing' process. By inserting '../' sequences in these parameters, attackers can traverse the directory structure and access files outside of the intended directory. Successful exploitation results in unauthorized access to sensitive information.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2178|2024-06-02T10:52:32.063Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 10:52:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2358|2024-05-16T09:03:45.397Z -- parisneo -- parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2358</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability in the '/apply_settings' endpoint of parisneo/lollms-webui allows attackers to execute arbitrary code. The vulnerability arises due to insufficient sanitization of user-supplied input in the configuration settings, specifically within the 'extensions' parameter. Attackers can exploit this by crafting a payload that includes relative path traversal sequences ('../../../'), enabling them to navigate to arbitrary directories. This flaw subsequently allows the server to load and execute a malicious '__init__.py' file, leading to remote code execution. The issue affects the latest version of parisneo/lollms-webui.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2358|2024-05-16T09:03:45.397Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:03:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2299|2024-05-12T20:27:55.262Z -- parisneo -- parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2299</link><description>A stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the parisneo/lollms-webui application due to improper validation of uploaded files in the profile picture upload functionality. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability by uploading malicious HTML files containing JavaScript code, which is executed when the file is accessed. This vulnerability is remotely exploitable via Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF), allowing attackers to perform actions on behalf of authenticated users and potentially leading to unauthorized access to sensitive information within the Lollms-webui application.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2299|2024-05-12T20:27:55.262Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 20:27:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2366|2024-05-16T09:03:49.643Z -- parisneo -- parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2366</link><description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in the parisneo/lollms-webui application, specifically within the reinstall_binding functionality in lollms_core/lollms/server/endpoints/lollms_binding_infos.py of the latest version. The vulnerability arises due to insufficient path sanitization, allowing an attacker to exploit path traversal to navigate to arbitrary directories. By manipulating the binding_path to point to a controlled directory and uploading a malicious __init__.py file, an attacker can execute arbitrary code on the server.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2366|2024-05-16T09:03:49.643Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:03:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2361|2024-05-16T09:03:50.151Z -- parisneo -- parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2361</link><description>A vulnerability in the parisneo/lollms-webui allows for arbitrary file upload and read due to insufficient sanitization of user-supplied input. Specifically, the issue resides in the `install_model()` function within `lollms_core/lollms/binding.py`, where the application fails to properly sanitize the `file://` protocol and other inputs, leading to arbitrary read and upload capabilities. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the `path` and `variant_name` parameters to achieve path traversal, allowing for the reading of arbitrary files and uploading files to arbitrary locations on the server. This vulnerability affects the latest version of parisneo/lollms-webui.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2361|2024-05-16T09:03:50.151Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:03:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3126|2024-05-16T09:03:47.640Z -- parisneo -- parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3126</link><description>A command injection vulnerability exists in the 'run_xtts_api_server' function of the parisneo/lollms-webui application, specifically within the 'lollms_xtts.py' script. The vulnerability arises due to the improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command. The affected function utilizes 'subprocess.Popen' to execute a command constructed with a Python f-string, without adequately sanitizing the 'xtts_base_url' input. This flaw allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands remotely by manipulating the 'xtts_base_url' parameter. The vulnerability affects versions up to and including the latest version before 9.5. Successful exploitation could lead to arbitrary remote code execution (RCE) on the system where the application is deployed.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3126|2024-05-16T09:03:47.640Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:03:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3435|2024-05-16T09:03:48.687Z -- parisneo -- parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3435</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the 'save_settings' endpoint of the parisneo/lollms-webui application, affecting versions up to the latest release before 9.5. The vulnerability arises due to insufficient sanitization of the 'config' parameter in the 'apply_settings' function, allowing an attacker to manipulate the application's configuration by sending specially crafted JSON payloads. This could lead to remote code execution (RCE) by bypassing existing patches designed to mitigate such vulnerabilities.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3435|2024-05-16T09:03:48.687Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:03:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4330|2024-05-30T14:43:40.842Z -- parisneo -- parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4330</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability was identified in the parisneo/lollms-webui repository, specifically within version 9.6. The vulnerability arises due to improper handling of user-supplied input in the 'list_personalities' endpoint. By crafting a malicious HTTP request, an attacker can traverse the directory structure and view the contents of any folder, albeit limited to subfolder names only. This issue was demonstrated via a specific HTTP request that manipulated the 'category' parameter to access arbitrary directories. The vulnerability is present in the code located at the 'endpoints/lollms_advanced.py' file.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4330|2024-05-30T14:43:40.842Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 14:43:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4326|2024-05-16T09:03:47.208Z -- parisneo -- parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4326</link><description>A vulnerability in parisneo/lollms-webui versions up to 9.3 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code. The vulnerability stems from insufficient protection of the `/apply_settings` and `/execute_code` endpoints. Attackers can bypass protections by setting the host to localhost, enabling code execution, and disabling code validation through the `/apply_settings` endpoint. Subsequently, arbitrary commands can be executed remotely via the `/execute_code` endpoint, exploiting the delay in settings enforcement. This issue was addressed in version 9.5.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4326|2024-05-16T09:03:47.208Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:03:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4267|2024-05-22T19:29:56.867Z -- parisneo -- parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4267</link><description>A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability exists in the parisneo/lollms-webui, specifically within the 'open_file' module, version 9.5. The vulnerability arises due to improper neutralization of special elements used in a command within the 'open_file' function. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by crafting a malicious file path that, when processed by the 'open_file' function, executes arbitrary system commands or reads sensitive file content. This issue is present in the code where subprocess.Popen is used unsafely to open files based on user-supplied paths without adequate validation, leading to potential command injection.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4267|2024-05-22T19:29:56.867Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 19:29:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4322|2024-05-16T09:03:45.504Z -- parisneo -- parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4322</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the parisneo/lollms-webui application, specifically within the `/list_personalities` endpoint. By manipulating the `category` parameter, an attacker can traverse the directory structure and list any directory on the system. This issue affects the latest version of the application. The vulnerability is due to improper handling of user-supplied input in the `list_personalities` function, where the `category` parameter can be controlled to specify arbitrary directories for listing. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an attacker to list all folders in the drive on the system, potentially leading to information disclosure.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4322|2024-05-16T09:03:45.504Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:03:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1646|2024-04-16T11:10:34.706Z -- parisneo -- parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1646</link><description>parisneo/lollms-webui is vulnerable to authentication bypass due to insufficient protection over sensitive endpoints. The application checks if the host parameter is not '0.0.0.0' to restrict access, which is inadequate when the application is bound to a specific interface, allowing unauthorized access to endpoints such as '/restart_program', '/update_software', '/check_update', '/start_recording', and '/stop_recording'. This vulnerability can lead to denial of service, unauthorized disabling or overriding of recordings, and potentially other impacts if certain features are enabled in the configuration.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1646|2024-04-16T11:10:34.706Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 00:00:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1522|2024-04-16T11:10:26.224Z -- parisneo -- parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1522</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the parisneo/lollms-webui project allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on a victim's system. The vulnerability stems from the `/execute_code` API endpoint, which does not properly validate requests, enabling an attacker to craft a malicious webpage that, when visited by a victim, submits a form to the victim's local lollms-webui instance to execute arbitrary OS commands. This issue allows attackers to take full control of the victim's system without requiring direct network access to the vulnerable application.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1522|2024-04-16T11:10:26.224Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 18:02:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1601|2024-04-16T11:10:47.905Z -- parisneo -- parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1601</link><description>An SQL injection vulnerability exists in the `delete_discussion()` function of the parisneo/lollms-webui application, allowing an attacker to delete all discussions and message data. The vulnerability is exploitable via a crafted HTTP POST request to the `/delete_discussion` endpoint, which internally calls the vulnerable `delete_discussion()` function. By sending a specially crafted payload in the 'id' parameter, an attacker can manipulate SQL queries to delete all records from the 'discussion' and 'message' tables. This issue is due to improper neutralization of special elements used in an SQL command.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1601|2024-04-16T11:10:47.905Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 00:00:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1569|2024-04-16T11:10:48.310Z -- parisneo -- parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1569</link><description>parisneo/lollms-webui is vulnerable to a denial of service (DoS) attack due to uncontrolled resource consumption. Attackers can exploit the `/open_code_in_vs_code` and similar endpoints without authentication by sending repeated HTTP POST requests, leading to the opening of Visual Studio Code or the default folder opener (e.g., File Explorer, xdg-open) multiple times. This can render the host machine unusable by exhausting system resources. The vulnerability is present in the latest version of the software.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1569|2024-04-16T11:10:48.310Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 00:00:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1600|2024-04-16T11:10:29.015Z -- parisneo -- parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1600</link><description>A Local File Inclusion (LFI) vulnerability exists in the parisneo/lollms-webui application, specifically within the `/personalities` route. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by crafting a URL that includes directory traversal sequences (`../../`) followed by the desired system file path, URL encoded. Successful exploitation allows the attacker to read any file on the filesystem accessible by the web server. This issue arises due to improper control of filename for include/require statement in the application.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1600|2024-04-16T11:10:29.015Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:07:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1511|2024-04-16T11:10:30.829Z -- parisneo -- parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1511</link><description>The parisneo/lollms-webui repository is susceptible to a path traversal vulnerability due to inadequate validation of user-supplied file paths. This flaw allows an unauthenticated attacker to read, write, and in certain configurations execute arbitrary files on the server by exploiting various endpoints. The vulnerability can be exploited even when the service is bound to localhost, through cross-site requests facilitated by malicious HTML/JS pages.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1511|2024-04-16T11:10:30.829Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:08:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1602|2024-04-16T11:10:31.851Z -- parisneo -- parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1602</link><description>parisneo/lollms-webui is vulnerable to stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) that leads to Remote Code Execution (RCE). The vulnerability arises due to inadequate sanitization and validation of model output data, allowing an attacker to inject malicious JavaScript code. This code can be executed within the user's browser context, enabling the attacker to send a request to the `/execute_code` endpoint and establish a reverse shell to the attacker's host. The issue affects various components of the application, including the handling of user input and model output.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1602|2024-04-16T11:10:31.851Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:08:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1520|2024-04-16T11:10:31.162Z -- parisneo -- parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1520</link><description>An OS Command Injection vulnerability exists in the '/open_code_folder' endpoint of the parisneo/lollms-webui application, due to improper validation of user-supplied input in the 'discussion_id' parameter. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious OS commands, leading to unauthorized command execution on the underlying operating system. This could result in unauthorized access, data leakage, or complete system compromise.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1520|2024-04-16T11:10:31.162Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:08:02 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>