<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Siemens AG -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/siemens%20ag/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Siemens AG -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 07:21:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13807|2024-09-17T00:37:09.724Z -- siemens%20ag -- scalance%20x300%2C%20scalance%20x408%2C%20scalance%20x414
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13807</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE X300 (All versions &lt; V4.0.0), SCALANCE X408 (All versions &lt; V4.0.0), SCALANCE X414 (All versions). The web interface on port 443/tcp could allow an attacker to cause a Denial-of-Service condition by sending specially crafted packets to the web server. The device will automatically reboot, impacting network availability for other devices. An attacker must have network access to port 443/tcp to exploit the vulnerability. Neither valid credentials nor interaction by a legitimate user is required to exploit the vulnerability. There is no confidentiality or integrity impact, only availability is temporarily impacted. This vulnerability could be triggered by publicly available tools.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13807|2024-09-17T00:37:09.724Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11447|2024-09-17T02:17:05.410Z -- siemens%20ag -- scalance%20m875
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11447</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE M875 (All versions). The web interface on port 443/tcp could allow a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) attack if an unsuspecting user is tricked into accessing a malicious link. Successful exploitation requires user interaction by an legitimate user, who must be authenticated to the web interface as administrative user. A successful attack could allow an attacker to interact with the web interface as an administrative user. This could allow the attacker to read or modify the device configuration, or to exploit other vulnerabilities that require authentication as administrative user. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11447|2024-09-17T02:17:05.410Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12736|2024-09-17T02:37:15.644Z -- siemens%20ag -- ruggedcom%20ros%20for%20rsl910%20devices%2C%20ruggedcom%20ros%20for%20all%20other%20devices%2C%20scalance%20xb-200%2Fxc-200%2Fxp-200%2Fxr300-wg%2C%20scalance%20xr-500%2Fxm-400
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12736</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM ROS for RSL910 devices (All versions &lt; ROS V5.0.1), RUGGEDCOM ROS for all other devices (All versions &lt; ROS V4.3.4), SCALANCE XB-200/XC-200/XP-200/XR300-WG (All versions between V3.0 (including) and V3.0.2 (excluding)), SCALANCE XR-500/XM-400 (All versions between V6.1 (including) and V6.1.1 (excluding)). After initial configuration, the Ruggedcom Discovery Protocol (RCDP) is still able to writeto the device under certain conditions, potentially allowing users located in the adjacentnetwork of the targeted device to perform unauthorized administrative actions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12736|2024-09-17T02:37:15.644Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2017 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-13935|2024-09-17T01:11:21.790Z -- siemens%20ag -- polarion
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-13935</link>
      <description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in webclient of Siemens AG Polarion could allow an attacker to exploit a reflected XSS vulnerability. This issue affects: Siemens AG Polarion All versions &lt; 19.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-13935|2024-09-17T01:11:21.790Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 13:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4851|2024-09-17T01:01:16.624Z -- siemens%20ag -- siclock%20tc100%2C%20siclock%20tc400
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4851</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SICLOCK TC100 (All versions) and SICLOCK TC400 (All versions). An attacker with network access to the device could cause a Denial-of-Service condition by sending certain packets to the device, causing potential reboots of the device. The core functionality of the device could be impacted. The time serving functionality recovers when time synchronization with GPS devices or other NTP servers are completed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4851|2024-09-17T01:01:16.624Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4846|2024-09-17T01:01:45.175Z -- siemens%20ag -- rapidlab%201200%20systems%20rapidpoint%20400%20systems%20rapidpoint%20500%20systems%20rapidlab%201200%20series%20rapidpoint%20500%20systems%20rapidpoint%20500%20systems%20rapidpoint%20500%20systems%20rapidpoint%20400%20systems
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4846</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in RAPIDLab 1200 systems / RAPIDPoint 400 systems / RAPIDPoint 500 systems (All versions_without_ use of Siemens Healthineers Informatics products), RAPIDLab 1200 Series (All versions &lt; V3.3 _with_ Siemens Healthineers Informatics products), RAPIDPoint 500 systems (All versions &gt;= V3.0 _with_ Siemens Healthineers Informatics products), RAPIDPoint 500 systems (V2.4.X_with_ Siemens Healthineers Informatics products), RAPIDPoint 500 systems (All versions =&lt; V2.3 _with_ Siemens Healthineers Informatics products), RAPIDPoint 400 systems (All versions _with_ Siemens Healthineers Informatics products). A factory account with hardcoded password might allow attackers access to the device over port 5900/tcp. Successful exploitation requires no user interaction or privileges and impacts the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the affected device. At the time of advisory publication, no public exploitation of this security vulnerability is known. Siemens Healthineers confirms the security vulnerability and provides mitigations to resolve the security issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4846|2024-09-17T01:01:45.175Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4847|2024-09-17T02:57:39.805Z -- siemens%20ag -- simatic%20wincc%20oa%20operator%20ios%20app
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4847</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC WinCC OA Operator iOS App (All versions &lt; V1.4). Insufficient protection of sensitive information (e.g. session key for accessing server) in Siemens WinCC OA Operator iOS app could allow an attacker with physical access to the mobile device to read unencrypted data from the app's directory. Siemens provides mitigations to resolve the security issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4847|2024-09-17T02:57:39.805Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4841|2024-09-17T03:02:01.165Z -- siemens%20ag -- tim%201531%20irc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4841</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in TIM 1531 IRC (All versions &lt; V1.1). A remote attacker with network access to port 80/tcp or port 443/tcp could perform administrative operations on the device without prior authentication. Successful exploitation could allow to cause a denial-of-service, or read and manipulate data as well as configuration settings of the affected device. At the stage of publishing this security advisory no public exploitation is known. Siemens provides mitigations to resolve it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4841|2024-09-17T03:02:01.165Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4856|2024-09-17T03:28:51.189Z -- siemens%20ag -- siclock%20tc100%2C%20siclock%20tc400
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4856</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SICLOCK TC100 (All versions) and SICLOCK TC400 (All versions). An attacker with administrative access to the device's management interface could lock out legitimate users. Manual interaction is required to restore the access of legitimate users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4856|2024-09-17T03:28:51.189Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4859|2024-09-17T00:31:04.082Z -- siemens%20ag -- scalance%20m875
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4859</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE M875 (All versions). An authenticated remote attacker with access to the web interface (443/tcp), could execute arbitrary operating system commands. Successful exploitation requires that the attacker has network access to the web interface. The attacker must be authenticated as administrative user to exploit the security vulnerability. The vulnerability could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code on the device. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4859|2024-09-17T00:31:04.082Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4852|2024-09-17T03:07:34.425Z -- siemens%20ag -- siclock%20tc100%2C%20siclock%20tc400
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4852</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SICLOCK TC100 (All versions) and SICLOCK TC400 (All versions). An attacker with network access to the device could potentially circumvent the authentication mechanism if he/she is able to obtain certain knowledge specific to the attacked device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4852|2024-09-17T03:07:34.425Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4835|2024-09-17T02:58:06.169Z -- siemens%20ag -- telecontrol%20server%20basic
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4835</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in TeleControl Server Basic &lt; V3.1. An attacker with network access to the TeleControl Server Basic's port 8000/tcp could bypass the authentication mechanism and read limited information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4835|2024-09-17T02:58:06.169Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4844|2024-09-17T03:12:54.178Z -- siemens%20ag -- simatic%20wincc%20oa%20ui%20for%20android%2C%20simatic%20wincc%20oa%20ui%20for%20ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4844</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC WinCC OA UI for Android (All versions &lt; V3.15.10), SIMATIC WinCC OA UI for iOS (All versions &lt; V3.15.10). Insufficient limitation of CONTROL script capabilities could allow read and write access from one HMI project cache folder to other HMI project cache folders within the app's sandbox on the same mobile device. This includes HMI project cache folders of other configured WinCC OA servers. The security vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker who tricks an app user to connect to an attacker-controlled WinCC OA server. Successful exploitation requires user interaction and read/write access to the app's folder on a mobile device. The vulnerability could allow reading data from and writing data to the app's folder. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known. Siemens confirms the security vulnerability and provides mitigations to resolve the security issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4844|2024-09-17T03:12:54.178Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11449|2024-09-17T03:44:14.245Z -- siemens%20ag -- scalance%20m875
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11449</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE M875 (All versions). An attacker with access to the local file system might obtain passwords for administrative users. Successful exploitation requires read access to files on the local file system. A successful attack could allow an attacker to obtain administrative passwords. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11449|2024-09-17T03:44:14.245Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4855|2024-09-17T03:08:21.334Z -- siemens%20ag -- siclock%20tc100%2C%20siclock%20tc400
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4855</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SICLOCK TC100 (All versions) and SICLOCK TC400 (All versions). Unencrypted storage of passwords in the client configuration files and during network transmission could allow an attacker in a privileged position to obtain access passwords.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4855|2024-09-17T03:08:21.334Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
