<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Siemens AG -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/siemens%20ag/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Siemens AG -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 21:23:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-19278|2024-08-05T02:09:39.676Z -- siemens%20ag -- sinamics%20perfect%20harmony%20gh180%20drives%0A%0A%20mlfb%206sr32..-.....-....%0A%0A%20mlfb%206sr4...-.....-....%0A%0A%20mlfb%206sr5...-.....-....%0A%0A%20with%20option%20a30%20%28hmis%2012%20inches%20or%20larger%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-19278</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINAMICS PERFECT HARMONY GH180 Drives MLFB 6SR32..-.....-.... MLFB 6SR4...-.....-.... MLFB 6SR5...-.....-.... With option A30 (HMIs 12 inches or larger) (All versions), SINAMICS PERFECT HARMONY GH180 Drives MLFB 6SR325.-.....-.... (High Availability) (All versions). The affected device contains a vulnerability that could allow an unauthenticated attacker to restore the affected device to a point where predefined application and operating system protection mechanisms are not in place. Successful exploitation requires physical access to the system, but no system privileges and no user interaction. An attacker could use the vulnerability to compromise confidentialiy, integrity and availability of the device. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-19278|2024-08-05T02:09:39.676Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 15:35:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13801|2024-08-05T09:14:47.229Z -- siemens%20ag -- rox%20ii
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13801</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in ROX II (All versions &lt; V2.12.1). An attacker with network access to port 22/tcp and valid low-privileged user credentials for the target device could perform a privilege escalation and gain root privileges. Successful exploitation requires user privileges of a low-privileged user but no user interaction. The vulnerability could allow an attacker to compromise confidentiality, integrity and availability of the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13801|2024-08-05T09:14:47.229Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11447|2024-08-05T08:10:14.455Z -- siemens%20ag -- scalance%20m875
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11447</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE M875 (All versions). The web interface on port 443/tcp could allow a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) attack if an unsuspecting user is tricked into accessing a malicious link. Successful exploitation requires user interaction by an legitimate user, who must be authenticated to the web interface as administrative user. A successful attack could allow an attacker to interact with the web interface as an administrative user. This could allow the attacker to read or modify the device configuration, or to exploit other vulnerabilities that require authentication as administrative user. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11447|2024-08-05T08:10:14.455Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11453|2024-08-05T08:10:14.192Z -- siemens%20ag -- simatic%20step%207%20%28tia%20portal%29%20and%20wincc%20%28tia%20portal%29%20v10%2C%20v11%2C%20v12%2C%20simatic%20step%207%20%28tia%20portal%29%20and%20wincc%20%28tia%20portal%29%20v13%2C%20simatic%20step%207%20%28tia%20portal%29%20and%20wincc%20%28t
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11453</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC STEP 7 (TIA Portal) and WinCC (TIA Portal) V10, V11, V12 (All versions), SIMATIC STEP 7 (TIA Portal) and WinCC (TIA Portal) V13 (All versions &lt; V13 SP2 Update 2), SIMATIC STEP 7 (TIA Portal) and WinCC (TIA Portal) V14 (All versions &lt; V14 SP1 Update 6), SIMATIC STEP 7 (TIA Portal) and WinCC (TIA Portal) V15 (All versions &lt; V15 Update 2). Improper file permissions in the default installation of TIA Portal may allow an attacker with local file system access to insert specially crafted files which may prevent TIA Portal startup (Denial-of-Service) or lead to local code execution. No special privileges are required, but the victim needs to attempt to start TIA Portal after the manipulation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11453|2024-08-05T08:10:14.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11463|2024-08-05T08:10:14.230Z -- siemens%20ag -- sinumerik%20808d%20v4.7%2C%20sinumerik%20808d%20v4.8%2C%20sinumerik%20828d%20v4.7%2C%20sinumerik%20840d%20sl%20v4.7%2C%20sinumerik%20840d%20sl%20v4.8
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11463</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINUMERIK 808D V4.7 (All versions), SINUMERIK 808D V4.8 (All versions), SINUMERIK 828D V4.7 (All versions &lt; V4.7 SP6 HF1), SINUMERIK 840D sl V4.7 (All versions &lt; V4.7 SP6 HF5), SINUMERIK 840D sl V4.8 (All versions &lt; V4.8 SP3). A buffer overflow in the service command application could allow a local attacker to execute code with elevated privileges. The security vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker with local access to the affected systems. Successful exploitation requires user privileges but no user interaction. The vulnerability could allow an attacker to compromise confidentiality, integrity and availability of the system. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11463|2024-08-05T08:10:14.230Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-19281|2024-08-05T02:09:39.528Z -- siemens%20ag -- simatic%20et%20200sp%20open%20controller%20cpu%201515sp%20pc2%20%28incl.%20siplus%20variants%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-19281</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC ET 200SP Open Controller CPU 1515SP PC2 (incl. SIPLUS variants) (All versions &gt;= V2.5 and &lt; V20.8), SIMATIC S7-1500 CPU family (incl. related ET200 CPUs and SIPLUS variants) (All versions &gt;= V2.5 and &lt; V2.8), SIMATIC S7-1500 Software Controller (All versions &gt;= V2.5 and &lt; V20.8). Affected devices contain a vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated attacker to trigger a Denial-of-Service condition. The vulnerability can be triggered if specially crafted UDP packets are sent to the device. The security vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker with network access to the affected systems. Successful exploitation requires no system privileges and no user interaction. An attacker could use the vulnerability to compromise the device availability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-19281|2024-08-05T02:09:39.528Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 19:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4849|2024-08-05T05:18:26.561Z -- siemens%20ag -- siveillance%20vms%20video%20for%20android%2C%20siveillance%20vms%20video%20for%20ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4849</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in Siveillance VMS Video for Android (All versions &lt; V12.1a (2018 R1)), Siveillance VMS Video for iOS (All versions &lt; V12.1a (2018 R1)). Improper certificate validation could allow an attacker in a privileged network position to read data from and write data to the encrypted communication channel between the app and a server. The security vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker in a privileged network position which allows intercepting the communication channel between the affected app and a server (such as Man-in-the-Middle). Furthermore, an attacker must be able to generate a certificate that results for the validation algorithm in a checksum identical to a trusted certificate. Successful exploitation requires no user interaction. The vulnerability could allow reading data from and writing data to the encrypted communication channel between the app and a server, impacting the communication's confidentiality and integrity. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known. Siemens confirms the security vulnerability and provides mitigations to resolve the security issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4849|2024-08-05T05:18:26.561Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11451|2024-08-05T08:10:14.145Z -- siemens%20ag -- firmware%20variant%20iec%2061850%20for%20en100%20ethernet%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11451</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in Firmware variant IEC 61850 for EN100 Ethernet module (All versions &lt; V4.33), Firmware variant PROFINET IO for EN100 Ethernet module (All versions), Firmware variant Modbus TCP for EN100 Ethernet module (All versions), Firmware variant DNP3 TCP for EN100 Ethernet module (All versions), Firmware variant IEC104 for EN100 Ethernet module (All versions &lt; V1.22), SIPROTEC 5 relays with CPU variants CP300 and CP100 and the respective Ethernet communication modules (All versions &lt; V7.80), SIPROTEC 5 relays with CPU variants CP200 and the respective Ethernet communication modules (All versions &lt; V7.58). Specially crafted packets to port 102/tcp could cause a denial-of-service condition in the affected products. A manual restart is required to recover the EN100 module functionality of the affected devices. Successful exploitation requires an attacker with network access to send multiple packets to the affected products or modules. As a precondition the IEC 61850-MMS communication needs to be activated on the affected products or modules. No user interaction or privileges are required to exploit the vulnerability. The vulnerability could allow causing a Denial-of-Service condition of the network functionality of the device, compromising the availability of the system. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11451|2024-08-05T08:10:14.145Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4855|2024-08-05T05:18:26.644Z -- siemens%20ag -- siclock%20tc100%2C%20siclock%20tc400
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4855</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SICLOCK TC100 (All versions) and SICLOCK TC400 (All versions). Unencrypted storage of passwords in the client configuration files and during network transmission could allow an attacker in a privileged position to obtain access passwords.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4855|2024-08-05T05:18:26.644Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-18336|2024-08-05T01:54:14.382Z -- siemens%20ag -- simatic%20s7-300%20cpu%20family%20%28incl.%20related%20et200%20cpus%20and%20siplus%20variants%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-18336</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC S7-300 CPU family (incl. related ET200 CPUs and SIPLUS variants) (All versions &lt; V3.X.17), SIMATIC TDC CP51M1 (All versions &lt; V1.1.8), SIMATIC TDC CPU555 (All versions &lt; V1.1.1), SINUMERIK 840D sl (All versions &lt; V4.8.6), SINUMERIK 840D sl (All versions &lt; V4.94). Specially crafted packets sent to port 102/tcp (Profinet) could cause the affected device to go into defect mode. A restart is required in order to recover the system. Successful exploitation requires an attacker to have network access to port 102/tcp, with no authentication. No user interation is required. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-18336|2024-08-05T01:54:14.382Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 19:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11461|2024-08-05T08:10:14.628Z -- siemens%20ag -- sinumerik%20808d%20v4.7%2C%20sinumerik%20808d%20v4.8%2C%20sinumerik%20828d%20v4.7%2C%20sinumerik%20840d%20sl%20v4.7%2C%20sinumerik%20840d%20sl%20v4.8
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11461</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINUMERIK 808D V4.7 (All versions), SINUMERIK 808D V4.8 (All versions), SINUMERIK 828D V4.7 (All versions &lt; V4.7 SP6 HF1), SINUMERIK 840D sl V4.7 (All versions &lt; V4.7 SP6 HF5), SINUMERIK 840D sl V4.8 (All versions &lt; V4.8 SP3). A local attacker with user privileges could use the service command application for privilege escalation to an elevated user but not root. The security vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker with local access to the affected systems. Successful exploitation requires user privileges but no user interaction. The vulnerability could allow an attacker to compromise confidentiality, integrity and availability of the system. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11461|2024-08-05T08:10:14.628Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11454|2024-08-05T08:10:14.570Z -- siemens%20ag -- simatic%20step%207%20%28tia%20portal%29%20and%20wincc%20%28tia%20portal%29%20v10%2C%20v11%2C%20v12%2C%20simatic%20step%207%20%28tia%20portal%29%20and%20wincc%20%28tia%20portal%29%20v13%2C%20simatic%20step%207%20%28tia%20portal%29%20and%20wincc%20%28t
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11454</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC STEP 7 (TIA Portal) and WinCC (TIA Portal) V10, V11, V12 (All versions), SIMATIC STEP 7 (TIA Portal) and WinCC (TIA Portal) V13 (All versions &lt; V13 SP2 Update 2), SIMATIC STEP 7 (TIA Portal) and WinCC (TIA Portal) V14 (All versions &lt; V14 SP1 Update 6), SIMATIC STEP 7 (TIA Portal) and WinCC (TIA Portal) V15 (All versions &lt; V15 Update 2). Improper file permissions in the default installation of TIA Portal may allow an attacker with local file system access to manipulate resources which may be transferred to devices and executed there by a different user. No special privileges are required, but the victim needs to transfer the manipulated files to a device. Execution is caused on the target device rather than on the PG device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11454|2024-08-05T08:10:14.570Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11456|2024-08-05T08:10:14.363Z -- siemens%20ag -- automation%20license%20manager%205
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11456</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in Automation License Manager 5 (All versions &lt; 5.3.4.4). An attacker with network access to the device could send specially crafted network packets to determine whether or not a network port on another remote system is accessible or not. This allows the attacker to do basic network scanning using the victims machine. Successful exploitation requires a network connection to the affected device. The attacker does not need privileges, no user interaction is required. The impact is limited to determining whether or not a port on a target system is accessible by the affected device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11456|2024-08-05T08:10:14.363Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4853|2024-08-05T05:18:26.490Z -- siemens%20ag -- siclock%20tc100%2C%20siclock%20tc400
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4853</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SICLOCK TC100 (All versions) and SICLOCK TC400 (All versions). An attacker with network access to port 69/udp could modify the firmware of the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4853|2024-08-05T05:18:26.490Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13800|2024-08-05T09:14:47.114Z -- siemens%20ag -- simatic%20s7-1200%20cpu%20family%20version%204
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13800</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC S7-1200 CPU family version 4 (All versions &lt; V4.2.3). The web interface could allow a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) attack if an unsuspecting user is tricked into accessing a malicious link. Successful exploitation requires user interaction by a legitimate user, who must be authenticated to the web interface. A successful attack could allow an attacker to trigger actions via the web interface that the legitimate user is allowed to perform. This could allow the attacker to read or modify parts of the device configuration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13800|2024-08-05T09:14:47.114Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13811|2024-08-05T09:14:47.273Z -- siemens%20ag -- simatic%20step%207%20%28tia%20portal%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13811</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC STEP 7 (TIA Portal) (All Versions &lt; V15.1). Password hashes with insufficient computational effort could allow an attacker to access to a project file and reconstruct passwords. The vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker with local access to the project file. No user interaction is required to exploit the vulnerability. The vulnerability could allow the attacker to obtain certain passwords from the project. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13811|2024-08-05T09:14:47.273Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4841|2024-08-05T05:18:26.477Z -- siemens%20ag -- tim%201531%20irc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4841</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in TIM 1531 IRC (All versions &lt; V1.1). A remote attacker with network access to port 80/tcp or port 443/tcp could perform administrative operations on the device without prior authentication. Successful exploitation could allow to cause a denial-of-service, or read and manipulate data as well as configuration settings of the affected device. At the stage of publishing this security advisory no public exploitation is known. Siemens provides mitigations to resolve it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4841|2024-08-05T05:18:26.477Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13807|2024-08-05T09:14:47.207Z -- siemens%20ag -- scalance%20x300%2C%20scalance%20x408%2C%20scalance%20x414
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13807</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE X300 (All versions &lt; V4.0.0), SCALANCE X408 (All versions &lt; V4.0.0), SCALANCE X414 (All versions). The web interface on port 443/tcp could allow an attacker to cause a Denial-of-Service condition by sending specially crafted packets to the web server. The device will automatically reboot, impacting network availability for other devices. An attacker must have network access to port 443/tcp to exploit the vulnerability. Neither valid credentials nor interaction by a legitimate user is required to exploit the vulnerability. There is no confidentiality or integrity impact, only availability is temporarily impacted. This vulnerability could be triggered by publicly available tools.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13807|2024-08-05T09:14:47.207Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13802|2024-08-05T09:14:47.316Z -- siemens%20ag -- rox%20ii
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13802</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in ROX II (All versions &lt; V2.12.1). An authenticated attacker with a high-privileged user account access via SSH could circumvent restrictions in place and execute arbitrary operating system commands. Successful exploitation requires that the attacker has network access to the SSH interface in on port 22/tcp. The attacker must be authenticated to exploit the vulnerability. The vulnerability could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13802|2024-08-05T09:14:47.316Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4856|2024-08-05T05:18:26.641Z -- siemens%20ag -- siclock%20tc100%2C%20siclock%20tc400
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4856</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SICLOCK TC100 (All versions) and SICLOCK TC400 (All versions). An attacker with administrative access to the device's management interface could lock out legitimate users. Manual interaction is required to restore the access of legitimate users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4856|2024-08-05T05:18:26.641Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13815|2024-08-05T09:14:47.135Z -- siemens%20ag -- simatic%20s7-1200%2C%20simatic%20s7-1500
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13815</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC S7-1200 (All versions), SIMATIC S7-1500 (All Versions &lt; V2.6). An attacker could exhaust the available connection pool of an affected device by opening a sufficient number of connections to the device. Successful exploitation requires an attacker to be able to send packets to port 102/tcp of the affected device. No user interaction and no user privileges are required to exploit the vulnerability. The vulnerability, if exploited, could cause a Denial-of-Service condition impacting the availability of the system. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13815|2024-08-05T09:14:47.135Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11457|2024-08-05T08:10:14.429Z -- siemens%20ag -- sinumerik%20828d%20v4.7%2C%20sinumerik%20840d%20sl%20v4.7%2C%20sinumerik%20840d%20sl%20v4.8
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11457</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINUMERIK 828D V4.7 (All versions &lt; V4.7 SP6 HF1), SINUMERIK 840D sl V4.7 (All versions &lt; V4.7 SP6 HF5), SINUMERIK 840D sl V4.8 (All versions &lt; V4.8 SP3). The integrated web server on port 4842/tcp of the affected products could allow a remote attacker to execute code with privileged permissions on the system by sending specially crafted network requests to port 4842/tcp. Please note that this vulnerability is only exploitable if port 4842/tcp is manually opened in the firewall configuration of network port X130. The security vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker with network access to the affected devices on port 4842/tcp. Successful exploitation requires no privileges and no user interaction. The vulnerability could allow an attacker to compromise confidentiality, integrity and availability of the web server. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11457|2024-08-05T08:10:14.429Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-12736|2024-08-05T18:43:56.622Z -- siemens%20ag -- ruggedcom%20ros%20for%20rsl910%20devices%2C%20ruggedcom%20ros%20for%20all%20other%20devices%2C%20scalance%20xb-200%2Fxc-200%2Fxp-200%2Fxr300-wg%2C%20scalance%20xr-500%2Fxm-400
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-12736</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM ROS for RSL910 devices (All versions &lt; ROS V5.0.1), RUGGEDCOM ROS for all other devices (All versions &lt; ROS V4.3.4), SCALANCE XB-200/XC-200/XP-200/XR300-WG (All versions between V3.0 (including) and V3.0.2 (excluding)), SCALANCE XR-500/XM-400 (All versions between V6.1 (including) and V6.1.1 (excluding)). After initial configuration, the Ruggedcom Discovery Protocol (RCDP) is still able to writeto the device under certain conditions, potentially allowing users located in the adjacentnetwork of the targeted device to perform unauthorized administrative actions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-12736|2024-08-05T18:43:56.622Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13812|2024-08-05T09:14:47.285Z -- siemens%20ag -- simatic%20hmi%20comfort%20panels%204%22%20-%2022%22%2C%20simatic%20hmi%20comfort%20outdoor%20panels%207%22%20%26%2015%22%2C%20simatic%20hmi%20ktp%20mobile%20panels%20ktp400f%2C%20ktp700%2C%20ktp700f%2C%20ktp900%20und%20ktp900f%2C%20simatic%20wincc%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13812</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC HMI Comfort Panels 4" - 22" (All versions &lt; V15 Update 4), SIMATIC HMI Comfort Outdoor Panels 7" &amp; 15" (All versions &lt; V15 Update 4), SIMATIC HMI KTP Mobile Panels KTP400F, KTP700, KTP700F, KTP900 and KTP900F (All versions &lt; V15 Update 4), SIMATIC WinCC Runtime Advanced (All versions &lt; V15 Update 4), SIMATIC WinCC Runtime Professional (All versions &lt; V15 Update 4), SIMATIC WinCC (TIA Portal) (All versions &lt; V15 Update 4), SIMATIC HMI Classic Devices (TP/MP/OP/MP Mobile Panel) (All versions). A directory traversal vulnerability could allow to download arbitrary files from the device. The security vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker with network access to the integrated web server. No user interaction and no authentication is required to exploit the vulnerability. The vulnerability impacts the confidentiality of the device. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13812|2024-08-05T09:14:47.285Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11449|2024-08-05T08:10:14.043Z -- siemens%20ag -- scalance%20m875
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11449</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE M875 (All versions). An attacker with access to the local file system might obtain passwords for administrative users. Successful exploitation requires read access to files on the local file system. A successful attack could allow an attacker to obtain administrative passwords. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11449|2024-08-05T08:10:14.043Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13798|2024-08-05T09:14:47.237Z -- siemens%20ag -- sicam%20a8000%20cp-8000%2C%20sicam%20a8000%20cp-802x%2C%20sicam%20a8000%20cp-8050
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13798</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SICAM A8000 CP-8000 (All versions &lt; V14), SICAM A8000 CP-802X (All versions &lt; V14), SICAM A8000 CP-8050 (All versions &lt; V2.00). Specially crafted network packets sent to port 80/TCP or 443/TCP could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to cause a Denial-of-Service condition of the web server. The security vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker with network access to the affected systems on port 80/TCP or 443/TCP. Successful exploitation requires no system privileges and no user interaction. An attacker could use the vulnerability to compromise availability of the web server. A system reboot is required to recover the web service of the device. At the time of advisory update, exploit code for this security vulnerability is public.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13798|2024-08-05T09:14:47.237Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 18:48:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13799|2024-08-05T09:14:47.217Z -- siemens%20ag -- simatic%20wincc%20oa%20v3.14%20and%20prior
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13799</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC WinCC OA V3.14 and prior (All versions &lt; V3.14-P021). Improper access control to a data point of the affected product could allow an unauthenticated remote user to escalate its privileges in the context of SIMATIC WinCC OA V3.14. This vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker with network access to port 5678/TCP of the SIMATIC WinCC OA V3.14 server. Successful exploitation requires no user privileges and no user interaction. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to compromise integrity and availability of the SIMATIC WinCC OA system. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13799|2024-08-05T09:14:47.217Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4861|2024-08-05T05:18:26.540Z -- siemens%20ag -- scalance%20m875
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4861</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE M875 (All versions). An authenticated remote attacker with access to the web interface (443/tcp), could potentially read and download arbitrary files from the device's file system. Successful exploitation requires that the attacker has network access to the web interface. The attacker must be authenticated as administrative user to exploit the security vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4861|2024-08-05T05:18:26.540Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4859|2024-08-05T05:18:26.563Z -- siemens%20ag -- scalance%20m875
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4859</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE M875 (All versions). An authenticated remote attacker with access to the web interface (443/tcp), could execute arbitrary operating system commands. Successful exploitation requires that the attacker has network access to the web interface. The attacker must be authenticated as administrative user to exploit the security vulnerability. The vulnerability could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code on the device. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4859|2024-08-05T05:18:26.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-16555|2024-08-05T10:24:32.846Z -- siemens%20ag -- scalance%20s602%2C%20scalance%20s612%2C%20scalance%20s623%2C%20scalance%20s627-2m
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-16555</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE S602 (All versions &lt; V4.0.1.1), SCALANCE S612 (All versions &lt; V4.0.1.1), SCALANCE S623 (All versions &lt; V4.0.1.1), SCALANCE S627-2M (All versions &lt; V4.0.1.1). The integrated web server could allow Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attacks if unsuspecting users are tricked into accessing a malicious link. User interaction is required for a successful exploitation. The user must be logged into the web interface in order for the exploitation to succeed. At the stage of publishing this security advisory no public exploitation is known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-16555|2024-08-05T10:24:32.846Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4860|2024-08-05T05:18:26.494Z -- siemens%20ag -- scalance%20m875
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4860</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE M875 (All versions). An authenticated remote attacker with access to the web interface (443/tcp), could execute arbitrary operating system commands. Successful exploitation requires that the attacker has network access to the web interface. The attacker must be authenticated as administrative user to exploit the security vulnerability. The vulnerability could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code on the device. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4860|2024-08-05T05:18:26.494Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13804|2024-08-05T09:14:47.168Z -- siemens%20ag -- simatic%20it%20lms%2C%20simatic%20it%20production%20suite%2C%20simatic%20it%20ua%20discrete%20manufacturing%2C%20simatic%20it%20ua%20discrete%20manufacturing%2C%20simatic%20it%20ua%20discrete%20manufacturing%2C%20simatic%20it%20ua%20discrete%20manufa
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13804</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC IT LMS (All versions), SIMATIC IT Production Suite (Versions V7.1 &lt; V7.1 Upd3), SIMATIC IT UA Discrete Manufacturing (Versions &lt; V1.2), SIMATIC IT UA Discrete Manufacturing (Versions V1.2), SIMATIC IT UA Discrete Manufacturing (Versions V1.3), SIMATIC IT UA Discrete Manufacturing (Versions V2.3), SIMATIC IT UA Discrete Manufacturing (Versions V2.4). An attacker with network access to the installation could bypass the application-level authentication. In order to exploit the vulnerability, an attacker must obtain network access to an affected installation and must obtain a valid username to the system. Successful exploitation requires no user privileges and no user interaction. The vulnerability could allow an attacker to compromise confidentiality, integrity and availability of the system. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13804|2024-08-05T09:14:47.168Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4837|2024-08-05T05:18:26.525Z -- siemens%20ag -- telecontrol%20server%20basic
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4837</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in TeleControl Server Basic &lt; V3.1. An attacker with access to the TeleControl Server Basic's webserver (port 80/tcp or 443/tcp) could cause a Denial-of-Service condition on the web server. The remaining functionality of the TeleControl Server Basic is not affected by the Denial-of-Service condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4837|2024-08-05T05:18:26.525Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13816|2024-08-05T09:14:47.170Z -- siemens%20ag -- tim%201531%20irc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13816</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in TIM 1531 IRC (All version &lt; V2.0). The devices was missing proper authentication on port 102/tcp, although configured. Successful exploitation requires an attacker to be able to send packets to port 102/tcp of the affected device. No user interaction and no user privileges are required to exploit the vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13816|2024-08-05T09:14:47.170Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4845|2024-08-05T05:18:26.591Z -- siemens%20ag -- rapidlab%201200%20systems%20%2F%20rapidpoint%20400%20systems%20%2F%20rapidpoint%20500%20systems%2C%20rapidlab%201200%20series%2C%20rapidpoint%20500%20systems%2C%20rapidpoint%20500%20systems%2C%20rapidpoint%20500%20systems%2C%20rapidpoint%20400%20syst
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4845</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in RAPIDLab 1200 systems / RAPIDPoint 400 systems / RAPIDPoint 500 systems (All versions_without_ use of Siemens Healthineers Informatics products), RAPIDLab 1200 Series (All versions &lt; V3.3 _with_ Siemens Healthineers Informatics products), RAPIDPoint 500 systems (All versions &gt;= V3.0 _with_ Siemens Healthineers Informatics products), RAPIDPoint 500 systems (V2.4.X_with_ Siemens Healthineers Informatics products), RAPIDPoint 500 systems (All versions =&lt; V2.3 _with_ Siemens Healthineers Informatics products), RAPIDPoint 400 systems (All versions _with_ Siemens Healthineers Informatics products). Remote attackers with either local or remote credentialed access to the "Remote View" feature might be able to elevate their privileges, compromising confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the system. No special skills or user interaction are required to perform this attack. At the time of advisory publication, no public exploitation of this security vulnerability is known. Siemens Healthineers confirms the security vulnerability and provides mitigations to resolve the security issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4845|2024-08-05T05:18:26.591Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11448|2024-08-05T08:10:14.315Z -- siemens%20ag -- scalance%20m875
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11448</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE M875 (All versions). The web interface on port 443/tcp could allow a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attack if an unsuspecting user is tricked into accessing a malicious link. Successful exploitation requires that the attacker has access to the web interface of an affected device. The attacker must be authenticated as administrative user on the web interface. Afterwards, a legitimate user must access the web interface. A successful attack could allow an attacker to execute malicious code in the browser of a legitimate user. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11448|2024-08-05T08:10:14.315Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11466|2024-08-05T08:10:14.337Z -- siemens%20ag -- sinumerik%20808d%20v4.7%2C%20sinumerik%20808d%20v4.8%2C%20sinumerik%20828d%20v4.7%2C%20sinumerik%20840d%20sl%20v4.7%2C%20sinumerik%20840d%20sl%20v4.8
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11466</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINUMERIK 808D V4.7 (All versions), SINUMERIK 808D V4.8 (All versions), SINUMERIK 828D V4.7 (All versions &lt; V4.7 SP6 HF1), SINUMERIK 840D sl V4.7 (All versions &lt; V4.7 SP6 HF5), SINUMERIK 840D sl V4.8 (All versions &lt; V4.8 SP3). Specially crafted network packets sent to port 102/tcp (ISO-TSAP) could allow a remote attacker to either cause a Denial-of-Service condition of the integrated software firewall or allow to execute code in the context of the software firewall. The security vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker with network access to the affected systems on port 102/tcp. Successful exploitation requires no user privileges and no user interaction. The vulnerability could allow an attacker to compromise confidentiality, integrity and availability of the system. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11466|2024-08-05T08:10:14.337Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11452|2024-08-05T08:10:14.304Z -- siemens%20ag -- firmware%20variant%20iec%2061850%20for%20en100%20ethernet%20module
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11452</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in Firmware variant IEC 61850 for EN100 Ethernet module (All versions &lt; V4.33), Firmware variant PROFINET IO for EN100 Ethernet module (All versions), Firmware variant Modbus TCP for EN100 Ethernet module (All versions), Firmware variant DNP3 TCP for EN100 Ethernet module (All versions), Firmware variant IEC104 for EN100 Ethernet module (All versions &lt; V1.22). Specially crafted packets to port 102/tcp could cause a denial-of-service condition in the EN100 communication module if oscillographs are running. A manual restart is required to recover the EN100 module functionality. Successful exploitation requires an attacker with network access to send multiple packets to the EN100 module. As a precondition the IEC 61850-MMS communication needs to be activated on the affected EN100 modules. No user interaction or privileges are required to exploit the security vulnerability. The vulnerability could allow causing a Denial-of-Service condition of the network functionality of the device, compromising the availability of the system. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11452|2024-08-05T08:10:14.304Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4846|2024-08-05T05:18:26.455Z -- siemens%20ag -- rapidlab%201200%20systems%20rapidpoint%20400%20systems%20rapidpoint%20500%20systems%20rapidlab%201200%20series%20rapidpoint%20500%20systems%20rapidpoint%20500%20systems%20rapidpoint%20500%20systems%20rapidpoint%20400%20systems
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4846</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in RAPIDLab 1200 systems / RAPIDPoint 400 systems / RAPIDPoint 500 systems (All versions_without_ use of Siemens Healthineers Informatics products), RAPIDLab 1200 Series (All versions &lt; V3.3 _with_ Siemens Healthineers Informatics products), RAPIDPoint 500 systems (All versions &gt;= V3.0 _with_ Siemens Healthineers Informatics products), RAPIDPoint 500 systems (V2.4.X_with_ Siemens Healthineers Informatics products), RAPIDPoint 500 systems (All versions =&lt; V2.3 _with_ Siemens Healthineers Informatics products), RAPIDPoint 400 systems (All versions _with_ Siemens Healthineers Informatics products). A factory account with hardcoded password might allow attackers access to the device over port 5900/tcp. Successful exploitation requires no user interaction or privileges and impacts the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the affected device. At the time of advisory publication, no public exploitation of this security vulnerability is known. Siemens Healthineers confirms the security vulnerability and provides mitigations to resolve the security issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4846|2024-08-05T05:18:26.455Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13806|2024-08-05T09:14:47.230Z -- siemens%20ag -- siemens%20td%20keypad%20designer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13806</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIEMENS TD Keypad Designer (All versions). A DLL hijacking vulnerability exists in all versions of SIEMENS TD Keypad Designer which could allow an attacker to execute code with the permission of the user running TD Designer. The attacker must have write access to the directory containing the TD project file in order to exploit the vulnerability. A legitimate user with higher privileges than the attacker must open the TD project in order for this vulnerability to be exploited. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13806|2024-08-05T09:14:47.230Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11460|2024-08-05T08:10:14.579Z -- siemens%20ag -- sinumerik%20808d%20v4.7%2C%20sinumerik%20808d%20v4.8%2C%20sinumerik%20828d%20v4.7%2C%20sinumerik%20840d%20sl%20v4.7%2C%20sinumerik%20840d%20sl%20v4.8
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11460</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINUMERIK 808D V4.7 (All versions), SINUMERIK 808D V4.8 (All versions), SINUMERIK 828D V4.7 (All versions &lt; V4.7 SP6 HF1), SINUMERIK 840D sl V4.7 (All versions &lt; V4.7 SP6 HF5), SINUMERIK 840D sl V4.8 (All versions &lt; V4.8 SP3). A local attacker with elevated user privileges (manufact) could modify a CRAMFS archive so that after reboot the system loads the modified CRAMFS file and attacker-controlled code is executed with root privileges. The security vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker with local access to the affected systems. Successful exploitation requires elevated user privileges (manufact) but no user interaction. The vulnerability could allow an attacker to compromise confidentiality, integrity and availability of the system. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11460|2024-08-05T08:10:14.579Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4838|2024-08-05T05:18:26.631Z -- siemens%20ag -- en100%20ethernet%20module%20iec%2061850%20variant
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4838</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in EN100 Ethernet module IEC 61850 variant (All versions &lt; V4.30), EN100 Ethernet module DNP3 variant (All versions &lt; V1.04), EN100 Ethernet module PROFINET IO variant (All versions), EN100 Ethernet module Modbus TCP variant (All versions), EN100 Ethernet module IEC 104 variant (All versions &lt; V1.22). The web interface (TCP/80) of affected devices allows an unauthenticated user to upgrade or downgrade the firmware of the device, including to older versions with known vulnerabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4838|2024-08-05T05:18:26.631Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13813|2024-08-05T09:14:47.263Z -- siemens%20ag -- simatic%20hmi%20comfort%20panels%204%22%20-%2022%22%2C%20simatic%20hmi%20comfort%20outdoor%20panels%207%22%20%26%2015%22%2C%20simatic%20hmi%20ktp%20mobile%20panels%20ktp400f%2C%20ktp700%2C%20ktp700f%2C%20ktp900%20und%20ktp900f%2C%20simatic%20wincc%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13813</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC HMI Comfort Panels 4" - 22" (All versions &lt; V15 Update 4), SIMATIC HMI Comfort Outdoor Panels 7" &amp; 15" (All versions &lt; V15 Update 4), SIMATIC HMI KTP Mobile Panels KTP400F, KTP700, KTP700F, KTP900 and KTP900F (All versions &lt; V15 Update 4), SIMATIC WinCC Runtime Advanced (All versions &lt; V15 Update 4), SIMATIC WinCC Runtime Professional (All versions &lt; V15 Update 4), SIMATIC WinCC (TIA Portal) (All versions &lt; V15 Update 4), SIMATIC HMI Classic Devices (TP/MP/OP/MP Mobile Panel) (All versions). The webserver of affected HMI devices may allow URL redirections to untrusted websites. An attacker must trick a valid user who is authenticated to the device into clicking on a malicious link to exploit the vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13813|2024-08-05T09:14:47.263Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11455|2024-08-05T08:10:14.446Z -- siemens%20ag -- automation%20license%20manager%205%2C%20automation%20license%20manager%206
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11455</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in Automation License Manager 5 (All versions &lt; 5.3.4.4), Automation License Manager 6 (All versions &lt; 6.0.1). A directory traversal vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to move arbitrary files, which can result in code execution, compromising confidentiality, integrity and availability of the system. Successful exploitation requires a network connection to the affected device. The attacker does not need privileges or special conditions of the system, but user interaction is required.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11455|2024-08-05T08:10:14.446Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4844|2024-08-05T05:18:26.503Z -- siemens%20ag -- simatic%20wincc%20oa%20ui%20for%20android%2C%20simatic%20wincc%20oa%20ui%20for%20ios
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4844</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC WinCC OA UI for Android (All versions &lt; V3.15.10), SIMATIC WinCC OA UI for iOS (All versions &lt; V3.15.10). Insufficient limitation of CONTROL script capabilities could allow read and write access from one HMI project cache folder to other HMI project cache folders within the app's sandbox on the same mobile device. This includes HMI project cache folders of other configured WinCC OA servers. The security vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker who tricks an app user to connect to an attacker-controlled WinCC OA server. Successful exploitation requires user interaction and read/write access to the app's folder on a mobile device. The vulnerability could allow reading data from and writing data to the app's folder. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known. Siemens confirms the security vulnerability and provides mitigations to resolve the security issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4844|2024-08-05T05:18:26.503Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-19277|2024-08-05T02:09:39.511Z -- siemens%20ag -- siport%20mp
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-19277</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIPORT MP (All versions &lt; 3.1.4). Vulnerable versions of the device allow the creation of special accounts ("service users") with administrative privileges that could enable a remote authenticated attacker to perform actions that are not visible to other users of the system, such as granting persons access to a secured area.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-19277|2024-08-05T02:09:39.511Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 19:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4835|2024-08-05T05:18:26.203Z -- siemens%20ag -- telecontrol%20server%20basic
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4835</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in TeleControl Server Basic &lt; V3.1. An attacker with network access to the TeleControl Server Basic's port 8000/tcp could bypass the authentication mechanism and read limited information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4835|2024-08-05T05:18:26.203Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4847|2024-08-05T05:18:26.463Z -- siemens%20ag -- simatic%20wincc%20oa%20operator%20ios%20app
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4847</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC WinCC OA Operator iOS App (All versions &lt; V1.4). Insufficient protection of sensitive information (e.g. session key for accessing server) in Siemens WinCC OA Operator iOS app could allow an attacker with physical access to the mobile device to read unencrypted data from the app's directory. Siemens provides mitigations to resolve the security issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4847|2024-08-05T05:18:26.463Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4858|2024-08-05T05:18:26.715Z -- siemens%20ag -- iec%2061850%20system%20configurator%2C%20digsi%205%20%28affected%20as%20iec%2061850%20system%20configurator%20is%20incorporated%29%2C%20digsi%204%2C%20sicam%20pas%2Fpqs%2C%20sicam%20pq%20analyzer%2C%20sicam%20scc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4858</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in IEC 61850 system configurator (All versions &lt; V5.80), DIGSI 5 (affected as IEC 61850 system configurator is incorporated) (All versions &lt; V7.80), DIGSI 4 (All versions &lt; V4.93), SICAM PAS/PQS (All versions &lt; V8.11), SICAM PQ Analyzer (All versions &lt; V3.11), SICAM SCC (All versions &lt; V9.02 HF3). A service of the affected products listening on all of the host's network interfaces on either port 4884/TCP, 5885/TCP, or port 5886/TCP could allow an attacker to either exfiltrate limited data from the system or to execute code with Microsoft Windows user permissions. Successful exploitation requires an attacker to be able to send a specially crafted network request to the vulnerable service and a user interacting with the service's client application on the host. In order to execute arbitrary code with Microsoft Windows user permissions, an attacker must be able to plant the code in advance on the host by other means. The vulnerability has limited impact to confidentiality and integrity of the affected system. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known. Siemens confirms the security vulnerability and provides mitigations to resolve the security issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4858|2024-08-05T05:18:26.715Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-19279|2024-08-05T02:09:39.609Z -- siemens%20ag -- siprotec%204%20and%20siprotec%20compact%20relays%20equipped%20with%20en100%20ethernet%20communication%20modules
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-19279</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIPROTEC 4 and SIPROTEC Compact relays equipped with EN100 Ethernet communication modules (All versions). Specially crafted packets sent to port 50000/UDP of the EN100 Ethernet communication modules could cause a Denial-of-Service of the affected device. A manual reboot is required to recover the service of the device. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known to Siemens.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-19279|2024-08-05T02:09:39.609Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 19:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11465|2024-08-05T08:10:14.330Z -- siemens%20ag -- sinumerik%20808d%20v4.7%2C%20sinumerik%20808d%20v4.8%2C%20sinumerik%20828d%20v4.7%2C%20sinumerik%20840d%20sl%20v4.7%2C%20sinumerik%20840d%20sl%20v4.8
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11465</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINUMERIK 808D V4.7 (All versions), SINUMERIK 808D V4.8 (All versions), SINUMERIK 828D V4.7 (All versions &lt; V4.7 SP6 HF1), SINUMERIK 840D sl V4.7 (All versions &lt; V4.7 SP6 HF5), SINUMERIK 840D sl V4.8 (All versions &lt; V4.8 SP3). A local attacker could use ioctl calls to do out of bounds reads, arbitrary writes, or execute code in kernel mode. The security vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker with local access to the affected systems. Successful exploitation requires user privileges but no user interaction. The vulnerability could allow an attacker to compromise confidentiality, integrity and availability of the system. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11465|2024-08-05T08:10:14.330Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-6865|2024-08-05T15:41:17.697Z -- siemens%20ag -- primary%20setup%20tool%20%28pst%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-6865</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in Primary Setup Tool (PST) (All versions &lt; V4.2 HF1), SIMATIC Automation Tool (All versions &lt; V3.0), SIMATIC NET PC-Software (All versions &lt; V14 SP1), SIMATIC PCS 7 V8.1 (All versions), SIMATIC PCS 7 V8.2 (All versions &lt; V8.2 SP1), SIMATIC STEP 7 (TIA Portal) V13 (All versions &lt; V13 SP2), SIMATIC STEP 7 (TIA Portal) V14 (All versions &lt; V14 SP1), SIMATIC STEP 7 V5.X (All versions &lt; V5.6), SIMATIC WinAC RTX 2010 SP2 (All versions), SIMATIC WinAC RTX F 2010 SP2 (All versions), SIMATIC WinCC (TIA Portal) V13 (All versions &lt; V13 SP2), SIMATIC WinCC (TIA Portal) V14 (All versions &lt; V14 SP1), SIMATIC WinCC V7.2 and prior (All versions), SIMATIC WinCC V7.3 (All versions &lt; V7.3 Update 15), SIMATIC WinCC V7.4 (All versions &lt; V7.4 SP1 Upd1), SIMATIC WinCC flexible 2008 (All versions &lt; flexible 2008 SP5), SINAUT ST7CC (All versions installed in conjunction with SIMATIC WinCC &lt; V7.3 Update 15), SINEMA Server (All versions &lt; V14), SINUMERIK 808D Programming Tool (All versions &lt; V4.7 SP4 HF2), SMART PC Access (All versions &lt; V2.3), STEP 7 - Micro/WIN SMART (All versions &lt; V2.3), Security Configuration Tool (SCT) (All versions &lt; V5.0). Specially crafted PROFINET DCP broadcast packets sent to the affected products on a local Ethernet segment (Layer 2) could cause a Denial-of-Service condition of some services. The services require manual restart to recover.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-6865|2024-08-05T15:41:17.697Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2017 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11458|2024-08-05T08:10:14.359Z -- siemens%20ag -- sinumerik%20828d%20v4.7%2C%20sinumerik%20840d%20sl%20v4.7%2C%20sinumerik%20840d%20sl%20v4.8
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11458</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINUMERIK 828D V4.7 (All versions &lt; V4.7 SP6 HF1), SINUMERIK 840D sl V4.7 (All versions &lt; V4.7 SP6 HF5), SINUMERIK 840D sl V4.8 (All versions &lt; V4.8 SP3). The integrated VNC server on port 5900/tcp of the affected products could allow a remote attacker to execute code with privileged permissions on the system by sending specially crafted network requests to port 5900/tcp. Please note that this vulnerability is only exploitable if port 5900/tcp is manually opened in the firewall configuration of network port X130. The security vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker with network access to the affected devices and port. Successful exploitation requires no privileges and no user interaction. The vulnerability could allow an attacker to compromise confidentiality, integrity and availability of the VNC server. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11458|2024-08-05T08:10:14.359Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4836|2024-08-05T05:18:26.576Z -- siemens%20ag -- telecontrol%20server%20basic
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4836</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in TeleControl Server Basic &lt; V3.1. An authenticated attacker with a low-privileged account to the TeleControl Server Basic's port 8000/tcp could escalate his privileges and perform administrative operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4836|2024-08-05T05:18:26.576Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11450|2024-08-05T08:10:14.153Z -- siemens%20ag -- siemens%20plm%20software%20teamcenter
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11450</link>
      <description>A reflected Cross-Site-Scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been identified in Siemens PLM Software TEAMCENTER (V9.1.2.5). If a user visits the login portal through the URL crafted by the attacker, the attacker can insert html/javascript and thus alter/rewrite the login portal page. Siemens PLM Software TEAMCENTER V9.1.3 and newer are not affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11450|2024-08-05T08:10:14.153Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4851|2024-08-05T05:18:26.689Z -- siemens%20ag -- siclock%20tc100%2C%20siclock%20tc400
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4851</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SICLOCK TC100 (All versions) and SICLOCK TC400 (All versions). An attacker with network access to the device could cause a Denial-of-Service condition by sending certain packets to the device, causing potential reboots of the device. The core functionality of the device could be impacted. The time serving functionality recovers when time synchronization with GPS devices or other NTP servers are completed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4851|2024-08-05T05:18:26.689Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4854|2024-08-05T05:18:26.578Z -- siemens%20ag -- siclock%20tc100%2C%20siclock%20tc400
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4854</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SICLOCK TC100 (All versions) and SICLOCK TC400 (All versions). An attacker with network access to port 69/udp could modify the administrative client stored on the device. If a legitimate user downloads and executes the modified client from the affected device, then he/she could obtain code execution on the client system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4854|2024-08-05T05:18:26.578Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13814|2024-08-05T09:14:47.244Z -- siemens%20ag -- simatic%20hmi%20comfort%20panels%204%22%20-%2022%22%2C%20simatic%20hmi%20comfort%20outdoor%20panels%207%22%20%26%2015%22%2C%20simatic%20hmi%20ktp%20mobile%20panels%20ktp400f%2C%20ktp700%2C%20ktp700f%2C%20ktp900%20und%20ktp900f%2C%20simatic%20wincc%20
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13814</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC HMI Comfort Panels 4" - 22" (All versions &lt; V14), SIMATIC HMI Comfort Outdoor Panels 7" &amp; 15" (All versions &lt; V14), SIMATIC HMI KTP Mobile Panels KTP400F, KTP700, KTP700F, KTP900 and KTP900F (All versions &lt; V14), SIMATIC WinCC Runtime Advanced (All versions &lt; V14), SIMATIC WinCC Runtime Professional (All versions &lt; V14), SIMATIC WinCC (TIA Portal) (All versions &lt; V14), SIMATIC HMI Classic Devices (TP/MP/OP/MP Mobile Panel) (All versions). The integrated web server (port 80/tcp and port 443/tcp) of the affected devices could allow an attacker to inject HTTP headers. An attacker must trick a valid user who is authenticated to the device into clicking on a malicious link to exploit the vulnerability. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13814|2024-08-05T09:14:47.244Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11464|2024-08-05T08:10:14.565Z -- siemens%20ag -- sinumerik%20828d%20v4.7%2C%20sinumerik%20840d%20sl%20v4.7%2C%20sinumerik%20840d%20sl%20v4.8
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11464</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINUMERIK 828D V4.7 (All versions &lt; V4.7 SP6 HF1), SINUMERIK 840D sl V4.7 (All versions &lt; V4.7 SP6 HF5), SINUMERIK 840D sl V4.8 (All versions &lt; V4.8 SP3). The integrated VNC server on port 5900/tcp of the affected products could allow a remote attacker to cause a Denial-of-Service condition of the VNC server. Please note that this vulnerability is only exploitable if port 5900/tcp is manually opened in the firewall configuration of network port X130. The security vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker with network access to the affected devices and port. Successful exploitation requires no privileges and no user interaction. The vulnerability could allow an attacker to compromise availability of the VNC server. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11464|2024-08-05T08:10:14.565Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11462|2024-08-05T08:10:14.563Z -- siemens%20ag -- sinumerik%20808d%20v4.7%2C%20sinumerik%20808d%20v4.8%2C%20sinumerik%20828d%20v4.7%2C%20sinumerik%20840d%20sl%20v4.7%2C%20sinumerik%20840d%20sl%20v4.8
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11462</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINUMERIK 808D V4.7 (All versions), SINUMERIK 808D V4.8 (All versions), SINUMERIK 828D V4.7 (All versions &lt; V4.7 SP6 HF1), SINUMERIK 840D sl V4.7 (All versions &lt; V4.7 SP6 HF5), SINUMERIK 840D sl V4.8 (All versions &lt; V4.8 SP3). By sending a specially crafted authentication request to the affected systems a remote attacker could escalate his privileges to an elevated user account but not to root. The security vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker with network access to the affected systems. Successful exploitation requires no privileges and no user interaction. The vulnerability could allow an attacker to compromise confidentiality, integrity and availability of the system. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11462|2024-08-05T08:10:14.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4850|2024-08-05T05:18:26.561Z -- siemens%20ag -- simatic%20s7-400%20%28incl.%20f%29%20cpu%20hardware%20version%204.0%20and%20below%2C%20simatic%20s7-400%20%28incl.%20f%29%20cpu%20hardware%20version%205.0%2C%20simatic%20s7-400h%20cpu%20hardware%20version%204.5%20and%20below
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4850</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC S7-400 (incl. F) CPU hardware version 4.0 and below (All versions), SIMATIC S7-400 (incl. F) CPU hardware version 5.0 (All firmware versions &lt; V5.2), SIMATIC S7-400H CPU hardware version 4.5 and below (All versions). The affected CPUs improperly validate S7 communication packets which could cause a Denial-of-Service condition of the CPU. The CPU will remain in DEFECT mode until manual restart.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4850|2024-08-05T05:18:26.561Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-13805|2024-08-05T09:14:47.124Z -- siemens%20ag -- simatic%20et%20200sp%20open%20controller
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-13805</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC ET 200SP Open Controller (All versions &gt;= V2.0 and &lt; V2.1.6), SIMATIC S7-1500 Software Controller (All versions &gt;= V2.0 and &lt; V2.5), SIMATIC S7-1500 incl. F (All versions &gt;= V2.0 and &lt; V2.5). An attacker can cause a denial-of-service condition on the network stack by sending a large number of specially crafted packets to the PLC. The PLC will lose its ability to communicate over the network. This vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker with network access to the affected systems. Successful exploitation requires no privileges and no user interaction. An attacker could use this vulnerability to compromise availability of the network connectivity. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-13805|2024-08-05T09:14:47.124Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11459|2024-08-05T08:10:14.329Z -- siemens%20ag -- sinumerik%20808d%20v4.7%2C%20sinumerik%20808d%20v4.8%2C%20sinumerik%20828d%20v4.7%2C%20sinumerik%20840d%20sl%20v4.7%2C%20sinumerik%20840d%20sl%20v4.8
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11459</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINUMERIK 808D V4.7 (All versions), SINUMERIK 808D V4.8 (All versions), SINUMERIK 828D V4.7 (All versions &lt; V4.7 SP6 HF1), SINUMERIK 840D sl V4.7 (All versions &lt; V4.7 SP6 HF5), SINUMERIK 840D sl V4.8 (All versions &lt; V4.8 SP3). A local attacker could modify a user-writeable configuration file so that after reboot or manual initiation the system reloads the modified configuration file and attacker-controlled code is executed with elevated privileges. The security vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker with local access to the affected system. Successful exploitation requires user privileges but no user interaction. The vulnerability could allow an attacker to compromise confidentiality, integrity and availability of the system. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11459|2024-08-05T08:10:14.329Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4852|2024-08-05T05:18:26.602Z -- siemens%20ag -- siclock%20tc100%2C%20siclock%20tc400
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4852</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SICLOCK TC100 (All versions) and SICLOCK TC400 (All versions). An attacker with network access to the device could potentially circumvent the authentication mechanism if he/she is able to obtain certain knowledge specific to the attacked device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4852|2024-08-05T05:18:26.602Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
