<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Siemens AG -- SCALANCE M875</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/siemens%20ag/scalance%20m875.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Siemens AG -- SCALANCE M875</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 05:23:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11447|2024-09-17T02:17:05.410Z -- siemens%20ag -- scalance%20m875
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11447</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE M875 (All versions). The web interface on port 443/tcp could allow a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) attack if an unsuspecting user is tricked into accessing a malicious link. Successful exploitation requires user interaction by an legitimate user, who must be authenticated to the web interface as administrative user. A successful attack could allow an attacker to interact with the web interface as an administrative user. This could allow the attacker to read or modify the device configuration, or to exploit other vulnerabilities that require authentication as administrative user. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11447|2024-09-17T02:17:05.410Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4859|2024-09-17T00:31:04.082Z -- siemens%20ag -- scalance%20m875
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4859</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE M875 (All versions). An authenticated remote attacker with access to the web interface (443/tcp), could execute arbitrary operating system commands. Successful exploitation requires that the attacker has network access to the web interface. The attacker must be authenticated as administrative user to exploit the security vulnerability. The vulnerability could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code on the device. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4859|2024-09-17T00:31:04.082Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-11449|2024-09-17T03:44:14.245Z -- siemens%20ag -- scalance%20m875
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-11449</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE M875 (All versions). An attacker with access to the local file system might obtain passwords for administrative users. Successful exploitation requires read access to files on the local file system. A successful attack could allow an attacker to obtain administrative passwords. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-11449|2024-09-17T03:44:14.245Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
