<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Siemens AG -- SICLOCK TC100, SICLOCK TC400</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/siemens%20ag/siclock%20tc100%2C%20siclock%20tc400.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Siemens AG -- SICLOCK TC100, SICLOCK TC400</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 19:20:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4851|2024-09-17T01:01:16.624Z -- siemens%20ag -- siclock%20tc100%2C%20siclock%20tc400
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4851</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SICLOCK TC100 (All versions) and SICLOCK TC400 (All versions). An attacker with network access to the device could cause a Denial-of-Service condition by sending certain packets to the device, causing potential reboots of the device. The core functionality of the device could be impacted. The time serving functionality recovers when time synchronization with GPS devices or other NTP servers are completed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4851|2024-09-17T01:01:16.624Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4856|2024-09-17T03:28:51.189Z -- siemens%20ag -- siclock%20tc100%2C%20siclock%20tc400
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4856</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SICLOCK TC100 (All versions) and SICLOCK TC400 (All versions). An attacker with administrative access to the device's management interface could lock out legitimate users. Manual interaction is required to restore the access of legitimate users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4856|2024-09-17T03:28:51.189Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4852|2024-09-17T03:07:34.425Z -- siemens%20ag -- siclock%20tc100%2C%20siclock%20tc400
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4852</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SICLOCK TC100 (All versions) and SICLOCK TC400 (All versions). An attacker with network access to the device could potentially circumvent the authentication mechanism if he/she is able to obtain certain knowledge specific to the attacked device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4852|2024-09-17T03:07:34.425Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-4855|2024-09-17T03:08:21.334Z -- siemens%20ag -- siclock%20tc100%2C%20siclock%20tc400
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-4855</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SICLOCK TC100 (All versions) and SICLOCK TC400 (All versions). Unencrypted storage of passwords in the client configuration files and during network transmission could allow an attacker in a privileged position to obtain access passwords.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-4855|2024-09-17T03:08:21.334Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
