<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Siemens AG -- SIEMENS LOGO!8</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/siemens%20ag/siemens%20logo%218.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Siemens AG -- SIEMENS LOGO!8</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 21:22:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6584|2024-08-04T20:23:22.246Z -- siemens%20ag -- siemens%20logo%218
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6584</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIEMENS LOGO!8 (6ED1052-xyyxx-0BA8 FS:01 to FS:06 / Firmware version V1.80.xx and V1.81.xx), SIEMENS LOGO!8 (6ED1052-xyy08-0BA0 FS:01 / Firmware version &lt; V1.82.02). The integrated webserver does not invalidate the Session ID upon user logout. An attacker that successfully extracted a valid Session ID is able to use it even after the user logs out. The security vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker in a privileged network position who is able to read the communication between the affected device and the user or by an attacker who is able to obtain valid Session IDs through other means. The user must invoke a session to the affected device. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6584|2024-08-04T20:23:22.246Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 13:47:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6571|2024-08-04T20:23:22.055Z -- siemens%20ag -- siemens%20logo%218
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6571</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIEMENS LOGO!8 (6ED1052-xyyxx-0BA8 FS:01 to FS:06 / Firmware version V1.80.xx and V1.81.xx), SIEMENS LOGO!8 (6ED1052-xyy08-0BA0 FS:01 / Firmware version &lt; V1.82.02). An attacker with network access to port 10005/tcp of the LOGO! device could cause a Denial-of-Service condition by sending specially crafted packets. The security vulnerability could be exploited by an unauthenticated attacker with network access to the affected service. No user interaction is required to exploit this security vulnerability. Successful exploitation of the security vulnerability compromises availability of the targeted system. At the time of advisory publication no public exploitation of this security vulnerability was known.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6571|2024-08-04T20:23:22.055Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 13:47:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
