<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for giuliopanda -- ADFO – Custom data in admin dashboard</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/giuliopanda/adfo%20%E2%80%93%20custom%20data%20in%20admin%20dashboard.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for giuliopanda -- ADFO – Custom data in admin dashboard</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 16:28:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-4104|2024-05-09T20:03:41.057Z -- giuliopanda -- ADFO – Custom data in admin dashboard
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4104</link><description>The ADFO – Custom data in admin dashboard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'dbp_id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4104|2024-05-09T20:03:41.057Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 20:03:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4103|2024-05-09T20:03:33.406Z -- giuliopanda -- ADFO – Custom data in admin dashboard
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4103</link><description>The ADFO – Custom data in admin dashboard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on several functions hooked via the controller() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to edit the plugin's settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4103|2024-05-09T20:03:33.406Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 20:03:33 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>