<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for Wpexpertsio -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/wpexpertsio/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for Wpexpertsio -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 23:21:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-0656|2024-02-20T18:56:39.506Z -- wpexpertsio -- Password Protected – Ultimate Plugin to Password Protect Your WordPress Content with Ease</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0656</link><description>The Password Protected – Ultimate Plugin to Password Protect Your WordPress Content with Ease plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Google Captcha Site Key in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0656|2024-02-20T18:56:39.506Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:56:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0437|2024-05-14T23:31:46.532Z -- wpexpertsio -- Password Protected – Ultimate Plugin to Password Protect Your WordPress Content with Ease</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0437</link><description>The Password Protected – Ultimate Plugin to Password Protect Your WordPress Content with Ease plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.6 via the API. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber access or higher, to extract post titles and content, thus bypassing the plugin's password protection.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0437|2024-05-14T23:31:46.532Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 23:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27959|2024-03-17T16:27:35.031Z -- Wpexpertsio -- WC Shop Sync – Integrate Square and WooCommerce for Seamless Shop Management</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-27959</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wpexpertsio WC Shop Sync – Integrate Square and WooCommerce for Seamless Shop Management allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WC Shop Sync – Integrate Square and WooCommerce for Seamless Shop Management: from n/a through 4.2.9.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-27959|2024-03-17T16:27:35.031Z</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 16:27:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5207|2024-05-30T05:33:15.366Z -- wpexpertsio -- Post SMTP – The WordPress SMTP Plugin with Email Logs and Mobile App for Email Failure Notifications</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5207</link><description>The POST SMTP – The #1 WordPress SMTP Plugin with Advanced Email Logging and Delivery Failure Notifications plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the selected parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.3 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with administrator access or higher to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5207|2024-05-30T05:33:15.366Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 05:33:15 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>