<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for wpexpertsio -- POST SMTP – The #1 WordPress SMTP Plugin with Advanced Email Logging and Delivery Failure Notifications</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/wpexpertsio/post%20smtp%20%E2%80%93%20the%20%231%20wordpress%20smtp%20plugin%20with%20advanced%20email%20logging%20and%20delivery%20failure%20notifications.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for wpexpertsio -- POST SMTP – The #1 WordPress SMTP Plugin with Advanced Email Logging and Delivery Failure Notifications</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 09:23:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6875|2024-08-02T08:42:08.006Z -- wpexpertsio -- post%20smtp%20%E2%80%93%20the%20%231%20wordpress%20smtp%20plugin%20with%20advanced%20email%20logging%20and%20delivery%20failure%20notifications
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6875</link>
      <description>The POST SMTP Mailer – Email log, Delivery Failure Notifications and Best Mail SMTP for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data and modification of data due to a type juggling issue on the connect-app REST endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.7. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to reset the API key used to authenticate to the mailer and view logs, including password reset emails, allowing site takeover.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6875|2024-08-02T08:42:08.006Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:33:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6629|2024-08-02T08:35:14.828Z -- wpexpertsio -- post%20smtp%20%E2%80%93%20the%20%231%20wordpress%20smtp%20plugin%20with%20advanced%20email%20logging%20and%20delivery%20failure%20notifications
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6629</link>
      <description>The POST SMTP Mailer – Email log, Delivery Failure Notifications and Best Mail SMTP for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘msg’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6629|2024-08-02T08:35:14.828Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 04:29:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-7027|2024-08-02T08:50:08.195Z -- wpexpertsio -- post%20smtp%20%E2%80%93%20the%20%231%20wordpress%20smtp%20plugin%20with%20advanced%20email%20logging%20and%20delivery%20failure%20notifications
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7027</link>
      <description>The POST SMTP Mailer – Email log, Delivery Failure Notifications and Best Mail SMTP for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘device’ header in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-7027|2024-08-02T08:50:08.195Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 04:29:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
