<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for themewinter -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/themewinter/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for themewinter -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 08:23:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-1855|2024-05-23T01:56:18.284Z -- themewinter -- WPCafe – Online Food Ordering, Restaurant Menu, Delivery, and Reservations for WooCommerce</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1855</link><description>The WPCafe – Restaurant Menu, Online Ordering for WooCommerce, Pickup / Delivery and Table Reservation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.23 via the wpc_check_for_submission function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1855|2024-05-23T01:56:18.284Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 01:56:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1122|2024-02-09T04:31:53.959Z -- themewinter -- Event Manager, Events Calendar, Events Tickets for WooCommerce – Eventin</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1122</link><description>The Event Manager, Events Calendar, Events Tickets for WooCommerce – Eventin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the export_data() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.50. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to export event data.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1122|2024-02-09T04:31:53.959Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 04:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5427|2024-05-31T06:40:54.597Z -- themewinter -- WPCafe – Online Food Ordering, Restaurant Menu, Delivery, and Reservations for WooCommerce</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5427</link><description>The WPCafe – Online Food Ordering, Restaurant Menu, Delivery, and Reservations for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Reservation Form shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.24 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5427|2024-05-31T06:40:54.597Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 06:40:54 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>