<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Thomson -- TCW710</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/thomson/tcw710.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Thomson -- TCW710</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:23:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-25038|2024-08-05T12:26:39.642Z -- thomson -- tcw710
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25038</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Thomson TCW710 ST5D.10.05. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /goform/RgDhcp. The manipulation of the argument PppUserName with the input &gt;&lt;script&gt;alert(1)&lt;/script&gt; as part of POST Request leads to cross site scripting (Persistent). It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-25038|2024-08-05T12:26:39.642Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 07:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-25037|2024-08-05T12:26:39.598Z -- thomson -- tcw710
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25037</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Thomson TCW710 ST5D.10.05 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /goform/RgDdns. The manipulation of the argument DdnsHostName with the input &gt;&lt;script&gt;alert(1)&lt;/script&gt; as part of POST Request leads to cross site scripting (Persistent). The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-25037|2024-08-05T12:26:39.598Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 07:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-25036|2024-08-05T12:26:39.637Z -- thomson -- tcw710
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25036</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Thomson TCW710 ST5D.10.05 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /goform/RgTime. The manipulation of the argument TimeServer1/TimeServer2/TimeServer3 with the input &gt;&lt;script&gt;alert(1)&lt;/script&gt; as part of POST Request leads to cross site scripting (Persistent). The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-25036|2024-08-05T12:26:39.637Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 07:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-25035|2024-08-05T12:26:39.562Z -- thomson -- tcw710
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25035</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Thomson TCW710 ST5D.10.05. Affected is an unknown function of the file /goform/RGFirewallEL. The manipulation of the argument EmailAddress/SmtpServerName with the input &gt;&lt;script&gt;alert(1)&lt;/script&gt; as part of POST Request leads to cross site scripting (Persistent). It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-25035|2024-08-05T12:26:39.562Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 07:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-25039|2024-08-05T12:26:39.588Z -- thomson -- tcw710
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25039</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Thomson TCW710 ST5D.10.05. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /goform/RgUrlBlock.asp. The manipulation of the argument BasicParentalNewKeyword with the input &gt;&lt;script&gt;alert(1)&lt;/script&gt; as part of POST Request leads to cross site scripting (Persistent). The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-25039|2024-08-05T12:26:39.588Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 07:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-25034|2024-08-05T12:26:39.613Z -- thomson -- tcw710
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25034</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Thomson TCW710 ST5D.10.05. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /goform/wlanPrimaryNetwork. The manipulation of the argument ServiceSetIdentifier with the input &gt;&lt;script&gt;alert(1)&lt;/script&gt; as part of POST Request leads to basic cross site scripting (Persistent). The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-126695.
Eine Schwachstelle wurde in Thomson TCW710 ST5D.10.05 entdeckt. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Davon betroffen ist unbekannter Code der Datei /goform/wlanPrimaryNetwork. Durch Manipulieren des Arguments ServiceSetIdentifier mit der Eingabe &gt;&lt;script&gt;alert(1)&lt;/script&gt; durch POST Request kann eine basic cross site scripting-Schwachstelle (Persistent) ausgenutzt werden. Der Angriff kann über das Netzwerk erfolgen. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-25034|2024-08-05T12:26:39.613Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 07:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
