<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Palo Alto Networks -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/palo%20alto%20networks/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Palo Alto Networks -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 13:22:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1989|2024-08-04T06:54:00.592Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- global%20protect%20agent
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1989</link>
      <description>An incorrect privilege assignment vulnerability when writing application-specific files in the Palo Alto Networks Global Protect Agent for Linux on ARM platform allows a local authenticated user to gain root privileges on the system. This issue affects Palo Alto Networks Global Protect Agent for Linux 5.0 versions before 5.0.8; 5.1 versions before 5.1.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1989|2024-08-04T06:54:00.592Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2005|2024-08-04T06:54:00.583Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2005</link>
      <description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists when visiting malicious websites with the Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect Clientless VPN that can compromise the user's active session. This issue affects: PAN-OS 7.1 versions earlier than 7.1.26; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than 8.1.13; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than 9.0.7; All versions of PAN-OS 8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2005|2024-08-04T06:54:00.583Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2012|2024-08-04T06:54:00.541Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2012</link>
      <description>Improper restriction of XML external entity reference ('XXE') vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Panorama management service allows remote unauthenticated attackers with network access to the Panorama management interface to read arbitrary files on the system. This issue affects: All versions of PAN-OS for Panorama 7.1 and 8.0; PAN-OS for Panorama 8.1 versions earlier than 8.1.13; PAN-OS for Panorama 9.0 versions earlier than 9.0.7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2012|2024-08-04T06:54:00.541Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2008|2024-08-04T06:54:00.559Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2008</link>
      <description>An OS command injection and external control of filename vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS allows authenticated administrators to execute code with root privileges or delete arbitrary system files and impact the system's integrity or cause a denial of service condition. This issue affects: All versions of PAN-OS 7.1 and 8.0; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than 8.1.14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2008|2024-08-04T06:54:00.559Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1995|2024-08-04T06:54:00.573Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1995</link>
      <description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS allows an authenticated administrator to send a request that causes the rasmgr daemon to crash. Repeated attempts to send this request result in denial of service to all PAN-OS services by restarting the device and putting it into maintenance mode. This issue affects: PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than 9.1.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1995|2024-08-04T06:54:00.573Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2033|2024-08-04T06:54:00.591Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- globalprotect%20app
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2033</link>
      <description>When the pre-logon feature is enabled, a missing certification validation in Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect app can disclose the pre-logon authentication cookie to a man-in-the-middle attacker on the same local area network segment with the ability to manipulate ARP or to conduct ARP spoofing attacks. This allows the attacker to access the GlobalProtect Server as allowed by configured Security rules for the 'pre-login' user. This access may be limited compared to the network access of regular users. This issue affects: GlobalProtect app 5.0 versions earlier than GlobalProtect app 5.0.10 when the prelogon feature is enabled; GlobalProtect app 5.1 versions earlier than GlobalProtect app 5.1.4 when the prelogon feature is enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2033|2024-08-04T06:54:00.591Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2011|2024-08-04T06:54:00.634Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2011</link>
      <description>An improper input validation vulnerability in the configuration daemon of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS Panorama allows for a remote unauthenticated user to send a specifically crafted registration request to the device that causes the configuration service to crash. Repeated attempts to send this request result in denial of service to all PAN-OS Panorama services by restarting the device and putting it into maintenance mode. This issue affects: All versions of PAN-OS 7.1, PAN-OS 8.0; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than 8.1.14; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than 9.0.7; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than 9.1.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2011|2024-08-04T06:54:00.634Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2018|2024-08-04T06:54:00.524Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2018</link>
      <description>An authentication bypass vulnerability in the Panorama context switching feature allows an attacker with network access to a Panorama's management interface to gain privileged access to managed firewalls. An attacker requires some knowledge of managed firewalls to exploit this issue. This issue does not affect Panorama configured with custom certificates authentication for communication between Panorama and managed devices. This issue affects: PAN-OS 7.1 versions earlier than 7.1.26; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than 8.1.12; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than 9.0.6; All versions of PAN-OS 8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2018|2024-08-04T06:54:00.524Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1982|2024-08-04T06:54:00.692Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1982</link>
      <description>Certain communication between PAN-OS and cloud-delivered services inadvertently use TLS 1.0, which is known to be a cryptographically weak protocol. These cloud services include Cortex Data Lake, the Customer Support Portal, and the Prisma Access infrastructure. Conditions required for exploitation of known TLS 1.0 weaknesses do not exist for the communication between PAN-OS and cloud-delivered services. We do not believe that any communication is impacted as a result of known attacks against TLS 1.0. This issue impacts: All versions of PAN-OS 8.0; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.14; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.9; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.3. PAN-OS 7.1 is not impacted by this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1982|2024-08-04T06:54:00.692Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1975|2024-08-04T06:54:00.317Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1975</link>
      <description>Missing XML validation vulnerability in the PAN-OS web interface on Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software allows authenticated users to inject arbitrary XML that results in privilege escalation. This issue affects PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.12 and PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.6. This issue does not affect PAN-OS 7.1, PAN-OS 8.0, or PAN-OS 9.1 or later versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1975|2024-08-04T06:54:00.317Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2038|2024-08-04T06:54:00.693Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2038</link>
      <description>An OS Command Injection vulnerability in the PAN-OS management interface that allows authenticated administrators to execute arbitrary OS commands with root privileges. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than 9.0.10; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than 9.1.4; PAN-OS 10.0 versions earlier than 10.0.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2038|2024-08-04T06:54:00.693Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1976|2024-08-04T06:54:00.347Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- globalprotect
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1976</link>
      <description>A denial-of-service (DoS) vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect software running on Mac OS allows authenticated local users to cause the Mac OS kernel to hang or crash. This issue affects GlobalProtect 5.0.5 and earlier versions of GlobalProtect 5.0 on Mac OS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1976|2024-08-04T06:54:00.347Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2022|2024-08-04T06:54:00.535Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2022</link>
      <description>An information exposure vulnerability exists in Palo Alto Networks Panorama software that discloses the token for the Panorama web interface administrator's session to a managed device when the Panorama administrator performs a context switch into that device. This vulnerability allows an attacker to gain privileged access to the Panorama web interface. An attacker requires some knowledge of managed firewalls to exploit this issue. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.17; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.11; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2022|2024-08-04T06:54:00.535Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1994|2024-08-04T06:54:00.551Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1994</link>
      <description>A predictable temporary file vulnerability in PAN-OS allows a local authenticated user with shell access to corrupt arbitrary system files affecting the integrity of the system. This issue affects: All versions of PAN-OS 7.1 and 8.0; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than 8.1.13; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than 9.0.7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1994|2024-08-04T06:54:00.551Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1998|2024-08-04T06:54:00.579Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1998</link>
      <description>An improper authorization vulnerability in PAN-OS that mistakenly uses the permissions of local linux users instead of the intended SAML permissions of the account when the username is shared for the purposes of SSO authentication. This can result in authentication bypass and unintended resource access for the user. This issue affects: PAN-OS 7.1 versions earlier than 7.1.26; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than 8.1.13; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than 9.0.6; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than 9.1.1; All versions of PAN-OS 8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1998|2024-08-04T06:54:00.579Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2042|2024-08-04T06:54:00.582Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2042</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow vulnerability in the PAN-OS management web interface allows authenticated administrators to disrupt system processes and potentially execute arbitrary code with root privileges. This issue impacts only PAN-OS 10.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.0.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2042|2024-08-04T06:54:00.582Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2039|2024-08-04T06:54:00.704Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2039</link>
      <description>An uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS allows for a remote unauthenticated user to upload temporary files through the management web interface that are not properly deleted after the request is finished. It is possible for an attacker to disrupt the availability of the management web interface by repeatedly uploading files until available disk space is exhausted. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.16; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.10; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.4; PAN-OS 10.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.0.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2039|2024-08-04T06:54:00.704Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2049|2024-08-04T06:54:00.705Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2049</link>
      <description>A local privilege escalation vulnerability exists in Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR Agent on the Windows platform that allows an authenticated local Windows user to execute programs with SYSTEM privileges. This requires the user to have the privilege to create files in the Windows root directory. This issue impacts: All versions of Cortex XDR Agent 7.1 with content update 149 and earlier versions; All versions of Cortex XDR Agent 7.2 with content update 149 and earlier versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2049|2024-08-04T06:54:00.705Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2034|2024-08-04T06:54:00.585Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2034</link>
      <description>An OS Command Injection vulnerability in the PAN-OS GlobalProtect portal allows an unauthenticated network based attacker to execute arbitrary OS commands with root privileges. An attacker requires some knowledge of the firewall to exploit this issue. This issue can not be exploited if GlobalProtect portal feature is not enabled. This issue impacts PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.3; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.15; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.9; all versions of PAN-OS 8.0 and PAN-OS 7.1. Prisma Access services are not impacted by this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2034|2024-08-04T06:54:00.585Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2004|2024-08-04T06:54:00.539Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- globalprotect%20app
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2004</link>
      <description>Under certain circumstances a user's password may be logged in cleartext in the PanGPS.log diagnostic file when logs are collected for troubleshooting on GlobalProtect app (also known as GlobalProtect Agent) for MacOS and Windows. For this issue to occur all of these conditions must be true: (1) 'Save User Credential' option should be set to 'Yes' in the GlobalProtect Portal's Agent configuration, (2) the GlobalProtect user manually selects a gateway, (3) and the logging level is set to 'Dump' while collecting troubleshooting logs. This issue does not affect GlobalProtect app on other platforms (for example iOS/Android/Linux). This issue affects GlobalProtect app 5.0 versions earlier than 5.0.9, GlobalProtect app 5.1 versions earlier than 5.1.2 on Windows or MacOS. Since becoming aware of the issue, Palo Alto Networks has safely deleted all the known GlobalProtectLogs zip files sent by customers with the credentials. We now filter and remove these credentials from all files sent to Customer Support. The GlobalProtectLogs zip files uploaded to Palo Alto Networks systems were only accessible by authorized personnel with valid Palo Alto Networks credentials. We do not have any evidence of malicious access or use of these credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2004|2024-08-04T06:54:00.539Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2037|2024-08-04T06:54:00.587Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2037</link>
      <description>An OS Command Injection vulnerability in the PAN-OS management interface that allows authenticated administrators to execute arbitrary OS commands with root privileges. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.16; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.10; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2037|2024-08-04T06:54:00.587Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2048|2024-08-04T06:54:00.591Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2048</link>
      <description>An information exposure through log file vulnerability exists where the password for the configured system proxy server for a PAN-OS appliance may be displayed in cleartext when using the CLI in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.17; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.11; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2048|2024-08-04T06:54:00.591Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2016|2024-08-04T06:54:00.578Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2016</link>
      <description>A race condition due to insecure creation of a file in a temporary directory vulnerability in PAN-OS allows for root privilege escalation from a limited linux user account. This allows an attacker who has escaped the restricted shell as a low privilege administrator, possibly by exploiting another vulnerability, to escalate privileges to become root user. This issue affects: PAN-OS 7.1 versions earlier than 7.1.26; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than 8.1.13; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than 9.0.6; All versions of PAN-OS 8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2016|2024-08-04T06:54:00.578Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2017|2024-08-04T06:54:00.561Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2017</link>
      <description>A DOM-Based Cross Site Scripting Vulnerability exists in PAN-OS and Panorama Management Web Interfaces. A remote attacker able to convince an authenticated administrator to click on a crafted link to PAN-OS and Panorama Web Interfaces could execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the administrator's browser and perform administrative actions. This issue affects: PAN-OS 7.1 versions earlier than 7.1.26; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than 8.1.13; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than 9.0.6; All versions of PAN-OS 8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2017|2024-08-04T06:54:00.561Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2031|2024-08-04T06:54:00.923Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2031</link>
      <description>An integer underflow vulnerability in the dnsproxyd component of the PAN-OS management interface allows authenticated administrators to issue a command from the command line interface that causes the component to stop responding. Repeated attempts to send this request result in denial of service to all PAN-OS services by restarting the device and putting it into maintenance mode. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.3. This issue does not impact PAN-OS 8.1, PAN-OS 9.0, or Prisma Access services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2031|2024-08-04T06:54:00.923Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1992|2024-08-04T06:54:00.532Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1992</link>
      <description>A format string vulnerability in the Varrcvr daemon of PAN-OS on PA-7000 Series devices with a Log Forwarding Card (LFC) allows remote attackers to crash the daemon creating a denial of service condition or potentially execute code with root privileges. This issue affects Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS 9.0 versions before 9.0.7; PAN-OS 9.1 versions before 9.1.2 on PA-7000 Series devices with an LFC installed and configured. This issue requires WildFire services to be configured and enabled. This issue does not affect PAN-OS 8.1 and earlier releases. This issue does not affect any other PA Series firewalls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1992|2024-08-04T06:54:00.532Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2040|2024-08-04T06:54:00.636Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2040</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow vulnerability in PAN-OS allows an unauthenticated attacker to disrupt system processes and potentially execute arbitrary code with root privileges by sending a malicious request to the Captive Portal or Multi-Factor Authentication interface. This issue impacts: All versions of PAN-OS 8.0; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.15; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.9; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2040|2024-08-04T06:54:00.636Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1988|2024-08-04T06:54:00.605Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- global%20protect%20agent
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1988</link>
      <description>An unquoted search path vulnerability in the Windows release of Global Protect Agent allows an authenticated local user with file creation privileges on the root of the OS disk (C:\) or to Program Files directory to gain system privileges. This issue affects Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect Agent 5.0 versions before 5.0.5; 4.1 versions before 4.1.13 on Windows;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1988|2024-08-04T06:54:00.605Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2014|2024-08-04T06:54:00.528Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2014</link>
      <description>An OS Command Injection vulnerability in PAN-OS management server allows authenticated users to inject and execute arbitrary shell commands with root privileges. This issue affects: All versions of PAN-OS 7.1 and 8.0; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than 8.1.14; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than 9.0.7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2014|2024-08-04T06:54:00.528Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1999|2024-08-04T06:54:00.597Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1999</link>
      <description>A vulnerability exists in the Palo Alto Network PAN-OS signature-based threat detection engine that allows an attacker to communicate with devices in the network in a way that is not analyzed for threats by sending data through specifically crafted TCP packets. This technique evades signature-based threat detection. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than 8.1.17; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than 9.0.11; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than 9.1.5; All versions of PAN-OS 7.1 and PAN-OS 8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1999|2024-08-04T06:54:00.597Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2015|2024-08-04T06:54:00.598Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2015</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow vulnerability in the PAN-OS management server allows authenticated users to crash system processes or potentially execute arbitrary code with root privileges. This issue affects: PAN-OS 7.1 versions earlier than 7.1.26; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than 8.1.13; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than 9.0.7; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than 9.1.1; All versions of PAN-OS 8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2015|2024-08-04T06:54:00.598Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1993|2024-08-04T06:54:00.589Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1993</link>
      <description>The GlobalProtect Portal feature in PAN-OS does not set a new session identifier after a successful user login, which allows session fixation attacks, if an attacker is able to control a user's session ID. This issue affects: All PAN-OS 7.1 and 8.0 versions; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than 8.1.14; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than 9.0.8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1993|2024-08-04T06:54:00.589Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1996|2024-08-04T06:54:00.563Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1996</link>
      <description>A missing authorization vulnerability in the management server component of PAN-OS Panorama allows a remote unauthenticated user to inject messages into the management server ms.log file. This vulnerability can be leveraged to obfuscate an ongoing attack or fabricate log entries in the ms.log file This issue affects: All versions of PAN-OS 7.1 and 8.0; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than 8.1.14; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than 9.0.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1996|2024-08-04T06:54:00.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2035|2024-08-04T06:54:00.688Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2035</link>
      <description>When SSL/TLS Forward Proxy Decryption mode has been configured to decrypt the web transactions, the PAN-OS URL filtering feature inspects the HTTP Host and URL path headers for policy enforcement on the decrypted HTTPS web transactions but does not consider Server Name Indication (SNI) field within the TLS Client Hello handshake. This allows a compromised host in a protected network to evade any security policy that uses URL filtering on a firewall configured with SSL Decryption in the Forward Proxy mode. A malicious actor can then use this technique to evade detection of communication on the TLS handshake phase between a compromised host and a remote malicious server. This technique does not increase the risk of a host being compromised in the network. It does not impact the confidentiality or availability of a firewall. This is considered to have a low impact on the integrity of the firewall because the firewall fails to enforce a policy on certain traffic that should have been blocked. This issue does not impact the URL filtering policy enforcement on clear text or encrypted web transactions. This technique can be used only after a malicious actor has compromised a host in the protected network and the TLS/SSL Decryption feature is enabled for the traffic that the attacker controls. Palo Alto Networks is not aware of any malware that uses this technique to exfiltrate data. This issue is applicable to all current versions of PAN-OS. This issue does not impact Panorama or WF-500 appliances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2035|2024-08-04T06:54:00.688Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1990|2024-08-04T06:54:00.591Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1990</link>
      <description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the management server component of PAN-OS allows an authenticated user to upload a corrupted PAN-OS configuration and potentially execute code with root privileges. This issue affects Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS 8.1 versions before 8.1.13; 9.0 versions before 9.0.7. This issue does not affect PAN-OS 7.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1990|2024-08-04T06:54:00.591Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1997|2024-08-04T06:54:00.554Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1997</link>
      <description>An open redirection vulnerability in the GlobalProtect component of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS allows an attacker to specify an arbitrary redirection target away from the trusted GlobalProtect gateway. If the user then successfully authenticates it will cause them to access an unexpected and potentially malicious website. This issue affects: PAN-OS 7.1 versions earlier than 7.1.26; PAN-OS 8.0 versions earlier than 8.0.14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1997|2024-08-04T06:54:00.554Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2021|2024-08-04T06:54:00.586Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2021</link>
      <description>When Security Assertion Markup Language (SAML) authentication is enabled and the 'Validate Identity Provider Certificate' option is disabled (unchecked), improper verification of signatures in PAN-OS SAML authentication enables an unauthenticated network-based attacker to access protected resources. The attacker must have network access to the vulnerable server to exploit this vulnerability. This issue affects PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.3; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.9; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.15, and all versions of PAN-OS 8.0 (EOL). This issue does not affect PAN-OS 7.1. This issue cannot be exploited if SAML is not used for authentication. This issue cannot be exploited if the 'Validate Identity Provider Certificate' option is enabled (checked) in the SAML Identity Provider Server Profile. Resources that can be protected by SAML-based single sign-on (SSO) authentication are: GlobalProtect Gateway, GlobalProtect Portal, GlobalProtect Clientless VPN, Authentication and Captive Portal, PAN-OS next-generation firewalls (PA-Series, VM-Series) and Panorama web interfaces, Prisma Access In the case of GlobalProtect Gateways, GlobalProtect Portal, Clientless VPN, Captive Portal, and Prisma Access, an unauthenticated attacker with network access to the affected servers can gain access to protected resources if allowed by configured authentication and Security policies. There is no impact on the integrity and availability of the gateway, portal or VPN server. An attacker cannot inspect or tamper with sessions of regular users. In the worst case, this is a critical severity vulnerability with a CVSS Base Score of 10.0 (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:N). In the case of PAN-OS and Panorama web interfaces, this issue allows an unauthenticated attacker with network access to the PAN-OS or Panorama web interfaces to log in as an administrator and perform administrative actions. In the worst-case scenario, this is a critical severity vulnerability with a CVSS Base Score of 10.0 (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H). If the web interfaces are only accessible to a restricted management network, then the issue is lowered to a CVSS Base Score of 9.6 (CVSS:3.1/AV:A/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H). Palo Alto Networks is not aware of any malicious attempts to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2021|2024-08-04T06:54:00.586Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2043|2024-08-04T06:54:00.924Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2043</link>
      <description>An information exposure through log file vulnerability where sensitive fields are recorded in the configuration log without masking on Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software when the after-change-detail custom syslog field is enabled for configuration logs and the sensitive field appears multiple times in one log entry. The first instance of the sensitive field is masked but subsequent instances are left in clear text. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.16; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.10; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2043|2024-08-04T06:54:00.924Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2007|2024-08-04T06:54:00.562Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2007</link>
      <description>An OS command injection vulnerability in the management server component of PAN-OS allows an authenticated user to potentially execute arbitrary commands with root privileges. This issue affects: All PAN-OS 7.1 versions; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than 8.1.14; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than 9.0.7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2007|2024-08-04T06:54:00.562Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2032|2024-08-04T06:54:00.590Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- globalprotect%20app
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2032</link>
      <description>A race condition vulnerability Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect app on Windows allows a local limited Windows user to execute programs with SYSTEM privileges. This issue can be exploited only while performing a GlobalProtect app upgrade. This issue affects: GlobalProtect app 5.0 versions earlier than GlobalProtect app 5.0.10 on Windows; GlobalProtect app 5.1 versions earlier than GlobalProtect app 5.1.4 on Windows.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2032|2024-08-04T06:54:00.590Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2013|2024-08-04T06:54:00.965Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2013</link>
      <description>A cleartext transmission of sensitive information vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS Panorama that discloses an authenticated PAN-OS administrator's PAN-OS session cookie. When an administrator issues a context switch request into a managed firewall with an affected PAN-OS Panorama version, their PAN-OS session cookie is transmitted over cleartext to the firewall. An attacker with the ability to intercept this network traffic between the firewall and Panorama can access the administrator's account and further manipulate devices managed by Panorama. This issue affects: PAN-OS 7.1 versions earlier than 7.1.26; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than 8.1.13; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than 9.0.6; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than 9.1.1; All version of PAN-OS 8.0;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2013|2024-08-04T06:54:00.965Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2001|2024-08-04T06:54:00.607Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2001</link>
      <description>An external control of path and data vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS Panorama XSLT processing logic that allows an unauthenticated user with network access to PAN-OS management interface to write attacker supplied file on the system and elevate privileges. This issue affects: All PAN-OS 7.1 Panorama and 8.0 Panorama versions; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than 8.1.12 on Panorama; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than 9.0.6 on Panorama.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2001|2024-08-04T06:54:00.607Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2050|2024-08-04T06:54:00.576Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2050</link>
      <description>An authentication bypass vulnerability exists in the GlobalProtect SSL VPN component of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software that allows an attacker to bypass all client certificate checks with an invalid certificate. A remote attacker can successfully authenticate as any user and gain access to restricted VPN network resources when the gateway or portal is configured to rely entirely on certificate-based authentication. Impacted features that use SSL VPN with client certificate verification are: GlobalProtect Gateway, GlobalProtect Portal, GlobalProtect Clientless VPN In configurations where client certificate verification is used in conjunction with other authentication methods, the protections added by the certificate check are ignored as a result of this issue. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.17; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.11; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.5; PAN-OS 10.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.0.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2050|2024-08-04T06:54:00.576Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2044|2024-08-04T06:54:00.567Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2044</link>
      <description>An information exposure through log file vulnerability where an administrator's password or other sensitive information may be logged in cleartext while using the CLI in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software. The opcmdhistory.log file was introduced to track operational command (op-command) usage but did not mask all sensitive information. The opcmdhistory.log file is removed in PAN-OS 9.1 and later PAN-OS versions. Command usage is recorded, instead, in the req_stats.log file in PAN-OS 9.1 and later PAN-OS versions. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.16; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.10; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2044|2024-08-04T06:54:00.567Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1980|2024-08-04T06:54:00.366Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1980</link>
      <description>A shell command injection vulnerability in the PAN-OS CLI allows a local authenticated user to escape the restricted shell and escalate privileges. This issue affects only PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.13. This issue does not affect PAN-OS 7.1, PAN-OS 9.0, or later PAN-OS versions. This issue is fixed in PAN-OS 8.1.13, and all later versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1980|2024-08-04T06:54:00.366Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2000|2024-08-04T06:54:00.615Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2000</link>
      <description>An OS command injection and memory corruption vulnerability in the PAN-OS management web interface that allows authenticated administrators to disrupt system processes and potentially execute arbitrary code and OS commands with root privileges. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.16; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.10; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.4; PAN-OS 10.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.0.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2000|2024-08-04T06:54:00.615Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2009|2024-08-04T06:54:00.585Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2009</link>
      <description>An external control of filename vulnerability in the SD WAN component of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS Panorama allows an authenticated administrator to send a request that results in the creation and write of an arbitrary file on all firewalls managed by the Panorama. In some cases this results in arbitrary code execution with root permissions. This issue affects: All versions of PAN-OS 7.1; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than 8.1.14; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than 9.0.7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2009|2024-08-04T06:54:00.585Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2020|2024-08-04T06:54:00.594Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2020</link>
      <description>An improper handling of exceptional conditions vulnerability in Cortex XDR Agent allows a local authenticated Windows user to create files in the software's internal program directory that prevents the Cortex XDR Agent from starting. The exceptional condition is persistent and prevents Cortex XDR Agent from starting when the software or machine is restarted. This issue impacts: Cortex XDR Agent 5.0 versions earlier than 5.0.10; Cortex XDR Agent 6.1 versions earlier than 6.1.7; Cortex XDR Agent 7.0 versions earlier than 7.0.3; Cortex XDR Agent 7.1 versions earlier than 7.1.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2020|2024-08-04T06:54:00.594Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1991|2024-08-04T06:54:00.653Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- traps
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1991</link>
      <description>An insecure temporary file vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Traps allows a local authenticated Windows user to escalate privileges or overwrite system files. This issue affects Palo Alto Networks Traps 5.0 versions before 5.0.8; 6.1 versions before 6.1.4 on Windows. This issue does not affect Cortex XDR 7.0. This issue does not affect Traps for Linux or MacOS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1991|2024-08-04T06:54:00.653Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2036|2024-08-04T06:54:00.681Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2036</link>
      <description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the PAN-OS management web interface. A remote attacker able to convince an administrator with an active authenticated session on the firewall management interface to click on a crafted link to that management web interface could potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the administrator's browser and perform administrative actions. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.16; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2036|2024-08-04T06:54:00.681Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1987|2024-08-04T06:54:00.525Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- global%20protect%20agent
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1987</link>
      <description>An information exposure vulnerability in the logging component of Palo Alto Networks Global Protect Agent allows a local authenticated user to read VPN cookie information when the troubleshooting logging level is set to "Dump". This issue affects Palo Alto Networks Global Protect Agent 5.0 versions prior to 5.0.9; 5.1 versions prior to 5.1.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1987|2024-08-04T06:54:00.525Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1977|2024-08-04T06:54:00.351Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- expedition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1977</link>
      <description>Insufficient Cross-Site Request Forgery (XSRF) protection on Expedition Migration Tool allows remote unauthenticated attackers to hijack the authentication of administrators and to perform actions on the Expedition Migration Tool. This issue affects Expedition Migration Tool 1.1.51 and earlier versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1977|2024-08-04T06:54:00.351Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2002|2024-08-04T06:54:00.539Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2002</link>
      <description>An authentication bypass by spoofing vulnerability exists in the authentication daemon and User-ID components of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS by failing to verify the integrity of the Kerberos key distribution center (KDC) before authenticating users. This affects all forms of authentication that use a Kerberos authentication profile. A man-in-the-middle type of attacker with the ability to intercept communication between PAN-OS and KDC can login to PAN-OS as an administrator. This issue affects: PAN-OS 7.1 versions earlier than 7.1.26; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than 8.1.13; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than 9.0.6; All version of PAN-OS 8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2002|2024-08-04T06:54:00.539Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2006|2024-08-04T06:54:00.630Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2006</link>
      <description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the management server component of PAN-OS that allows an authenticated user to potentially execute arbitrary code with root privileges. This issue affects: All versions of PAN-OS 7.1 and 8.0; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than 8.1.14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2006|2024-08-04T06:54:00.630Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2028|2024-08-04T06:54:00.584Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2028</link>
      <description>An OS Command Injection vulnerability in PAN-OS management server allows authenticated administrators to execute arbitrary OS commands with root privileges when uploading a new certificate in FIPS-CC mode. This issue affects: All versions of PAN-OS 7.1 and PAN-OS 8.0; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.13; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2028|2024-08-04T06:54:00.584Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2003|2024-08-04T06:54:00.728Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2003</link>
      <description>An external control of filename vulnerability in the command processing of PAN-OS allows an authenticated administrator to delete arbitrary system files affecting the integrity of the system or causing denial of service to all PAN-OS services. This issue affects: All versions of PAN-OS 7.1 and 8.0; PAN-OS 8.1 versions before 8.1.14; PAN-OS 9.0 versions before 9.0.7; PAN-OS 9.1 versions before 9.1.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2003|2024-08-04T06:54:00.728Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1978|2024-08-04T06:54:00.431Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- vm-series%20plugin
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1978</link>
      <description>TechSupport files generated on Palo Alto Networks VM Series firewalls for Microsoft Azure platform configured with high availability (HA) inadvertently collect Azure dashboard service account credentials. These credentials are equivalent to the credentials associated with the Contributor role in Azure. A user with the credentials will be able to manage all the Azure resources in the subscription except for granting access to other resources. These credentials do not allow login access to the VMs themselves. This issue affects VM Series Plugin versions before 1.0.9 for PAN-OS 9.0. This issue does not affect VM Series in non-HA configurations or on other cloud platforms. It does not affect hardware firewall appliances. Since becoming aware of the issue, Palo Alto Networks has safely deleted all the tech support files with the credentials. We now filter and remove these credentials from all TechSupport files sent to us. The TechSupport files uploaded to Palo Alto Networks systems were only accessible by authorized personnel with valid Palo Alto Networks credentials. We do not have any evidence of malicious access or use of these credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1978|2024-08-04T06:54:00.431Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1981|2024-08-04T06:54:00.381Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1981</link>
      <description>A predictable temporary filename vulnerability in PAN-OS allows local privilege escalation. This issue allows a local attacker who bypassed the restricted shell to execute commands as a low privileged user and gain root access on the PAN-OS hardware or virtual appliance. This issue affects only PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.13. This issue does not affect PAN-OS 7.1, PAN-OS 9.0, or later PAN-OS versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1981|2024-08-04T06:54:00.381Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1979|2024-08-04T06:54:00.395Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1979</link>
      <description>A format string vulnerability in the PAN-OS log daemon (logd) on Panorama allows a network based attacker with knowledge of registered firewall devices and access to Panorama management interfaces to execute arbitrary code, bypassing the restricted shell and escalating privileges. This issue affects only PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.13 on Panorama. This issue does not affect PAN-OS 7.1, PAN-OS 9.0, or later PAN-OS versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1979|2024-08-04T06:54:00.395Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2030|2024-08-04T06:54:00.594Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2030</link>
      <description>An OS Command Injection vulnerability in the PAN-OS management interface that allows authenticated administrators to execute arbitrary OS commands with root privileges. This issue impacts PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.15; and all versions of PAN-OS 7.1 and PAN-OS 8.0. This issue does not impact PAN-OS 9.0, PAN-OS 9.1, or Prisma Access services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2030|2024-08-04T06:54:00.594Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2029|2024-08-04T06:54:00.584Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2029</link>
      <description>An OS Command Injection vulnerability in the PAN-OS web management interface allows authenticated administrators to execute arbitrary OS commands with root privileges by sending a malicious request to generate new certificates for use in the PAN-OS configuration. This issue affects: All versions of PAN-OS 8.0; PAN-OS 7.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 7.1.26; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2029|2024-08-04T06:54:00.584Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2027|2024-08-04T06:54:00.565Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2027</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow vulnerability in the authd component of the PAN-OS management server allows authenticated administrators to disrupt system processes and potentially execute arbitrary code with root privileges. This issue affects: All versions of PAN-OS 7.1 and PAN-OS 8.0; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.13; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2027|2024-08-04T06:54:00.565Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2041|2024-08-04T06:54:00.595Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2041</link>
      <description>An insecure configuration of the appweb daemon of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS 8.1 allows a remote unauthenticated user to send a specifically crafted request to the device that causes the appweb service to crash. Repeated attempts to send this request result in denial of service to all PAN-OS services by restarting the device and putting it into maintenance mode. This issue impacts all versions of PAN-OS 8.0, and PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than 8.1.16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2041|2024-08-04T06:54:00.595Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2010|2024-08-04T06:54:00.563Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2010</link>
      <description>An OS command injection vulnerability in PAN-OS management interface allows an authenticated administrator to execute arbitrary OS commands with root privileges. This issue affects: All versions of PAN-OS 7.1 and 8.0; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than 8.1.14; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than 9.0.7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2010|2024-08-04T06:54:00.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3400|2024-08-01T20:12:06.667Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3400</link>
      <description>A command injection as a result of arbitrary file creation vulnerability in the GlobalProtect feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software for specific PAN-OS versions and distinct feature configurations may enable an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code with root privileges on the firewall.

Cloud NGFW, Panorama appliances, and Prisma Access are not impacted by this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3400|2024-08-01T20:12:06.667Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 07:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3385|2024-08-01T20:12:06.539Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3385</link>
      <description>A packet processing mechanism in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a remote attacker to reboot hardware-based firewalls. Repeated attacks eventually cause the firewall to enter maintenance mode, which requires manual intervention to bring the firewall back online.

This affects the following hardware firewall models:
- PA-5400 Series firewalls
- PA-7000 Series firewalls</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3385|2024-08-01T20:12:06.539Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3386|2024-08-01T20:12:06.667Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3386</link>
      <description>An incorrect string comparison vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software prevents Predefined Decryption Exclusions from functioning as intended. This can cause traffic destined for domains that are not specified in Predefined Decryption Exclusions to be unintentionally excluded from decryption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3386|2024-08-01T20:12:06.667Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3384|2024-08-01T20:12:06.484Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3384</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a remote attacker to reboot PAN-OS firewalls when receiving Windows New Technology LAN Manager (NTLM) packets from Windows servers. Repeated attacks eventually cause the firewall to enter maintenance mode, which requires manual intervention to bring the firewall back online.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3384|2024-08-01T20:12:06.484Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3383|2024-08-01T20:12:06.566Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3383</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in how Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software processes data received from Cloud Identity Engine (CIE) agents enables modification of User-ID groups. This impacts user access to network resources where users may be inappropriately denied or allowed access to resources based on your existing Security Policy rules.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3383|2024-08-01T20:12:06.566Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3382|2024-08-01T20:12:06.637Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3382</link>
      <description>A memory leak exists in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software that enables an attacker to send a burst of crafted packets through the firewall that eventually prevents the firewall from processing traffic. This issue applies only to PA-5400 Series devices that are running PAN-OS software with the SSL Forward Proxy feature enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3382|2024-08-01T20:12:06.637Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3387|2024-08-01T20:12:06.646Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3387</link>
      <description>A weak (low bit strength) device certificate in Palo Alto Networks Panorama software enables an attacker to perform a meddler-in-the-middle (MitM) attack to capture encrypted traffic between the Panorama management server and the firewalls it manages. With sufficient computing resources, the attacker could break encrypted communication and expose sensitive information that is shared between the management server and the firewalls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3387|2024-08-01T20:12:06.646Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3388|2024-08-01T20:12:06.617Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3388</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the GlobalProtect Gateway in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an authenticated attacker to impersonate another user and send network packets to internal assets. However, this vulnerability does not allow the attacker to receive response packets from those internal assets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3388|2024-08-01T20:12:06.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0011|2024-08-01T17:41:15.533Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0011</link>
      <description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Captive Portal feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables execution of malicious JavaScript (in the context of an authenticated Captive Portal users browser) if a user clicks on a malicious link, allowing phishing attacks that could lead to credential theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0011|2024-08-01T17:41:15.533Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0009|2024-08-01T17:41:15.849Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0009</link>
      <description>An improper verification vulnerability in the GlobalProtect gateway feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a malicious user with stolen credentials to establish a VPN connection from an unauthorized IP address.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0009|2024-08-01T17:41:15.849Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:32:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0010|2024-08-01T17:41:14.685Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0010</link>
      <description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the GlobalProtect portal feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables execution of malicious JavaScript (in the context of a users browser) if a user clicks on a malicious link, allowing phishing attacks that could lead to credential theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0010|2024-08-01T17:41:14.685Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:32:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0008|2024-08-01T17:41:15.529Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0008</link>
      <description>Web sessions in the management interface in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software do not expire in certain situations, making it susceptible to unauthorized access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0008|2024-08-01T17:41:15.529Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0007|2024-08-01T17:41:15.121Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0007</link>
      <description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a malicious authenticated read-write administrator to store a JavaScript payload using the web interface on Panorama appliances. This enables the impersonation of another authenticated administrator.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0007|2024-08-01T17:41:15.121Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5910|2024-07-12T03:55:26.351Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- expedition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5910</link>
      <description>Missing authentication for a critical function in Palo Alto Networks Expedition can lead to an Expedition admin account takeover for attackers with network access to Expedition.

Note: Expedition is a tool aiding in configuration migration, tuning, and enrichment. Configuration secrets, credentials, and other data imported into Expedition is at risk due to this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5910|2024-07-12T03:55:26.351Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:39:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5912|2024-07-11T14:37:33.165Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5912</link>
      <description>An improper file signature check in Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent may allow an attacker to bypass the Cortex XDR agent's executable blocking capabilities and run untrusted executables on the device. This issue can be leveraged to execute untrusted software without being detected or blocked.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5912|2024-07-11T14:37:33.165Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5911|2024-07-10T18:40:02.209Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5911</link>
      <description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Panorama software enables an authenticated read-write administrator with access to the web interface to disrupt system processes and crash the Panorama. Repeated attacks eventually cause the Panorama to enter maintenance mode, which requires manual intervention to bring the Panorama back online.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5911|2024-07-10T18:40:02.209Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5912|2024-07-10T18:40:16.240Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5912</link>
      <description>An improper file signature check in Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent may allow an attacker to bypass the Cortex XDR agent's executable blocking capabilities and run untrusted executables on the device. This issue can be leveraged to execute untrusted software without being detected or blocked.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5912|2024-07-10T18:40:16.240Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5913|2024-07-10T18:40:29.769Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5913</link>
      <description>An improper input validation vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an attacker with the ability to tamper with the physical file system to elevate privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5913|2024-07-10T18:40:29.769Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5910|2024-07-10T18:39:26.006Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- expedition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5910</link>
      <description>Missing authentication for a critical function in Palo Alto Networks Expedition can lead to an Expedition admin account takeover for attackers with network access to Expedition.

Note: Expedition is a tool aiding in configuration migration, tuning, and enrichment. Configuration secrets, credentials, and other data imported into Expedition is at risk due to this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5910|2024-07-10T18:39:26.006Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:39:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5909|2024-06-12T19:52:05.711Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5909</link>
      <description>A problem with a protection mechanism in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices allows a low privileged local Windows user to disable the agent. This issue may be leveraged by malware to disable the Cortex XDR agent and then to perform malicious activity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5909|2024-06-12T19:52:05.711Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:29:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5905|2024-06-12T17:58:51.232Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5905</link>
      <description>A problem with a protection mechanism in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices allows a local low privileged Windows user to disrupt some functionality of the agent. However, they are not able to disrupt Cortex XDR agent protection mechanisms using this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5905|2024-06-12T17:58:51.232Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:20:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0009|2024-06-04T17:59:03.434Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0009</link>
      <description>An improper verification vulnerability in the GlobalProtect gateway feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a malicious user with stolen credentials to establish a VPN connection from an unauthorized IP address.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0009|2024-06-04T17:59:03.434Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:32:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0008|2024-02-14T17:32:17.611Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0008</link>
      <description>Web sessions in the management interface in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software do not expire in certain situations, making it susceptible to unauthorized access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0008|2024-02-14T17:32:17.611Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0011|2024-02-14T17:32:34.809Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0011</link>
      <description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Captive Portal feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables execution of malicious JavaScript (in the context of an authenticated Captive Portal users browser) if a user clicks on a malicious link, allowing phishing attacks that could lead to credential theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0011|2024-02-14T17:32:34.809Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0007|2024-06-04T17:58:43.367Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0007</link>
      <description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a malicious authenticated read-write administrator to store a JavaScript payload using the web interface on Panorama appliances. This enables the impersonation of another authenticated administrator.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0007|2024-06-04T17:58:43.367Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0010|2024-06-04T17:58:38.476Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0010</link>
      <description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the GlobalProtect portal feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables execution of malicious JavaScript (in the context of a users browser) if a user clicks on a malicious link, allowing phishing attacks that could lead to credential theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0010|2024-06-04T17:58:38.476Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:32:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3382|2024-04-10T17:05:47.325Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3382</link>
      <description>A memory leak exists in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software that enables an attacker to send a burst of crafted packets through the firewall that eventually prevents the firewall from processing traffic. This issue applies only to PA-5400 Series devices that are running PAN-OS software with the SSL Forward Proxy feature enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3382|2024-04-10T17:05:47.325Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3383|2024-04-10T17:06:15.823Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3383</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in how Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software processes data received from Cloud Identity Engine (CIE) agents enables modification of User-ID groups. This impacts user access to network resources where users may be inappropriately denied or allowed access to resources based on your existing Security Policy rules.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3383|2024-04-10T17:06:15.823Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3388|2024-06-04T17:32:48.331Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3388</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the GlobalProtect Gateway in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an authenticated attacker to impersonate another user and send network packets to internal assets. However, this vulnerability does not allow the attacker to receive response packets from those internal assets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3388|2024-06-04T17:32:48.331Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3384|2024-06-04T17:32:38.411Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3384</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a remote attacker to reboot PAN-OS firewalls when receiving Windows New Technology LAN Manager (NTLM) packets from Windows servers. Repeated attacks eventually cause the firewall to enter maintenance mode, which requires manual intervention to bring the firewall back online.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3384|2024-06-04T17:32:38.411Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3385|2024-04-10T17:06:28.153Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3385</link>
      <description>A packet processing mechanism in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a remote attacker to reboot hardware-based firewalls. Repeated attacks eventually cause the firewall to enter maintenance mode, which requires manual intervention to bring the firewall back online.

This affects the following hardware firewall models:
- PA-5400 Series firewalls
- PA-7000 Series firewalls</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3385|2024-04-10T17:06:28.153Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3386|2024-06-07T15:13:59.508Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3386</link>
      <description>An incorrect string comparison vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software prevents Predefined Decryption Exclusions from functioning as intended. This can cause traffic destined for domains that are not specified in Predefined Decryption Exclusions to be unintentionally excluded from decryption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3386|2024-06-07T15:13:59.508Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3387|2024-06-04T17:31:52.758Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3387</link>
      <description>A weak (low bit strength) device certificate in Palo Alto Networks Panorama software enables an attacker to perform a meddler-in-the-middle (MitM) attack to capture encrypted traffic between the Panorama management server and the firewalls it manages. With sufficient computing resources, the attacker could break encrypted communication and expose sensitive information that is shared between the management server and the firewalls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3387|2024-06-04T17:31:52.758Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3400|2024-06-04T17:31:26.144Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3400</link>
      <description>A command injection as a result of arbitrary file creation vulnerability in the GlobalProtect feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software for specific PAN-OS versions and distinct feature configurations may enable an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code with root privileges on the firewall.

Cloud NGFW, Panorama appliances, and Prisma Access are not impacted by this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3400|2024-06-04T17:31:26.144Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 07:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2433|2024-03-13T17:51:45.578Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2433</link>
      <description>An improper authorization vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Panorama software enables an authenticated read-only administrator to upload files using the web interface and completely fill one of the disk partitions with those uploaded files, which prevents the ability to log into the web interface or to download PAN-OS, WildFire, and content images. 



This issue affects only the web interface of the management plane; the dataplane is unaffected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2433|2024-03-13T17:51:45.578Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 17:51:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2432|2024-03-13T17:51:33.908Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- globalprotect%20app</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2432</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation (PE) vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect app on Windows devices enables a local user to execute programs with elevated privileges. However, execution requires that the local user is able to successfully exploit a race condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2432|2024-03-13T17:51:33.908Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 17:51:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2431|2024-03-13T17:51:17.735Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- globalprotect%20app</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2431</link>
      <description>An issue in the Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect app enables a non-privileged user to disable the GlobalProtect app in configurations that allow a user to disable GlobalProtect with a passcode.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2431|2024-03-13T17:51:17.735Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 17:51:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5907|2024-06-12T16:26:39.742Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5907</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation (PE) vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices enables a local user to execute programs with elevated privileges. However, execution does require the local user to successfully exploit a race condition, which makes this vulnerability difficult to exploit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5907|2024-06-12T16:26:39.742Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:26:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5909|2024-06-12T16:29:23.822Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5909</link>
      <description>A problem with a protection mechanism in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices allows a low privileged local Windows user to disable the agent. This issue may be leveraged by malware to disable the Cortex XDR agent and then to perform malicious activity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5909|2024-06-12T16:29:23.822Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:29:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5908|2024-06-12T16:28:08.131Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- globalprotect%20app</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5908</link>
      <description>A problem with the Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect app can result in exposure of encrypted user credentials, used for connecting to GlobalProtect, in application logs. Normally, these application logs are only viewable by local users and are included when generating logs for troubleshooting purposes. This means that these encrypted credentials are exposed to recipients of the application logs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5908|2024-06-12T16:28:08.131Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5905|2024-06-12T16:22:57.869Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5905</link>
      <description>A problem with a protection mechanism in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices allows a local low privileged Windows user to disrupt some functionality of the agent. However, they are not able to disrupt Cortex XDR agent protection mechanisms using this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5905|2024-06-12T16:22:57.869Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:20:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5906|2024-06-12T16:22:38.881Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- prisma%20cloud%20compute</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5906</link>
      <description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Prisma Cloud Compute software enables a malicious administrator with add/edit permissions for identity providers to store a JavaScript payload using the web interface on Prisma Cloud Compute. This enables a malicious administrator to perform actions in the context of another user's browser when accessed by that other user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5906|2024-06-12T16:22:38.881Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:22:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5907|2024-06-12T17:59:59.312Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5907</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation (PE) vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices enables a local user to execute programs with elevated privileges. However, execution does require the local user to successfully exploit a race condition, which makes this vulnerability difficult to exploit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5907|2024-06-12T17:59:59.312Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:26:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5906|2024-06-12T18:17:47.920Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- prisma%20cloud%20compute</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5906</link>
      <description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Prisma Cloud Compute software enables a malicious administrator with add/edit permissions for identity providers to store a JavaScript payload using the web interface on Prisma Cloud Compute. This enables a malicious administrator to perform actions in the context of another user's browser when accessed by that other user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5906|2024-06-12T18:17:47.920Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:22:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5907|2024-06-14T03:56:05.821Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5907</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation (PE) vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices enables a local user to execute programs with elevated privileges. However, execution does require the local user to successfully exploit a race condition, which makes this vulnerability difficult to exploit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5907|2024-06-14T03:56:05.821Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:26:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0011|2024-07-05T17:21:19.407Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0011</link>
      <description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Captive Portal feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables execution of malicious JavaScript (in the context of an authenticated Captive Portal users browser) if a user clicks on a malicious link, allowing phishing attacks that could lead to credential theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0011|2024-07-05T17:21:19.407Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5913|2024-07-10T20:05:27.355Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5913</link>
      <description>An improper input validation vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an attacker with the ability to tamper with the physical file system to elevate privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5913|2024-07-10T20:05:27.355Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5910|2024-07-11T15:21:46.184Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- expedition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5910</link>
      <description>Missing authentication for a critical function in Palo Alto Networks Expedition can lead to an Expedition admin account takeover for attackers with network access to Expedition.

Note: Expedition is a tool aiding in configuration migration, tuning, and enrichment. Configuration secrets, credentials, and other data imported into Expedition is at risk due to this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5910|2024-07-11T15:21:46.184Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:39:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5911|2024-07-11T15:23:41.410Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5911</link>
      <description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Panorama software enables an authenticated read-write administrator with access to the web interface to disrupt system processes and crash the Panorama. Repeated attacks eventually cause the Panorama to enter maintenance mode, which requires manual intervention to bring the Panorama back online.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5911|2024-07-11T15:23:41.410Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3382|2024-07-31T20:04:14.546Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3382</link>
      <description>A memory leak exists in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software that enables an attacker to send a burst of crafted packets through the firewall that eventually prevents the firewall from processing traffic. This issue applies only to PA-5400 Series devices that are running PAN-OS software with the SSL Forward Proxy feature enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3382|2024-07-31T20:04:14.546Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2432|2024-08-01T19:11:53.524Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- globalprotect%20app</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2432</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation (PE) vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect app on Windows devices enables a local user to execute programs with elevated privileges. However, execution requires that the local user is able to successfully exploit a race condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2432|2024-08-01T19:11:53.524Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 17:51:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2431|2024-08-01T19:11:53.593Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- globalprotect%20app</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2431</link>
      <description>An issue in the Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect app enables a non-privileged user to disable the GlobalProtect app in configurations that allow a user to disable GlobalProtect with a passcode.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2431|2024-08-01T19:11:53.593Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 17:51:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2433|2024-08-01T19:11:53.562Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2433</link>
      <description>An improper authorization vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Panorama software enables an authenticated read-only administrator to upload files using the web interface and completely fill one of the disk partitions with those uploaded files, which prevents the ability to log into the web interface or to download PAN-OS, WildFire, and content images. 



This issue affects only the web interface of the management plane; the dataplane is unaffected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2433|2024-08-01T19:11:53.562Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 17:51:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5907|2024-08-01T21:25:03.047Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5907</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation (PE) vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices enables a local user to execute programs with elevated privileges. However, execution does require the local user to successfully exploit a race condition, which makes this vulnerability difficult to exploit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5907|2024-08-01T21:25:03.047Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:26:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5910|2024-08-01T21:25:03.163Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- expedition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5910</link>
      <description>Missing authentication for a critical function in Palo Alto Networks Expedition can lead to an Expedition admin account takeover for attackers with network access to Expedition.

Note: Expedition is a tool aiding in configuration migration, tuning, and enrichment. Configuration secrets, credentials, and other data imported into Expedition is at risk due to this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5910|2024-08-01T21:25:03.163Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:39:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5913|2024-08-01T21:25:02.975Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5913</link>
      <description>An improper input validation vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an attacker with the ability to tamper with the physical file system to elevate privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5913|2024-08-01T21:25:02.975Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5912|2024-08-01T21:25:03.178Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5912</link>
      <description>An improper file signature check in Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent may allow an attacker to bypass the Cortex XDR agent's executable blocking capabilities and run untrusted executables on the device. This issue can be leveraged to execute untrusted software without being detected or blocked.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5912|2024-08-01T21:25:03.178Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5908|2024-08-01T21:25:03.175Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- globalprotect%20app</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5908</link>
      <description>A problem with the Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect app can result in exposure of encrypted user credentials, used for connecting to GlobalProtect, in application logs. Normally, these application logs are only viewable by local users and are included when generating logs for troubleshooting purposes. This means that these encrypted credentials are exposed to recipients of the application logs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5908|2024-08-01T21:25:03.175Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5906|2024-08-01T21:25:03.163Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- prisma%20cloud%20compute</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5906</link>
      <description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Prisma Cloud Compute software enables a malicious administrator with add/edit permissions for identity providers to store a JavaScript payload using the web interface on Prisma Cloud Compute. This enables a malicious administrator to perform actions in the context of another user's browser when accessed by that other user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5906|2024-08-01T21:25:03.163Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:22:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5911|2024-08-01T21:25:03.109Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5911</link>
      <description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Panorama software enables an authenticated read-write administrator with access to the web interface to disrupt system processes and crash the Panorama. Repeated attacks eventually cause the Panorama to enter maintenance mode, which requires manual intervention to bring the Panorama back online.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5911|2024-08-01T21:25:03.109Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5905|2024-08-01T21:25:03.270Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5905</link>
      <description>A problem with a protection mechanism in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices allows a local low privileged Windows user to disrupt some functionality of the agent. However, they are not able to disrupt Cortex XDR agent protection mechanisms using this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5905|2024-08-01T21:25:03.270Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:20:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5909|2024-08-01T21:25:03.192Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5909</link>
      <description>A problem with a protection mechanism in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices allows a low privileged local Windows user to disable the agent. This issue may be leveraged by malware to disable the Cortex XDR agent and then to perform malicious activity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5909|2024-08-01T21:25:03.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:29:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
