<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Palo Alto Networks -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/palo%20alto%20networks/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Palo Alto Networks -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 18:24:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6790|2024-08-02T08:42:07.444Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6790</link>
      <description>A DOM-Based cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a remote attacker to execute a JavaScript payload in the context of an administrator’s browser when they view a specifically crafted link to the PAN-OS web interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6790|2024-08-02T08:42:07.444Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 18:15:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6792|2024-08-02T08:42:07.471Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6792</link>
      <description>An OS command injection vulnerability in the XML API of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an authenticated API user to disrupt system processes and potentially execute arbitrary code with limited privileges on the firewall.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6792|2024-08-02T08:42:07.471Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 18:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0006|2024-08-02T04:54:32.563Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- globalprotect%20app
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0006</link>
      <description>A local file deletion vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect app on Windows devices enables a user to delete system files from the endpoint with elevated privileges through a race condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0006|2024-08-02T04:54:32.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 16:41:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6794|2024-08-02T08:42:07.397Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6794</link>
      <description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an authenticated read-write administrator with access to the web interface to disrupt system processes and potentially execute arbitrary code with limited privileges on the firewall.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6794|2024-08-02T08:42:07.397Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 18:16:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0007|2024-08-02T04:54:32.609Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0007</link>
      <description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software on Panorama appliances enables an authenticated read-write administrator to store a JavaScript payload in the web interface that will execute in the context of another administrator’s browser when viewed.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0007|2024-08-02T04:54:32.609Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 16:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0005|2024-08-02T04:54:32.662Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0005</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an authenticated administrator to expose the plaintext values of secrets stored in the device configuration and encrypted API keys.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0005|2024-08-02T04:54:32.662Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 16:41:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0009|2024-08-02T04:54:32.577Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- globalprotect%20app
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0009</link>
      <description>A local privilege escalation (PE) vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect app on Windows enables a local user to execute programs with elevated privileges.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0009|2024-08-02T04:54:32.577Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 16:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6795|2024-08-02T08:42:08.431Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6795</link>
      <description>An OS command injection vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an authenticated administrator to disrupt system processes and potentially execute arbitrary code with limited privileges on the firewall.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6795|2024-08-02T08:42:08.431Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 18:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0010|2024-08-02T04:54:32.569Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0010</link>
      <description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Captive Portal feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software can allow a JavaScript payload to be executed in the context of an authenticated Captive Portal user’s browser when they click on a specifically crafted link.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0010|2024-08-02T04:54:32.569Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 16:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0003|2024-08-02T04:54:32.567Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xsoar
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0003</link>
      <description>A file disclosure vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XSOAR server software enables an authenticated user with access to the web interface to read local files from the server.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0003|2024-08-02T04:54:32.567Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 17:22:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0001|2024-08-02T04:54:32.569Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0001</link>
      <description>An information exposure vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices allows a local system administrator to disclose the admin password for the agent in cleartext, which bad actors can then use to execute privileged cytool commands that disable or uninstall the agent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0001|2024-08-02T04:54:32.569Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 17:20:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0004|2024-08-02T04:54:32.562Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0004</link>
      <description>A local file deletion vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an authenticated administrator to delete files from the local file system with elevated privileges.

These files can include logs and system components that impact the integrity and availability of PAN-OS software.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0004|2024-08-02T04:54:32.562Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 16:41:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3282|2024-08-02T06:48:08.442Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xsoar
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3282</link>
      <description>A local privilege escalation (PE) vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XSOAR engine software running on a Linux operating system enables a local attacker to execute programs with elevated privileges if the attacker has shell access to the engine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3282|2024-08-02T06:48:08.442Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 17:22:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-3280|2024-08-02T06:48:08.400Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3280</link>
      <description>A problem with a protection mechanism in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices allows a local user to disable the agent.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-3280|2024-08-02T06:48:08.400Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 16:13:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6789|2024-08-02T08:42:07.423Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6789</link>
      <description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a malicious authenticated read-write administrator to store a JavaScript payload using the web interface. Then, when viewed by a properly authenticated administrator, the JavaScript payload executes and disguises all associated actions as performed by that unsuspecting authenticated administrator.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6789|2024-08-02T08:42:07.423Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 18:26:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6793|2024-08-02T08:42:07.419Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6793</link>
      <description>An improper privilege management vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an authenticated read-only administrator to revoke active XML API keys from the firewall and disrupt XML API usage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6793|2024-08-02T08:42:07.419Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 18:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-38046|2024-08-02T17:30:13.102Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38046</link>
      <description>A vulnerability exists in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software that enables an authenticated administrator with the privilege to commit a specifically created configuration to read local files and resources from the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-38046|2024-08-02T17:30:13.102Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 16:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0008|2024-08-02T04:54:32.571Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0008</link>
      <description>A file disclosure vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an authenticated read-write administrator with access to the web interface to export local files from the firewall through a race condition.

</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0008|2024-08-02T04:54:32.571Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 16:34:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-6791|2024-08-02T08:42:07.408Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6791</link>
      <description>A credential disclosure vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an authenticated read-only administrator to obtain the plaintext credentials of stored external system integrations such as LDAP, SCP, RADIUS, TACACS+, and SNMP from the web interface.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-6791|2024-08-02T08:42:07.408Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 18:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0002|2024-08-02T04:54:32.601Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0002</link>
      <description>A problem with a protection mechanism in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices allows a local user to execute privileged cytool commands that disable or uninstall the agent.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0002|2024-08-02T04:54:32.601Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 17:21:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5909|2024-08-01T21:25:03.192Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5909</link>
      <description>A problem with a protection mechanism in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices allows a low privileged local Windows user to disable the agent. This issue may be leveraged by malware to disable the Cortex XDR agent and then to perform malicious activity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5909|2024-08-01T21:25:03.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:29:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5905|2024-08-01T21:25:03.270Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5905</link>
      <description>A problem with a protection mechanism in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices allows a local low privileged Windows user to disrupt some functionality of the agent. However, they are not able to disrupt Cortex XDR agent protection mechanisms using this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5905|2024-08-01T21:25:03.270Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:20:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5911|2024-08-01T21:25:03.109Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5911</link>
      <description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Panorama software enables an authenticated read-write administrator with access to the web interface to disrupt system processes and crash the Panorama. Repeated attacks eventually cause the Panorama to enter maintenance mode, which requires manual intervention to bring the Panorama back online.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5911|2024-08-01T21:25:03.109Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5906|2024-08-01T21:25:03.163Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- prisma%20cloud%20compute</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5906</link>
      <description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Prisma Cloud Compute software enables a malicious administrator with add/edit permissions for identity providers to store a JavaScript payload using the web interface on Prisma Cloud Compute. This enables a malicious administrator to perform actions in the context of another user's browser when accessed by that other user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5906|2024-08-01T21:25:03.163Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:22:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5908|2024-08-01T21:25:03.175Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- globalprotect%20app</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5908</link>
      <description>A problem with the Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect app can result in exposure of encrypted user credentials, used for connecting to GlobalProtect, in application logs. Normally, these application logs are only viewable by local users and are included when generating logs for troubleshooting purposes. This means that these encrypted credentials are exposed to recipients of the application logs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5908|2024-08-01T21:25:03.175Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5912|2024-08-01T21:25:03.178Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5912</link>
      <description>An improper file signature check in Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent may allow an attacker to bypass the Cortex XDR agent's executable blocking capabilities and run untrusted executables on the device. This issue can be leveraged to execute untrusted software without being detected or blocked.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5912|2024-08-01T21:25:03.178Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5913|2024-08-01T21:25:02.975Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5913</link>
      <description>An improper input validation vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an attacker with the ability to tamper with the physical file system to elevate privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5913|2024-08-01T21:25:02.975Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5910|2024-08-01T21:25:03.163Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- expedition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5910</link>
      <description>Missing authentication for a critical function in Palo Alto Networks Expedition can lead to an Expedition admin account takeover for attackers with network access to Expedition.

Note: Expedition is a tool aiding in configuration migration, tuning, and enrichment. Configuration secrets, credentials, and other data imported into Expedition is at risk due to this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5910|2024-08-01T21:25:03.163Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:39:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5907|2024-08-01T21:25:03.047Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5907</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation (PE) vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices enables a local user to execute programs with elevated privileges. However, execution does require the local user to successfully exploit a race condition, which makes this vulnerability difficult to exploit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5907|2024-08-01T21:25:03.047Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:26:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2433|2024-08-01T19:11:53.562Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2433</link>
      <description>An improper authorization vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Panorama software enables an authenticated read-only administrator to upload files using the web interface and completely fill one of the disk partitions with those uploaded files, which prevents the ability to log into the web interface or to download PAN-OS, WildFire, and content images. 



This issue affects only the web interface of the management plane; the dataplane is unaffected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2433|2024-08-01T19:11:53.562Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 17:51:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2431|2024-08-01T19:11:53.593Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- globalprotect%20app</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2431</link>
      <description>An issue in the Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect app enables a non-privileged user to disable the GlobalProtect app in configurations that allow a user to disable GlobalProtect with a passcode.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2431|2024-08-01T19:11:53.593Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 17:51:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2432|2024-08-01T19:11:53.524Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- globalprotect%20app</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2432</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation (PE) vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect app on Windows devices enables a local user to execute programs with elevated privileges. However, execution requires that the local user is able to successfully exploit a race condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2432|2024-08-01T19:11:53.524Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 17:51:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3382|2024-07-31T20:04:14.546Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3382</link>
      <description>A memory leak exists in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software that enables an attacker to send a burst of crafted packets through the firewall that eventually prevents the firewall from processing traffic. This issue applies only to PA-5400 Series devices that are running PAN-OS software with the SSL Forward Proxy feature enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3382|2024-07-31T20:04:14.546Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5911|2024-07-11T15:23:41.410Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5911</link>
      <description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Panorama software enables an authenticated read-write administrator with access to the web interface to disrupt system processes and crash the Panorama. Repeated attacks eventually cause the Panorama to enter maintenance mode, which requires manual intervention to bring the Panorama back online.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5911|2024-07-11T15:23:41.410Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5910|2024-07-11T15:21:46.184Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- expedition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5910</link>
      <description>Missing authentication for a critical function in Palo Alto Networks Expedition can lead to an Expedition admin account takeover for attackers with network access to Expedition.

Note: Expedition is a tool aiding in configuration migration, tuning, and enrichment. Configuration secrets, credentials, and other data imported into Expedition is at risk due to this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5910|2024-07-11T15:21:46.184Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:39:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5913|2024-07-10T20:05:27.355Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5913</link>
      <description>An improper input validation vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an attacker with the ability to tamper with the physical file system to elevate privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5913|2024-07-10T20:05:27.355Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0011|2024-07-05T17:21:19.407Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0011</link>
      <description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Captive Portal feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables execution of malicious JavaScript (in the context of an authenticated Captive Portal user’s browser) if a user clicks on a malicious link, allowing phishing attacks that could lead to credential theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0011|2024-07-05T17:21:19.407Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5907|2024-06-14T03:56:05.821Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5907</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation (PE) vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices enables a local user to execute programs with elevated privileges. However, execution does require the local user to successfully exploit a race condition, which makes this vulnerability difficult to exploit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5907|2024-06-14T03:56:05.821Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:26:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5906|2024-06-12T18:17:47.920Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- prisma%20cloud%20compute</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5906</link>
      <description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Prisma Cloud Compute software enables a malicious administrator with add/edit permissions for identity providers to store a JavaScript payload using the web interface on Prisma Cloud Compute. This enables a malicious administrator to perform actions in the context of another user's browser when accessed by that other user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5906|2024-06-12T18:17:47.920Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:22:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5907|2024-06-12T17:59:59.312Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5907</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation (PE) vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices enables a local user to execute programs with elevated privileges. However, execution does require the local user to successfully exploit a race condition, which makes this vulnerability difficult to exploit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5907|2024-06-12T17:59:59.312Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:26:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5906|2024-06-12T16:22:38.881Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- prisma%20cloud%20compute</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5906</link>
      <description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Prisma Cloud Compute software enables a malicious administrator with add/edit permissions for identity providers to store a JavaScript payload using the web interface on Prisma Cloud Compute. This enables a malicious administrator to perform actions in the context of another user's browser when accessed by that other user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5906|2024-06-12T16:22:38.881Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:22:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5905|2024-06-12T16:22:57.869Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5905</link>
      <description>A problem with a protection mechanism in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices allows a local low privileged Windows user to disrupt some functionality of the agent. However, they are not able to disrupt Cortex XDR agent protection mechanisms using this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5905|2024-06-12T16:22:57.869Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:20:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5908|2024-06-12T16:28:08.131Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- globalprotect%20app</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5908</link>
      <description>A problem with the Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect app can result in exposure of encrypted user credentials, used for connecting to GlobalProtect, in application logs. Normally, these application logs are only viewable by local users and are included when generating logs for troubleshooting purposes. This means that these encrypted credentials are exposed to recipients of the application logs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5908|2024-06-12T16:28:08.131Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5909|2024-06-12T16:29:23.822Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5909</link>
      <description>A problem with a protection mechanism in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices allows a low privileged local Windows user to disable the agent. This issue may be leveraged by malware to disable the Cortex XDR agent and then to perform malicious activity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5909|2024-06-12T16:29:23.822Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:29:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5907|2024-06-12T16:26:39.742Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5907</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation (PE) vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices enables a local user to execute programs with elevated privileges. However, execution does require the local user to successfully exploit a race condition, which makes this vulnerability difficult to exploit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5907|2024-06-12T16:26:39.742Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:26:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2431|2024-03-13T17:51:17.735Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- globalprotect%20app</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2431</link>
      <description>An issue in the Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect app enables a non-privileged user to disable the GlobalProtect app in configurations that allow a user to disable GlobalProtect with a passcode.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2431|2024-03-13T17:51:17.735Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 17:51:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2432|2024-03-13T17:51:33.908Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- globalprotect%20app</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2432</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation (PE) vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect app on Windows devices enables a local user to execute programs with elevated privileges. However, execution requires that the local user is able to successfully exploit a race condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2432|2024-03-13T17:51:33.908Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 17:51:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2433|2024-03-13T17:51:45.578Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2433</link>
      <description>An improper authorization vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Panorama software enables an authenticated read-only administrator to upload files using the web interface and completely fill one of the disk partitions with those uploaded files, which prevents the ability to log into the web interface or to download PAN-OS, WildFire, and content images. 



This issue affects only the web interface of the management plane; the dataplane is unaffected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2433|2024-03-13T17:51:45.578Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 17:51:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3400|2024-06-04T17:31:26.144Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3400</link>
      <description>A command injection as a result of arbitrary file creation vulnerability in the GlobalProtect feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software for specific PAN-OS versions and distinct feature configurations may enable an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code with root privileges on the firewall.

Cloud NGFW, Panorama appliances, and Prisma Access are not impacted by this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3400|2024-06-04T17:31:26.144Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 07:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3387|2024-06-04T17:31:52.758Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3387</link>
      <description>A weak (low bit strength) device certificate in Palo Alto Networks Panorama software enables an attacker to perform a meddler-in-the-middle (MitM) attack to capture encrypted traffic between the Panorama management server and the firewalls it manages. With sufficient computing resources, the attacker could break encrypted communication and expose sensitive information that is shared between the management server and the firewalls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3387|2024-06-04T17:31:52.758Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3386|2024-06-07T15:13:59.508Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3386</link>
      <description>An incorrect string comparison vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software prevents Predefined Decryption Exclusions from functioning as intended. This can cause traffic destined for domains that are not specified in Predefined Decryption Exclusions to be unintentionally excluded from decryption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3386|2024-06-07T15:13:59.508Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3385|2024-04-10T17:06:28.153Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3385</link>
      <description>A packet processing mechanism in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a remote attacker to reboot hardware-based firewalls. Repeated attacks eventually cause the firewall to enter maintenance mode, which requires manual intervention to bring the firewall back online.

This affects the following hardware firewall models:
- PA-5400 Series firewalls
- PA-7000 Series firewalls</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3385|2024-04-10T17:06:28.153Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3384|2024-06-04T17:32:38.411Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3384</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a remote attacker to reboot PAN-OS firewalls when receiving Windows New Technology LAN Manager (NTLM) packets from Windows servers. Repeated attacks eventually cause the firewall to enter maintenance mode, which requires manual intervention to bring the firewall back online.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3384|2024-06-04T17:32:38.411Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3388|2024-06-04T17:32:48.331Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3388</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the GlobalProtect Gateway in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an authenticated attacker to impersonate another user and send network packets to internal assets. However, this vulnerability does not allow the attacker to receive response packets from those internal assets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3388|2024-06-04T17:32:48.331Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3383|2024-04-10T17:06:15.823Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3383</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in how Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software processes data received from Cloud Identity Engine (CIE) agents enables modification of User-ID groups. This impacts user access to network resources where users may be inappropriately denied or allowed access to resources based on your existing Security Policy rules.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3383|2024-04-10T17:06:15.823Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3382|2024-04-10T17:05:47.325Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3382</link>
      <description>A memory leak exists in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software that enables an attacker to send a burst of crafted packets through the firewall that eventually prevents the firewall from processing traffic. This issue applies only to PA-5400 Series devices that are running PAN-OS software with the SSL Forward Proxy feature enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3382|2024-04-10T17:05:47.325Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0010|2024-06-04T17:58:38.476Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0010</link>
      <description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the GlobalProtect portal feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables execution of malicious JavaScript (in the context of a user’s browser) if a user clicks on a malicious link, allowing phishing attacks that could lead to credential theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0010|2024-06-04T17:58:38.476Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:32:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0007|2024-06-04T17:58:43.367Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0007</link>
      <description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a malicious authenticated read-write administrator to store a JavaScript payload using the web interface on Panorama appliances. This enables the impersonation of another authenticated administrator.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0007|2024-06-04T17:58:43.367Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0011|2024-02-14T17:32:34.809Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0011</link>
      <description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Captive Portal feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables execution of malicious JavaScript (in the context of an authenticated Captive Portal user’s browser) if a user clicks on a malicious link, allowing phishing attacks that could lead to credential theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0011|2024-02-14T17:32:34.809Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0008|2024-02-14T17:32:17.611Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0008</link>
      <description>Web sessions in the management interface in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software do not expire in certain situations, making it susceptible to unauthorized access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0008|2024-02-14T17:32:17.611Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0009|2024-06-04T17:59:03.434Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0009</link>
      <description>An improper verification vulnerability in the GlobalProtect gateway feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a malicious user with stolen credentials to establish a VPN connection from an unauthorized IP address.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0009|2024-06-04T17:59:03.434Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:32:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5905|2024-06-12T17:58:51.232Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5905</link>
      <description>A problem with a protection mechanism in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices allows a local low privileged Windows user to disrupt some functionality of the agent. However, they are not able to disrupt Cortex XDR agent protection mechanisms using this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5905|2024-06-12T17:58:51.232Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:20:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5909|2024-06-12T19:52:05.711Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5909</link>
      <description>A problem with a protection mechanism in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices allows a low privileged local Windows user to disable the agent. This issue may be leveraged by malware to disable the Cortex XDR agent and then to perform malicious activity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5909|2024-06-12T19:52:05.711Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:29:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5910|2024-07-10T18:39:26.006Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- expedition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5910</link>
      <description>Missing authentication for a critical function in Palo Alto Networks Expedition can lead to an Expedition admin account takeover for attackers with network access to Expedition.

Note: Expedition is a tool aiding in configuration migration, tuning, and enrichment. Configuration secrets, credentials, and other data imported into Expedition is at risk due to this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5910|2024-07-10T18:39:26.006Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:39:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5913|2024-07-10T18:40:29.769Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5913</link>
      <description>An improper input validation vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an attacker with the ability to tamper with the physical file system to elevate privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5913|2024-07-10T18:40:29.769Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5912|2024-07-10T18:40:16.240Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5912</link>
      <description>An improper file signature check in Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent may allow an attacker to bypass the Cortex XDR agent's executable blocking capabilities and run untrusted executables on the device. This issue can be leveraged to execute untrusted software without being detected or blocked.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5912|2024-07-10T18:40:16.240Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5911|2024-07-10T18:40:02.209Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5911</link>
      <description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Panorama software enables an authenticated read-write administrator with access to the web interface to disrupt system processes and crash the Panorama. Repeated attacks eventually cause the Panorama to enter maintenance mode, which requires manual intervention to bring the Panorama back online.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5911|2024-07-10T18:40:02.209Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5912|2024-07-11T14:37:33.165Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5912</link>
      <description>An improper file signature check in Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent may allow an attacker to bypass the Cortex XDR agent's executable blocking capabilities and run untrusted executables on the device. This issue can be leveraged to execute untrusted software without being detected or blocked.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5912|2024-07-11T14:37:33.165Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5910|2024-07-12T03:55:26.351Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- expedition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5910</link>
      <description>Missing authentication for a critical function in Palo Alto Networks Expedition can lead to an Expedition admin account takeover for attackers with network access to Expedition.

Note: Expedition is a tool aiding in configuration migration, tuning, and enrichment. Configuration secrets, credentials, and other data imported into Expedition is at risk due to this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5910|2024-07-12T03:55:26.351Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:39:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0007|2024-08-01T17:41:15.121Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0007</link>
      <description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a malicious authenticated read-write administrator to store a JavaScript payload using the web interface on Panorama appliances. This enables the impersonation of another authenticated administrator.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0007|2024-08-01T17:41:15.121Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0008|2024-08-01T17:41:15.529Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0008</link>
      <description>Web sessions in the management interface in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software do not expire in certain situations, making it susceptible to unauthorized access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0008|2024-08-01T17:41:15.529Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0010|2024-08-01T17:41:14.685Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0010</link>
      <description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the GlobalProtect portal feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables execution of malicious JavaScript (in the context of a user’s browser) if a user clicks on a malicious link, allowing phishing attacks that could lead to credential theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0010|2024-08-01T17:41:14.685Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:32:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0009|2024-08-01T17:41:15.849Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0009</link>
      <description>An improper verification vulnerability in the GlobalProtect gateway feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a malicious user with stolen credentials to establish a VPN connection from an unauthorized IP address.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0009|2024-08-01T17:41:15.849Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:32:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0011|2024-08-01T17:41:15.533Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0011</link>
      <description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Captive Portal feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables execution of malicious JavaScript (in the context of an authenticated Captive Portal user’s browser) if a user clicks on a malicious link, allowing phishing attacks that could lead to credential theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0011|2024-08-01T17:41:15.533Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3388|2024-08-01T20:12:06.617Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3388</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the GlobalProtect Gateway in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an authenticated attacker to impersonate another user and send network packets to internal assets. However, this vulnerability does not allow the attacker to receive response packets from those internal assets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3388|2024-08-01T20:12:06.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3387|2024-08-01T20:12:06.646Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3387</link>
      <description>A weak (low bit strength) device certificate in Palo Alto Networks Panorama software enables an attacker to perform a meddler-in-the-middle (MitM) attack to capture encrypted traffic between the Panorama management server and the firewalls it manages. With sufficient computing resources, the attacker could break encrypted communication and expose sensitive information that is shared between the management server and the firewalls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3387|2024-08-01T20:12:06.646Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3382|2024-08-01T20:12:06.637Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3382</link>
      <description>A memory leak exists in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software that enables an attacker to send a burst of crafted packets through the firewall that eventually prevents the firewall from processing traffic. This issue applies only to PA-5400 Series devices that are running PAN-OS software with the SSL Forward Proxy feature enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3382|2024-08-01T20:12:06.637Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3383|2024-08-01T20:12:06.566Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3383</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in how Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software processes data received from Cloud Identity Engine (CIE) agents enables modification of User-ID groups. This impacts user access to network resources where users may be inappropriately denied or allowed access to resources based on your existing Security Policy rules.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3383|2024-08-01T20:12:06.566Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3384|2024-08-01T20:12:06.484Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3384</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a remote attacker to reboot PAN-OS firewalls when receiving Windows New Technology LAN Manager (NTLM) packets from Windows servers. Repeated attacks eventually cause the firewall to enter maintenance mode, which requires manual intervention to bring the firewall back online.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3384|2024-08-01T20:12:06.484Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3386|2024-08-01T20:12:06.667Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3386</link>
      <description>An incorrect string comparison vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software prevents Predefined Decryption Exclusions from functioning as intended. This can cause traffic destined for domains that are not specified in Predefined Decryption Exclusions to be unintentionally excluded from decryption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3386|2024-08-01T20:12:06.667Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3385|2024-08-01T20:12:06.539Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3385</link>
      <description>A packet processing mechanism in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a remote attacker to reboot hardware-based firewalls. Repeated attacks eventually cause the firewall to enter maintenance mode, which requires manual intervention to bring the firewall back online.

This affects the following hardware firewall models:
- PA-5400 Series firewalls
- PA-7000 Series firewalls</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3385|2024-08-01T20:12:06.539Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3400|2024-08-01T20:12:06.667Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3400</link>
      <description>A command injection as a result of arbitrary file creation vulnerability in the GlobalProtect feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software for specific PAN-OS versions and distinct feature configurations may enable an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code with root privileges on the firewall.

Cloud NGFW, Panorama appliances, and Prisma Access are not impacted by this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3400|2024-08-01T20:12:06.667Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 07:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
