<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Palo Alto Networks -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/palo%20alto%20networks/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Palo Alto Networks -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 17:21:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3054|2024-08-03T16:45:50.998Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3054</link>
      <description>A time-of-check to time-of-use (TOCTOU) race condition vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS web interface enables an authenticated administrator with permission to upload plugins to execute arbitrary code with root user privileges. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.20; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.14; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.11; PAN-OS 10.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.0.7; PAN-OS 10.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.1.2. This issue does not affect Prisma Access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3054|2024-08-03T16:45:50.998Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3035|2024-08-03T16:45:50.739Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- bridgecrew%20checkov
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3035</link>
      <description>An unsafe deserialization vulnerability in Bridgecrew Checkov by Prisma Cloud allows arbitrary code execution when processing a malicious terraform file. This issue impacts Checkov 2.0 versions earlier than Checkov 2.0.26. Checkov 1.0 versions are not impacted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3035|2024-08-03T16:45:50.739Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3061|2024-08-03T16:45:51.381Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3061</link>
      <description>An OS command injection vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS command line interface (CLI) enables an authenticated administrator with access to the CLI to execute arbitrary OS commands to escalate privileges. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.20-h1; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.14-h3; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.11-h2; PAN-OS 10.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.0.8; PAN-OS 10.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.1.3. Prisma Access customers that have Prisma Access 2.1 firewalls are impacted by this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3061|2024-08-03T16:45:51.381Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3036|2024-08-03T16:45:50.755Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3036</link>
      <description>An information exposure through log file vulnerability exists in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software where secrets in PAN-OS XML API requests are logged in cleartext to the web server logs when the API is used incorrectly. This vulnerability applies only to PAN-OS appliances that are configured to use the PAN-OS XML API and exists only when a client includes a duplicate API parameter in API requests. Logged information includes the cleartext username, password, and API key of the administrator making the PAN-OS XML API request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3036|2024-08-03T16:45:50.755Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3051|2024-08-03T16:45:51.050Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xsoar
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3051</link>
      <description>An improper verification of cryptographic signature vulnerability exists in Cortex XSOAR SAML authentication that enables an unauthenticated network-based attacker with specific knowledge of the Cortex XSOAR instance to access protected resources and perform unauthorized actions on the Cortex XSOAR server. This issue impacts: Cortex XSOAR 5.5.0 builds earlier than 1578677; Cortex XSOAR 6.0.2 builds earlier than 1576452; Cortex XSOAR 6.1.0 builds earlier than 1578663; Cortex XSOAR 6.2.0 builds earlier than 1578666. All Cortex XSOAR instances hosted by Palo Alto Networks are protected from this vulnerability; no additional action is required for these instances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3051|2024-08-03T16:45:51.050Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3058|2024-08-03T16:45:50.919Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3058</link>
      <description>An OS command injection vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS web interface enables an authenticated administrator with permissions to use XML API the ability to execute arbitrary OS commands to escalate privileges. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.20-h1; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.14-h3; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.11-h2; PAN-OS 10.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.0.8; PAN-OS 10.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.1.3. This issue does not impact Prisma Access firewalls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3058|2024-08-03T16:45:50.919Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3037|2024-08-03T16:45:50.613Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3037</link>
      <description>An information exposure through log file vulnerability exists in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software where the connection details for a scheduled configuration export are logged in system logs. Logged information includes the cleartext username, password, and IP address used to export the PAN-OS configuration to the destination server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3037|2024-08-03T16:45:50.613Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3034|2024-08-03T16:45:50.845Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xsoar
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3034</link>
      <description>An information exposure through log file vulnerability exists in Cortex XSOAR software where the secrets configured for the SAML single sign-on (SSO) integration can be logged to the '/var/log/demisto/' server logs when testing the integration during setup. This logged information includes the private key and identity provider certificate used to configure the SAML SSO integration. This issue impacts: Cortex XSOAR 5.5.0 builds earlier than 98622; Cortex XSOAR 6.0.1 builds earlier than 830029; Cortex XSOAR 6.0.2 builds earlier than 98623; Cortex XSOAR 6.1.0 builds earlier than 848144.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3034|2024-08-03T16:45:50.845Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3043|2024-08-03T16:45:51.169Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- prisma%20cloud%20compute
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3043</link>
      <description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Prisma Cloud Compute web console that enables a remote attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the browser-based web console while an authenticated administrator is using that web interface. Prisma Cloud Compute SaaS versions were automatically upgraded to the fixed release. No additional action is required for these instances. This issue impacts: Prisma Cloud Compute 20.12 versions earlier than Prisma Cloud Compute 20.12.552; Prisma Cloud Compute 21.04 versions earlier than Prisma Cloud Compute 21.04.439.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3043|2024-08-03T16:45:51.169Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3047|2024-08-03T16:45:51.081Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3047</link>
      <description>A cryptographically weak pseudo-random number generator (PRNG) is used during authentication to the Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS web interface. This enables an authenticated attacker, with the capability to observe their own authentication secrets over a long duration on the PAN-OS appliance, to impersonate another authenticated web interface administrator's session. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.19; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.14; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.10; PAN-OS 10.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.0.4. PAN-OS 10.1 versions are not impacted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3047|2024-08-03T16:45:51.081Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3044|2024-08-03T16:45:50.915Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xsoar
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3044</link>
      <description>An improper authorization vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Cortex XSOAR enables a remote unauthenticated attacker with network access to the Cortex XSOAR server to perform unauthorized actions through the REST API. This issue impacts: Cortex XSOAR 6.1.0 builds later than 1016923 and earlier than 1271064; Cortex XSOAR 6.2.0 builds earlier than 1271065. This issue does not impact Cortex XSOAR 5.5.0, Cortex XSOAR 6.0.0, Cortex XSOAR 6.0.1, or Cortex XSOAR 6.0.2 versions. All Cortex XSOAR instances hosted by Palo Alto Networks are upgraded to resolve this vulnerability. No additional action is required for these instances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3044|2024-08-03T16:45:50.915Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3060|2024-08-03T16:45:51.222Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3060</link>
      <description>An OS command injection vulnerability in the Simple Certificate Enrollment Protocol (SCEP) feature of PAN-OS software allows an unauthenticated network-based attacker with specific knowledge of the firewall configuration to execute arbitrary code with root user privileges. The attacker must have network access to the GlobalProtect interfaces to exploit this issue. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.20-h1; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.14-h3; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.11-h2; PAN-OS 10.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.0.8; PAN-OS 10.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.1.3. Prisma Access customers with Prisma Access 2.1 Preferred and Prisma Access 2.1 Innovation firewalls are impacted by this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3060|2024-08-03T16:45:51.222Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3064|2024-08-03T16:45:51.363Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3064</link>
      <description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists in Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect portal and gateway interfaces that enables an unauthenticated network-based attacker to disrupt system processes and potentially execute arbitrary code with root privileges. The attacker must have network access to the GlobalProtect interface to exploit this issue. This issue impacts PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.17. Prisma Access customers are not impacted by this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3064|2024-08-03T16:45:51.363Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3063|2024-08-03T16:45:51.265Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3063</link>
      <description>An improper handling of exceptional conditions vulnerability exists in Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect portal and gateway interfaces that enables an unauthenticated network-based attacker to send specifically crafted traffic to a GlobalProtect interface that causes the service to stop responding. Repeated attempts to send this request result in denial of service to all PAN-OS services by restarting the device and putting it into maintenance mode. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.21; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.14-h4; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.11-h3; PAN-OS 10.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.0.8-h4; PAN-OS 10.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.1.3. Prisma Access customers are not impacted by this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3063|2024-08-03T16:45:51.265Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3050|2024-08-03T16:45:50.994Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3050</link>
      <description>An OS command injection vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS web interface enables an authenticated administrator to execute arbitrary OS commands to escalate privileges. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 9.0 version 9.0.10 through PAN-OS 9.0.14; PAN-OS 9.1 version 9.1.4 through PAN-OS 9.1.10; PAN-OS 10.0 version 10.0.7 and earlier PAN-OS 10.0 versions; PAN-OS 10.1 version 10.1.0 through PAN-OS 10.1.1. Prisma Access firewalls and firewalls running PAN-OS 8.1 versions are not impacted by this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3050|2024-08-03T16:45:50.994Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3062|2024-08-03T16:45:51.083Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3062</link>
      <description>An improper access control vulnerability in PAN-OS software enables an attacker with authenticated access to GlobalProtect portals and gateways to connect to the EC2 instance metadata endpoint for VM-Series firewalls hosted on Amazon AWS. Exploitation of this vulnerability enables an attacker to perform any operations allowed by the EC2 role in AWS. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.20 VM-Series firewalls; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.11 VM-Series firewalls; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.14 VM-Series firewalls; PAN-OS 10.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.0.8 VM-Series firewalls. Prisma Access customers are not impacted by this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3062|2024-08-03T16:45:51.083Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3053|2024-08-03T16:45:50.995Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3053</link>
      <description>An improper handling of exceptional conditions vulnerability exists in the Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS dataplane that enables an unauthenticated network-based attacker to send specifically crafted traffic through the firewall that causes the service to crash. Repeated attempts to send this request result in denial of service to all PAN-OS services by restarting the device and putting it into maintenance mode. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.20; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.14; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.9; PAN-OS 10.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.0.5. This issue does not affect Prisma Access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3053|2024-08-03T16:45:50.995Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3057|2024-08-03T16:45:51.156Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- globalprotect%20app
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3057</link>
      <description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect app that enables a man-in-the-middle attacker to disrupt system processes and potentially execute arbitrary code with SYSTEM privileges. This issue impacts: GlobalProtect app 5.1 versions earlier than GlobalProtect app 5.1.9 on Windows; GlobalProtect app 5.2 versions earlier than GlobalProtect app 5.2.8 on Windows; GlobalProtect app 5.2 versions earlier than GlobalProtect app 5.2.8 on the Universal Windows Platform; GlobalProtect app 5.3 versions earlier than GlobalProtect app 5.3.1 on Linux.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3057|2024-08-03T16:45:51.156Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3031|2024-08-03T16:45:50.688Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3031</link>
      <description>Padding bytes in Ethernet packets on PA-200, PA-220, PA-500, PA-800, PA-2000 Series, PA-3000 Series, PA-3200 Series, PA-5200 Series, and PA-7000 Series firewalls are not cleared before the data frame is created. This leaks a small amount of random information from the firewall memory into the Ethernet packets. An attacker on the same Ethernet subnet as the PAN-OS firewall is able to collect potentially sensitive information from these packets. This issue is also known as Etherleak and is detected by security scanners as CVE-2003-0001. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 version earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.18; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.12; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3031|2024-08-03T16:45:50.688Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3041|2024-08-03T16:45:50.941Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3041</link>
      <description>A local privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows platforms that enables an authenticated local Windows user to execute programs with SYSTEM privileges. This requires the user to have the privilege to create files in the Windows root directory or to manipulate key registry values. This issue impacts: Cortex XDR agent 5.0 versions earlier than Cortex XDR agent 5.0.11; Cortex XDR agent 6.1 versions earlier than Cortex XDR agent 6.1.8; Cortex XDR agent 7.2 versions earlier than Cortex XDR agent 7.2.3; All versions of Cortex XDR agent 7.2 without content update release 171 or a later version.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3041|2024-08-03T16:45:50.941Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3056|2024-08-03T16:45:51.085Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3056</link>
      <description>A memory corruption vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS GlobalProtect Clientless VPN enables an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code with root user privileges during SAML authentication. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.20; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.14; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.9; PAN-OS 10.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.0.1. Prisma Access customers with Prisma Access 2.1 Preferred firewalls are impacted by this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3056|2024-08-03T16:45:51.085Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3059|2024-08-03T16:45:51.098Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3059</link>
      <description>An OS command injection vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS management interface exists when performing dynamic updates. This vulnerability enables a man-in-the-middle attacker to execute arbitrary OS commands to escalate privileges. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.20-h1; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.14-h3; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.11-h2; PAN-OS 10.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.0.8; PAN-OS 10.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.1.3. Prisma Access customers that have Prisma Access 2.1 Preferred or Prisma Access 2.1 Innovation firewalls are impacted by this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3059|2024-08-03T16:45:51.098Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3055|2024-08-03T16:45:50.940Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3055</link>
      <description>An improper restriction of XML external entity (XXE) reference vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS web interface enables an authenticated administrator to read any arbitrary file from the file system and send a specifically crafted request to the firewall that causes the service to crash. Repeated attempts to send this request result in denial of service to all PAN-OS services by restarting the device and putting it into maintenance mode. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.20; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.14; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.10; PAN-OS 10.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.0.6. This issue does not affect Prisma Access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3055|2024-08-03T16:45:50.940Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3040|2024-08-03T16:45:50.966Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- bridgecrew%20checkov
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3040</link>
      <description>An unsafe deserialization vulnerability in Bridgecrew Checkov by Prisma Cloud allows arbitrary code execution when processing a malicious terraform file. This issue impacts Checkov 2.0 versions earlier than Checkov 2.0.139. Checkov 1.0 versions are not impacted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3040|2024-08-03T16:45:50.966Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3049|2024-08-03T16:45:50.963Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xsoar
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3049</link>
      <description>An improper authorization vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XSOAR server enables an authenticated network-based attacker with investigation read permissions to download files from incident investigations of which they are aware but are not a part of. This issue impacts: All Cortex XSOAR 5.5.0 builds; Cortex XSOAR 6.1.0 builds earlier than 12099345. This issue does not impact Cortex XSOAR 6.2.0 versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3049|2024-08-03T16:45:50.963Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3033|2024-08-03T16:45:50.754Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- prisma%20cloud%20compute
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3033</link>
      <description>An improper verification of cryptographic signature vulnerability exists in the Palo Alto Networks Prisma Cloud Compute console. This vulnerability enables an attacker to bypass signature validation during SAML authentication by logging in to the Prisma Cloud Compute console as any authorized user. This issue impacts: All versions of Prisma Cloud Compute 19.11, Prisma Cloud Compute 20.04, and Prisma Cloud Compute 20.09; Prisma Cloud Compute 20.12 before update 1. Prisma Cloud Compute SaaS version is not impacted by this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3033|2024-08-03T16:45:50.754Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3042|2024-08-03T16:45:50.872Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3042</link>
      <description>A local privilege escalation (PE) vulnerability exists in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows platforms that enables an authenticated local Windows user to execute programs with SYSTEM privileges. Exploiting this vulnerability requires the user to have file creation privilege in the Windows root directory (such as C:\). This issue impacts: All versions of Cortex XDR agent 6.1 without content update 181 or a later version; All versions of Cortex XDR agent 7.2 without content update 181 or a later version; All versions of Cortex XDR agent 7.3 without content update 181 or a later version. Cortex XDR agent 5.0 versions are not impacted by this issue. Content updates are required to resolve this issue and are automatically applied for the agent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3042|2024-08-03T16:45:50.872Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3048|2024-08-03T16:45:51.024Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3048</link>
      <description>Certain invalid URL entries contained in an External Dynamic List (EDL) cause the Device Server daemon (devsrvr) to stop responding. This condition causes subsequent commits on the firewall to fail and prevents administrators from performing commits and configuration changes even though the firewall remains otherwise functional. If the firewall then restarts, it results in a denial-of-service (DoS) condition and the firewall stops processing traffic. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.14; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.9; PAN-OS 10.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.0.5. PAN-OS 8.1 and PAN-OS 10.1 versions are not impacted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3048|2024-08-03T16:45:51.024Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3039|2024-08-03T16:45:51.031Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- prisma%20cloud%20compute
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3039</link>
      <description>An information exposure through log file vulnerability exists in the Palo Alto Networks Prisma Cloud Compute Console where a secret used to authorize the role of the authenticated user is logged to a debug log file. Authenticated Operator role and Auditor role users with access to the debug log files can use this secret to gain Administrator role access for their active session in Prisma Cloud Compute. Prisma Cloud Compute SaaS versions were automatically upgraded to the fixed release. This issue impacts all Prisma Cloud Compute versions earlier than Prisma Cloud Compute 21.04.412.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3039|2024-08-03T16:45:51.031Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3045|2024-08-03T16:45:51.191Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3045</link>
      <description>An OS command argument injection vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS web interface enables an authenticated administrator to read any arbitrary file from the file system. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.19; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.14; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.10. PAN-OS 10.0 and later versions are not impacted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3045|2024-08-03T16:45:51.191Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3052|2024-08-03T16:45:50.871Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3052</link>
      <description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Palo Alto Network PAN-OS web interface enables an authenticated network-based attacker to mislead another authenticated PAN-OS administrator to click on a specially crafted link that performs arbitrary actions in the PAN-OS web interface as the targeted authenticated administrator. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than 8.1.20; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than 9.0.14; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than 9.1.10; PAN-OS 10.0 versions earlier than 10.0.2. This issue does not affect Prisma Access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3052|2024-08-03T16:45:50.871Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3038|2024-08-03T16:45:50.745Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- globalprotect%20app
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3038</link>
      <description>A denial-of-service (DoS) vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect app on Windows systems allows a limited Windows user to send specifically-crafted input to the GlobalProtect app that results in a Windows blue screen of death (BSOD) error. This issue impacts: GlobalProtect app 5.1 versions earlier than GlobalProtect app 5.1.8; GlobalProtect app 5.2 versions earlier than GlobalProtect app 5.2.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3038|2024-08-03T16:45:50.745Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3032|2024-08-03T16:45:50.784Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3032</link>
      <description>An information exposure through log file vulnerability exists in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software where configuration secrets for the “http”, “email”, and “snmptrap” v3 log forwarding server profiles can be logged to the logrcvr.log system log. Logged information may include up to 1024 bytes of the configuration including the username and password in an encrypted form and private keys used in any certificate profiles set for log forwarding server profiles. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.18; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.12; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.4; PAN-OS 10.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.0.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3032|2024-08-03T16:45:50.784Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3046|2024-08-03T16:45:50.968Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3046</link>
      <description>An improper authentication vulnerability exists in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software that enables a SAML authenticated attacker to impersonate any other user in the GlobalProtect Portal and GlobalProtect Gateway when they are configured to use SAML authentication. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.19; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.14; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.9; PAN-OS 10.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.0.5. PAN-OS 10.1 versions are not impacted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3046|2024-08-03T16:45:50.968Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5909|2024-08-01T21:25:03.192Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5909</link>
      <description>A problem with a protection mechanism in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices allows a low privileged local Windows user to disable the agent. This issue may be leveraged by malware to disable the Cortex XDR agent and then to perform malicious activity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5909|2024-08-01T21:25:03.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:29:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5905|2024-08-01T21:25:03.270Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5905</link>
      <description>A problem with a protection mechanism in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices allows a local low privileged Windows user to disrupt some functionality of the agent. However, they are not able to disrupt Cortex XDR agent protection mechanisms using this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5905|2024-08-01T21:25:03.270Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:20:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5911|2024-08-01T21:25:03.109Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5911</link>
      <description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Panorama software enables an authenticated read-write administrator with access to the web interface to disrupt system processes and crash the Panorama. Repeated attacks eventually cause the Panorama to enter maintenance mode, which requires manual intervention to bring the Panorama back online.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5911|2024-08-01T21:25:03.109Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5906|2024-08-01T21:25:03.163Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- prisma%20cloud%20compute</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5906</link>
      <description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Prisma Cloud Compute software enables a malicious administrator with add/edit permissions for identity providers to store a JavaScript payload using the web interface on Prisma Cloud Compute. This enables a malicious administrator to perform actions in the context of another user's browser when accessed by that other user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5906|2024-08-01T21:25:03.163Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:22:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5908|2024-08-01T21:25:03.175Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- globalprotect%20app</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5908</link>
      <description>A problem with the Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect app can result in exposure of encrypted user credentials, used for connecting to GlobalProtect, in application logs. Normally, these application logs are only viewable by local users and are included when generating logs for troubleshooting purposes. This means that these encrypted credentials are exposed to recipients of the application logs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5908|2024-08-01T21:25:03.175Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5912|2024-08-01T21:25:03.178Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5912</link>
      <description>An improper file signature check in Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent may allow an attacker to bypass the Cortex XDR agent's executable blocking capabilities and run untrusted executables on the device. This issue can be leveraged to execute untrusted software without being detected or blocked.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5912|2024-08-01T21:25:03.178Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5913|2024-08-01T21:25:02.975Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5913</link>
      <description>An improper input validation vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an attacker with the ability to tamper with the physical file system to elevate privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5913|2024-08-01T21:25:02.975Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5910|2024-08-01T21:25:03.163Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- expedition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5910</link>
      <description>Missing authentication for a critical function in Palo Alto Networks Expedition can lead to an Expedition admin account takeover for attackers with network access to Expedition.

Note: Expedition is a tool aiding in configuration migration, tuning, and enrichment. Configuration secrets, credentials, and other data imported into Expedition is at risk due to this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5910|2024-08-01T21:25:03.163Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:39:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5907|2024-08-01T21:25:03.047Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5907</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation (PE) vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices enables a local user to execute programs with elevated privileges. However, execution does require the local user to successfully exploit a race condition, which makes this vulnerability difficult to exploit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5907|2024-08-01T21:25:03.047Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:26:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2433|2024-08-01T19:11:53.562Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2433</link>
      <description>An improper authorization vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Panorama software enables an authenticated read-only administrator to upload files using the web interface and completely fill one of the disk partitions with those uploaded files, which prevents the ability to log into the web interface or to download PAN-OS, WildFire, and content images. 



This issue affects only the web interface of the management plane; the dataplane is unaffected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2433|2024-08-01T19:11:53.562Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 17:51:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2431|2024-08-01T19:11:53.593Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- globalprotect%20app</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2431</link>
      <description>An issue in the Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect app enables a non-privileged user to disable the GlobalProtect app in configurations that allow a user to disable GlobalProtect with a passcode.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2431|2024-08-01T19:11:53.593Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 17:51:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2432|2024-08-01T19:11:53.524Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- globalprotect%20app</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2432</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation (PE) vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect app on Windows devices enables a local user to execute programs with elevated privileges. However, execution requires that the local user is able to successfully exploit a race condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2432|2024-08-01T19:11:53.524Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 17:51:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3382|2024-07-31T20:04:14.546Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3382</link>
      <description>A memory leak exists in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software that enables an attacker to send a burst of crafted packets through the firewall that eventually prevents the firewall from processing traffic. This issue applies only to PA-5400 Series devices that are running PAN-OS software with the SSL Forward Proxy feature enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3382|2024-07-31T20:04:14.546Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5911|2024-07-11T15:23:41.410Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5911</link>
      <description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Panorama software enables an authenticated read-write administrator with access to the web interface to disrupt system processes and crash the Panorama. Repeated attacks eventually cause the Panorama to enter maintenance mode, which requires manual intervention to bring the Panorama back online.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5911|2024-07-11T15:23:41.410Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5910|2024-07-11T15:21:46.184Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- expedition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5910</link>
      <description>Missing authentication for a critical function in Palo Alto Networks Expedition can lead to an Expedition admin account takeover for attackers with network access to Expedition.

Note: Expedition is a tool aiding in configuration migration, tuning, and enrichment. Configuration secrets, credentials, and other data imported into Expedition is at risk due to this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5910|2024-07-11T15:21:46.184Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:39:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5913|2024-07-10T20:05:27.355Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5913</link>
      <description>An improper input validation vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an attacker with the ability to tamper with the physical file system to elevate privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5913|2024-07-10T20:05:27.355Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0011|2024-07-05T17:21:19.407Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0011</link>
      <description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Captive Portal feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables execution of malicious JavaScript (in the context of an authenticated Captive Portal user’s browser) if a user clicks on a malicious link, allowing phishing attacks that could lead to credential theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0011|2024-07-05T17:21:19.407Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5907|2024-06-14T03:56:05.821Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5907</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation (PE) vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices enables a local user to execute programs with elevated privileges. However, execution does require the local user to successfully exploit a race condition, which makes this vulnerability difficult to exploit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5907|2024-06-14T03:56:05.821Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:26:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5906|2024-06-12T18:17:47.920Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- prisma%20cloud%20compute</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5906</link>
      <description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Prisma Cloud Compute software enables a malicious administrator with add/edit permissions for identity providers to store a JavaScript payload using the web interface on Prisma Cloud Compute. This enables a malicious administrator to perform actions in the context of another user's browser when accessed by that other user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5906|2024-06-12T18:17:47.920Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:22:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5907|2024-06-12T17:59:59.312Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5907</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation (PE) vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices enables a local user to execute programs with elevated privileges. However, execution does require the local user to successfully exploit a race condition, which makes this vulnerability difficult to exploit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5907|2024-06-12T17:59:59.312Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:26:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5906|2024-06-12T16:22:38.881Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- prisma%20cloud%20compute</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5906</link>
      <description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Prisma Cloud Compute software enables a malicious administrator with add/edit permissions for identity providers to store a JavaScript payload using the web interface on Prisma Cloud Compute. This enables a malicious administrator to perform actions in the context of another user's browser when accessed by that other user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5906|2024-06-12T16:22:38.881Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:22:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5905|2024-06-12T16:22:57.869Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5905</link>
      <description>A problem with a protection mechanism in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices allows a local low privileged Windows user to disrupt some functionality of the agent. However, they are not able to disrupt Cortex XDR agent protection mechanisms using this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5905|2024-06-12T16:22:57.869Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:20:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5908|2024-06-12T16:28:08.131Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- globalprotect%20app</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5908</link>
      <description>A problem with the Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect app can result in exposure of encrypted user credentials, used for connecting to GlobalProtect, in application logs. Normally, these application logs are only viewable by local users and are included when generating logs for troubleshooting purposes. This means that these encrypted credentials are exposed to recipients of the application logs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5908|2024-06-12T16:28:08.131Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5909|2024-06-12T16:29:23.822Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5909</link>
      <description>A problem with a protection mechanism in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices allows a low privileged local Windows user to disable the agent. This issue may be leveraged by malware to disable the Cortex XDR agent and then to perform malicious activity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5909|2024-06-12T16:29:23.822Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:29:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5907|2024-06-12T16:26:39.742Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5907</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation (PE) vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices enables a local user to execute programs with elevated privileges. However, execution does require the local user to successfully exploit a race condition, which makes this vulnerability difficult to exploit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5907|2024-06-12T16:26:39.742Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:26:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2431|2024-03-13T17:51:17.735Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- globalprotect%20app</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2431</link>
      <description>An issue in the Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect app enables a non-privileged user to disable the GlobalProtect app in configurations that allow a user to disable GlobalProtect with a passcode.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2431|2024-03-13T17:51:17.735Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 17:51:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2432|2024-03-13T17:51:33.908Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- globalprotect%20app</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2432</link>
      <description>A privilege escalation (PE) vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect app on Windows devices enables a local user to execute programs with elevated privileges. However, execution requires that the local user is able to successfully exploit a race condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2432|2024-03-13T17:51:33.908Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 17:51:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-2433|2024-03-13T17:51:45.578Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2433</link>
      <description>An improper authorization vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Panorama software enables an authenticated read-only administrator to upload files using the web interface and completely fill one of the disk partitions with those uploaded files, which prevents the ability to log into the web interface or to download PAN-OS, WildFire, and content images. 



This issue affects only the web interface of the management plane; the dataplane is unaffected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2433|2024-03-13T17:51:45.578Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 17:51:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3400|2024-06-04T17:31:26.144Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3400</link>
      <description>A command injection as a result of arbitrary file creation vulnerability in the GlobalProtect feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software for specific PAN-OS versions and distinct feature configurations may enable an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code with root privileges on the firewall.

Cloud NGFW, Panorama appliances, and Prisma Access are not impacted by this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3400|2024-06-04T17:31:26.144Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 07:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3387|2024-06-04T17:31:52.758Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3387</link>
      <description>A weak (low bit strength) device certificate in Palo Alto Networks Panorama software enables an attacker to perform a meddler-in-the-middle (MitM) attack to capture encrypted traffic between the Panorama management server and the firewalls it manages. With sufficient computing resources, the attacker could break encrypted communication and expose sensitive information that is shared between the management server and the firewalls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3387|2024-06-04T17:31:52.758Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3386|2024-06-07T15:13:59.508Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3386</link>
      <description>An incorrect string comparison vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software prevents Predefined Decryption Exclusions from functioning as intended. This can cause traffic destined for domains that are not specified in Predefined Decryption Exclusions to be unintentionally excluded from decryption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3386|2024-06-07T15:13:59.508Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3385|2024-04-10T17:06:28.153Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3385</link>
      <description>A packet processing mechanism in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a remote attacker to reboot hardware-based firewalls. Repeated attacks eventually cause the firewall to enter maintenance mode, which requires manual intervention to bring the firewall back online.

This affects the following hardware firewall models:
- PA-5400 Series firewalls
- PA-7000 Series firewalls</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3385|2024-04-10T17:06:28.153Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3384|2024-06-04T17:32:38.411Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3384</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a remote attacker to reboot PAN-OS firewalls when receiving Windows New Technology LAN Manager (NTLM) packets from Windows servers. Repeated attacks eventually cause the firewall to enter maintenance mode, which requires manual intervention to bring the firewall back online.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3384|2024-06-04T17:32:38.411Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3388|2024-06-04T17:32:48.331Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3388</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the GlobalProtect Gateway in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an authenticated attacker to impersonate another user and send network packets to internal assets. However, this vulnerability does not allow the attacker to receive response packets from those internal assets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3388|2024-06-04T17:32:48.331Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3383|2024-04-10T17:06:15.823Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3383</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in how Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software processes data received from Cloud Identity Engine (CIE) agents enables modification of User-ID groups. This impacts user access to network resources where users may be inappropriately denied or allowed access to resources based on your existing Security Policy rules.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3383|2024-04-10T17:06:15.823Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3382|2024-04-10T17:05:47.325Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3382</link>
      <description>A memory leak exists in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software that enables an attacker to send a burst of crafted packets through the firewall that eventually prevents the firewall from processing traffic. This issue applies only to PA-5400 Series devices that are running PAN-OS software with the SSL Forward Proxy feature enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3382|2024-04-10T17:05:47.325Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0010|2024-06-04T17:58:38.476Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0010</link>
      <description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the GlobalProtect portal feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables execution of malicious JavaScript (in the context of a user’s browser) if a user clicks on a malicious link, allowing phishing attacks that could lead to credential theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0010|2024-06-04T17:58:38.476Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:32:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0007|2024-06-04T17:58:43.367Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0007</link>
      <description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a malicious authenticated read-write administrator to store a JavaScript payload using the web interface on Panorama appliances. This enables the impersonation of another authenticated administrator.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0007|2024-06-04T17:58:43.367Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0011|2024-02-14T17:32:34.809Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0011</link>
      <description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Captive Portal feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables execution of malicious JavaScript (in the context of an authenticated Captive Portal user’s browser) if a user clicks on a malicious link, allowing phishing attacks that could lead to credential theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0011|2024-02-14T17:32:34.809Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0008|2024-02-14T17:32:17.611Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0008</link>
      <description>Web sessions in the management interface in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software do not expire in certain situations, making it susceptible to unauthorized access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0008|2024-02-14T17:32:17.611Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0009|2024-06-04T17:59:03.434Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0009</link>
      <description>An improper verification vulnerability in the GlobalProtect gateway feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a malicious user with stolen credentials to establish a VPN connection from an unauthorized IP address.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0009|2024-06-04T17:59:03.434Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:32:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5905|2024-06-12T17:58:51.232Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5905</link>
      <description>A problem with a protection mechanism in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices allows a local low privileged Windows user to disrupt some functionality of the agent. However, they are not able to disrupt Cortex XDR agent protection mechanisms using this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5905|2024-06-12T17:58:51.232Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:20:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5909|2024-06-12T19:52:05.711Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5909</link>
      <description>A problem with a protection mechanism in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices allows a low privileged local Windows user to disable the agent. This issue may be leveraged by malware to disable the Cortex XDR agent and then to perform malicious activity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5909|2024-06-12T19:52:05.711Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:29:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5910|2024-07-10T18:39:26.006Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- expedition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5910</link>
      <description>Missing authentication for a critical function in Palo Alto Networks Expedition can lead to an Expedition admin account takeover for attackers with network access to Expedition.

Note: Expedition is a tool aiding in configuration migration, tuning, and enrichment. Configuration secrets, credentials, and other data imported into Expedition is at risk due to this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5910|2024-07-10T18:39:26.006Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:39:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5913|2024-07-10T18:40:29.769Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5913</link>
      <description>An improper input validation vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an attacker with the ability to tamper with the physical file system to elevate privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5913|2024-07-10T18:40:29.769Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5912|2024-07-10T18:40:16.240Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5912</link>
      <description>An improper file signature check in Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent may allow an attacker to bypass the Cortex XDR agent's executable blocking capabilities and run untrusted executables on the device. This issue can be leveraged to execute untrusted software without being detected or blocked.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5912|2024-07-10T18:40:16.240Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5911|2024-07-10T18:40:02.209Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5911</link>
      <description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Panorama software enables an authenticated read-write administrator with access to the web interface to disrupt system processes and crash the Panorama. Repeated attacks eventually cause the Panorama to enter maintenance mode, which requires manual intervention to bring the Panorama back online.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5911|2024-07-10T18:40:02.209Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5912|2024-07-11T14:37:33.165Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xdr%20agent</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5912</link>
      <description>An improper file signature check in Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent may allow an attacker to bypass the Cortex XDR agent's executable blocking capabilities and run untrusted executables on the device. This issue can be leveraged to execute untrusted software without being detected or blocked.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5912|2024-07-11T14:37:33.165Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5910|2024-07-12T03:55:26.351Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- expedition</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5910</link>
      <description>Missing authentication for a critical function in Palo Alto Networks Expedition can lead to an Expedition admin account takeover for attackers with network access to Expedition.

Note: Expedition is a tool aiding in configuration migration, tuning, and enrichment. Configuration secrets, credentials, and other data imported into Expedition is at risk due to this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5910|2024-07-12T03:55:26.351Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:39:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0007|2024-08-01T17:41:15.121Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0007</link>
      <description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a malicious authenticated read-write administrator to store a JavaScript payload using the web interface on Panorama appliances. This enables the impersonation of another authenticated administrator.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0007|2024-08-01T17:41:15.121Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0008|2024-08-01T17:41:15.529Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0008</link>
      <description>Web sessions in the management interface in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software do not expire in certain situations, making it susceptible to unauthorized access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0008|2024-08-01T17:41:15.529Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0010|2024-08-01T17:41:14.685Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0010</link>
      <description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the GlobalProtect portal feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables execution of malicious JavaScript (in the context of a user’s browser) if a user clicks on a malicious link, allowing phishing attacks that could lead to credential theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0010|2024-08-01T17:41:14.685Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:32:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0009|2024-08-01T17:41:15.849Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0009</link>
      <description>An improper verification vulnerability in the GlobalProtect gateway feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a malicious user with stolen credentials to establish a VPN connection from an unauthorized IP address.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0009|2024-08-01T17:41:15.849Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:32:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0011|2024-08-01T17:41:15.533Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0011</link>
      <description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Captive Portal feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables execution of malicious JavaScript (in the context of an authenticated Captive Portal user’s browser) if a user clicks on a malicious link, allowing phishing attacks that could lead to credential theft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0011|2024-08-01T17:41:15.533Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3388|2024-08-01T20:12:06.617Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3388</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the GlobalProtect Gateway in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an authenticated attacker to impersonate another user and send network packets to internal assets. However, this vulnerability does not allow the attacker to receive response packets from those internal assets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3388|2024-08-01T20:12:06.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3387|2024-08-01T20:12:06.646Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3387</link>
      <description>A weak (low bit strength) device certificate in Palo Alto Networks Panorama software enables an attacker to perform a meddler-in-the-middle (MitM) attack to capture encrypted traffic between the Panorama management server and the firewalls it manages. With sufficient computing resources, the attacker could break encrypted communication and expose sensitive information that is shared between the management server and the firewalls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3387|2024-08-01T20:12:06.646Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3382|2024-08-01T20:12:06.637Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3382</link>
      <description>A memory leak exists in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software that enables an attacker to send a burst of crafted packets through the firewall that eventually prevents the firewall from processing traffic. This issue applies only to PA-5400 Series devices that are running PAN-OS software with the SSL Forward Proxy feature enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3382|2024-08-01T20:12:06.637Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3383|2024-08-01T20:12:06.566Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3383</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in how Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software processes data received from Cloud Identity Engine (CIE) agents enables modification of User-ID groups. This impacts user access to network resources where users may be inappropriately denied or allowed access to resources based on your existing Security Policy rules.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3383|2024-08-01T20:12:06.566Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3384|2024-08-01T20:12:06.484Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3384</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a remote attacker to reboot PAN-OS firewalls when receiving Windows New Technology LAN Manager (NTLM) packets from Windows servers. Repeated attacks eventually cause the firewall to enter maintenance mode, which requires manual intervention to bring the firewall back online.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3384|2024-08-01T20:12:06.484Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3386|2024-08-01T20:12:06.667Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3386</link>
      <description>An incorrect string comparison vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software prevents Predefined Decryption Exclusions from functioning as intended. This can cause traffic destined for domains that are not specified in Predefined Decryption Exclusions to be unintentionally excluded from decryption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3386|2024-08-01T20:12:06.667Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3385|2024-08-01T20:12:06.539Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3385</link>
      <description>A packet processing mechanism in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a remote attacker to reboot hardware-based firewalls. Repeated attacks eventually cause the firewall to enter maintenance mode, which requires manual intervention to bring the firewall back online.

This affects the following hardware firewall models:
- PA-5400 Series firewalls
- PA-7000 Series firewalls</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3385|2024-08-01T20:12:06.539Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3400|2024-08-01T20:12:06.667Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3400</link>
      <description>A command injection as a result of arbitrary file creation vulnerability in the GlobalProtect feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software for specific PAN-OS versions and distinct feature configurations may enable an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code with root privileges on the firewall.

Cloud NGFW, Panorama appliances, and Prisma Access are not impacted by this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3400|2024-08-01T20:12:06.667Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 07:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
