<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Palo Alto Networks -- Cortex XSOAR</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/palo%20alto%20networks/cortex%20xsoar.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Palo Alto Networks -- Cortex XSOAR</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 22:22:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-0020|2024-09-16T16:53:59.807Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xsoar
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-0020</link>
      <description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Palo Alto Network Cortex XSOAR web interface enables an authenticated network-based attacker to store a persistent javascript payload that will perform arbitrary actions in the Cortex XSOAR web interface on behalf of authenticated administrators who encounter the payload during normal operations. This issue impacts: All builds of Cortex XSOAR 6.1.0; Cortex XSOAR 6.2.0 builds earlier than build 1958888.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-0020|2024-09-16T16:53:59.807Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 18:10:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3044|2024-09-16T17:23:37.359Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xsoar
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3044</link>
      <description>An improper authorization vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Cortex XSOAR enables a remote unauthenticated attacker with network access to the Cortex XSOAR server to perform unauthorized actions through the REST API. This issue impacts: Cortex XSOAR 6.1.0 builds later than 1016923 and earlier than 1271064; Cortex XSOAR 6.2.0 builds earlier than 1271065. This issue does not impact Cortex XSOAR 5.5.0, Cortex XSOAR 6.0.0, Cortex XSOAR 6.0.1, or Cortex XSOAR 6.0.2 versions. All Cortex XSOAR instances hosted by Palo Alto Networks are upgraded to resolve this vulnerability. No additional action is required for these instances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3044|2024-09-16T17:23:37.359Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 17:15:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3049|2024-09-16T20:58:16.361Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xsoar
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3049</link>
      <description>An improper authorization vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XSOAR server enables an authenticated network-based attacker with investigation read permissions to download files from incident investigations of which they are aware but are not a part of. This issue impacts: All Cortex XSOAR 5.5.0 builds; Cortex XSOAR 6.1.0 builds earlier than 12099345. This issue does not impact Cortex XSOAR 6.2.0 versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3049|2024-09-16T20:58:16.361Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 17:10:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3034|2024-09-16T16:38:50.120Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- cortex%20xsoar
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3034</link>
      <description>An information exposure through log file vulnerability exists in Cortex XSOAR software where the secrets configured for the SAML single sign-on (SSO) integration can be logged to the '/var/log/demisto/' server logs when testing the integration during setup. This logged information includes the private key and identity provider certificate used to configure the SAML SSO integration. This issue impacts: Cortex XSOAR 5.5.0 builds earlier than 98622; Cortex XSOAR 6.0.1 builds earlier than 830029; Cortex XSOAR 6.0.2 builds earlier than 98623; Cortex XSOAR 6.1.0 builds earlier than 848144.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3034|2024-09-16T16:38:50.120Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 18:10:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
