<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Palo Alto Networks -- PAN-OS</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/palo%20alto%20networks/pan-os.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Palo Alto Networks -- PAN-OS</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 21:42:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3059|2024-09-16T17:03:16.819Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3059</link>
      <description>An OS command injection vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS management interface exists when performing dynamic updates. This vulnerability enables a man-in-the-middle attacker to execute arbitrary OS commands to escalate privileges. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.20-h1; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.14-h3; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.11-h2; PAN-OS 10.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.0.8; PAN-OS 10.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.1.3. Prisma Access customers that have Prisma Access 2.1 Preferred or Prisma Access 2.1 Innovation firewalls are impacted by this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3059|2024-09-16T17:03:16.819Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 17:10:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2038|2024-09-16T16:47:58.614Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2038</link>
      <description>An OS Command Injection vulnerability in the PAN-OS management interface that allows authenticated administrators to execute arbitrary OS commands with root privileges. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than 9.0.10; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than 9.1.4; PAN-OS 10.0 versions earlier than 10.0.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2038|2024-09-16T16:47:58.614Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 16:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3052|2024-09-16T20:02:59.171Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3052</link>
      <description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Palo Alto Network PAN-OS web interface enables an authenticated network-based attacker to mislead another authenticated PAN-OS administrator to click on a specially crafted link that performs arbitrary actions in the PAN-OS web interface as the targeted authenticated administrator. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than 8.1.20; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than 9.0.14; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than 9.1.10; PAN-OS 10.0 versions earlier than 10.0.2. This issue does not affect Prisma Access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3052|2024-09-16T20:02:59.171Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 17:10:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1980|2024-09-16T16:29:01.339Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1980</link>
      <description>A shell command injection vulnerability in the PAN-OS CLI allows a local authenticated user to escape the restricted shell and escalate privileges. This issue affects only PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.13. This issue does not affect PAN-OS 7.1, PAN-OS 9.0, or later PAN-OS versions. This issue is fixed in PAN-OS 8.1.13, and all later versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1980|2024-09-16T16:29:01.339Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 18:58:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3061|2024-09-16T17:49:25.709Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3061</link>
      <description>An OS command injection vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS command line interface (CLI) enables an authenticated administrator with access to the CLI to execute arbitrary OS commands to escalate privileges. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.20-h1; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.14-h3; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.11-h2; PAN-OS 10.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.0.8; PAN-OS 10.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.1.3. Prisma Access customers that have Prisma Access 2.1 firewalls are impacted by this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3061|2024-09-16T17:49:25.709Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 17:10:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10140|2024-09-16T18:39:24.873Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10140</link>
      <description>The PAN-OS Management Web Interface in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS 8.1.2 and earlier may allow an authenticated user to shut down all management sessions, resulting in all logged in users to be redirected to the login page. PAN-OS 6.1, PAN-OS 7.1 and PAN-OS 8.0 are NOT affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10140|2024-09-16T18:39:24.873Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2001|2024-09-16T20:48:20.875Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2001</link>
      <description>An external control of path and data vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS Panorama XSLT processing logic that allows an unauthenticated user with network access to PAN-OS management interface to write attacker supplied file on the system and elevate privileges. This issue affects: All PAN-OS 7.1 Panorama and 8.0 Panorama versions; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than 8.1.12 on Panorama; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than 9.0.6 on Panorama.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2001|2024-09-16T20:48:20.875Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 19:07:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3063|2024-09-16T20:26:42.141Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3063</link>
      <description>An improper handling of exceptional conditions vulnerability exists in Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect portal and gateway interfaces that enables an unauthenticated network-based attacker to send specifically crafted traffic to a GlobalProtect interface that causes the service to stop responding. Repeated attempts to send this request result in denial of service to all PAN-OS services by restarting the device and putting it into maintenance mode. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.21; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.14-h4; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.11-h3; PAN-OS 10.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.0.8-h4; PAN-OS 10.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.1.3. Prisma Access customers are not impacted by this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3063|2024-09-16T20:26:42.141Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 17:10:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2009|2024-09-16T18:07:53.255Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2009</link>
      <description>An external control of filename vulnerability in the SD WAN component of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS Panorama allows an authenticated administrator to send a request that results in the creation and write of an arbitrary file on all firewalls managed by the Panorama. In some cases this results in arbitrary code execution with root permissions. This issue affects: All versions of PAN-OS 7.1; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than 8.1.14; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than 9.0.7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2009|2024-09-16T18:07:53.255Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 19:07:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3053|2024-09-16T16:17:55.225Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3053</link>
      <description>An improper handling of exceptional conditions vulnerability exists in the Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS dataplane that enables an unauthenticated network-based attacker to send specifically crafted traffic through the firewall that causes the service to crash. Repeated attempts to send this request result in denial of service to all PAN-OS services by restarting the device and putting it into maintenance mode. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.20; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.14; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.9; PAN-OS 10.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.0.5. This issue does not affect Prisma Access.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3053|2024-09-16T16:17:55.225Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 17:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2029|2024-09-16T16:52:57.682Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2029</link>
      <description>An OS Command Injection vulnerability in the PAN-OS web management interface allows authenticated administrators to execute arbitrary OS commands with root privileges by sending a malicious request to generate new certificates for use in the PAN-OS configuration. This issue affects: All versions of PAN-OS 8.0; PAN-OS 7.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 7.1.26; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2029|2024-09-16T16:52:57.682Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 17:28:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3060|2024-09-16T18:56:09.537Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3060</link>
      <description>An OS command injection vulnerability in the Simple Certificate Enrollment Protocol (SCEP) feature of PAN-OS software allows an unauthenticated network-based attacker with specific knowledge of the firewall configuration to execute arbitrary code with root user privileges. The attacker must have network access to the GlobalProtect interfaces to exploit this issue. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.20-h1; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.14-h3; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.11-h2; PAN-OS 10.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.0.8; PAN-OS 10.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.1.3. Prisma Access customers with Prisma Access 2.1 Preferred and Prisma Access 2.1 Innovation firewalls are impacted by this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3060|2024-09-16T18:56:09.537Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 17:10:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3048|2024-09-16T19:31:48.430Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3048</link>
      <description>Certain invalid URL entries contained in an External Dynamic List (EDL) cause the Device Server daemon (devsrvr) to stop responding. This condition causes subsequent commits on the firewall to fail and prevents administrators from performing commits and configuration changes even though the firewall remains otherwise functional. If the firewall then restarts, it results in a denial-of-service (DoS) condition and the firewall stops processing traffic. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.14; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.9; PAN-OS 10.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.0.5. PAN-OS 8.1 and PAN-OS 10.1 versions are not impacted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3048|2024-09-16T19:31:48.430Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 17:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2015|2024-09-16T16:13:05.308Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2015</link>
      <description>A buffer overflow vulnerability in the PAN-OS management server allows authenticated users to crash system processes or potentially execute arbitrary code with root privileges. This issue affects: PAN-OS 7.1 versions earlier than 7.1.26; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than 8.1.13; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than 9.0.7; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than 9.1.1; All versions of PAN-OS 8.0.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2015|2024-09-16T16:13:05.308Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 19:07:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2014|2024-09-16T19:30:56.709Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2014</link>
      <description>An OS Command Injection vulnerability in PAN-OS management server allows authenticated users to inject and execute arbitrary shell commands with root privileges. This issue affects: All versions of PAN-OS 7.1 and 8.0; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than 8.1.14; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than 9.0.7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2014|2024-09-16T19:30:56.709Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 19:07:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2039|2024-09-16T17:54:09.808Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2039</link>
      <description>An uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS allows for a remote unauthenticated user to upload temporary files through the management web interface that are not properly deleted after the request is finished. It is possible for an attacker to disrupt the availability of the management web interface by repeatedly uploading files until available disk space is exhausted. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.16; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.10; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.4; PAN-OS 10.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.0.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2039|2024-09-16T17:54:09.808Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 16:45:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2028|2024-09-16T18:18:19.426Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2028</link>
      <description>An OS Command Injection vulnerability in PAN-OS management server allows authenticated administrators to execute arbitrary OS commands with root privileges when uploading a new certificate in FIPS-CC mode. This issue affects: All versions of PAN-OS 7.1 and PAN-OS 8.0; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.13; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2028|2024-09-16T18:18:19.426Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 17:28:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2044|2024-09-16T18:09:13.065Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2044</link>
      <description>An information exposure through log file vulnerability where an administrator's password or other sensitive information may be logged in cleartext while using the CLI in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software. The opcmdhistory.log file was introduced to track operational command (op-command) usage but did not mask all sensitive information. The opcmdhistory.log file is removed in PAN-OS 9.1 and later PAN-OS versions. Command usage is recorded, instead, in the req_stats.log file in PAN-OS 9.1 and later PAN-OS versions. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.16; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.10; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2044|2024-09-16T18:09:13.065Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 16:45:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2041|2024-09-16T19:47:23.091Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2041</link>
      <description>An insecure configuration of the appweb daemon of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS 8.1 allows a remote unauthenticated user to send a specifically crafted request to the device that causes the appweb service to crash. Repeated attempts to send this request result in denial of service to all PAN-OS services by restarting the device and putting it into maintenance mode. This issue impacts all versions of PAN-OS 8.0, and PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than 8.1.16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2041|2024-09-16T19:47:23.091Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 16:45:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2034|2024-09-16T19:46:13.523Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2034</link>
      <description>An OS Command Injection vulnerability in the PAN-OS GlobalProtect portal allows an unauthenticated network based attacker to execute arbitrary OS commands with root privileges. An attacker requires some knowledge of the firewall to exploit this issue. This issue can not be exploited if GlobalProtect portal feature is not enabled. This issue impacts PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.3; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.15; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.9; all versions of PAN-OS 8.0 and PAN-OS 7.1. Prisma Access services are not impacted by this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2034|2024-09-16T19:46:13.523Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 16:35:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2010|2024-09-16T16:33:43.415Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2010</link>
      <description>An OS command injection vulnerability in PAN-OS management interface allows an authenticated administrator to execute arbitrary OS commands with root privileges. This issue affects: All versions of PAN-OS 7.1 and 8.0; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than 8.1.14; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than 9.0.7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2010|2024-09-16T16:33:43.415Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 19:07:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2037|2024-09-16T19:15:01.275Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2037</link>
      <description>An OS Command Injection vulnerability in the PAN-OS management interface that allows authenticated administrators to execute arbitrary OS commands with root privileges. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.16; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.10; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2037|2024-09-16T19:15:01.275Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 16:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1975|2024-09-16T18:23:27.053Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1975</link>
      <description>Missing XML validation vulnerability in the PAN-OS web interface on Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software allows authenticated users to inject arbitrary XML that results in privilege escalation. This issue affects PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.12 and PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.6. This issue does not affect PAN-OS 7.1, PAN-OS 8.0, or PAN-OS 9.1 or later versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1975|2024-09-16T18:23:27.053Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 22:57:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2021|2024-09-16T20:58:19.017Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2021</link>
      <description>When Security Assertion Markup Language (SAML) authentication is enabled and the 'Validate Identity Provider Certificate' option is disabled (unchecked), improper verification of signatures in PAN-OS SAML authentication enables an unauthenticated network-based attacker to access protected resources. The attacker must have network access to the vulnerable server to exploit this vulnerability. This issue affects PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.3; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.9; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.15, and all versions of PAN-OS 8.0 (EOL). This issue does not affect PAN-OS 7.1. This issue cannot be exploited if SAML is not used for authentication. This issue cannot be exploited if the 'Validate Identity Provider Certificate' option is enabled (checked) in the SAML Identity Provider Server Profile. Resources that can be protected by SAML-based single sign-on (SSO) authentication are: GlobalProtect Gateway, GlobalProtect Portal, GlobalProtect Clientless VPN, Authentication and Captive Portal, PAN-OS next-generation firewalls (PA-Series, VM-Series) and Panorama web interfaces, Prisma Access In the case of GlobalProtect Gateways, GlobalProtect Portal, Clientless VPN, Captive Portal, and Prisma Access, an unauthenticated attacker with network access to the affected servers can gain access to protected resources if allowed by configured authentication and Security policies. There is no impact on the integrity and availability of the gateway, portal or VPN server. An attacker cannot inspect or tamper with sessions of regular users. In the worst case, this is a critical severity vulnerability with a CVSS Base Score of 10.0 (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:N). In the case of PAN-OS and Panorama web interfaces, this issue allows an unauthenticated attacker with network access to the PAN-OS or Panorama web interfaces to log in as an administrator and perform administrative actions. In the worst-case scenario, this is a critical severity vulnerability with a CVSS Base Score of 10.0 (CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H). If the web interfaces are only accessible to a restricted management network, then the issue is lowered to a CVSS Base Score of 9.6 (CVSS:3.1/AV:A/AC:L/PR:N/UI:N/S:C/C:H/I:H/A:H). Palo Alto Networks is not aware of any malicious attempts to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2021|2024-09-16T20:58:19.017Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 15:10:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-1997|2024-09-16T19:36:57.272Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-1997</link>
      <description>An open redirection vulnerability in the GlobalProtect component of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS allows an attacker to specify an arbitrary redirection target away from the trusted GlobalProtect gateway. If the user then successfully authenticates it will cause them to access an unexpected and potentially malicious website. This issue affects: PAN-OS 7.1 versions earlier than 7.1.26; PAN-OS 8.0 versions earlier than 8.0.14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-1997|2024-09-16T19:36:57.272Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 19:07:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-0022|2024-09-16T20:47:18.031Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-0022</link>
      <description>Usage of a weak cryptographic algorithm in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software where the password hashes of administrator and local user accounts are not created with a sufficient level of computational effort, which allows for password cracking attacks on accounts in normal (non-FIPS-CC) operational mode. An attacker must have access to the account password hashes to take advantage of this weakness and can acquire those hashes if they are able to gain access to the PAN-OS software configuration. Fixed versions of PAN-OS software use a secure cryptographic algorithm for account password hashes. This issue does not impact Prisma Access firewalls. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.21; All versions of PAN-OS 9.0; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.11; PAN-OS 10.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.0.7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-0022|2024-09-16T20:47:18.031Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 17:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-0030|2024-09-16T20:36:43.575Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-0030</link>
      <description>An authentication bypass vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS 8.1 web interface allows a network-based attacker with specific knowledge of the target firewall or Panorama appliance to impersonate an existing PAN-OS administrator and perform privileged actions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-0030|2024-09-16T20:36:43.575Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 16:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2000|2024-09-16T16:58:42.346Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2000</link>
      <description>An OS command injection and memory corruption vulnerability in the PAN-OS management web interface that allows authenticated administrators to disrupt system processes and potentially execute arbitrary code and OS commands with root privileges. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.16; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.10; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.4; PAN-OS 10.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.0.1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2000|2024-09-16T16:58:42.346Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 00:05:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3056|2024-09-16T20:36:56.323Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3056</link>
      <description>A memory corruption vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS GlobalProtect Clientless VPN enables an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code with root user privileges during SAML authentication. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.20; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.14; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.9; PAN-OS 10.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.0.1. Prisma Access customers with Prisma Access 2.1 Preferred firewalls are impacted by this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3056|2024-09-16T20:36:56.323Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 17:10:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2008|2024-09-16T17:08:04.547Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2008</link>
      <description>An OS command injection and external control of filename vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS allows authenticated administrators to execute code with root privileges or delete arbitrary system files and impact the system's integrity or cause a denial of service condition. This issue affects: All versions of PAN-OS 7.1 and 8.0; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than 8.1.14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2008|2024-09-16T17:08:04.547Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 19:07:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2006|2024-09-16T16:57:44.922Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2006</link>
      <description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the management server component of PAN-OS that allows an authenticated user to potentially execute arbitrary code with root privileges. This issue affects: All versions of PAN-OS 7.1 and 8.0; PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than 8.1.14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2006|2024-09-16T16:57:44.922Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 19:07:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2022|2024-09-16T17:08:08.587Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2022</link>
      <description>An information exposure vulnerability exists in Palo Alto Networks Panorama software that discloses the token for the Panorama web interface administrator's session to a managed device when the Panorama administrator performs a context switch into that device. This vulnerability allows an attacker to gain privileged access to the Panorama web interface. An attacker requires some knowledge of managed firewalls to exploit this issue. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.17; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.11; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2022|2024-09-16T17:08:08.587Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 00:05:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3031|2024-09-16T16:48:43.134Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3031</link>
      <description>Padding bytes in Ethernet packets on PA-200, PA-220, PA-500, PA-800, PA-2000 Series, PA-3000 Series, PA-3200 Series, PA-5200 Series, and PA-7000 Series firewalls are not cleared before the data frame is created. This leaks a small amount of random information from the firewall memory into the Ethernet packets. An attacker on the same Ethernet subnet as the PAN-OS firewall is able to collect potentially sensitive information from these packets. This issue is also known as Etherleak and is detected by security scanners as CVE-2003-0001. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 version earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.18; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.12; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3031|2024-09-16T16:48:43.134Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 18:10:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2020-2031|2024-09-16T17:58:42.448Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-2031</link>
      <description>An integer underflow vulnerability in the dnsproxyd component of the PAN-OS management interface allows authenticated administrators to issue a command from the command line interface that causes the component to stop responding. Repeated attempts to send this request result in denial of service to all PAN-OS services by restarting the device and putting it into maintenance mode. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.3. This issue does not impact PAN-OS 8.1, PAN-OS 9.0, or Prisma Access services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2020-2031|2024-09-16T17:58:42.448Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 16:35:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-0023|2024-09-16T19:05:33.962Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-0023</link>
      <description>An improper handling of exceptional conditions vulnerability exists in the DNS proxy feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software that enables a meddler-in-the-middle (MITM) to send specifically crafted traffic to the firewall that causes the service to restart unexpectedly. Repeated attempts to send this request result in denial-of-service to all PAN-OS services by restarting the device in maintenance mode. This issue does not impact Panorama appliances and Prisma Access customers. This issue impacts: PAN-OS 8.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 8.1.22; PAN-OS 9.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.0.16; PAN-OS 9.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 9.1.13; PAN-OS 10.0 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.0.10; PAN-OS 10.1 versions earlier than PAN-OS 10.1.5. This issue does not impact PAN-OS 10.2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-0023|2024-09-16T19:05:33.962Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 18:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8686|2024-09-11T18:48:53.965Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8686</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an authenticated administrator to bypass system restrictions and run arbitrary commands as root on the firewall.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8686|2024-09-11T18:48:53.965Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:34:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8691|2024-09-11T18:19:46.897Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8691</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the GlobalProtect portal in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a malicious authenticated GlobalProtect user to impersonate another GlobalProtect user. Active GlobalProtect users impersonated by an attacker who is exploiting this vulnerability are disconnected from GlobalProtect. Upon exploitation, PAN-OS logs indicate that the impersonated user authenticated to GlobalProtect, which hides the identity of the attacker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8691|2024-09-11T18:19:46.897Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:43:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8688|2024-09-11T18:24:45.419Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8688</link>
      <description>An improper neutralization of matching symbols vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS command line interface (CLI) enables authenticated administrators (including read-only administrators) with access to the CLI to to read arbitrary files on the firewall.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8688|2024-09-11T18:24:45.419Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:40:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8687|2024-09-11T18:25:14.604Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8687</link>
      <description>An information exposure vulnerability exists in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software that enables a GlobalProtect end user to learn both the configured GlobalProtect uninstall password and the configured disable or disconnect passcode. After the password or passcode is known, end users can uninstall, disable, or disconnect GlobalProtect even if the GlobalProtect app configuration would not normally permit them to do so.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8687|2024-09-11T18:25:14.604Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3385|2024-08-22T18:10:55.925Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3385</link>
      <description>A packet processing mechanism in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a remote attacker to reboot hardware-based firewalls. Repeated attacks eventually cause the firewall to enter maintenance mode, which requires manual intervention to bring the firewall back online.

This affects the following hardware firewall models:
- PA-5400 Series firewalls
- PA-7000 Series firewalls</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3385|2024-08-22T18:10:55.925Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5916|2024-08-14T16:41:15.812Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5916</link>
      <description>An information exposure vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a local system administrator to unintentionally disclose secrets, passwords, and tokens of external systems. A read-only administrator who has access to the config log, can read secrets, passwords, and tokens to external systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5916|2024-08-14T16:41:15.812Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:41:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3383|2024-08-09T20:22:18.991Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3383</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in how Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software processes data received from Cloud Identity Engine (CIE) agents enables modification of User-ID groups. This impacts user access to network resources where users may be inappropriately denied or allowed access to resources based on your existing Security Policy rules.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3383|2024-08-09T20:22:18.991Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3400|2024-08-01T20:12:06.667Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3400</link>
      <description>A command injection as a result of arbitrary file creation vulnerability in the GlobalProtect feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software for specific PAN-OS versions and distinct feature configurations may enable an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code with root privileges on the firewall.

Cloud NGFW, Panorama appliances, and Prisma Access are not impacted by this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3400|2024-08-01T20:12:06.667Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 07:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3385|2024-08-01T20:12:06.539Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3385</link>
      <description>A packet processing mechanism in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a remote attacker to reboot hardware-based firewalls. Repeated attacks eventually cause the firewall to enter maintenance mode, which requires manual intervention to bring the firewall back online.

This affects the following hardware firewall models:
- PA-5400 Series firewalls
- PA-7000 Series firewalls</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3385|2024-08-01T20:12:06.539Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3386|2024-08-01T20:12:06.667Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3386</link>
      <description>An incorrect string comparison vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software prevents Predefined Decryption Exclusions from functioning as intended. This can cause traffic destined for domains that are not specified in Predefined Decryption Exclusions to be unintentionally excluded from decryption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3386|2024-08-01T20:12:06.667Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3384|2024-08-01T20:12:06.484Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3384</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a remote attacker to reboot PAN-OS firewalls when receiving Windows New Technology LAN Manager (NTLM) packets from Windows servers. Repeated attacks eventually cause the firewall to enter maintenance mode, which requires manual intervention to bring the firewall back online.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3384|2024-08-01T20:12:06.484Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3383|2024-08-01T20:12:06.566Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3383</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in how Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software processes data received from Cloud Identity Engine (CIE) agents enables modification of User-ID groups. This impacts user access to network resources where users may be inappropriately denied or allowed access to resources based on your existing Security Policy rules.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3383|2024-08-01T20:12:06.566Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3382|2024-08-01T20:12:06.637Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3382</link>
      <description>A memory leak exists in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software that enables an attacker to send a burst of crafted packets through the firewall that eventually prevents the firewall from processing traffic. This issue applies only to PA-5400 Series devices that are running PAN-OS software with the SSL Forward Proxy feature enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3382|2024-08-01T20:12:06.637Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3387|2024-08-01T20:12:06.646Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3387</link>
      <description>A weak (low bit strength) device certificate in Palo Alto Networks Panorama software enables an attacker to perform a meddler-in-the-middle (MitM) attack to capture encrypted traffic between the Panorama management server and the firewalls it manages. With sufficient computing resources, the attacker could break encrypted communication and expose sensitive information that is shared between the management server and the firewalls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3387|2024-08-01T20:12:06.646Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3388|2024-08-01T20:12:06.617Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3388</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the GlobalProtect Gateway in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an authenticated attacker to impersonate another user and send network packets to internal assets. However, this vulnerability does not allow the attacker to receive response packets from those internal assets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3388|2024-08-01T20:12:06.617Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5911|2024-07-11T15:23:41.410Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5911</link>
      <description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Panorama software enables an authenticated read-write administrator with access to the web interface to disrupt system processes and crash the Panorama. Repeated attacks eventually cause the Panorama to enter maintenance mode, which requires manual intervention to bring the Panorama back online.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5911|2024-07-11T15:23:41.410Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5911|2024-07-10T18:40:02.209Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5911</link>
      <description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Panorama software enables an authenticated read-write administrator with access to the web interface to disrupt system processes and crash the Panorama. Repeated attacks eventually cause the Panorama to enter maintenance mode, which requires manual intervention to bring the Panorama back online.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5911|2024-07-10T18:40:02.209Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5913|2024-07-10T18:40:29.769Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5913</link>
      <description>An improper input validation vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an attacker with the ability to tamper with the physical file system to elevate privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5913|2024-07-10T18:40:29.769Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3382|2024-04-10T17:05:47.325Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3382</link>
      <description>A memory leak exists in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software that enables an attacker to send a burst of crafted packets through the firewall that eventually prevents the firewall from processing traffic. This issue applies only to PA-5400 Series devices that are running PAN-OS software with the SSL Forward Proxy feature enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3382|2024-04-10T17:05:47.325Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3383|2024-04-10T17:06:15.823Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3383</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in how Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software processes data received from Cloud Identity Engine (CIE) agents enables modification of User-ID groups. This impacts user access to network resources where users may be inappropriately denied or allowed access to resources based on your existing Security Policy rules.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3383|2024-04-10T17:06:15.823Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3388|2024-06-04T17:32:48.331Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3388</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the GlobalProtect Gateway in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an authenticated attacker to impersonate another user and send network packets to internal assets. However, this vulnerability does not allow the attacker to receive response packets from those internal assets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3388|2024-06-04T17:32:48.331Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3384|2024-06-04T17:32:38.411Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3384</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a remote attacker to reboot PAN-OS firewalls when receiving Windows New Technology LAN Manager (NTLM) packets from Windows servers. Repeated attacks eventually cause the firewall to enter maintenance mode, which requires manual intervention to bring the firewall back online.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3384|2024-06-04T17:32:38.411Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3385|2024-04-10T17:06:28.153Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3385</link>
      <description>A packet processing mechanism in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a remote attacker to reboot hardware-based firewalls. Repeated attacks eventually cause the firewall to enter maintenance mode, which requires manual intervention to bring the firewall back online.

This affects the following hardware firewall models:
- PA-5400 Series firewalls
- PA-7000 Series firewalls</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3385|2024-04-10T17:06:28.153Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3386|2024-06-07T15:13:59.508Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3386</link>
      <description>An incorrect string comparison vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software prevents Predefined Decryption Exclusions from functioning as intended. This can cause traffic destined for domains that are not specified in Predefined Decryption Exclusions to be unintentionally excluded from decryption.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3386|2024-06-07T15:13:59.508Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3387|2024-06-04T17:31:52.758Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3387</link>
      <description>A weak (low bit strength) device certificate in Palo Alto Networks Panorama software enables an attacker to perform a meddler-in-the-middle (MitM) attack to capture encrypted traffic between the Panorama management server and the firewalls it manages. With sufficient computing resources, the attacker could break encrypted communication and expose sensitive information that is shared between the management server and the firewalls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3387|2024-06-04T17:31:52.758Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3400|2024-06-04T17:31:26.144Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-3400</link>
      <description>A command injection as a result of arbitrary file creation vulnerability in the GlobalProtect feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software for specific PAN-OS versions and distinct feature configurations may enable an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code with root privileges on the firewall.

Cloud NGFW, Panorama appliances, and Prisma Access are not impacted by this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3400|2024-06-04T17:31:26.144Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 07:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5913|2024-07-10T20:05:27.355Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5913</link>
      <description>An improper input validation vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an attacker with the ability to tamper with the physical file system to elevate privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5913|2024-07-10T20:05:27.355Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-3382|2024-07-31T20:04:14.546Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3382</link>
      <description>A memory leak exists in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software that enables an attacker to send a burst of crafted packets through the firewall that eventually prevents the firewall from processing traffic. This issue applies only to PA-5400 Series devices that are running PAN-OS software with the SSL Forward Proxy feature enabled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-3382|2024-07-31T20:04:14.546Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5913|2024-08-01T21:25:02.975Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5913</link>
      <description>An improper input validation vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an attacker with the ability to tamper with the physical file system to elevate privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5913|2024-08-01T21:25:02.975Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5911|2024-08-01T21:25:03.109Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5911</link>
      <description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Panorama software enables an authenticated read-write administrator with access to the web interface to disrupt system processes and crash the Panorama. Repeated attacks eventually cause the Panorama to enter maintenance mode, which requires manual intervention to bring the Panorama back online.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5911|2024-08-01T21:25:03.109Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5913|2024-08-06T04:19:19.068Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5913</link>
      <description>An improper input validation vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an attacker with the ability to tamper with the physical file system to elevate privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5913|2024-08-06T04:19:19.068Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-5916|2024-08-14T18:25:01.965Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5916</link>
      <description>An information exposure vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a local system administrator to unintentionally disclose secrets, passwords, and tokens of external systems. A read-only administrator who has access to the config log, can read secrets, passwords, and tokens to external systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5916|2024-08-14T18:25:01.965Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:41:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8687|2024-09-11T16:40:21.066Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8687</link>
      <description>An information exposure vulnerability exists in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software that enables a GlobalProtect end user to learn both the configured GlobalProtect uninstall password and the configured disable or disconnect passcode. After the password or passcode is known, end users can uninstall, disable, or disconnect GlobalProtect even if the GlobalProtect app configuration would not normally permit them to do so.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8687|2024-09-11T16:40:21.066Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8688|2024-09-11T16:48:22.674Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8688</link>
      <description>An improper neutralization of matching symbols vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS command line interface (CLI) enables authenticated administrators (including read-only administrators) with access to the CLI to to read arbitrary files on the firewall.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8688|2024-09-11T16:48:22.674Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:40:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8691|2024-09-11T16:43:30.608Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8691</link>
      <description>A vulnerability in the GlobalProtect portal in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a malicious authenticated GlobalProtect user to impersonate another GlobalProtect user. Active GlobalProtect users impersonated by an attacker who is exploiting this vulnerability are disconnected from GlobalProtect. Upon exploitation, PAN-OS logs indicate that the impersonated user authenticated to GlobalProtect, which hides the identity of the attacker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8691|2024-09-11T16:43:30.608Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:43:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8686|2024-09-11T16:34:21.618Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8686</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an authenticated administrator to bypass system restrictions and run arbitrary commands as root on the firewall.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8686|2024-09-11T16:34:21.618Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:34:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-8686|2024-09-12T03:55:28.915Z -- palo%20alto%20networks -- pan-os</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8686</link>
      <description>A command injection vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an authenticated administrator to bypass system restrictions and run arbitrary commands as root on the firewall.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-8686|2024-09-12T03:55:28.915Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:34:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
