<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for ideaboxcreations -- PowerPack Addons for Elementor (Free Widgets, Extensions and Templates)</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ideaboxcreations/powerpack%20addons%20for%20elementor%20%28free%20widgets%2C%20extensions%20and%20templates%29.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for ideaboxcreations -- PowerPack Addons for Elementor (Free Widgets, Extensions and Templates)</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 07:20:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-5327|2024-05-30T06:48:08.180Z -- ideaboxcreations -- PowerPack Addons for Elementor (Free Widgets, Extensions and Templates)
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-5327</link><description>The PowerPack Addons for Elementor (Free Widgets, Extensions and Templates) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘pp_animated_gradient_bg_color’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.19 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-5327|2024-05-30T06:48:08.180Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 06:48:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2492|2024-04-09T18:58:33.548Z -- ideaboxcreations -- PowerPack Addons for Elementor (Free Widgets, Extensions and Templates)</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2492</link><description>The PowerPack Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Twitter Tweet widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.18 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2492|2024-04-09T18:58:33.548Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:58:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2491|2024-03-30T09:37:29.932Z -- ideaboxcreations -- PowerPack Addons for Elementor (Free Widgets, Extensions and Templates)</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2491</link><description>The PowerPack Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the *_html_tag* attribute of multiple widgets in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.17 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2491|2024-03-30T09:37:29.932Z</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 09:37:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1411|2024-02-20T18:56:32.905Z -- ideaboxcreations -- PowerPack Addons for Elementor (Free Widgets, Extensions and Templates)</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1411</link><description>The PowerPack Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the settings of the Twitter Buttons Widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.15 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1411|2024-02-20T18:56:32.905Z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 18:56:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1055|2024-02-07T06:46:55.779Z -- ideaboxcreations -- PowerPack Addons for Elementor (Free Widgets, Extensions and Templates)</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1055</link><description>The PowerPack Addons for Elementor (Free Widgets, Extensions and Templates) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's buttons in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied URL values. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1055|2024-02-07T06:46:55.779Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 06:46:55 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>