<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for Fortra -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/fortra/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for Fortra -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 22:22:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-4332|2024-06-03T17:38:54.516Z -- Fortra -- Tripwire Enterprise</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4332</link><description>An authentication bypass vulnerability has been identified in the REST and SOAP API components of Tripwire Enterprise (TE) 9.1.0 when TE is configured to use LDAP/Active Directory SAML authentication and its optional "Auto-synchronize LDAP Users, Roles, and Groups" feature is enabled. This vulnerability allows unauthenticated attackers to bypass authentication if a valid username is known. Exploitation of this vulnerability could allow remote attackers to gain privileged access to the APIs and lead to unauthorized information disclosure or modification.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4332|2024-06-03T17:38:54.516Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 17:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25156|2024-03-14T14:06:01.498Z -- Fortra -- GoAnywhere MFT</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25156</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in GoAnywhere MFT prior to 7.4.2 which allows attackers to circumvent endpoint-specific permission checks in the GoAnywhere Admin and Web Clients.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25156|2024-03-14T14:06:01.498Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 14:06:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25153|2024-03-13T14:10:36.029Z -- Fortra -- FileCatalyst</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25153</link><description>A directory traversal within the ‘ftpservlet’ of the FileCatalyst Workflow Web Portal allows files to be uploaded outside of the intended ‘uploadtemp’ directory with a specially crafted POST request. In situations where a file is successfully uploaded to web portal’s DocumentRoot, specially crafted JSP files could be used to execute code, including web shells.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25153|2024-03-13T14:10:36.029Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 14:10:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25154|2024-03-13T14:13:56.214Z -- Fortra -- FileCatalyst</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25154</link><description>Improper URL validation leads to path traversal in FileCatalyst Direct 3.8.8 and earlier allowing an encoded payload to cause the web server to return files located outside of the web root which may lead to data leakage.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25154|2024-03-13T14:13:56.214Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 14:13:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25155|2024-03-13T14:15:54.156Z -- Fortra -- FileCatalyst</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-25155</link><description>In FileCatalyst Direct 3.8.8 and earlier through 3.8.6, the web server does not properly sanitize illegal characters in a URL which is then displayed on a subsequent error page. A malicious actor could craft a URL which would then execute arbitrary code within an HTML script tag.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-25155|2024-03-13T14:15:54.156Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 14:15:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0204|2024-01-22T18:05:13.194Z -- Fortra -- GoAnywhere MFT</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0204</link><description>Authentication bypass in Fortra's GoAnywhere MFT prior to 7.4.1 allows an unauthorized user to create an admin user via the administration portal.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0204|2024-01-22T18:05:13.194Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 18:05:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0259|2024-03-28T14:31:07.986Z -- Fortra -- Robot Schedule Enterprise Agent</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-0259</link><description>Fortra's Robot Schedule Enterprise Agent for Windows prior to version 3.04 is susceptible to privilege escalation. A low-privileged user can overwrite the service executable. When the service is restarted, the replaced binary runs with local system privileges, allowing a low-privileged user to gain elevated privileges.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-0259|2024-03-28T14:31:07.986Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 14:31:07 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>