<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for The OpenNMS Group -- Horizon</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/the%20opennms%20group/horizon.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for The OpenNMS Group -- Horizon</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0872|2023-08-14T17:21:58.203Z -- the%20opennms%20group -- horizon
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0872</link>
      <description>The Horizon REST API includes a users endpoint in OpenMNS Horizon 31.0.8 and versions earlier than 32.0.2 on multiple platforms is vulnerable to elevation of privilege. The solution is to upgrade to Meridian 2023.1.6, 2022.1.19, 2021.1.30, 2020.1.38 or Horizon 32.0.2 or newer. Meridian and Horizon installation instructions state that they are intended for installation within an organization's private networks and should not be directly accessible from the Internet.

OpenNMS thanks Erik Wynter for reporting this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0872|2023-08-14T17:21:58.203Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 17:21:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0846|2023-02-27T18:56:27.133Z -- the%20opennms%20group -- horizon
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0846</link>
      <description>Unauthenticated, stored cross-site scripting in the display of alarm reduction keys in multiple versions of OpenNMS Horizon and Meridian could allow an attacker access to confidential session information. Users
should upgrade to Meridian 2023.1.0 or newer, or Horizon 31.0.4. Meridian and
Horizon installation instructions state that they are intended for installation
within an organization's private networks and should not be directly accessible
from the Internet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0846|2023-02-27T18:56:27.133Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 18:35:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-0871|2023-08-22T18:29:33.329Z -- the%20opennms%20group -- horizon
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-0871</link>
      <description>XXE injection in /rtc/post/ endpoint in OpenMNS Horizon 31.0.8 and versions earlier than 32.0.2 on multiple platforms is vulnerable to XML external entity (XXE) injection, which can be used for instance to force Horizon to make arbitrary HTTP requests to internal and external services. The solution is to upgrade to Meridian 2023.1.6, 2022.1.19, 2021.1.30, 2020.1.38 or Horizon 32.0.2 or newer. Meridian and Horizon installation instructions state that they are intended for installation within an organization's private networks and should not be directly accessible from the Internet. OpenNMS thanks Erik Wynter and Moshe Apelbaum for reporting this issue.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-0871|2023-08-22T18:29:33.329Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 16:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40612|2023-08-23T18:35:01.032Z -- the%20opennms%20group -- horizon
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40612</link>
      <description>In OpenMNS Horizon 31.0.8 and versions earlier than 32.0.2, the file editor which is accessible to any user with ROLE_FILESYSTEM_EDITOR privileges is vulnerable to XXE injection attacks. The solution is to upgrade to Meridian 2023.1.5 or Horizon 32.0.2 or newer. Meridian and Horizon installation instructions state that they are intended for installation within an organization's private networks and should not be directly accessible from the Internet. OpenNMS thanks Erik Wynter for reporting this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40612|2023-08-23T18:35:01.032Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 18:22:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40311|2023-08-14T17:31:29.877Z -- the%20opennms%20group -- horizon
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40311</link>
      <description>Multiple stored XSS were found on different JSP files with unsanitized parameters in OpenMNS Horizon 31.0.8 and versions earlier than 32.0.2 on multiple platforms that allow an attacker to store on database and then load on JSPs or Angular templates. The solution is to upgrade to Meridian 2023.1.6, 2022.1.19, 2021.1.30, 2020.1.38 or Horizon 32.0.2 or newer. Meridian and Horizon installation instructions state that they are intended for installation within an organization's private networks and should not be directly accessible from the Internet. OpenNMS thanks Jordi Miralles Comins for reporting this issue.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40311|2023-08-14T17:31:29.877Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 17:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40312|2023-08-14T17:35:26.710Z -- the%20opennms%20group -- horizon
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40312</link>
      <description>Multiple reflected XSS were found on different JSP files with unsanitized parameters in OpenMNS Horizon 31.0.8 and versions earlier than 32.0.2 on multiple platforms that an attacker can modify to craft a malicious XSS payload. The solution is to upgrade to Meridian 2023.1.6, 2022.1.19, 2021.1.30, 2020.1.38 or Horizon 32.0.2 or newer. Meridian and Horizon installation instructions state that they are intended for installation within an organization's private networks and should not be directly accessible from the Internet. OpenNMS thanks Jordi Miralles Comins for reporting this issue.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40312|2023-08-14T17:35:26.710Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 17:35:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40313|2023-08-17T18:24:08.866Z -- the%20opennms%20group -- horizon
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40313</link>
      <description>A BeanShell interpreter in remote server mode runs in OpenMNS Horizon versions earlier than 32.0.2 and in related Meridian versions which could allow arbitrary remote Java code execution. The solution is to upgrade to Meridian 2023.1.6, 2022.1.19, 2021.1.30, 2020.1.38 or Horizon 32.0.2 or newer. Meridian and Horizon installation instructions state that they are intended for installation within an organization's private networks and should not be directly accessible from the Internet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40313|2023-08-17T18:24:08.866Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 18:24:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40314|2023-11-16T21:14:07.488Z -- the%20opennms%20group -- horizon
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40314</link>
      <description>


Cross-site scripting in bootstrap.jsp in multiple versions of OpenNMS Meridian and Horizon allows an attacker access to confidential session information. The solution is to upgrade to Horizon 32.0.5 or newer and Meridian 2023.1.9 or newer










Meridian
and Horizon installation instructions state that they are intended for
installation within an organization's private networks and should not be
directly accessible from the Internet. 

OpenNMS thanks 

Moshe Apelbaum

 for reporting this issue.







</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40314|2023-11-16T21:14:07.488Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 21:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-40315|2023-08-17T19:04:01.437Z -- the%20opennms%20group -- horizon
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-40315</link>
      <description>In OpenMNS Horizon 31.0.8 and versions earlier than 32.0.2 and related Meridian versions, any user that has the ROLE_FILESYSTEM_EDITOR can easily escalate their privileges to ROLE_ADMIN or any other role. The solution is to upgrade to Meridian 2023.1.5 or Horizon 32.0.2 or newer. Meridian and Horizon installation instructions state that they are intended for installation within an organization's private networks and should not be directly accessible from the Internet. OpenNMS thanks Erik Wynter for reporting this issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-40315|2023-08-17T19:04:01.437Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 19:04:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
