<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for KubeOperator -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/kubeoperator/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for KubeOperator -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 21:22:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22463|2024-08-02T10:13:48.349Z -- kubeoperator -- kubepi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22463</link>
      <description>KubePi is a k8s panel. The jwt authentication function of KubePi through version 1.6.2 uses hard-coded Jwtsigkeys, resulting in the same Jwtsigkeys for all online projects. This means that an attacker can forge any jwt token to take over the administrator account of any online project. Furthermore, they may use the administrator to take over the k8s cluster of the target enterprise. `session.go`, the use of hard-coded JwtSigKey, allows an attacker to use this value to forge jwt tokens arbitrarily. The JwtSigKey is confidential and should not be hard-coded in the code. The vulnerability has been fixed in 1.6.3. In the patch, JWT key is specified in app.yml. If the user leaves it blank, a random key will be used. There are no workarounds aside from upgrading.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22463|2024-08-02T10:13:48.349Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 15:04:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22480|2024-08-02T10:13:48.545Z -- kubeoperator -- kubeoperator
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22480</link>
      <description>KubeOperator is an open source Kubernetes distribution focused on helping enterprises plan, deploy and operate production-level K8s clusters. In KubeOperator versions 3.16.3 and below, API interfaces with unauthorized entities and can leak sensitive information. This vulnerability could be used to take over the cluster under certain conditions. This issue has been patched in version 3.16.4.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22480|2024-08-02T10:13:48.545Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 00:03:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22479|2024-08-02T10:13:48.544Z -- kubeoperator -- kubepi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22479</link>
      <description>KubePi is a modern Kubernetes panel. A session fixation attack allows an attacker to hijack a legitimate user session, versions 1.6.3 and below are susceptible. A patch will be released in version 1.6.4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22479|2024-08-02T10:13:48.544Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 20:34:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-22478|2024-08-02T10:13:48.550Z -- kubeoperator -- kubepi
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22478</link>
      <description>KubePi is a modern Kubernetes panel. The API interfaces with unauthorized entities and may leak sensitive information. This issue has been patched in version 1.6.4. There are currently no known workarounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-22478|2024-08-02T10:13:48.550Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 00:22:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
