<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Contemporary Controls -- BASrouter BACnet BASRT-B</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/contemporary%20controls/basrouter%20bacnet%20basrt-b.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Contemporary Controls -- BASrouter BACnet BASRT-B</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 17:29:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-4292|2024-04-27T20:31:05.009Z -- contemporary%20controls -- basrouter%20bacnet%20basrt-b
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-4292</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Contemporary Controls BASrouter BACnet BASRT-B 2.7.2. Affected is an unknown function of the component Device-Communication-Control Service. The manipulation with the input 55ff0500370015f30104025506110afb7519035d0841e4bece257b6acfc71f leads to denial of service. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-262224. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.
Es wurde eine kritische Schwachstelle in Contemporary Controls BASrouter BACnet BASRT-B 2.7.2 entdeckt. Betroffen hiervon ist ein unbekannter Ablauf der Komponente Device-Communication-Control Service. Mittels Manipulieren mit der Eingabe 55ff0500370015f30104025506110afb7519035d0841e4bece257b6acfc71f mit unbekannten Daten kann eine denial of service-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Der Exploit steht zur öffentlichen Verfügung.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-4292|2024-04-27T20:31:05.009Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 20:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
