<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for getsentry -- all</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/getsentry/all.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for getsentry -- all</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 21:54:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-32474|2024-04-18T19:50:44.541Z -- getsentry -- sentry
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-32474</link><description>Sentry is an error tracking and performance monitoring platform. Prior to 24.4.1, when authenticating as a superuser to Sentry with a username and password, the password is leaked as cleartext in logs under the _event_: `auth-index.validate_superuser`. An attacker with access to the log data could use these leaked credentials to login to the Sentry system as superuser. Self-hosted users on affected versions should upgrade to 24.4.1 or later. Users can configure the logging level to exclude logs of the `INFO` level and only generate logs for levels at `WARNING` or more.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-32474|2024-04-18T19:50:44.541Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 19:50:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24829|2024-02-08T23:44:07.676Z -- getsentry -- sentry
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-24829</link><description>Sentry is an error tracking and performance monitoring platform. Sentry’s integration platform provides a way for external services to interact with Sentry. One of such integrations, the Phabricator integration (maintained by Sentry) with version &lt;=24.1.1 contains a constrained SSRF vulnerability. An attacker could make Sentry send POST HTTP requests to arbitrary URLs (including internal IP addresses) by providing an unsanitized input to the Phabricator integration. However, the body payload is constrained to a specific format. If an attacker has access to a Sentry instance, this allows them to: 1. interact with internal network; 2. scan local/remote ports. This issue has been fixed in Sentry self-hosted release 24.1.2, and has already been mitigated on sentry.io on February 8. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-24829|2024-02-08T23:44:07.676Z</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 23:44:07 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>