<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Tabit  -- Tabit</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/tabit/tabit.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Tabit  -- Tabit</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 17:22:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-34771|2024-08-03T09:22:09.837Z -- tabit -- tabit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34771</link>
      <description>Tabit - arbitrary SMS send on Tabits behalf. The resend OTP API of tabit allows an adversary to send messages on tabits behalf to anyone registered on the system - the API receives the parameters: phone number, and CustomMessage, We can use that API to craft malicious messages to any user of the system. In addition, the API probably has some kind of template injection potential. When entering {{OTP}} in the custom message field it is formatted into an OTP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-34771|2024-08-03T09:22:09.837Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-34774|2024-08-03T09:22:10.174Z -- tabit -- tabit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34774</link>
      <description>Tabit - Arbitrary account modification. One of the endpoints mapped by the tiny URL, was a page where an adversary can modify personal details, such as email addresses and phone numbers of a specific user in a restaurant's loyalty program. Possibly allowing account takeover (the mail can be used to reset password).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-34774|2024-08-03T09:22:10.174Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-34775|2024-08-03T09:22:10.692Z -- tabit -- tabit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34775</link>
      <description>Tabit - Excessive data exposure. Another endpoint mapped by the tiny url, was one for reservation cancellation, containing the MongoDB ID of the reservation, and organization. This can be used to query the http://tgm-api.tabit.cloud/rsv/management/{reservationId}?organization={orgId} API which returns a lot of data regarding the reservation (OWASP: API3): Name, mail, phone number, the number of visits of the user to this specific restaurant, the money he spent there, the money he spent on alcohol, whether he left a deposit etc. This information can easily be used for a phishing attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-34775|2024-08-03T09:22:10.692Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-34776|2024-08-03T09:22:10.411Z -- tabit -- tabit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34776</link>
      <description>Tabit - giftcard stealth. Several APIs on the web system display, without authorization, sensitive information such as health statements, previous bills in a specific restaurant, alcohol consumption and smoking habits. Each of the described APIs, has in its URL one or more MongoDB ID which is not so simple to enumerate. However, they each receive a 'tiny URL' in tabits domain, in the form of https://tbit.be/{suffix} with suffix being a 5 character long string containing numbers, lower and upper case letters. It is not so simple to enumerate them all, but really easy to find some that work and lead to a personal endpoint. Furthermore, the redirect URL disclosed the MongoDB IDs discussed above, and we could use them to query other endpoints disclosing more personal information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-34776|2024-08-03T09:22:10.411Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-34773|2024-08-03T09:22:09.947Z -- tabit -- tabit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34773</link>
      <description>Tabit - HTTP Method manipulation. https://bridge.tabit.cloud/configuration/addresses-query - can be POST-ed to add addresses to the DB. This is an example of OWASP:API8 – Injection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-34773|2024-08-03T09:22:09.947Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-34772|2024-08-03T09:22:10.297Z -- tabit -- tabit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34772</link>
      <description>Tabit - password enumeration. Description: Tabit - password enumeration. The passwords for the Tabit system is a 4 digit OTP. One can resend OTP and try logging in indefinitely. Once again, this is an example of OWASP: API4 - Rate limiting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-34772|2024-08-03T09:22:10.297Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-34770|2024-08-03T09:22:09.917Z -- tabit -- tabit
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34770</link>
      <description>Tabit - sensitive information disclosure. Several APIs on the web system display, without authorization, sensitive information such as health statements, previous bills in a specific restaurant, alcohol consumption and smoking habits. Each of the described API’s, has in its URL one or more MongoDB ID which is not so simple to enumerate. However, they each receive a ‘tiny URL’ in Tabit’s domain, in the form of https://tbit.be/{suffix} with suffix being a 5 characters long string containing numbers, lower- and upper-case letters. It is not so simple to enumerate them all, but really easy to find some that work and lead to a personal endpoint. This is both an example of OWASP: API4 - rate limiting and OWASP: API1 - Broken object level authorization. Furthermore, the redirect URL disclosed the MongoDB IDs discussed above, and we could use them to query other endpoints disclosing more personal information. For example: The URL https://tabitisrael.co.il/online-reservations/health-statement?orgId={org_id}&amp;healthStatementId={health_statement_id} is used to invite friends to fill a health statement before attending the restaurant. We can use the health_statement_id to access the https://tgm-api.tabit.cloud/health-statement/{health_statement_id} API which disclose medical information as well as id number.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-34770|2024-08-03T09:22:09.917Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
