<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for contiki-ng -- contiki-ng</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/contiki-ng/contiki-ng.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for contiki-ng -- contiki-ng</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 13:24:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-28116|2024-08-02T12:30:24.192Z -- contiki-ng -- contiki-ng
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28116</link>
      <description>Contiki-NG is an open-source, cross-platform operating system for internet of things (IoT) devices. In versions 4.8 and prior, an out-of-bounds write can occur in the BLE L2CAP module of the Contiki-NG operating system.  The network stack of Contiki-NG uses a global buffer (packetbuf) for processing of packets, with the size of PACKETBUF_SIZE. In particular, when using the BLE L2CAP module with the default configuration, the PACKETBUF_SIZE value becomes larger then the actual size of the packetbuf.  When large packets are processed by the L2CAP module, a buffer overflow can therefore occur when copying the packet data to the packetbuf. The vulnerability has been patched in the "develop" branch of Contiki-NG, and will be included in release 4.9. The problem can be worked around by applying the patch manually.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-28116|2024-08-02T12:30:24.192Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 21:22:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-23609|2024-08-02T10:35:33.614Z -- contiki-ng -- contiki-ng
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23609</link>
      <description>Contiki-NG is an open-source, cross-platform operating system for Next-Generation IoT devices. Versions prior to and including 4.8 are vulnerable to an out-of-bounds write that can occur in the BLE-L2CAP module. The Bluetooth Low Energy - Logical Link Control and Adaptation Layer Protocol (BLE-L2CAP) module handles fragmentation of packets up the configured MTU size. When fragments are reassembled, they are stored in a packet buffer of a configurable size, but there is no check to verify that the packet buffer is large enough to hold the reassembled packet. In Contiki-NG's default configuration, it is possible that an out-of-bounds write of up to 1152 bytes occurs. The vulnerability has been patched in the "develop" branch of Contiki-NG, and will be included in release 4.9. The problem can be fixed by applying the patch in Contiki-NG pull request #2254 prior to the release of version 4.9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-23609|2024-08-02T10:35:33.614Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 06:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50926|2024-07-16T18:23:16.224Z -- contiki-ng -- contiki-ng</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50926</link>
      <description>Contiki-NG is an open-source, cross-platform operating system for Next-Generation IoT devices. An out-of-bounds read can be caused by an incoming DIO message when using the RPL-Lite implementation in the Contiki-NG operating system. More specifically, the prefix information of the DIO message contains a field that specifies the length of an IPv6 address prefix. The value of this field is not validated, which means that an attacker can set a value that is longer than the maximum prefix length. Subsequently, a memcmp function call that compares different prefixes can be called with a length argument that surpasses the boundary of the array allocated for the prefix, causing an out-of-bounds read. The problem has been patched in the "develop" branch of Contiki-NG, and is expected to be included in the next release. Users are advised to update as soon as they are able to or to manually apply the changes in Contiki-NG pull request #2721.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50926|2024-07-16T18:23:16.224Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 19:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50927|2024-02-14T19:22:05.243Z -- contiki-ng -- contiki-ng</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50927</link>
      <description>Contiki-NG is an open-source, cross-platform operating system for Next-Generation IoT devices. An attacker can trigger out-of-bounds reads in the RPL-Lite implementation of the RPL protocol in the Contiki-NG operating system. This vulnerability is caused by insufficient control of the lengths for DIO and DAO messages, in particular when they contain RPL sub-option headers. The problem has been patched in Contiki-NG 4.9. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should manually apply the code changes in PR #2484.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50927|2024-02-14T19:22:05.243Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 19:22:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50926|2024-02-14T19:28:11.556Z -- contiki-ng -- contiki-ng</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-50926</link>
      <description>Contiki-NG is an open-source, cross-platform operating system for Next-Generation IoT devices. An out-of-bounds read can be caused by an incoming DIO message when using the RPL-Lite implementation in the Contiki-NG operating system. More specifically, the prefix information of the DIO message contains a field that specifies the length of an IPv6 address prefix. The value of this field is not validated, which means that an attacker can set a value that is longer than the maximum prefix length. Subsequently, a memcmp function call that compares different prefixes can be called with a length argument that surpasses the boundary of the array allocated for the prefix, causing an out-of-bounds read. The problem has been patched in the "develop" branch of Contiki-NG, and is expected to be included in the next release. Users are advised to update as soon as they are able to or to manually apply the changes in Contiki-NG pull request #2721.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50926|2024-02-14T19:28:11.556Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 19:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-48229|2024-06-04T17:27:39.833Z -- contiki-ng -- contiki-ng</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-48229</link>
      <description>Contiki-NG is an open-source, cross-platform operating system for Next-Generation IoT devices. An out-of-bounds write exists in the driver for IEEE 802.15.4 radios on nRF platforms in the Contiki-NG operating system. The problem is triggered when parsing radio frames in the `read_frame` function in the `arch/cpu/nrf/net/nrf-ieee-driver-arch.c` module. More specifically, the `read_frame` function performs an incomplete validation of the payload length of the packet, which is a value that can be set by an external party that sends radio packets to a Contiki-NG system. Although the value is validated to be in the range of the MTU length, it is not validated to fit into the given buffer into which the packet will be copied. The problem has been patched in the "develop" branch of Contiki-NG and is expected to be included in subsequent releases. Users are advised to update their develop branch or to update to a subsequent release when available. Users unable to upgrade should consider manually applying the changes in PR #2741.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-48229|2024-06-04T17:27:39.833Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 18:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-50927|2024-07-29T15:45:17.437Z -- contiki-ng -- contiki-ng</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50927</link>
      <description>Contiki-NG is an open-source, cross-platform operating system for Next-Generation IoT devices. An attacker can trigger out-of-bounds reads in the RPL-Lite implementation of the RPL protocol in the Contiki-NG operating system. This vulnerability is caused by insufficient control of the lengths for DIO and DAO messages, in particular when they contain RPL sub-option headers. The problem has been patched in Contiki-NG 4.9. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should manually apply the code changes in PR #2484.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-50927|2024-07-29T15:45:17.437Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 19:22:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
