<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for ClickHouse -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/clickhouse/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for ClickHouse -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:24:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-48298|2023-12-21T23:07:43.901Z -- clickhouse -- clickhouse
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-48298</link>
      <description>ClickHouse® is an open-source column-oriented database management system that allows generating analytical data reports in real-time. This vulnerability is an integer underflow resulting in crash due to stack buffer overflow in decompression of FPC codec. It can be triggered and exploited by an unauthenticated attacker. The vulnerability is very similar to CVE-2023-47118 with how the vulnerable function can be exploited.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-48298|2023-12-21T23:07:43.901Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 23:07:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-48704|2023-12-22T15:18:12.846Z -- clickhouse -- clickhouse
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-48704</link>
      <description>ClickHouse is an open-source column-oriented database management system that allows generating analytical data reports in real-time. A heap buffer overflow issue was discovered in ClickHouse server. An attacker could send a specially crafted payload to the native interface exposed by default on port 9000/tcp, triggering a bug in the decompression logic of Gorilla codec that crashes the ClickHouse server process. This attack does not require authentication. This issue has been addressed in ClickHouse Cloud version 23.9.2.47551 and ClickHouse versions 23.10.5.20, 23.3.18.15, 23.8.8.20, and 23.9.6.20.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-48704|2023-12-22T15:18:12.846Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 15:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-47118|2023-12-20T16:30:21.942Z -- clickhouse -- clickhouse
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2023-47118</link>
      <description>ClickHouse® is an open-source column-oriented database management system that allows generating analytical data reports in real-time. A heap buffer overflow issue was discovered in ClickHouse server. An attacker could send a specially crafted payload to the native interface exposed by default on port 9000/tcp, triggering a bug in the decompression logic of T64 codec that crashes the ClickHouse server process. This attack does not require authentication. Note that this exploit can also be triggered via HTTP protocol, however, the attacker will need a valid credential as the HTTP authentication take places first. This issue has been fixed in version 23.10.2.13-stable, 23.9.4.11-stable, 23.8.6.16-lts and 23.3.16.7-lts.
</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-47118|2023-12-20T16:30:21.942Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 16:30:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-22412|2024-03-18T20:51:40.313Z -- clickhouse -- clickhouse
</title>
      <link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-22412</link>
      <description>ClickHouse is an open-source column-oriented database management system. A bug exists in the cloud ClickHouse offering prior to version 24.0.2.54535 and in github.com/clickhouse/clickhouse version 23.1. Query caching bypasses the role based access controls and the policies being enforced on roles. In affected versions, the query cache only respects separate users, however this is not documented and not expected behavior. People relying on ClickHouse roles can have their access control lists bypassed if they are using query caching. Attackers who have control of a role could guess queries and see data they shouldn't have access to. Version 24.1 of ClickHouse and version 24.0.2.54535 of ClickHouse Cloud contain a patch for this issue. Based on the documentation, role based access control should be enforced regardless if query caching is enabled or not.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-22412|2024-03-18T20:51:40.313Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 20:51:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
