<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for ICS-CERT -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ics-cert/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for ICS-CERT -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 11:21:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-8835|2024-09-17T00:52:16.770Z -- ics-cert -- advantech%20webaccess%20hmi%20designer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-8835</link>
      <description>Double free vulnerabilities in Advantech WebAccess HMI Designer 2.1.7.32 and prior caused by processing specially crafted .pm3 files may allow remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-8835|2024-09-17T00:52:16.770Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6527|2024-09-17T02:32:35.184Z -- ics-cert -- pr100088%20modbus%20gateway
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6527</link>
      <description>PR100088 Modbus gateway versions prior to Release R02 (or Software Version 1.1.13166) may allow an attacker to be able to change the password for an admin user who is currently or previously logged in, provided the device has not been restarted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6527|2024-09-17T02:32:35.184Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7506|2024-09-17T02:07:03.368Z -- ics-cert -- moxa%20mxview
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7506</link>
      <description>The private key of the web server in Moxa MXview versions 2.8 and prior is able to be read and accessed via an HTTP GET request, which may allow a remote attacker to decrypt encrypted information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7506|2024-09-17T02:07:03.368Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-19020|2024-09-17T03:27:41.239Z -- ics-cert -- cx-supervisor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-19020</link>
      <description>When CX-Supervisor (Versions 3.42 and prior) processes project files and tampers with the value of an offset, an attacker can force the application to read a value outside of an array.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-19020|2024-09-17T03:27:41.239Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-19012|2024-09-17T04:08:49.934Z -- ics-cert -- dr%26%23195%3B%26%23164%3Bger%20infinity%20delta
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-19012</link>
      <description>Drager Infinity Delta, Infinity Delta, all versions, Delta XL, all versions, Kappa, all version, and Infinity Explorer C700, all versions. Via a specific dialog it is possible to break out of the kiosk mode and reach the underlying operating system. By breaking out of the kiosk mode, an attacker is able to take control of the operating system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-19012|2024-09-17T04:08:49.934Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-14781|2024-09-17T03:43:42.929Z -- ics-cert -- medtronic%20insulin%20pump
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-14781</link>
      <description>Medtronic MMT 508 MiniMed insulin pump, 522 / MMT - 722 Paradigm REAL-TIME, 523 / MMT - 723 Paradigm Revel, 523K / MMT - 723K Paradigm Revel, and 551 / MMT - 751 MiniMed 530G The models identified above, when paired with a remote controller and having the "easy bolus" and "remote bolus" options enabled (non-default), are vulnerable to a capture-replay attack. An attacker can capture the wireless transmissions between the remote controller and the pump and replay them to cause an insulin (bolus) delivery.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-14781|2024-09-17T03:43:42.929Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7513|2024-09-17T02:42:59.350Z -- ics-cert -- omron%20cx-supervisor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7513</link>
      <description>In Omron CX-Supervisor Versions 3.30 and prior, parsing malformed project files may cause a stack-based buffer overflow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7513|2024-09-17T02:42:59.350Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10631|2024-09-17T03:22:23.847Z -- ics-cert -- medtronic%20n%27vision%20clinician%20programmer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10631</link>
      <description>Medtronic N'Vision Clinician Programmer 8840 N'Vision Clinician Programmer, all versions, and 8870 N'Vision removable Application Card, all versions. The 8840 Clinician Programmer executes the application program from the 8870 Application Card. An attacker with physical access to an 8870 Application Card and sufficient technical capability can modify the contents of this card, including the binary executables. If modified to bypass protection mechanisms, this malicious code will be run when the card is inserted into an 8840 Clinician Programmer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10631|2024-09-17T03:22:23.847Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6547|2024-09-17T01:16:41.112Z -- ics-cert -- delta%20industrial%20automation%20cncsoft
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6547</link>
      <description>Delta Industrial Automation CNCSoft, CNCSoft ScreenEditor Version 1.00.84 and prior. An out-of-bounds read vulnerability may cause the software to crash due to lacking user input validation for processing project files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6547|2024-09-17T01:16:41.112Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16744|2024-09-17T00:42:31.941Z -- ics-cert -- niagara%20ax%20framework%20and%20niagara%204%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16744</link>
      <description>A path traversal vulnerability in Tridium Niagara AX Versions 3.8 and prior and Niagara 4 systems Versions 4.4 and prior installed on Microsoft Windows Systems can be exploited by leveraging valid platform (administrator) credentials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16744|2024-09-17T00:42:31.941Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7515|2024-09-17T02:52:00.046Z -- ics-cert -- beaconmed%26%23195%3B%26%23166%3Bs%20totalalert%20scroll%20medical%20air%20systems%20web%20application
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7515</link>
      <description>In Omron CX-Supervisor Versions 3.30 and prior, access of uninitialized pointer vulnerabilities can be exploited when CX Supervisor indirectly calls an initialized pointer when parsing malformed packets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7515|2024-09-17T02:52:00.046Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16748|2024-09-17T03:13:38.893Z -- ics-cert -- niagara%20ax%20framework%20and%20niagara%204%20framework
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16748</link>
      <description>An attacker can log into the local Niagara platform (Niagara AX Framework Versions 3.8 and prior or Niagara 4 Framework Versions 4.4 and prior) using a disabled account name and a blank password, granting the attacker administrator access to the Niagara system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16748|2024-09-17T03:13:38.893Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5446|2024-09-17T02:57:36.551Z -- ics-cert -- medtronic%202090%20carelink%20programmer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5446</link>
      <description>All versions of the Medtronic 2090 Carelink Programmer are affected by a per-product username and password that is stored in a recoverable format which could allow an attacker with physical access to a 2090 Programmer to obtain per-product credentials to the software deployment network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5446|2024-09-17T02:57:36.551Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7517|2024-09-17T02:21:26.823Z -- ics-cert -- omron%20cx-supervisor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7517</link>
      <description>In Omron CX-Supervisor Versions 3.30 and prior, parsing malformed project files may cause an out of bounds vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7517|2024-09-17T02:21:26.823Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18990|2024-09-17T01:21:51.337Z -- ics-cert -- lcds%20laquis%20scada
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18990</link>
      <description>LCDS Laquis SCADA prior to version 4.1.0.4150 allows a user-supplied path in file operations prior to proper validation. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose sensitive information under the context of the web server process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18990|2024-09-17T01:21:51.337Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6522|2024-09-17T02:32:19.762Z -- ics-cert -- moxa%20iks%2C%20eds
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6522</link>
      <description>Moxa IKS and EDS fails to properly check array bounds which may allow an attacker to read device memory on arbitrary addresses, and may allow an attacker to retrieve sensitive data or cause device reboot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6522|2024-09-17T02:32:19.762Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-19008|2024-09-17T03:52:53.725Z -- ics-cert -- abb%20cp400%20panel%20builder%20texteditor%202.0
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-19008</link>
      <description>The TextEditor 2.0 in ABB CP400 Panel Builder versions 2.0.7.05 and earlier contain a vulnerability in the file parser of the Text Editor wherein the application doesn't properly prevent the insertion of specially crafted files which could allow arbitrary code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-19008|2024-09-17T03:52:53.725Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-8868|2024-09-17T00:16:29.512Z -- ics-cert -- medtronic%20mycarelink%20patient%20monitor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-8868</link>
      <description>Medtronic MyCareLink Patient Monitor, 24950 MyCareLink Monitor, all versions, and 24952 MyCareLink Monitor, all versions, contains debug code meant to test the functionality of the monitor's communication interfaces, including the interface between the monitor and implantable cardiac device. An attacker with physical access to the device can apply the other vulnerabilities within this advisory to access this debug functionality. This debug functionality provides the ability to read and write arbitrary memory values to implantable cardiac devices via inductive or short range wireless protocols. An attacker with close physical proximity to a target implantable cardiac device can use this debug functionality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-8868|2024-09-17T00:16:29.512Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-8860|2024-09-17T01:30:43.321Z -- ics-cert -- vgo%20robot
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-8860</link>
      <description>In Vecna VGo Robot versions prior to 3.0.3.52164, an attacker may be able to capture firmware updates through the adjacent network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-8860|2024-09-17T01:30:43.321Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10598|2024-09-17T02:47:50.846Z -- ics-cert -- cncsoft%20with%20screeneditor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10598</link>
      <description>CNCSoft Version 1.00.83 and prior with ScreenEditor Version 1.00.54 has two out-of-bounds read vulnerabilities could cause the software to crash due to lacking user input validation for processing project files. Which may allow an attacker to gain remote code execution with administrator privileges if exploited.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10598|2024-09-17T02:47:50.846Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7906|2024-09-17T01:31:38.404Z -- ics-cert -- abb%20ip%20gateway
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7906</link>
      <description>In ABB IP GATEWAY 3.39 and prior, the web server does not sufficiently verify that a request was performed by the authenticated user, which may allow an attacker to launch a request impersonating that user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7906|2024-09-17T01:31:38.404Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-8838|2024-09-17T00:30:30.233Z -- ics-cert -- yokogawa%20centum%20and%20exaopc
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-8838</link>
      <description>A weakness in access controls in CENTUM CS 1000 all versions, CENTUM CS 3000 versions R3.09.50 and earlier, CENTUM CS 3000 Small versions R3.09.50 and earlier, CENTUM VP versions R6.03.10 and earlier, CENTUM VP Small versions R6.03.10 and earlier, CENTUM VP Basic versions R6.03.10 and earlier, Exaopc versions R3.75.00 and earlier, B/M9000 CS all versions, and B/M9000 VP versions R8.01.01 and earlier may allow a local attacker to exploit the message management function of the system. A CVSS v3 base score of 6.5 has been calculated; the CVSS vector string is (AV:L/AC:H/PR:L/UI:N/S:U/C:L/I:H/A:H).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-8838|2024-09-17T00:30:30.233Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5448|2024-09-17T01:01:17.088Z -- ics-cert -- medtronic%202090%20carelink%20programmer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5448</link>
      <description>All versions of the Medtronic 2090 Carelink Programmer are affected by a directory traversal vulnerability where the product's software deployment network could allow an attacker to read files on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5448|2024-09-17T01:01:17.088Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7931|2024-09-17T02:47:46.978Z -- ics-cert -- abb%20ip%20gateway
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7931</link>
      <description>In ABB IP GATEWAY 3.39 and prior, by accessing a specific uniform resource locator (URL) on the web server, a malicious user is able to access the configuration files and application pages without authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7931|2024-09-17T02:47:46.978Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10601|2024-09-17T02:36:04.782Z -- ics-cert -- intellivue%20patient%20monitors%2C%20avalon%20fetal%2Fmaternal%20monitors
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10601</link>
      <description>IntelliVue Patient Monitors MP Series (including MP2/X2/MP30/MP50/MP70/NP90/MX700/800) Rev B-M, IntelliVue Patient Monitors MX (MX400-550) Rev J-M and (X3/MX100 for Rev M only), and Avalon Fetal/Maternal Monitors FM20/FM30/FM40/FM50 with software Revisions F.0, G.0 and J.3 have a vulnerability that exposes an "echo" service, in which an attacker-sent buffer to an attacker-chosen device address within the same subnet is copied to the stack with no boundary checks, hence resulting in stack overflow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10601|2024-09-17T02:36:04.782Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17930|2024-09-17T04:00:05.112Z -- ics-cert -- teledyne%20dalsa%20sherlock
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17930</link>
      <description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability has been identified in Teledyne DALSA Sherlock Version 7.2.7.4 and prior, which may allow remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17930|2024-09-17T04:00:05.112Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-19017|2024-09-17T01:00:42.376Z -- ics-cert -- cx-supervisor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-19017</link>
      <description>Several use after free vulnerabilities have been identified in CX-Supervisor (Versions 3.42 and prior). When processing project files, the application fails to check if it is referencing freed memory. An attacker could use a specially crafted project file to exploit and execute code under the privileges of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-19017|2024-09-17T01:00:42.376Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-14805|2024-09-17T04:29:00.499Z -- ics-cert -- abb%20esoms
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-14805</link>
      <description>ABB eSOMS version 6.0.2 may allow unauthorized access to the system when LDAP is set to allow anonymous authentication, and specific key values within the eSOMS web.config file are present. Both conditions are required to exploit this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-14805|2024-09-17T04:29:00.499Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-8833|2024-09-17T00:52:16.210Z -- ics-cert -- advantech%20webaccess%20hmi%20designer
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-8833</link>
      <description>Heap-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities in Advantech WebAccess HMI Designer 2.1.7.32 and prior caused by processing specially crafted .pm3 files may allow remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-8833|2024-09-17T00:52:16.210Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-5175|2024-09-17T02:01:34.846Z -- ics-cert -- advantech%20webaccess%20versions%208.1%20and%20prior.
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-5175</link>
      <description>Advantech WebAccess 8.1 and earlier contains a DLL hijacking vulnerability which may allow an attacker to run a malicious DLL file within the search path resulting in execution of arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-5175|2024-09-17T02:01:34.846Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-19019|2024-09-17T01:16:24.999Z -- ics-cert -- cx-supervisor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-19019</link>
      <description>A type confusion vulnerability exists when processing project files in CX-Supervisor (Versions 3.42 and prior). An attacker could use a specially crafted project file to exploit and execute code under the privileges of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-19019|2024-09-17T01:16:24.999Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-14785|2024-09-17T03:27:55.496Z -- ics-cert -- netcomm%20wireless%20g%20lte%20light%20industrial%20m2m%20router%20%28nwl-25%29%20with%20firmware%202.0.29.11%20and%20prior.
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-14785</link>
      <description>NetComm Wireless G LTE Light Industrial M2M Router (NWL-25) with firmware 2.0.29.11 and prior. The directory of the device is listed openly without authentication.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-14785|2024-09-17T03:27:55.496Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10631|2024-08-19T18:26:09.940Z -- ics-cert -- medtronic%20n%27vision%20clinician%20programmer</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10631</link>
      <description>Medtronic N'Vision Clinician Programmer 8840 N'Vision Clinician Programmer, all versions, and 8870 N'Vision removable Application Card, all versions. The 8840 Clinician Programmer executes the application program from the 8870 Application Card. An attacker with physical access to an 8870 Application Card and sufficient technical capability can modify the contents of this card, including the binary executables. If modified to bypass protection mechanisms, this malicious code will be run when the card is inserted into an 8840 Clinician Programmer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10631|2024-08-19T18:26:09.940Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 18:26:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10631|2024-08-05T07:46:46.502Z -- ics-cert -- medtronic%20n%27vision%20clinician%20programmer</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10631</link>
      <description>Medtronic N'Vision Clinician Programmer 8840 N'Vision Clinician Programmer, all versions, and 8870 N'Vision removable Application Card, all versions. The 8840 Clinician Programmer executes the application program from the 8870 Application Card. An attacker with physical access to an 8870 Application Card and sufficient technical capability can modify the contents of this card, including the binary executables. If modified to bypass protection mechanisms, this malicious code will be run when the card is inserted into an 8840 Clinician Programmer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10631|2024-08-05T07:46:46.502Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 07:46:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
