<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for ICS-CERT -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ics-cert/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for ICS-CERT -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 21:42:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-19011|2024-09-16T20:57:24.608Z -- ics-cert -- cx-supervisor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-19011</link>
      <description>CX-Supervisor (Versions 3.42 and prior) can execute code that has been injected into a project file. An attacker could exploit this to execute code under the privileges of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-19011|2024-09-16T20:57:24.608Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-8834|2024-09-16T19:25:23.504Z -- ics-cert -- omron%20cx-one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-8834</link>
      <description>Parsing malformed project files in Omron CX-One versions 4.42 and prior, including the following applications: CX-FLnet versions 1.00 and prior, CX-Protocol versions 1.992 and prior, CX-Programmer versions 9.65 and prior, CX-Server versions 5.0.22 and prior, Network Configurator versions 3.63 and prior, and Switch Box Utility versions 1.68 and prior, may cause a heap-based buffer overflow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-8834|2024-09-16T19:25:23.504Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10619|2024-09-16T16:23:04.934Z -- ics-cert -- rockwell%20automation%20rslinx%20classic%20and%20factorytalk%20linx%20gateway
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10619</link>
      <description>An unquoted search path or element in RSLinx Classic Versions 3.90.01 and prior and FactoryTalk Linx Gateway Versions 3.90.00 and prior may allow an authorized, but non-privileged local user to execute arbitrary code and allow a threat actor to escalate user privileges on the affected workstation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10619|2024-09-16T16:23:04.934Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7525|2024-09-16T20:21:41.541Z -- ics-cert -- omron%20cx-supervisor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7525</link>
      <description>In Omron CX-Supervisor Versions 3.30 and prior, processing a malformed packet by a certain executable may cause an untrusted pointer dereference vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7525|2024-09-16T20:21:41.541Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7530|2024-09-16T16:28:21.613Z -- ics-cert -- omron%20cx-one
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7530</link>
      <description>Parsing malformed project files in Omron CX-One versions 4.42 and prior, including the following applications: CX-FLnet versions 1.00 and prior, CX-Protocol versions 1.992 and prior, CX-Programmer versions 9.65 and prior, CX-Server versions 5.0.22 and prior, Network Configurator versions 3.63 and prior, and Switch Box Utility versions 1.68 and prior, may allow the pointer to call an incorrect object resulting in an access of resource using incompatible type condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7530|2024-09-16T16:28:21.613Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7502|2024-09-16T17:14:23.452Z -- ics-cert -- beckhoff%20twincat%20plc%20products
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7502</link>
      <description>Kernel drivers in Beckhoff TwinCAT 3.1 Build 4022.4, TwinCAT 2.11 R3 2259, and TwinCAT 3.1 lack proper validation of user-supplied pointer values. An attacker who is able to execute code on the target may be able to exploit this vulnerability to obtain SYSTEM privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7502|2024-09-16T17:14:23.452Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-19014|2024-09-16T20:31:32.329Z -- ics-cert -- dr%26%23195%3B%26%23164%3Bger%20infinity%20delta
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-19014</link>
      <description>Drager Infinity Delta, Infinity Delta, all versions, Delta XL, all versions, Kappa, all version, and Infinity Explorer C700, all versions. Log files are accessible over an unauthenticated network connection. By accessing the log files, an attacker is able to gain insights about internals of the patient monitor, the location of the monitor, and wired network configuration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-19014|2024-09-16T20:31:32.329Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7509|2024-09-16T18:23:50.927Z -- ics-cert -- delta%20electronics%20wplsoft
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7509</link>
      <description>WPLSoft in Delta Electronics versions 2.45.0 and prior writes data from a file outside the bounds of the intended buffer space, which could cause memory corruption or may allow remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7509|2024-09-16T18:23:50.927Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6517|2024-09-16T20:22:23.258Z -- ics-cert -- bd%20facslyric
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6517</link>
      <description>BD FACSLyric Research Use Only, Windows 10 Professional Operating System, U.S. and Malaysian Releases, between November 2017 and November 2018 and BD FACSLyric IVD Windows 10 Professional Operating System US release does not properly enforce user access control to privileged accounts, which may allow for unauthorized access to administrative level functions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6517|2024-09-16T20:22:23.258Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10594|2024-09-16T16:58:55.973Z -- ics-cert -- delta%20industrial%20automation%20commgr%20and%20accompanying%20plc%20simulators%20%28dvpsimulator%20eh2%2C%20eh3%2C%20es2%2C%20se%2C%20ss2%20and%20ahsim_5x0%2C%20ahsim_5x1%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10594</link>
      <description>Delta Industrial Automation COMMGR from Delta Electronics versions 1.08 and prior with accompanying PLC Simulators (DVPSimulator EH2, EH3, ES2, SE, SS2 and AHSIM_5x0, AHSIM_5x1) utilize a fixed-length stack buffer where an unverified length value can be read from the network packets via a specific network port, causing the buffer to be overwritten. This may allow remote code execution, cause the application to crash, or result in a denial-of-service condition in the application server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10594|2024-09-16T16:58:55.973Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6551|2024-09-16T19:40:09.741Z -- ics-cert -- pangea%20communications%20internet%20fax%20ata
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6551</link>
      <description>Pangea Communications Internet FAX ATA all Versions 3.1.8 and prior allow an attacker to bypass user authentication using a specially crafted URL to cause the device to reboot, which may be used to cause a continual denial-of-service condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6551|2024-09-16T19:40:09.741Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16718|2024-09-16T17:28:00.754Z -- ics-cert -- beckhoff%20twincat
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16718</link>
      <description>Beckhoff TwinCAT 3 supports communication over ADS. ADS is a protocol for industrial automation in protected environments. This protocol uses user configured routes, that can be edited remotely via ADS. This special command supports encrypted authentication with username/password. The encryption uses a fixed key, that could be extracted by an attacker. Precondition of the exploitation of this weakness is network access at the moment a route is added.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16718|2024-09-16T17:28:00.754Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-19010|2024-09-16T17:32:40.689Z -- ics-cert -- dr%26%23195%3B%26%23164%3Bger%20infinity%20delta
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-19010</link>
      <description>Drager Infinity Delta, Infinity Delta, all versions, Delta XL, all versions, Kappa, all version, and Infinity Explorer C700, all versions. A malformed network packet may cause the monitor to reboot. By repeatedly sending the malformed network packet, an attacker may be able to disrupt patient monitoring by causing the monitor to repeatedly reboot until it falls back to default configuration and loses network connectivity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-19010|2024-09-16T17:32:40.689Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7494|2024-09-16T19:46:54.978Z -- ics-cert -- delta%20electronics%20wplsoft
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7494</link>
      <description>WPLSoft in Delta Electronics versions 2.45.0 and prior utilizes a fixed length stack buffer where a value larger than the buffer can be read from a file into the buffer, causing the buffer to be overwritten, which may allow remote code execution or cause the application to crash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7494|2024-09-16T19:46:54.978Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7523|2024-09-16T16:37:44.622Z -- ics-cert -- omron%20cx-supervisor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7523</link>
      <description>In Omron CX-Supervisor Versions 3.30 and prior, parsing malformed project files may cause a double free vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7523|2024-09-16T16:37:44.622Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-19000|2024-09-16T19:57:27.111Z -- ics-cert -- lcds%20laquis%20scada
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-19000</link>
      <description>LCDS Laquis SCADA prior to version 4.1.0.4150 allows an authentication bypass, which may allow an attacker access to sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-19000|2024-09-16T19:57:27.111Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18998|2024-09-16T20:16:26.205Z -- ics-cert -- lcds%20laquis%20scada
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18998</link>
      <description>LCDS Laquis SCADA prior to version 4.1.0.4150 uses hard coded credentials, which may allow an attacker unauthorized access to the system with high privileges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18998|2024-09-16T20:16:26.205Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-8840|2024-09-16T17:53:19.851Z -- ics-cert -- schneider%20electric%20indusoft%20web%20studio%20and%20intouch%20machine%20edition
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-8840</link>
      <description>A remote attacker could send a carefully crafted packet in InduSoft Web Studio v8.1 and prior versions, and/or InTouch Machine Edition 2017 v8.1 and prior versions during a tag, alarm, or event related action such as read and write, which may allow remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-8840|2024-09-16T17:53:19.851Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-19013|2024-09-16T19:40:40.349Z -- ics-cert -- cx-supervisor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-19013</link>
      <description>An attacker could inject commands to delete files and/or delete the contents of a file on CX-Supervisor (Versions 3.42 and prior) through a specially crafted project file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-19013|2024-09-16T19:40:40.349Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10622|2024-09-16T18:43:40.859Z -- ics-cert -- medtronic%20mycarelink%2024950%2C%2024952%20patient%20monitor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10622</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was discovered in all versions of Medtronic MyCareLink 24950 and 24952 Patient Monitor. The affected products use per-product credentials that are stored in a recoverable format. An attacker can use these credentials for network authentication and encryption of local data at rest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10622|2024-09-16T18:43:40.859Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6524|2024-09-16T16:57:49.226Z -- ics-cert -- moxa%20iks%2C%20eds
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6524</link>
      <description>Moxa IKS and EDS do not implement sufficient measures to prevent multiple failed authentication attempts, which may allow an attacker to discover passwords via brute force attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6524|2024-09-16T16:57:49.226Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7519|2024-09-16T18:13:44.973Z -- ics-cert -- omron%20cx-supervisor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7519</link>
      <description>In Omron CX-Supervisor Versions 3.30 and prior, parsing malformed project files may cause a heap-based buffer overflow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7519|2024-09-16T18:13:44.973Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-14782|2024-09-16T17:34:12.905Z -- ics-cert -- netcomm%20wireless%20g%20lte%20light%20industrial%20m2m%20router%20%28nwl-25%29%20with%20firmware%202.0.29.11%20and%20prior.
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-14782</link>
      <description>NetComm Wireless G LTE Light Industrial M2M Router (NWL-25) with firmware 2.0.29.11 and prior. The device allows access to configuration files and profiles without authenticating the user.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-14782|2024-09-16T17:34:12.905Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-8847|2024-09-16T17:27:52.109Z -- ics-cert -- eaton%209000x%20drive
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-8847</link>
      <description>Eaton 9000X DriveA versions 2.0.29 and prior has a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability, which may allow remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-8847|2024-09-16T17:27:52.109Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-14783|2024-09-16T16:13:07.238Z -- ics-cert -- netcomm%20wireless%20g%20lte%20light%20industrial%20m2m%20router%20%28nwl-25%29%20with%20firmware%202.0.29.11%20and%20prior.
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-14783</link>
      <description>NetComm Wireless G LTE Light Industrial M2M Router (NWL-25) with firmware 2.0.29.11 and prior. A cross-site request forgery condition can occur, allowing an attacker to change passwords of the device remotely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-14783|2024-09-16T16:13:07.238Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-17937|2024-09-16T19:36:34.191Z -- ics-cert -- gpsd%20and%20microjson%20%28open%20source%20project%29
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-17937</link>
      <description>gpsd versions 2.90 to 3.17 and microjson versions 1.0 to 1.3, an open source project, allow a stack-based buffer overflow, which may allow remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on embedded platforms via traffic on Port 2947/TCP or crafted JSON inputs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-17937|2024-09-16T19:36:34.191Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-14795|2024-09-16T20:26:38.250Z -- ics-cert -- deltav
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-14795</link>
      <description>DeltaV Versions 11.3.1, 12.3.1, 13.3.0, 13.3.1, and R5 is vulnerable due to improper path validation which may allow an attacker to replace executable files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-14795|2024-09-16T20:26:38.250Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6563|2024-09-16T18:44:20.929Z -- ics-cert -- moxa%20iks%2C%20eds
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6563</link>
      <description>Moxa IKS and EDS generate a predictable cookie calculated with an MD5 hash, allowing an attacker to capture the administrator's password, which could lead to a full compromise of the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6563|2024-09-16T18:44:20.929Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10626|2024-09-16T17:15:18.866Z -- ics-cert -- medtronic%20mycarelink%2024950%2C%2024952%20patient%20monitor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10626</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was discovered in all versions of Medtronic MyCareLink 24950 and 24952 Patient Monitor. The affected product's update service does not sufficiently verify the authenticity of the data uploaded. An attacker who obtains per-product credentials from the monitor and paired implantable cardiac device information can potentially upload invalid data to the Medtronic CareLink network.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10626|2024-09-16T17:15:18.866Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-8866|2024-09-16T16:33:35.624Z -- ics-cert -- vgo%20robot
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-8866</link>
      <description>In Vecna VGo Robot versions prior to 3.0.3.52164, an attacker on an adjacent network could perform command injection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-8866|2024-09-16T16:33:35.624Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10599|2024-09-16T16:33:25.211Z -- ics-cert -- intellivue%20patient%20monitors%2C%20avalon%20fetal%2Fmaternal%20monitors
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10599</link>
      <description>IntelliVue Patient Monitors MP Series (including MP2/X2/MP30/MP50/MP70/NP90/MX700/800) Rev B-M, IntelliVue Patient Monitors MX (MX400-550) Rev J-M and (X3/MX100 for Rev M only), and Avalon Fetal/Maternal Monitors FM20/FM30/FM40/FM50 with software Revisions F.0, G.0 and J.3 have a vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated attacker to read memory from an attacker-chosen device address within the same subnet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10599|2024-09-16T16:33:25.211Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6561|2024-09-16T17:27:37.822Z -- ics-cert -- moxa%20iks%2C%20eds
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6561</link>
      <description>Cross-site request forgery has been identified in Moxa IKS and EDS, which may allow for the execution of unauthorized actions on the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6561|2024-09-16T17:27:37.822Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6539|2024-09-16T19:56:23.233Z -- ics-cert -- wecon%20levistudiou
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6539</link>
      <description>Several heap-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities in WECON LeviStudioU version 1.8.56 and prior have been identified, which may allow arbitrary code execution. Mat Powell, Ziad Badawi, and Natnael Samson working with Trend Micro's Zero Day Initiative, reported these vulnerabilities to NCCIC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6539|2024-09-16T19:56:23.233Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10630|2024-09-16T16:52:46.583Z -- ics-cert -- crestron%20tsw-x60%20version%20prior%20to%202.001.0037.001%20and%20mc3%20version%20prior%20to%201.502.0047.001
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10630</link>
      <description>For Crestron TSW-X60 version prior to 2.001.0037.001 and MC3 version prior to 1.502.0047.001, The devices are shipped with authentication disabled, and there is no indication to users that they need to take steps to enable it. When compromised, the access to the CTP console is left open.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10630|2024-09-16T16:52:46.583Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-8843|2024-09-16T20:27:15.193Z -- ics-cert -- rockwell%20automation%20arena
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-8843</link>
      <description>Rockwell Automation Arena versions 15.10.00 and prior contains a use after free vulnerability caused by processing specially crafted Arena Simulation Software files that may cause the software application to crash, potentially losing any unsaved data..</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-8843|2024-09-16T20:27:15.193Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7507|2024-09-16T17:43:16.317Z -- ics-cert -- delta%20electronics%20wplsoft
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7507</link>
      <description>WPLSoft in Delta Electronics versions 2.45.0 and prior utilizes a fixed length heap buffer where a value larger than the buffer can be read from a file into the buffer, causing the buffer to be overwritten, which may allow remote code execution or cause the application to crash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7507|2024-09-16T17:43:16.317Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-16726|2024-09-16T17:08:08.110Z -- ics-cert -- beckhoff%20twincat
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-16726</link>
      <description>Beckhoff TwinCAT supports communication over ADS. ADS is a protocol for industrial automation in protected environments. ADS has not been designed to achieve security purposes and therefore does not include any encryption algorithms because of their negative effect on performance and throughput. An attacker can forge arbitrary ADS packets when legitimate ADS traffic is observable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-16726|2024-09-16T17:08:08.110Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6533|2024-09-16T17:18:38.780Z -- ics-cert -- pr100088%20modbus%20gateway
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6533</link>
      <description>Registers used to store Modbus values can be read and written from the web interface without authentication in the PR100088 Modbus gateway versions prior to Release R02 (or Software Version 1.1.13166).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6533|2024-09-16T17:18:38.780Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-19004|2024-09-16T18:44:50.704Z -- ics-cert -- lcds%20laquis%20scada
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-19004</link>
      <description>LCDS Laquis SCADA prior to version 4.1.0.4150 allows out of bounds read when opening a specially crafted project file, which may allow data exfiltration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-19004|2024-09-16T18:44:50.704Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10636|2024-09-16T18:13:08.613Z -- ics-cert -- cncsoft%20with%20screeneditor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10636</link>
      <description>CNCSoft Version 1.00.83 and prior with ScreenEditor Version 1.00.54 has multiple stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities that could cause the software to crash due to lacking user input validation before copying data from project files onto the stack. Which may allow an attacker to gain remote code execution with administrator privileges if exploited.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10636|2024-09-16T18:13:08.613Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-19018|2024-09-16T20:32:03.769Z -- ics-cert -- cx-supervisor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-19018</link>
      <description>An access of uninitialized pointer vulnerability in CX-Supervisor (Versions 3.42 and prior) could lead to type confusion when processing project files. An attacker could use a specially crafted project file to exploit and execute code under the privileges of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-19018|2024-09-16T20:32:03.769Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-7521|2024-09-16T19:04:25.113Z -- ics-cert -- omron%20cx-supervisor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-7521</link>
      <description>In Omron CX-Supervisor Versions 3.30 and prior, use after free vulnerabilities can be exploited when CX Supervisor parses a specially crafted project file.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-7521|2024-09-16T19:04:25.113Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6520|2024-09-16T19:01:03.479Z -- ics-cert -- moxa%20iks%2C%20eds
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6520</link>
      <description>Moxa IKS and EDS does not properly check authority on server side, which results in a read-only user being able to perform arbitrary configuration changes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6520|2024-09-16T19:01:03.479Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-19015|2024-09-16T17:03:35.726Z -- ics-cert -- cx-supervisor
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-19015</link>
      <description>An attacker could inject commands to launch programs and create, write, and read files on CX-Supervisor (Versions 3.42 and prior) through a specially crafted project file. An attacker could exploit this to execute code under the privileges of the application.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-19015|2024-09-16T17:03:35.726Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6557|2024-09-16T18:24:17.372Z -- ics-cert -- moxa%20iks%2C%20eds
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6557</link>
      <description>Several buffer overflow vulnerabilities have been identified in Moxa IKS and EDS, which may allow remote code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6557|2024-09-16T18:24:17.372Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18988|2024-09-16T17:14:06.193Z -- ics-cert -- lcds%20laquis%20scada
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18988</link>
      <description>LCDS Laquis SCADA prior to version 4.1.0.4150 allows execution of script code by opening a specially crafted report format file. This may allow remote code execution, data exfiltration, or cause a system crash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18988|2024-09-16T17:14:06.193Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-8867|2024-09-16T18:43:49.739Z -- ics-cert -- ge%20pacsystems%20rx3i%20cpe305%2F310%20version%209.20%20and%20prior%20rx3i%20cpe330%20version%209.21%20and%20prior%20rx3i%20cpe%20400%20version%209.30%20and%20prior%20pacsystems%20rsti-ep%20cpe%20100%20all%20versionspacsystems%20cpu320%2Fcru320%20rx
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-8867</link>
      <description>In GE PACSystems RX3i CPE305/310 version 9.20 and prior, RX3i CPE330 version 9.21 and prior, RX3i CPE 400 version 9.30 and prior, PACSystems RSTi-EP CPE 100 all versions, and PACSystems CPU320/CRU320 RXi all versions, the device does not properly validate input, which could allow a remote attacker to send specially crafted packets causing the device to become unavailable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-8867|2024-09-16T18:43:49.739Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5463|2024-09-16T20:26:49.223Z -- ics-cert -- lcds%20-%20le%26%23195%3B%26%23163%3Bo%20consultoria%20e%20desenvolvimento%20de%20sistemas%20ltda%20me%20laquis%20scada
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5463</link>
      <description>A structured exception handler overflow vulnerability in Leao Consultoria e Desenvolvimento de Sistemas (LCDS) LTDA ME LAquis SCADA 4.1.0.3391 and earlier may allow code execution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5463|2024-09-16T20:26:49.223Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-18992|2024-09-16T18:09:12.562Z -- ics-cert -- lcds%20laquis%20scada
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-18992</link>
      <description>LCDS Laquis SCADA prior to version 4.1.0.4150 allows taking in user input without proper sanitation, which may allow an attacker to execute remote code on the server.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-18992|2024-09-16T18:09:12.562Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6543|2024-09-16T18:14:25.090Z -- ics-cert -- aveva%20software%2C%20llc%20indusoft%20web%20studio%20prior%20to%20version%208.1%20sp3%20and%20intouch%20edge%20hmi%20%28formerly%20intouch%20machine%20edition%29%20prior%20to%20version%202017%20update
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6543</link>
      <description>AVEVA Software, LLC InduSoft Web Studio prior to Version 8.1 SP3 and InTouch Edge HMI (formerly InTouch Machine Edition) prior to Version 2017 Update. Code is executed under the program runtime privileges, which could lead to the compromise of the machine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6543|2024-09-16T18:14:25.090Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6518|2024-09-16T18:49:44.263Z -- ics-cert -- moxa%20iks%2C%20eds
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6518</link>
      <description>Moxa IKS and EDS store plaintext passwords, which may allow sensitive information to be read by someone with access to the device.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6518|2024-09-16T18:49:44.263Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10631|2024-08-05T07:46:46.502Z -- ics-cert -- medtronic%20n%27vision%20clinician%20programmer</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10631</link>
      <description>Medtronic N'Vision Clinician Programmer 8840 N'Vision Clinician Programmer, all versions, and 8870 N'Vision removable Application Card, all versions. The 8840 Clinician Programmer executes the application program from the 8870 Application Card. An attacker with physical access to an 8870 Application Card and sufficient technical capability can modify the contents of this card, including the binary executables. If modified to bypass protection mechanisms, this malicious code will be run when the card is inserted into an 8840 Clinician Programmer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10631|2024-08-05T07:46:46.502Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 07:46:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10631|2024-08-19T18:26:09.940Z -- ics-cert -- medtronic%20n%27vision%20clinician%20programmer</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10631</link>
      <description>Medtronic N'Vision Clinician Programmer 8840 N'Vision Clinician Programmer, all versions, and 8870 N'Vision removable Application Card, all versions. The 8840 Clinician Programmer executes the application program from the 8870 Application Card. An attacker with physical access to an 8870 Application Card and sufficient technical capability can modify the contents of this card, including the binary executables. If modified to bypass protection mechanisms, this malicious code will be run when the card is inserted into an 8840 Clinician Programmer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10631|2024-08-19T18:26:09.940Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 18:26:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
