<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for ICS-CERT -- WECON LeviStudioU</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/ics-cert/wecon%20levistudiou.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for ICS-CERT -- WECON LeviStudioU</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:23:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6541|2024-08-04T20:23:21.844Z -- ics-cert -- wecon%20levistudiou
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6541</link>
      <description>A memory corruption vulnerability has been identified in WECON LeviStudioU version 1.8.56 and prior, which may allow arbitrary code execution. Mat Powell, Ziad Badawi, and Natnael Samson working with Trend Micro's Zero Day Initiative, reported these vulnerabilities to NCCIC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6541|2024-08-04T20:23:21.844Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6537|2024-08-04T20:23:21.496Z -- ics-cert -- wecon%20levistudiou
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6537</link>
      <description>Multiple stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities in WECON LeviStudioU version 1.8.56 and prior may be exploited when parsing strings within project files. The process does not properly validate the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage these vulnerabilities to execute code under the context of the current process. Mat Powell, Ziad Badawi, and Natnael Samson working with Trend Micro's Zero Day Initiative, reported these vulnerabilities to NCCIC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6537|2024-08-04T20:23:21.496Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-6539|2024-08-04T20:23:21.466Z -- ics-cert -- wecon%20levistudiou
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-6539</link>
      <description>Several heap-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities in WECON LeviStudioU version 1.8.56 and prior have been identified, which may allow arbitrary code execution. Mat Powell, Ziad Badawi, and Natnael Samson working with Trend Micro's Zero Day Initiative, reported these vulnerabilities to NCCIC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-6539|2024-08-04T20:23:21.466Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
