<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Quest -- Quest NetVault Backup</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/quest/quest%20netvault%20backup.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Quest -- Quest NetVault Backup</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 21:23:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1161|2024-08-05T03:51:48.973Z -- quest -- quest%20netvault%20backup
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1161</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Quest NetVault Backup 11.2.0.13. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within nvwsworker.exe. When parsing the boundary header of a multipart request, the process does not properly validate the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code under the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-4215.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1161|2024-08-05T03:51:48.973Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17423|2024-08-05T20:51:31.338Z -- quest -- quest%20netvault%20backup
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17423</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Quest NetVault Backup 11.3.0.12. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of NVBUBackupSegment Get method requests. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the underlying database. Was ZDI-CAN-4234.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17423|2024-08-05T20:51:31.338Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1163|2024-08-05T03:51:48.993Z -- quest -- quest%20netvault%20backup
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1163</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on vulnerable installations of Quest NetVault Backup 11.2.0.13. The specific flaw exists within JSON RPC Request handling. By setting the checksession parameter to a specific value, it is possible to bypass authentication to critical functions. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-4752.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1163|2024-08-05T03:51:48.993Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17412|2024-08-05T20:51:31.335Z -- quest -- quest%20netvault%20backup
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17412</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Quest NetVault Backup 11.3.0.12. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of GET method requests. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code in the context of the underlying database. Was ZDI-CAN-4223.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17412|2024-08-05T20:51:31.335Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17414|2024-08-05T20:51:31.400Z -- quest -- quest%20netvault%20backup
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17414</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Quest NetVault Backup 11.3.0.12. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of NVBUPhaseStatus Get method requests. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the underlying database. Was ZDI-CAN-4225.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17414|2024-08-05T20:51:31.400Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17654|2024-08-05T20:59:17.152Z -- quest -- quest%20netvault%20backup
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17654</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Quest NetVault Backup 11.3.0.12. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of NVBUBackup ClientList method requests. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the underlying database. Was ZDI-CAN-4287.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17654|2024-08-05T20:59:17.152Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17418|2024-08-05T20:51:31.423Z -- quest -- quest%20netvault%20backup
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17418</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Quest NetVault Backup 11.3.0.12. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of NVBUPolicy Get method requests. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the underlying database. Was ZDI-CAN-4229.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17418|2024-08-05T20:51:31.423Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17653|2024-08-05T20:59:17.343Z -- quest -- quest%20netvault%20backup
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17653</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Quest NetVault Backup 11.3.0.12. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of NVBUBackupOptionSet Get method requests. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the underlying database. Was ZDI-CAN-4286.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17653|2024-08-05T20:59:17.343Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17425|2024-08-05T20:51:31.654Z -- quest -- quest%20netvault%20backup
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17425</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Quest NetVault Backup 11.3.0.12. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of NVBUSourceDeviceSet Get method requests. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the underlying database. Was ZDI-CAN-4237.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17425|2024-08-05T20:51:31.654Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17657|2024-08-05T20:59:17.274Z -- quest -- quest%20netvault%20backup
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17657</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Quest NetVault Backup 11.3.0.12. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of NVBUBackup TimeRange method requests. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the underlying database. Was ZDI-CAN-4294.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17657|2024-08-05T20:59:17.274Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17656|2024-08-05T20:59:17.499Z -- quest -- quest%20netvault%20backup
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17656</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Quest NetVault Backup 11.3.0.12. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of NVBUBackup JobList method requests. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the underlying database. Was ZDI-CAN-4292.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17656|2024-08-05T20:59:17.499Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17416|2024-08-05T20:51:31.424Z -- quest -- quest%20netvault%20backup
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17416</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Quest NetVault Backup 11.3.0.12. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of NVBUPhaseStatus GetPlugins method requests. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the underlying database. Was ZDI-CAN-4227.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17416|2024-08-05T20:51:31.424Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17421|2024-08-05T20:51:31.389Z -- quest -- quest%20netvault%20backup
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17421</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Quest NetVault Backup 11.3.0.12. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of NVBUSelectionSet Get method requests. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the underlying database. Was ZDI-CAN-4232.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17421|2024-08-05T20:51:31.389Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17420|2024-08-05T20:51:31.135Z -- quest -- quest%20netvault%20backup
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17420</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Quest NetVault Backup 11.3.0.12. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of NVBUJobCountHistory Get method requests. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the underlying database. Was ZDI-CAN-4231.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17420|2024-08-05T20:51:31.135Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17659|2024-08-05T20:59:17.466Z -- quest -- quest%20netvault%20backup
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17659</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Quest NetVault Backup 11.3.0.12. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of NVBUJobHistory Get method requests. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the underlying database. Was ZDI-CAN-4906.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17659|2024-08-05T20:59:17.466Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-1162|2024-08-05T03:51:48.995Z -- quest -- quest%20netvault%20backup
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-1162</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to create a denial-of-service condition on vulnerable installations of Quest NetVault Backup 11.2.0.13. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be easily bypassed. The specific flaw exists within the handling of Export requests. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to arbitrarily overwrite files resulting in a denial-of-service condition. Was ZDI-CAN-4222.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-1162|2024-08-05T03:51:48.995Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17419|2024-08-05T20:51:31.145Z -- quest -- quest%20netvault%20backup
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17419</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Quest NetVault Backup 11.3.0.12. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of NVBUTransferHistory Get method requests. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the underlying database. Was ZDI-CAN-4230.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17419|2024-08-05T20:51:31.145Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17424|2024-08-05T20:51:31.408Z -- quest -- quest%20netvault%20backup
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17424</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Quest NetVault Backup 11.3.0.12. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of NVBUScheduleSet Get method requests. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the underlying database. Was ZDI-CAN-4235.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17424|2024-08-05T20:51:31.408Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17417|2024-08-05T20:51:31.300Z -- quest -- quest%20netvault%20backup
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17417</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Quest NetVault Backup 11.3.0.12. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of NVBUPhaseStatus Acknowledge method requests. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the underlying database. Was ZDI-CAN-4228.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17417|2024-08-05T20:51:31.300Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17422|2024-08-05T20:51:31.436Z -- quest -- quest%20netvault%20backup
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17422</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Quest NetVault Backup 11.3.0.12. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of NVBUBackup Get method requests. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the underlying database. Was ZDI-CAN-4233.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17422|2024-08-05T20:51:31.436Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17415|2024-08-05T20:51:31.391Z -- quest -- quest%20netvault%20backup
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17415</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Quest NetVault Backup 11.3.0.12. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of NVBUPhaseStatus Count method requests. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the underlying database. Was ZDI-CAN-4226.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17415|2024-08-05T20:51:31.391Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17652|2024-08-05T20:59:17.628Z -- quest -- quest%20netvault%20backup
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17652</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Quest NetVault Backup 11.3.0.12. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of NVBUBackup Count method requests. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the underlying database. Was ZDI-CAN-4238.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17652|2024-08-05T20:59:17.628Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17658|2024-08-05T20:59:17.378Z -- quest -- quest%20netvault%20backup
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17658</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Quest NetVault Backup 11.3.0.12. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of NVBUJobDefinitions Get method requests. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the underlying database. Was ZDI-CAN-4316.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17658|2024-08-05T20:59:17.378Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-17655|2024-08-05T20:59:17.360Z -- quest -- quest%20netvault%20backup
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-17655</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on vulnerable installations of Quest NetVault Backup 11.3.0.12. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the handling of NVBUBackup PluginList method requests. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the underlying database. Was ZDI-CAN-4289.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-17655|2024-08-05T20:59:17.360Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
