<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for shakee93 -- all</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/shakee93/all.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for shakee93 -- all products</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 20:23:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1338|2024-08-02T05:41:00.276Z -- shakee93 -- rapidload%20power-up%20for%20autoptimize
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1338</link>
      <description>The RapidLoad Power-Up for Autoptimize plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized cache modification due to a missing capability check on the attach_rule function in versions up to, and including, 1.7.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level access to modify cache rules.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1338|2024-08-02T05:41:00.276Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 19:20:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1333|2024-08-02T05:41:00.072Z -- shakee93 -- rapidload%20power-up%20for%20autoptimize
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1333</link>
      <description>The RapidLoad Power-Up for Autoptimize plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the clear_page_cache function in versions up to, and including, 1.7.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level access to delete the plugin's cache.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1333|2024-08-02T05:41:00.072Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 19:02:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1337|2024-08-02T05:40:59.852Z -- shakee93 -- rapidload%20power-up%20for%20autoptimize
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1337</link>
      <description>The RapidLoad Power-Up for Autoptimize plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized data loss due to a missing capability check on the clear_uucss_logs function in versions up to, and including, 1.7.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level access to delete plugin log files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1337|2024-08-02T05:40:59.852Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 19:20:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1344|2024-08-02T05:41:00.065Z -- shakee93 -- rapidload%20power-up%20for%20autoptimize
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1344</link>
      <description>The RapidLoad Power-Up for Autoptimize plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.7.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the uucss_update_rule function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify the plugin's cache via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1344|2024-08-02T05:41:00.065Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 19:07:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1346|2024-08-02T05:40:59.915Z -- shakee93 -- rapidload%20power-up%20for%20autoptimize
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1346</link>
      <description>The RapidLoad Power-Up for Autoptimize plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.7.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the clear_page_cache function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to clear the plugin's cache via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1346|2024-08-02T05:40:59.915Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 19:07:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1343|2024-08-02T05:41:00.164Z -- shakee93 -- rapidload%20power-up%20for%20autoptimize
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1343</link>
      <description>The RapidLoad Power-Up for Autoptimize plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.7.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the attach_rule function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify the plugin's cache via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1343|2024-08-02T05:41:00.164Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 19:06:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1345|2024-08-02T05:41:00.315Z -- shakee93 -- rapidload%20power-up%20for%20autoptimize
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1345</link>
      <description>The RapidLoad Power-Up for Autoptimize plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.7.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the queue_posts function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify the plugin's cache via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1345|2024-08-02T05:41:00.315Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 19:07:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1339|2024-08-02T05:41:00.063Z -- shakee93 -- rapidload%20power-up%20for%20autoptimize
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1339</link>
      <description>The RapidLoad Power-Up for Autoptimize plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized settings update due to a missing capability check on the uucss_update_rule function in versions up to, and including, 1.7.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level access to update caching rules.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1339|2024-08-02T05:41:00.063Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 19:19:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1336|2024-08-02T05:41:00.275Z -- shakee93 -- rapidload%20power-up%20for%20autoptimize
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1336</link>
      <description>The RapidLoad Power-Up for Autoptimize plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized settings update due to a missing capability check on the ajax_deactivate function in versions up to, and including, 1.7.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level access to disable caching.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1336|2024-08-02T05:41:00.275Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 19:19:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1335|2024-08-02T05:40:59.912Z -- shakee93 -- rapidload%20power-up%20for%20autoptimize
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1335</link>
      <description>The RapidLoad Power-Up for Autoptimize plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized plugin settings update due to a missing capability check on the ucss_connect function in versions up to, and including, 1.7.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level access to connect a new license key to the site.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1335|2024-08-02T05:40:59.912Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 19:20:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1472|2024-08-02T05:49:11.641Z -- shakee93 -- rapidload%20power-up%20for%20autoptimize
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1472</link>
      <description>The RapidLoad Power-Up for Autoptimize plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.7.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on its AJAX actions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to invoke those functions, via forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. Actions include resetting the API key, accessing or deleting log files, and deleting cache among others.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1472|2024-08-02T05:49:11.641Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 14:21:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1341|2024-08-02T05:41:00.002Z -- shakee93 -- rapidload%20power-up%20for%20autoptimize
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1341</link>
      <description>The RapidLoad Power-Up for Autoptimize plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.7.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the ajax_deactivate function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to turn off caching via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1341|2024-08-02T05:41:00.002Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 19:05:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1334|2024-08-02T05:41:00.040Z -- shakee93 -- rapidload%20power-up%20for%20autoptimize
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1334</link>
      <description>The RapidLoad Power-Up for Autoptimize plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized cache modification due to a missing capability check on the queue_posts function in versions up to, and including, 1.7.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level access to modify the plugin's cache.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1334|2024-08-02T05:41:00.040Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 19:02:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1342|2024-08-02T05:40:59.863Z -- shakee93 -- rapidload%20power-up%20for%20autoptimize
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1342</link>
      <description>The RapidLoad Power-Up for Autoptimize plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.7.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the ucss_connect function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to connect the site to a new license key via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1342|2024-08-02T05:40:59.863Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 19:06:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-1340|2024-08-02T05:41:00.068Z -- shakee93 -- rapidload%20power-up%20for%20autoptimize
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1340</link>
      <description>The RapidLoad Power-Up for Autoptimize plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.7.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the clear_uucss_logs function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to clear plugin logs via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2023-1340|2024-08-02T05:41:00.068Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 19:05:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
