<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Linux -- Kernel</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/linux/kernel.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Linux -- Kernel</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 22:22:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-2618|2024-08-05T14:02:07.208Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-2618</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's handling of clearing SELinux attributes on /proc/pid/attr files before 4.9.10. An empty (null) write to this file can crash the system by causing the system to attempt to access unmapped kernel memory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-2618|2024-08-05T14:02:07.208Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2017-7558|2024-08-05T16:04:12.011Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-7558</link>
      <description>A kernel data leak due to an out-of-bound read was found in the Linux kernel in inet_diag_msg_sctp{,l}addr_fill() and sctp_get_sctp_info() functions present since version 4.7-rc1 through version 4.13. A data leak happens when these functions fill in sockaddr data structures used to export socket's diagnostic information. As a result, up to 100 bytes of the slab data could be leaked to a userspace.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2017-7558|2024-08-05T16:04:12.011Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10872|2024-08-05T07:46:47.310Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10872</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the way the Linux kernel handled exceptions delivered after a stack switch operation via Mov SS or Pop SS instructions. During the stack switch operation, processor does not deliver interrupts and exceptions, they are delivered once the first instruction after the stack switch is executed. An unprivileged system user could use this flaw to crash the system kernel resulting in DoS. This CVE-2018-10872 was assigned due to regression of CVE-2018-8897 in Red Hat Enterprise Linux 6.10 GA kernel. No other versions are affected by this CVE.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10872|2024-08-05T07:46:47.310Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14816|2024-08-05T00:26:39.113Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14816</link>
      <description>There is heap-based buffer overflow in kernel, all versions up to, excluding 5.3, in the marvell wifi chip driver in Linux kernel, that allows local users to cause a denial of service(system crash) or possibly execute arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14816|2024-08-05T00:26:39.113Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 18:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14815|2024-08-05T00:26:38.908Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14815</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Linux Kernel, where a Heap Overflow was found in mwifiex_set_wmm_params() function of Marvell Wifi Driver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14815|2024-08-05T00:26:38.908Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 10:51:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-19332|2024-08-05T02:16:47.112Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-19332</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds memory write issue was found in the Linux Kernel, version 3.13 through 5.4, in the way the Linux kernel's KVM hypervisor handled the 'KVM_GET_EMULATED_CPUID' ioctl(2) request to get CPUID features emulated by the KVM hypervisor. A user or process able to access the '/dev/kvm' device could use this flaw to crash the system, resulting in a denial of service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-19332|2024-08-05T02:16:47.112Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 14:41:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-10853|2024-08-05T07:46:47.491Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-10853</link>
      <description>A flaw was found in the way Linux kernel KVM hypervisor before 4.18 emulated instructions such as sgdt/sidt/fxsave/fxrstor. It did not check current privilege(CPL) level while emulating unprivileged instructions. An unprivileged guest user/process could use this flaw to potentially escalate privileges inside guest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-10853|2024-08-05T07:46:47.491Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14814|2024-08-05T00:26:39.067Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14814</link>
      <description>There is heap-based buffer overflow in Linux kernel, all versions up to, excluding 5.3, in the marvell wifi chip driver in Linux kernel, that allows local users to cause a denial of service(system crash) or possibly execute arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14814|2024-08-05T00:26:39.067Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 18:27:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14821|2024-08-05T00:26:39.131Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14821</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds access issue was found in the Linux kernel, all versions through 5.3, in the way Linux kernel's KVM hypervisor implements the Coalesced MMIO write operation. It operates on an MMIO ring buffer 'struct kvm_coalesced_mmio' object, wherein write indices 'ring-&gt;first' and 'ring-&gt;last' value could be supplied by a host user-space process. An unprivileged host user or process with access to '/dev/kvm' device could use this flaw to crash the host kernel, resulting in a denial of service or potentially escalating privileges on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14821|2024-08-05T00:26:39.131Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 17:37:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2018-5391|2024-08-05T05:33:44.368Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-5391</link>
      <description>The Linux kernel, versions 3.9+, is vulnerable to a denial of service attack with low rates of specially modified packets targeting IP fragment re-assembly. An attacker may cause a denial of service condition by sending specially crafted IP fragments. Various vulnerabilities in IP fragmentation have been discovered and fixed over the years. The current vulnerability (CVE-2018-5391) became exploitable in the Linux kernel with the increase of the IP fragment reassembly queue size.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2018-5391|2024-08-05T05:33:44.368Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34981|2024-08-04T00:26:55.716Z -- linux -- kernel</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34981</link>
      <description>Linux Kernel Bluetooth CMTP Module Double Free Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Linux Kernel. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the CMTP module. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing further free operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute code in the context of the kernel. Was ZDI-CAN-11977.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34981|2024-08-04T00:26:55.716Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
