<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Linux -- Kernel</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/linux/kernel.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Linux -- Kernel</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 02:29:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14816|2024-08-05T00:26:39.113Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14816</link>
      <description>There is heap-based buffer overflow in kernel, all versions up to, excluding 5.3, in the marvell wifi chip driver in Linux kernel, that allows local users to cause a denial of service(system crash) or possibly execute arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14816|2024-08-05T00:26:39.113Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 18:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14815|2024-08-05T00:26:38.908Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14815</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Linux Kernel, where a Heap Overflow was found in mwifiex_set_wmm_params() function of Marvell Wifi Driver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14815|2024-08-05T00:26:38.908Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 10:51:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14814|2024-08-05T00:26:39.067Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14814</link>
      <description>There is heap-based buffer overflow in Linux kernel, all versions up to, excluding 5.3, in the marvell wifi chip driver in Linux kernel, that allows local users to cause a denial of service(system crash) or possibly execute arbitrary code.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14814|2024-08-05T00:26:39.067Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 18:27:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2019-14821|2024-08-05T00:26:39.131Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-14821</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds access issue was found in the Linux kernel, all versions through 5.3, in the way Linux kernel's KVM hypervisor implements the Coalesced MMIO write operation. It operates on an MMIO ring buffer 'struct kvm_coalesced_mmio' object, wherein write indices 'ring-&gt;first' and 'ring-&gt;last' value could be supplied by a host user-space process. An unprivileged host user or process with access to '/dev/kvm' device could use this flaw to crash the host kernel, resulting in a denial of service or potentially escalating privileges on the system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2019-14821|2024-08-05T00:26:39.131Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 17:37:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-34981|2024-08-04T00:26:55.716Z -- linux -- kernel</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34981</link>
      <description>Linux Kernel Bluetooth CMTP Module Double Free Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Linux Kernel. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the CMTP module. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing further free operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute code in the context of the kernel. Was ZDI-CAN-11977.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-34981|2024-08-04T00:26:55.716Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:54:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
