<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CVE Feed for Linux -- Kernel</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/linux/kernel.rss</link>
    <description>The latest CVEs for Linux -- Kernel</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 18:24:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3636|2024-08-03T01:14:03.212Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3636</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Linux Kernel. This affects the function __mtk_ppe_check_skb of the file drivers/net/ethernet/mediatek/mtk_ppe.c of the component Ethernet Handler. The manipulation leads to use after free. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-211935.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3636|2024-08-03T01:14:03.212Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-42432|2024-08-03T13:10:40.840Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-42432</link>
      <description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of the Linux Kernel 6.0-rc2. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. The specific flaw exists within the nft_osf_eval function. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of memory prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the kernel. Was ZDI-CAN-18540.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-42432|2024-08-03T13:10:40.840Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-40133|2024-08-03T12:14:39.687Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40133</link>
      <description>A use-after-free(UAF) vulnerability was found in function 'vmw_execbuf_tie_context' in drivers/gpu/vmxgfx/vmxgfx_execbuf.c in Linux kernel's vmwgfx driver with device file '/dev/dri/renderD128 (or Dxxx)'. This flaw allows a local attacker with a user account on the system to gain privilege, causing a denial of service(DoS).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-40133|2024-08-03T12:14:39.687Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3435|2024-08-03T01:07:06.583Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3435</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Linux Kernel. This affects the function fib_nh_match of the file net/ipv4/fib_semantics.c of the component IPv4 Handler. The manipulation leads to out-of-bounds read. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier VDB-210357 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3435|2024-08-03T01:07:06.583Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36280|2024-08-03T10:00:04.335Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36280</link>
      <description>An out-of-bounds(OOB) memory access vulnerability was found in vmwgfx driver in drivers/gpu/vmxgfx/vmxgfx_kms.c in GPU component in the Linux kernel with device file '/dev/dri/renderD128 (or Dxxx)'. This flaw allows a local attacker with a user account on the system to gain privilege, causing a denial of service(DoS).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36280|2024-08-03T10:00:04.335Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3629|2024-08-03T01:14:02.789Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3629</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Linux Kernel. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function vsock_connect of the file net/vmw_vsock/af_vsock.c. The manipulation leads to memory leak. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. VDB-211930 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.
In Linux Kernel wurde eine Schwachstelle ausgemacht. Sie wurde als problematisch eingestuft. Es geht um die Funktion vsock_connect der Datei net/vmw_vsock/af_vsock.c. Durch Manipulation mit unbekannten Daten kann eine memory leak-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Die Komplexität eines Angriffs ist eher hoch. Das Ausnutzen gilt als schwierig. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3629|2024-08-03T01:14:02.789Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3621|2024-08-03T01:14:03.245Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3621</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Linux Kernel. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is the function nilfs_bmap_lookup_at_level of the file fs/nilfs2/inode.c of the component nilfs2. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-211920.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3621|2024-08-03T01:14:03.245Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3625|2024-08-03T01:14:02.495Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3625</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Linux Kernel. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function devlink_param_set/devlink_param_get of the file net/core/devlink.c of the component IPsec. The manipulation leads to use after free. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier VDB-211929 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3625|2024-08-03T01:14:02.495Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-29581|2024-08-03T06:26:06.284Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29581</link>
      <description>Improper Update of Reference Count vulnerability in net/sched of Linux Kernel allows local attacker to cause privilege escalation to root. This issue affects: Linux Kernel versions prior to 5.18; version 4.14 and later versions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-29581|2024-08-03T06:26:06.284Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 16:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3545|2024-08-03T01:14:01.597Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3545</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Linux Kernel and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function area_cache_get of the file drivers/net/ethernet/netronome/nfp/nfpcore/nfp_cppcore.c of the component IPsec. The manipulation leads to use after free. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier VDB-211045 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3545|2024-08-03T01:14:01.597Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3564|2024-08-03T01:14:01.563Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3564</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Linux Kernel. Affected by this vulnerability is the function l2cap_reassemble_sdu of the file net/bluetooth/l2cap_core.c of the component Bluetooth. The manipulation leads to use after free. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-211087.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3564|2024-08-03T01:14:01.563Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3521|2024-08-03T01:14:02.040Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3521</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Linux Kernel and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function kcm_tx_work of the file net/kcm/kcmsock.c of the component kcm. The manipulation leads to race condition. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. VDB-211018 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3521|2024-08-03T01:14:02.040Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3637|2024-08-03T01:14:03.293Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3637</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Linux Kernel and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function jlink_init of the file monitor/jlink.c of the component BlueZ. The manipulation leads to denial of service. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-211936.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3637|2024-08-03T01:14:03.293Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3541|2024-08-03T01:14:02.638Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3541</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Linux Kernel. This affects the function spl2sw_nvmem_get_mac_address of the file drivers/net/ethernet/sunplus/spl2sw_driver.c of the component BPF. The manipulation leads to use after free. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier VDB-211041 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3541|2024-08-03T01:14:02.638Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3623|2024-08-03T01:14:02.805Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3623</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Linux Kernel. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function follow_page_pte of the file mm/gup.c of the component BPF. The manipulation leads to race condition. The attack can be launched remotely. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier VDB-211921 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3623|2024-08-03T01:14:02.805Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3534|2024-08-03T01:14:02.420Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3534</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Linux Kernel. Affected is the function btf_dump_name_dups of the file tools/lib/bpf/btf_dump.c of the component libbpf. The manipulation leads to use after free. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-211032.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3534|2024-08-03T01:14:02.420Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3563|2024-08-03T01:14:01.568Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3563</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Linux Kernel. Affected is the function read_50_controller_cap_complete of the file tools/mgmt-tester.c of the component BlueZ. The manipulation of the argument cap_len leads to null pointer dereference. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. VDB-211086 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3563|2024-08-03T01:14:01.568Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3630|2024-08-03T01:14:03.136Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3630</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Linux Kernel. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file fs/fscache/cookie.c of the component IPsec. The manipulation leads to memory leak. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-211931.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3630|2024-08-03T01:14:03.136Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3523|2024-08-03T01:14:02.094Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3523</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Linux Kernel. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file mm/memory.c of the component Driver Handler. The manipulation leads to use after free. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-211020.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3523|2024-08-03T01:14:02.094Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3640|2024-08-03T01:14:03.216Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3640</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Linux Kernel. Affected is the function l2cap_conn_del of the file net/bluetooth/l2cap_core.c of the component Bluetooth. The manipulation leads to use after free. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-211944.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3640|2024-08-03T01:14:03.216Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3649|2024-08-03T01:14:03.289Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3649</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Linux Kernel. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is the function nilfs_new_inode of the file fs/nilfs2/inode.c of the component BPF. The manipulation leads to use after free. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-211992.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3649|2024-08-03T01:14:03.289Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3633|2024-08-03T01:14:03.231Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3633</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Linux Kernel. Affected is the function j1939_session_destroy of the file net/can/j1939/transport.c. The manipulation leads to memory leak. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-211932.
Es wurde eine problematische Schwachstelle in Linux Kernel entdeckt. Es geht dabei um die Funktion j1939_session_destroy der Datei net/can/j1939/transport.c. Mittels Manipulieren mit unbekannten Daten kann eine memory leak-Schwachstelle ausgenutzt werden. Als bestmögliche Massnahme wird Patching empfohlen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3633|2024-08-03T01:14:03.231Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3624|2024-08-03T01:14:03.276Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3624</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Linux Kernel and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function rlb_arp_xmit of the file drivers/net/bonding/bond_alb.c of the component IPsec. The manipulation leads to memory leak. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-211928.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3624|2024-08-03T01:14:03.276Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38457|2024-08-03T10:54:03.666Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38457</link>
      <description>A use-after-free(UAF) vulnerability was found in function 'vmw_cmd_res_check' in drivers/gpu/vmxgfx/vmxgfx_execbuf.c in Linux kernel's vmwgfx driver with device file '/dev/dri/renderD128 (or Dxxx)'. This flaw allows a local attacker with a user account on the system to gain privilege, causing a denial of service(DoS).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38457|2024-08-03T10:54:03.666Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3526|2024-08-03T01:14:01.564Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3526</link>
      <description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Linux Kernel. This vulnerability affects the function macvlan_handle_frame of the file drivers/net/macvlan.c of the component skb. The manipulation leads to memory leak. The attack can be initiated remotely. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-211024.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3526|2024-08-03T01:14:01.564Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-3444|2024-08-03T16:53:17.550Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3444</link>
      <description>The bpf verifier in the Linux kernel did not properly handle mod32 destination register truncation when the source register was known to be 0. A local attacker with the ability to load bpf programs could use this gain out-of-bounds reads in kernel memory leading to information disclosure (kernel memory), and possibly out-of-bounds writes that could potentially lead to code execution. This issue was addressed in the upstream kernel in commit 9b00f1b78809 ("bpf: Fix truncation handling for mod32 dst reg wrt zero") and in Linux stable kernels 5.11.2, 5.10.19, and 5.4.101.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2021-3444|2024-08-03T16:53:17.550Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3594|2024-08-03T01:14:02.039Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3594</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Linux Kernel. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function intr_callback of the file drivers/net/usb/r8152.c of the component BPF. The manipulation leads to logging of excessive data. The attack can be launched remotely. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-211363.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3594|2024-08-03T01:14:02.039Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3544|2024-08-03T01:14:01.524Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3544</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Linux Kernel. Affected is the function damon_sysfs_add_target of the file mm/damon/sysfs.c of the component Netfilter. The manipulation leads to memory leak. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-211044.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3544|2024-08-03T01:14:01.524Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3567|2024-08-03T01:14:02.055Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3567</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Linux Kernel and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function inet6_stream_ops/inet6_dgram_ops of the component IPv6 Handler. The manipulation leads to race condition. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. VDB-211090 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3567|2024-08-03T01:14:02.055Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3635|2024-08-03T01:14:03.270Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3635</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Linux Kernel. Affected by this issue is the function tst_timer of the file drivers/atm/idt77252.c of the component IPsec. The manipulation leads to use after free. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. VDB-211934 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3635|2024-08-03T01:14:03.270Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3565|2024-08-03T01:14:02.837Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3565</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Linux Kernel. Affected by this issue is the function del_timer of the file drivers/isdn/mISDN/l1oip_core.c of the component Bluetooth. The manipulation leads to use after free. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-211088.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3565|2024-08-03T01:14:02.837Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3566|2024-08-03T01:14:02.604Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3566</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Linux Kernel. This affects the function tcp_getsockopt/tcp_setsockopt of the component TCP Handler. The manipulation leads to race condition. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier VDB-211089 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3566|2024-08-03T01:14:02.604Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3524|2024-08-03T01:14:02.569Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3524</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Linux Kernel. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function ipv6_renew_options of the component IPv6 Handler. The manipulation leads to memory leak. The attack can be launched remotely. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier VDB-211021 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3524|2024-08-03T01:14:02.569Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-36402|2024-08-03T10:00:04.458Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36402</link>
      <description>An integer overflow vulnerability was found in vmwgfx driver in drivers/gpu/vmxgfx/vmxgfx_execbuf.c in GPU component of Linux kernel with device file '/dev/dri/renderD128 (or Dxxx)'. This flaw allows a local attacker with a user account on the system to gain privilege, causing a denial of service(DoS).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-36402|2024-08-03T10:00:04.458Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3646|2024-08-03T01:14:03.291Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3646</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Linux Kernel. This issue affects the function nilfs_attach_log_writer of the file fs/nilfs2/segment.c of the component BPF. The manipulation leads to memory leak. The attack may be initiated remotely. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier VDB-211961 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3646|2024-08-03T01:14:03.291Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-38096|2024-08-03T10:45:52.802Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38096</link>
      <description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability was found in vmwgfx driver in drivers/gpu/vmxgfx/vmxgfx_execbuf.c in GPU component of Linux kernel with device file '/dev/dri/renderD128 (or Dxxx)'. This flaw allows a local attacker with a user account on the system to gain privilege, causing a denial of service(DoS).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-38096|2024-08-03T10:45:52.802Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3619|2024-08-03T01:14:02.535Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3619</link>
      <description>A vulnerability has been found in Linux Kernel and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function l2cap_recv_acldata of the file net/bluetooth/l2cap_core.c of the component Bluetooth. The manipulation leads to memory leak. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. VDB-211918 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3619|2024-08-03T01:14:02.535Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3606|2024-08-03T01:14:02.479Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3606</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Linux Kernel. It has been classified as problematic. This affects the function find_prog_by_sec_insn of the file tools/lib/bpf/libbpf.c of the component BPF. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier VDB-211749 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3606|2024-08-03T01:14:02.479Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3176|2024-08-03T01:00:10.627Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3176</link>
      <description>There exists a use-after-free in io_uring in the Linux kernel. Signalfd_poll() and binder_poll() use a waitqueue whose lifetime is the current task. It will send a POLLFREE notification to all waiters before the queue is freed. Unfortunately, the io_uring poll doesn't handle POLLFREE. This allows a use-after-free to occur if a signalfd or binder fd is polled with io_uring poll, and the waitqueue gets freed. We recommend upgrading past commit fc78b2fc21f10c4c9c4d5d659a685710ffa63659</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3176|2024-08-03T01:00:10.627Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3533|2024-08-03T01:14:03.207Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3533</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Linux Kernel. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects the function parse_usdt_arg of the file tools/lib/bpf/usdt.c of the component BPF. The manipulation of the argument reg_name leads to memory leak. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-211031.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3533|2024-08-03T01:14:03.207Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3543|2024-08-03T01:14:02.530Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3543</link>
      <description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Linux Kernel. This issue affects the function unix_sock_destructor/unix_release_sock of the file net/unix/af_unix.c of the component BPF. The manipulation leads to memory leak. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-211043.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3543|2024-08-03T01:14:02.530Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2022-3595|2024-08-03T01:14:03.263Z -- linux -- kernel
</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3595</link>
      <description>A vulnerability was found in Linux Kernel. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function sess_free_buffer of the file fs/cifs/sess.c of the component CIFS Handler. The manipulation leads to double free. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-211364.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2022-3595|2024-08-03T01:14:03.263Z</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
