<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>CVE Feed for Premium Addons for Elementor -- Premium Addons Pro for Elementor</title><link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/deepseas/cvelistV5monitor/main/feeds/premium%20addons%20for%20elementor/premium%20addons%20pro%20for%20elementor.rss</link><description>The latest CVEs for Premium Addons for Elementor -- Premium Addons Pro for Elementor</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 21:54:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>CVE-2024-1997|2024-03-13T15:32:39.456Z -- Premium Addons for Elementor -- Premium Addons Pro for Elementor
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1997</link><description>The Premium Addons PRO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'premium_fbchat_app_id' parameter of the Messenger Chat Widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1997|2024-03-13T15:32:39.456Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:32:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1996|2024-03-13T15:32:38.990Z -- Premium Addons for Elementor -- Premium Addons Pro for Elementor
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-1996</link><description>The Premium Addons PRO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's IHover widget link in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-1996|2024-03-13T15:32:38.990Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:32:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2399|2024-03-15T06:48:46.034Z -- Premium Addons for Elementor -- Premium Addons Pro for Elementor
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2399</link><description>The Premium Addons PRO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's widgets in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.23 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2399|2024-03-15T06:48:46.034Z</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 06:48:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2239|2024-03-13T15:32:37.901Z -- Premium Addons for Elementor -- Premium Addons Pro for Elementor
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2239</link><description>The Premium Addons PRO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Premium Magic Scroll module in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2239|2024-03-13T15:32:37.901Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:32:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2238|2024-03-13T15:32:39.917Z -- Premium Addons for Elementor -- Premium Addons Pro for Elementor
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2238</link><description>The Premium Addons PRO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Custom Mouse Cursor module in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2238|2024-03-13T15:32:39.917Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:32:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2237|2024-03-13T15:32:38.512Z -- Premium Addons for Elementor -- Premium Addons Pro for Elementor
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2237</link><description>The Premium Addons PRO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Global Badge module in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2237|2024-03-13T15:32:38.512Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:32:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2000|2024-03-13T15:32:40.870Z -- Premium Addons for Elementor -- Premium Addons Pro for Elementor
</title><link>https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2024-2000</link><description>The Premium Addons PRO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'navigation_dots' parameter of the Multi Scroll Widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">CVE-2024-2000|2024-03-13T15:32:40.870Z</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:32:40 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>